It's dark.
D'oh!
Hot dogs! Not so hot dogs!
Cold and droopy!
Fried dough! America's worst legal food!
Never leaves your body!
Wow. The Truth in Boardwalking Law
has really done a number on this place.
Shoot an oversized basketball
into an undersized hoop!
It's impossible!
The prizes have been here for 50 years!
HOMER: Ooh. Oh.
Maybe we should just check out
the street performers.
Big deal! I could juggle six pins
if they let me use a unicycle.
Well, if you think it's too easy,
why don't you throw me something else?
Are you insane?
You can't throw a little boy
into my cascade.
Stop tossing kids!
Oh, man. I love Saturdays.
Man, I love Saturdays.
Finally I can have fun
with something I bought for myself,
a new water heater.
Almost there...
Five more water heaters
and we get a free water heater.
Huh?
A mysterious door?
It's like a sauna in here.
It is a sauna in here!
It must've been put in
by a previous owner.
This house is full of surprises,
but this is the first good one.
I can't wait to tell everyone.
This is great, honey.
Thanks for telling me about it.
I hope you don't mind I invited Lenny.
And I hope you don't mind
I invited Carl and Moe.
Yeah, you know, my invitation
didn't say nothing about no towels.
So I guess we should all just go
Scandinavian, huh?
Huh?
Maybe I'll keep this
to myself for a while.
Ooh! Lamb kebob!
Ooh!
Chicken kebob.
Fire kebob!
Dad, no!
- Dad, yes!
Water! Thank you!
Why you little...
Burn, Barty, burn!
I'm afraid his tongue will be in that cast
for a few weeks.
It may put something of a cramp
in your lovemaking.
No, it won't.
If he wants me to do something,
he'll just write it down.
What does it say?
Is it complimentary?
Yeah, sure. It's complimentary.
It is? Hey, everybody!
Check out my compliment!
Now, Homer,
how would you like me to remove it?
Yanky or peely?
Got it.
I held up two for peely!
- I thought that was a Y for yanky!
I'll make a note in your chart
that you aren't always clear.
Well, at least I can eat again.
Cherry.
Too much cherry!
Lemon! That'll stop the cherry!
Doctor, why is this happening to me?
- Well, I do have an idea.
But just to be sure,
let's run some expensive tests.
The fire burned off your old taste buds,
exposing new ones.
That'll be our Christmas card this year.
Homer, you've become a supertaster.
The mildest spices
will overwhelm your tongue.
Even a taco could drive you insane.
I can't eat tacos?
Oh, my God. What day of mayo is it?
- Cinco.
Try these beets. I boiled all the red out.
I still taste overtones of pink.
Dad, I got the perfect thing.
Mmm. Hmm...
It feels like food,
but it has no flavor whatsoever.
It's mac and cheese
from the school cafeteria,
the blandest food known to man.
What else do they got?
Tofu cubes, tidy joes,
chili con cottage cheese,
pecan blandies, cream of steam,
you-guess-thems.
Man, who comes up with this stuff?
Old comedy writers
who now have to work at our kitchen.
The one rule we had on Charles in Charge
is, Charles must always be in charge.
Oh, yeah. That makes sense to me.
- That's a great rule.
Lunch card. Lunch card.
Lunch card.
- Don't have one.
Dad, what are you doing here?
Son, from now on, I'm eating all my meals
here at school with you!
What? No!
Come on. Relax. I won't embarrass you.
$3.85.
- Yeah.
Can I work it off? Don't worry.
I won't embarrass you!
I'll start you on Jell-O.
I'm big and yellow and I'm serving Jell-O
If you're a fellow
and you want some Jell-O
You better bellow
Hey, big guy! Give me some Jell-O
No Jell-O for you, Bart.
It'll keep you up at night,
like last week when you crawled into bed
with me and Mommy.
Sure is hot back here.
And there we go.
Don't worry. I won't embarrass you.
I used to date your daughter.
Buddy, I'm here to eat,
not make interesting conversation.
Dad, do you have to hang out
at my school?
It's bad enough
I have to be here three days a week.
Well! I know when I'm not wanted!
Am I wanted?
- No.
Hi. Homer Simpson.
Mind if I sit near your son? Mine sucks.
Well, we certainly are proud of Noah.
He's a straight-A student.
Noah! State capitals, alphabetical order,
on my clap.
Albany, Annapolis, Atlanta, Augusta,
Austin, Baton Rouge,
Bismarck, Boise, Boston,
Capital City, Carson City.
Wow. He's terrified of you.
That's why I'm here.
To make sure he gets good grades.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
You come to school
to help him get good grades?
Isn't that why we pay public school
teachers those enormous salaries?
Well, call me over-involved,
but someday,
your son will be my son's chauffeur.
Well, I hope your son enjoys
being driven around...
...by the President of the United States.
Really? Let's see what the future
president's doing right now.
You don't see many presidents doing that.
Maybe LBJ, you know, at the end.
It's not your son's fault. It's yours.
You have to hover over your kid's shoulder
to force him to succeed.
It's called helicopter parenting.
I don't have to helicopter Bart.
I've got a backup plan called Lisa.
Oh, right. Your second grader.
Sure she's smart,
but how could she be successful
if she's not popular?
Do you mind if I join you?
Well, that depends. What are you eating?
- Baked potato, side salad, and a...
Well, we're having cold shoulder.
Is this seat taken?
- No. Go ahead. Take it.
Take it way over there.
Oh, my God.
My son's a loser
and my daughter's a Ioner.
Way to go, Marge!
Marge, where have you been?
- Well, I...
No time! I'll just deduce where you were
from a list of possibilities in my head.
That makes sense. Moving on.
If we don't get more
involved in their lives,
Bart and Lisa are gonna be failures,
failures who work for Noah!
- Noah. I like that name.
Noah.
New-ah. Noah.
Aren't you the one
who usually worries about stuff?
Am I?
If Marge doesn't worry about the kids,
then that leaves me!
Help me, mayonnaise!
Look at all these helicopter parents.
I hope Bart's doing okay on his own.
There's no future in that!
Don't forget, children.
Monday is the balsa wood
model building competition.
The American Balsa Council
will award this year's winner...
...a $1000 savings bond
for their college education.
$1000? That's what my house is worth.
Bart Simpson, what will you be making?
I don't know.
Time to take control of my son's life.
Let's see. What can he build?
Too obvious.
Gotta be something from earth.
You're no help!
Perfect.
'The Washington Monument?'
Washington Monument.
- I like Bart's idea.
You're not in this class.
- Willie swept me in here.
My mistake.
I did it. I helped my son.
Helicopter Homer, away!
Black Hawk down! Black Hawk down!
Lisa, I found this book...
...in the 'What's wrong with my daughter'
section of the bookstore.
It tells you how you can get popular.
Dad, if I join a clique,
I'll be the kind of person I hate.
Sweetie, our country was founded
by a clique,
the Continental Congress!
Dolphins swim in cliques.
Those are my two examples.
Well, they are good ones.
And to show you how this book works,
I will demonstrate on some rats.
Let's try
what chapter seven calls 'Unsults,'
insults disguised as compliments.
Hey, Lenny.
It takes a lot of courage to wear
suspenders when you're not in the circus.
Well, that's very nice of you... Hey!
Are you saying my clothes are clown-like?
Oh, God. I feel so insecure.
Please be my friend.
See? It works.
And unsults are just the beginning.
There's also 'Envytations,' 'Hate hugs,'
'Spamming with faint praise,' and...
Hey, everyone,
wanna go get frozen yogurt?
I do...
- Yeah!
I'm sorry, Moe.
I didn't mean 'everyone' everyone.
Hope you don't mind?
- No. That's all right.
If I didn't sell booze,
they probably wouldn't even come here!
And that, my dear girl,
is called the Toledo Take-back.
Dad, I don't want to
hurt people's feelings.
I see.
Well, maybe you're not
ready for this book.
It is more of a big girl thing.
- I'm a big girl! I'm a big girl!
One of you said something bad
about the other.
He did?
- He did?
Son, you buy an awful
lot of airplane glue,
but you never buy any models.
Oh, right. Models.
One Messerschmitt 262, a '67 SS GTO,
an Alfred E. Neuman,
with interchangeable arms.
We'd like some balsa wood, please.
- Enough to build a Washington Monument.
What scale are you using?
What cologne are you wearing?
None of your business!
Now we'd like our Washington Monument...
...to be one-five hundredth
the size of the real one.
Washington Monument?
Aren't you gonna even try?
What do you mean? And who are you?
- I'm your son's principal.
And the Washington Monument is
the most uninspired model choice there is.
It's like saying,
'I don't care. My kid's a loser.'
But... You...
What's the hardest model there is?
That would be, Westminster Abbey.
Attention, parents, children
and childless weirdoes,
my son and I are going
to build Westminster Abbey!
You've gotta be crazy!
- Prepare to be frustrated.
You won't get past the north transept!
Hey, how hard can it be?
All we have to do is
follow the directions.
Marge, the boy and I
will be making Westminster Abbey.
Blabby's gonna build an abbey. Groovy.
But first, as part of
Operation Popularity,
Lisa and I are hosting a 'Decorate Your
Own Cell Phone' party in the backyard.
Britney and Caitlin are here!
Where's my spray-on tan?
Why do I always read the labels after?
Ladies, we've got it all.
Rhinestones, stickers, tassels,
everything to make those $100 phones
look like $5 toys!
Lisa, this party is twisted!
- You're fierce!
I've never been called fierce before.
Strident. Hectoring has been
tossed around.
Let me take a picture of you
for my cell phone.
I'll put you on my desktop.
I'm gonna make you my friend on Facebook.
Please confirm.
- Confirmed!
I am such a great parent to both my kids.
Hello, little girl. Who do you belong to?
Hey, boy. Why don't I do that for you?
- Isn't this supposed to be my project?
All the other parents
are doing it for their kids.
Now stand back and I'll take it from here.
A little further back.
Do you want me to watch and learn?
- No. That kind of creeps me out.
Must finish Poets' Corner
or Bart will work for Noah...
...with his hot mom.
That's not Henry VII! That's Henry VI!
Stupid, stupid, stupid!
Homer, don't give up
till you finish my dear abbey!
Geoffrey Chaucer?
What are you doing here?
Well, I'm buried here,
and I want to tell you you're right
to do all Bart's work for him.
It's the best thing for the boy.
That's terrible advice.
Anne of Cleves?
What you do for your son,
he'll never learn to do for himself.
And where is this delightful boy?
Oscar Wilde?
Homer, there are only
two tragedies in life.
One is not getting what one wants,
and the other is getting it.
But that makes no sense!
Experience is simply
the name we give to our mistakes.
Shut up!
These days, man knows the price
of everything and the value of nothing.
Whatever happened to 'boo'?
Now we could smash the real
Westminster Abbey so it looks like this.
There are no flights to London
till 5:00.
Welcome to Springfield Elementary's
Next Top Model Building Contest.
Kenny, he said your show.
- I watched it once!
Now, judges, start your nodding.
Mmm-hmm.
- Mmm.
Mmm. Mmm-hmm.
Flawless. Stunning. Awe-inspiring.
Meticulous.
Mmm?
Hmm.
Skinner!
These models are clearly
the work of meddling parents.
The only entry that repels my eye enough...
...to be constructed by
a student is this one.
Congratulations, son.
At least you followed the rules.
Yes! Yes! In your face, losers!
This helicopter is taking off!
No! Stop the hovering!
I didn't make this terrible model.
My dad did.
Why can't you guys
let us do things for ourselves?
In the words of Oscar
Wilde, 'Experience is...
...simply the name we
give to our mistakes.'
I saw him, too, Dad.
I'm sorry. I got carried away.
From now on, the only thing I'll ever do
for you is cosign if you want a gun.
Well, at least I made Lisa popular.
'I H8 this'?
I'm sorry, Dad.
These girls are nice on the surface.
But it's hard work staying this shallow.
I hope you understand.
Yeah. It's clear to me now.
The best thing I can do as a parent
is simply check out.
No, there's a middle ground.
Lisa, a light bulb is
either on or it's off.
Not if you use a dimmer switch.
That's what the dimmer switch companies
want you to think.
What's wrong, Homie?
- I tried to fix the kids' lives.
But instead, I led them to rich and
rewarding personal decisions of their own.
Well, I know a place in this house
where you can really relax.
The mattress the dog sleeps on
in the cellar?
No. I gave that to the homeless shelter.
That was stuffed with cash!
- Well, I'll make you forget all about it.
Feeling better, Super Dad?
- Oh, yeah.
I feel like I've died and gone to hell.
The Simpsons
English - US - SDH