It's dark!
Hey!
D'oh!
You've fallen right into my trap,
just like you did in Africa.
Krusty, there you are.
We've got business to discuss.
First off, we got big problems
with your talking home pregnancy tests.
Hey, hey! You're pregnant!
And it's not mine!
It's giving 20% false 'Hey, hey's.'
Okay. Repackage them as coffee stirrers
and sell them in the Philippines.
Genius. Now, another issue.
Studies show your Krusty Burger...
...is the unhealthiest fast food item
in the world.
Worse than a Double Krusty Burger?
- Somehow, yes.
Okay, here's what we do.
What's that food we never put
in any of our meals?
Vegetables?
- Yeah, those guys.
Find the cheapest one
and make a burger out of it.
Then throw it in a green wrapper
and double the price.
And say it's got none of those...
What are those unhealthy
he/she-sounding things?
Trans fats?
- That's it. And while you're in there,
spray a little nicotine juice
on the kids meals.
Get them hooked.
ANNOUNCER:
Coming up on The Drowningest Catch.
It was worth it to be on TV!
- Put our dying screams in the promo!
You know, kids,
the real drowningest catch is man.
It's a new world out there.
People care about their health
for some reason.
We know times have changed.
We at Krusty Burger
want to take advantage of that.
Introducing the Mother Nature Burger!
Made from 100% wheat-fed barley.
And now to take a yummy bite.
Mmm.
Tastes like a healthy future!
We're going to Krusty Burger!
Finally, a hamburger for the Hindus.
By the tusks of great Ganesh,
now no one can tell I am not American.
Look at me! I'm saving the Earth!
Where's my Nobel Prize?
What's wrong, old friend? Can't sleep?
Would some warm beer settle you down?
Uh-oh.
Those barley burgers were tainted?
Why did I eat twelve of them? Why?
Taken!
Occupied!
Hurling!
SEYMOUR: Attention, students.
Due to the recent queasiness,
both the Presidential
Ab Crunch Challenge...
...and the Sloppy Joe-a-thon
have been canceled.
Skinner, if I die, I
want you to take over...
Really?
...the search committee...
...for a new superintendent.
Just hold my head
and say soothing things.
Third-grade math scores
are holding steady.
Oh, yeah.
The food poisoning has been
traced to a single ingredient,
tainted barley.
And where does that barley come from?
Our neighbor to the southeast, Ogdenville,
the state's barley basket
since it was settled 100 years ago...
...by Norwegian immigrants.
I'm here with barley farmer
Brendlif Jensen.
Brendlif?
- What happened is,
a big old rat
got caught up in the grinders there.
So my wife Dagne took a hose to it,
and it's all cleaned out now.
So you're guaranteeing it's safe to eat
Ogdenville barley once more?
Well, where there's barley,
there's rats, you know.
Now, when will you be starting
the interview?
That just went out live.
Well, then we're screwed.
Dad, are you sure you can put in
these new rain gutters all by yourself?
Yeah, maybe you're right.
I do have a bad history of going up
on roofs and waking up in hospitals.
Perhaps we could be of help,
don't you know?
Ogdenvillians work on my house?
Yeah. Ever since the barley bust,
the only work we can get is day labor.
We don't mind it. Work is work.
I like your can-do attitude.
And your facial hair screams
'rugged but reliable.'
You won't regret this, sir.
- You hear that, Bart? He called me 'sir.'
That means he knows I'm better than him.
Nicely done, guys. Lemonade?
A lemon version of barley-ade?
When in Springfield...
Don't that glug down right good, then?
Oh, yeah. Almost as good as barley-ade.
- Oh, yeah!
You know, I'm glad you've come here
to take all the jobs we don't want to do.
Can't have too much of a good thing.
MAN: You fellas, too! Come on!
MAN 1: Oh, yeah!
MAN 2: Be right there then.
So Inga, this is our kitchen.
Did you have kitchens back in Ogdenville?
Ja. Before the dark days fell on my people
and we lost everything.
Great!
So you know your way around a blender.
Okay.
So if the dog's in the house,
don't let Grampa in, and vice versa.
Our neighbor Ned Flanders
drops by unexpectedly...
That I do.
...but he doesn't stay long.
No, I don't.
Kids, this is Inga, your new nanny.
A nanny? Woo-hoo!
Mom says I can have
ice cream for breakfast.
Oh, she's still here.
Mom, can I have ice cream for breakfast?
- No way, mister.
It's just chocolate chip pancakes
and syrup for you.
Inga, I'll be happy to eat
whatever you make.
Maggie, now you have a nanny.
Just like the ones Joe Piscopo
and Ethan Hawke left their wives for.
But hands off my Homie.
'Hands off the Homie.' Got it.
Sorry. Sometimes she's nervous
around new people.
Actually, she's just gassy.
A little lingonberry oil under the tongue
will clear it right up.
That's amazing! Now I feel bad
about calling your references.
So Selma, how did you meet?
I hired Thor Bjorn here
to kill some moles in my garden,
and, well, one thing led to another.
Ja. She has the same beautiful face
as my Great-Uncle Magnus...
...when he lay in the coffin
after his trolley accident.
Gee, this Ogdenville influx
has been great for everybody.
Yeah. Talk about taking jobs
Springfield men don't want.
Hey, Homer. Your blubber would light
our lamps for a year.
I zinged the oaf good?
- You zinged the oaf great!
Minnesota Vikings apparel?
This is Tennessee Titans country!
So many meters!
Step aside, Norwads.
Watch how the natives ride sky.
Three hours
and we still can't see a doctor?
It's because it's filled
with all these Norwads.
They even sneeze funny.
We're out of English forms.
You'll have to fill out a Norwegian one.
I can't read this sloopy-bloopy writing.
Typical foreigners,
clogging up the system.
I hurt my back unclogging
your septic system.
Sven, can you stop by tomorrow?
It's clogged again.
Come on, Bart.
We'll take care of you at home.
Oh, great. I caught their cold.
Okay, Bart. Now bite down
on the rubber dog bone and...
Thanks, Mom.
- Now how did this happen, again?
It wasn't my fault, I swear.
A couple of barley jerks dared me to.
Yeah? Well, I'm starting to wonder
if this town wasn't better off...
...before all these immigrants showed up.
I'd just like to remind
you that we were all...
...immigrants at one time.
Well, you were a baby once.
Does that mean you still like milk
and hugs?
Yes. I'd like both right now.
Hey, this is all right.
Look at them barleyjacks celebrating
another one of their stupid holidays.
Hey, I ain't got no problem with them.
They pay in cash, they keep it clean,
and their mythology is rich
and enchanting.
Yeah. The redhead one said
today's the day Woden gave the herring...
...the greatest gift of
all. Its fishy taste.
Hey, Moe, what is that hoity-toity
beer they're drinking?
Oh, I don't sell beer no more.
I only serve Aquavit,
the Norwegian caraway-scented liqueur.
Wait a minute!
You're selling barleyjack booze?
How could you, Moe?
Hey, it's all about the King Haralds.
Well, since it's all you got,
give me a mug of that Aquavit.
Better go slow there, friend.
That stuff'll open up a can
of 'Oh, my goodness' on you.
I think I can handle it.
Hey!
Where did that Homer guy go?
More Aquavit, please.
You're late! And drunk!
- Shut up!
You lost your job?
- Well, it's not my fault!
Those Ogdenville guys plied me
with their native liqueurs and liquors.
But mostly liqueurs.
- Oh, poor Homie.
And you with your alcoholism.
- Yeah.
I propose that no Ogdenvillian be allowed
within the city limits of Springfield.
I share your xylophobia.
Dad, you mean 'xenophobia.'
'X ylophobia' would be
a fear of xylophones.
I am afraid of xylophones.
It's the music you hear
when skeletons are dancing.
Very well. Springfield will ban immigrants
and xylophones.
All in favor say 'aye.'
- ALL: Aye!
The border is now closed.
You'll never take my xylophone!
Notes, don't fail me now!
There's one, Chief.
Well, he's too far, Lou. That's not fair.
Hey, there's another!
- He's on a bike, Lou.
So?
- So what am I? Superman?
Well, there's one coming
between your legs.
Where?
- There! Now! Right now!
Look between your legs!
- I don't... Oh, yeah.
Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh...
No, he's too fast. It's hopeless, Lou.
We can't handle this.
We need help patrolling the border.
I mean, Springfield only has three cops.
Yeah, and Eddie's laid up
because of his gout.
Yep. Eddie loves his
lobster and port wine.
But it comes with a price.
Excuse me.
Do you have to pay to get in, or...
No, no, no. It's free. It's free.
Maybe we can ask private citizens
to guard the border.
Yeah. You know, vigilantes,
who would agree to do our job
for the adrenaline rush...
...that comes from having a tiny taste
of authority over your fellow man.
And all we're paying them is
bullets and beer.
I almost made a big mistake!
Men, our negative energy
has been harnessed...
...to help keep Springfield's border
secure from Ogdenvillians.
But first, our group needs a name
that evokes America's proud history...
...of citizens rising up
to defend our way of life.
The Klan?
Well, there are no bad ideas,
but let's keep trying.
The Nazis!
- Okay, you stop trying.
Hey, how about
The Star-Spangled Goofballs?
Goofballs it is!
I'll float above the border and radio
the location of illegals down to you.
My code name will be Screaming Eagle.
Yours will be Ground Losers.
What a fun day.
- Oh, this is gonna be good.
Release the sandbags!
Hey, why don't you let Carl and me try?
Okay. You guys get in as I get off.
This is Ground Loser,
what's your position? Over.
Cold. So very cold.
I'm sorry to say
that this poorly conceived patrol...
...carried out by a
group of rank amateurs...
...has somehow been a failure!
- Yeah, those barleyjacks are crafty.
One of them handcuffed me to this tree!
Not a tree, Chief. That's a street sign.
You just looped your belt around it
when you were changing your pants.
Okay. I'm hearing lots of problems
but no solutions!
This immigration problem is bigger
than we thought.
We need a way to keep these people
out of our community!
What can we do
to keep one group of people...
...away from another group of people?
Why you little... I'll kill you!
That's it! We'll build a fence!
Fence! Fence! Fence! Fence!
- Fence! Fence! Fence! Fence!
Homie, I don't think
we should build a fence.
Haven't we always taught the children
to make friends...
...with those who are a little different?
Yes.
- Yeah.
Maggie's first words are in Ogdenvillese!
- Now do you see, Marge?
Now do you see
why we must build that fence?
Build it, Homie!
Make it as tall as the sky
and deeper than hell!
All right.
Who here knows how to build a wall?
I know how to hire guys to build a wall.
Such as?
- The barleyjacks?
Yeah, right.
Okay. They can help us build the wall,
because they're good at it.
But then those good-for-nothings
have to go.
Yeah!
- Yeah! Yeah, get them out of here!
So my girlfriend puts all these
pillows on the bed.
And you have to, like,
take them all off at night...
...and put them all back on every morning.
And if the little one
is in back of the big one, God help you.
And they always want the cat
to sleep in bed with you.
Exactly!
I had trouble finding
a four-button cardigan,
so I bought a three-button one
and sewed the extra button on myself.
This baby was a five-buttoner.
But I took a button off.
Maybe we're not so different, Sven.
- Maybe so.
You know,
if you put down an acrylic primer,
your satiric drawing
and its clever stink lines...
...will be there long after
your principal is gone.
Well, the guy at the store said
it didn't matter,
but I knew he was wrong. Thanks, man.
Sure is quiet around here.
Do you miss us?
- We miss you.
That's why we build a door!
Oh, we did miss you.
We missed your kindness, your hard work,
your sweet, plainspoken ways.
What are you barleyjacks waiting for?
Get in here!
We'd be more than pleased
to join you donut dunkers.
All right, boys. Round them up.
And throw them the swinging-est soiree
they've ever seen!
English - US - SDH