D'oh!
Lemonade! Sweet sunshine in your mouth!
Buy a cup or I punch my sister!
- It's true! He's not bluffing!
Ow.
Maybe we should put a dollar in the jar,
prime the pump.
What are we? A piano bar?
I'll take 15 lemonades.
- Make that 16.
Huh?
Lousy dog. If you had your way,
I'd walk you every day.
Lemonade!
GIRL: Stop pushing.
Six cups, please. And put it on my tab.
Keep moving, deadbeat. Cash only.
Fine. Lemonade's for babies, anyways.
I'm going to Moe's for beer!
Have fun drinking your lemonade, babies!
Lisa? Can Daddy borrow your bike?
- I guess.
Hey, Moe. Give me a...
- Homer, shush.
We're watching Krabappel
try to break up with Skinner.
Seymour, I have something difficult
I want to say to you.
I understand.
It can be very difficult for a woman
to propose marriage.
But I am willing to go halfsies on a ring.
- Seymour... Excuse me.
Any of you lugs want to break up
with my boyfriend for me?
I'll buy you a beer.
Seymour, Edna asked me to talk to you.
Splendid. Shall we discuss music
or the weather?
No. This is about you.
Edna wants to break up.
She wants to break up?
- Yeah.
With me?
Look at it this way.
You're a free man, unlike me.
You have all your hair, unlike me.
No kids tying you down
or a crippling mortgage...
...that you refinanced at 26% because
a dancing Internet cowboy told you to?
Oh, God, I hate my life.
Gee, compared to you,
my life is one big half day.
Exactly. You're good-Iooking.
You have a decent job.
What Ionely widow
wouldn't consider you an option?
Thanks, Homer.
I don't think the school pep squad
could've cheered me up more,
and they were state runners-up in 1997.
Homer, that was amazing.
He actually felt better coming out
of the breakup than he did going in.
Say, Homer, you're real good at this.
Think you could dump
my girlfriend Doreen for me?
Doreen, she's cheated on you
with everyone.
Well, except for me.
And I've showered her with gifts,
fancy soaps and massage oils...
...and what have you.
Here she comes.
Work your magic, Homer.
Is Lenny here?
- I'm afraid Lenny's dead.
What? I just talked to him.
And you will again
because he isn't really dead.
Now this next piece of news
won't seem so bad.
Lemonade! We want lemonade!
- Lemonade! We want lemonade!
Don't worry, folks. Our master chef
is stirring up a fresh batch.
Stop that transaction!
I'm a part-time field agent with
the Springfield Department of Commerce!
Great gig.
- It is a great gig.
May I see your vendor's license?
I think it's... We don't have one.
35 cents? Where did that come from?
Can't be mine. Must be yours!
I don't care if it's 45
cents, I don't want it.
Submit this form to the license bureau.
Until then, this stand is closed!
Boys!
Geez, I'm thirsty. You got any lemonade?
- Not anymore!
Come on, come on! I was halfway through
an operation when my license expired.
I'll get to you just as soon
as I finish this crossword puzzle.
Come on.
- Let's go, buddy!
I left bananas in my car!
Let's see, 10 across,
Franklin Roosevelt's middle name.
Excitement! Wait, that don't fit.
Maybe you could use some help.
FDR's middle name, Delano.
Oxidized surface, well, that's rusty.
Bartenders serve them 'dirty.'
- Ham sandwiches!
No, martinis.
- Oh, right.
One more word. Singer
of Yentl. 13 letters!
I got it! Isaac Bashevis.
Now give me my license!
Give everyone their license!
What is a four letter word for hero?
Hero!
- Yes. But I meant Lisa.
Lisa! Lisa! Lisa!
- Lisa! Lisa! Lisa!
Y'ello?
- Homer? It's your old roommate, Grady.
The gay guy?
That's not all I am!
Well, it's a lot of what I am.
Anyhoo, I heard how good you are
at breaking up couples.
I need your help to break up with Julio.
Because I met someone new,
someone much more cool and refreshing.
Uh-huh.
Got it.
Marge, I'm going to a hardcore gay club...
...and I won't be home
till 3:00 in the morning!
MARGE: Have fun!
Ay, caramba!
Bart, I've fallen in love with crosswords.
It finally happened.
You've gone completely fruit loops.
Froot Loops!
That's the answer to 38 down,
Toucan's delight.
No. I mean you're loco in the coco!
Cocoa! Ice rink drink.
You're losing it!
- Losin'It! Risqué '80s teen flick.
Fine! Go nuts! See if I care!
- Eye care. Optician's concern.
Thanks for your help, Bart!
BART. San Francisco people mover!
Speaking of San Francisco people mover...
Grady is breaking up with me?
You'll always have a special place
in his heart.
In his what?
Oh!
Oh, baby, you are the breakup king.
You have made the seven minutes
that I'm gonna go without love...
...so much more bearable.
Anyone else want me
to get rid of that special someone?
Okay, everyone. Rotate one to your right.
Guess what, Mom? I'm a cruciverbalist!
- Another religion?
You know, you're just gonna drop
the whole thing when you go to college...
...and get a Jewish boyfriend.
Probably. But a cruciverbalist
is a fan of crossword puzzles, which I am.
Me, too! I've been doing them since 1958.
Back then, we called
them alphabet hotels...
'cause every letter
gets its own little room.
I still do the Springfield Shopper puzzle
every day.
Let's see there...
Grampa, everyone knows
that the only real test of skill...
...is the New York Times puzzle,
edited by Will Shortz.
'Will' and 'Shorts,' two things
I'm no longer allowed to change by myself.
Okay, back to the real world.
Isn't it beautiful?
- Sure is.
Who's driving the bus?
- What bus?
HOMER: Sweet Conclusions Breakup Service.
Oh, yes.
We dispose of your loved one humanely,
thanks to our patented Tenderdump system.
I'll be there in 30 minutes
or your breakup is free!
I'm leaving you, baby
With my clothes in my hand
Farewell to you, baby
Get yourself a monkey man
I'm leaving
With my clothes in my hand
Farewell to you
Get yourself a monkey man
Simpson!
What in the blue blazes
are you doing to my hopscotching grids?
I made them into a crossword.
Well, I'm a bit of a puzzle-head myself.
They help me wind down
after a day of dealing with Skinner!
You called?
- Made reference.
My mistake.
Lisa, I think you might be ready for this.
'Bald Man's Basketball League'?
Sorry. Wrong flier. I meant this.
'Citywide Crossword Tournament'?
Thank you!
You're welcome.
Now I have to go home and make sure
my pool boy is using his skimmer!
You called?
- You misheard.
My mistake.
Marge, if I had $100 for every customer
I'd broken up, I'd have
exactly this amount...
'cause that's what I charge!
Homie, I'm not sure about
this new business of yours.
You're making it too easy
for couples to break up...
...just because they hit a rough patch.
I know this is hard on you.
But in time, you'll come to see
it's for the best.
That's one of your breakup lines!
What would've happened if there was
someone who could break us up...
...every time I had my doubts about you?
Who are you?
We are the spirits of the relationships
you killed.
We're the babies
those couples would have had.
And we're the antiques
those couples would have bought together.
Get him, chairs and babies!
Homie?
Marge, I'm getting out
of the breakup business,
and I don't know
if I'll ever sleep soundly again.
Well, maybe...
Wow. So this is what this is.
Cruciverbalists from far and wide
have gathered here...
...for a no-holds-barred test of skill.
Surely some holds are barred?
- No, none.
Well, it sounds really exciting
and you're a delightful young lady.
Now if you'll excuse me.
Hey, what's going on?
It's kind of a secret,
so shut the door most of the way.
We found a way
to make this tournament interesting.
We bet on the matches.
Really? Well, I did bring
this envelope full of money.
And these days,
betting in a bar is safer than any stock,
bond or real estate investment.
Agreed. So who are you gonna bet on?
I want you to put it
all on my little girl.
And parlay with the Asian kid.
He has a name, you know.
What is it?
- I don't know. He's not my kid.
I win!
She won! And like any prudent gambler,
I know when to walk away... Never!
Dah pretty ladies around the world
Got a weird thing to show you
So tell all the boys and girls
Tell your brother, your sister
And your mama, too...
'Cause they're about to go down
And you'll know just what to do
Wave your hands in the air
Like you don't care
Glide by the people
As they start to look and stare
Do your dance, do your dance
Do your dance quick
Mama, come on baby
Tell me what's the word
Word up
Everybody say
When you hear the call
You've got to get it underway
Word up
Okay, everybody. Take a break.
Dad, I could actually win this thing.
And when you win, I win.
I'll explain that to you on your deathbed.
My only fear is, I always sabotage myself
when I'm on the verge of happiness.
You what?
- In my young life,
I've seen that every time
I'm about to achieve true happiness,
some little piece of me says,
'You don't deserve this.'
And another little piece says, 'I agree.'
Right, right! But will
it happen this time?
With my luck, I bet it will.
It's practically a sure thing.
Hmm.
Contestants to your boards.
Wish me luck!
- Just be yourself!
I want to change my bet.
I'm going against my daughter!
I'll take your money,
but I won't look you in the eye.
Fine. I won't look you in the eye.
Have I made the bet yet?
- I got it.
We're down to our final two contestants.
But before they compete,
we would like to pay tribute...
...to all the words that have been removed
from the dictionary in the past year.
You know, my wife, Shirley,
she's the real crossword
ace in our family.
Fills in those letters
fast as hail on a tin roof.
Ping-ping-ping, she's done.
Shirley passed away two years ago.
But I'm still not over it.
That's so sad.
- Hey, what can you do?
Life keeps changing the music, but
you gotta keep up the cha-cha-cha, huh?
Let's see. I'll spread some Q's around.
That'll get my brain going.
I dropped my glasses!
Oh, Shirley baby, I let you down.
Hey, there are no lenses in these glasses.
Let's see. That's Enrico Fermi.
And there you got the Pet Shop Boys.
And cross the 'T' and zing the 'z.'
And skit-skat-skoodly,
I'm all the way home.
Lisa got hustled.
I blew it again.
She blew it again!
Woo-hoo!
Here's your money,
drenched in your daughter's tears.
You know, for a bartender bookie,
you're awfully judgmental.
Boy, Dad seems awfully happy.
And there's something different
about him.
He bought new shoelaces
with fancy metal tips.
Dad, did you come into some money
we don't know about?
No.
- You got highlights in your hair!
The sun did that.
And your car antenna
has been straightened and re-balled.
What's going on?
Well, sweetie,
Daddy made a little extra money...
...betting against you
in the crossword tournament.
You'll understand when you're a parent...
...placing large wagers
against your own children.
I hope you're not mad.
No, I'm not mad.
You sure you're not mad?
- No, I'm not mad.
Mr. Teddy, can you ask Lisa if she's mad?
What's that, Mr. Teddy?
You're saying that you know women.
And that when women say
they're not mad, they're madder than ever?
She's gone. Can you drive me home?
I'm a little drunk.
Lisa? Lisa?
Lisa, sweetie, please look at your daddy.
You stopped being my daddy
as soon as you bet against me!
All I have now is a mom.
Which is why I'm taking her maiden name.
From now on, I'm Lisa Bouvier!
Hey, Mr. S, Lisa B.
No!
Would you like to buy some band candy?
- Yes!
Lisa's mad at me,
and now she's using
Marge's maiden name instead of mine.
Homer, whatever you done
to that little girl,
you just gotta do something even nicer
to win her back.
She may never take back your name,
but there's still a chance
she'll take you back as her daddy.
Wow. Nobody gives better
parenting advice than childless drunks.
So the name Lisa Simpson
is available, huh?
A lot of goodwill attached to that name.
I'm gonna take it.
Lisa's Tavern. Lisa speaking.
Lisa, sweetie,
I'm honored that you chose my name,
but it's not that great.
Back in high school,
the boys used to call me Marge Boobier.
Hey, Bouvier was Jackie Kennedy's
maiden name.
Really? I never knew that.
Well, what did you think her name was
before it was Kennedy?
Jackie O! Like SpaghettiOs!
I thought that was where
her money came from.
Look, why don't you cheer up by doing
a New York Times crossword puzzle, huh?
I'm through with crosswords.
My innocence died
in those 441 little boxes.
It might be a fun way
to kill a couple hours.
A couple hours?
I can do the Sunday puzzle
in less than one hour.
'Couple of hours.'
Last clue, loses on purpose.
Huh...
Diet!
Will Shortz, you clever rascal.
And a new record time! Wait a second.
'Dumb dad sorry for his bet.'
Wow. It's almost as if
Dad planted that message.
No. It must just be a weird coincidence.
But what if it's not? It must be.
Or mustn't it not?
Dad, I know this is crazy,
but did you plant a message to me
in the New York Times crossword puzzle?
Well, I had a little help from this guy.
New York Times crossword editor,
Will Shortz!
And master puzzle constructor,
Merl Reagle!
I actually wrote that crossword.
- And I edited it.
Now get back to crosswording!
- Yes, sir.
Well, I must admit, I'm kind of touched.
'Dumb dad sorry for his bet.' Nice.
You didn't get Homer's
whole message, Lisa.
I didn't?
Take a look at the first letters
of all the clues.
Dear Lisa, you make me so happy.
Really, really, really happy.
Sorry. He told me I needed 144 letters.
What was my point again?
Oh, right.
Bouvier or Simpson, I cherish you.
Oh, Dad.
...
...Cherish is the word I use to describe
All the feeling that I have
hiding here for you inside
You don't know how many times
I've wished that I had told you
English - US - SDH