D'oh!
SANTAS: Ho-ho-ho.
ALL: O Christmas Tree, O Christmas Tree...
You're on the curb and dead now
- You're on the curb and dead now...
Your Christmas lights are in the box
- Your Christmas lights are in the box
In two months we will change the clocks
O Christmas Tree, O...
They sure give the Christmas spirit
the bum's rush around here.
And they've already started exploiting
the next holiday.
So, young man, have you judged people...
...by the content of
their character this year?
Yes, Reverend Doctor.
- Lunch time!
Free at last! Free at last!
Okay, remember our deal.
Everyone gets to return one
Christmas present with no hurt feelings.
I'm returning this kitten calendar.
I'm also returning this kitten calendar.
Kitten calendar.
Hey, those are 15 month calendars!
That gives you three extra kittens!
That's the last time I get you guys
a Christmas present at the last minute.
Man, those are ugly kittens.
Mom! Dad! Our mall got a Mapple Store!
It's so sterile.
MyPods. MyPhones.
A Brainiac Bar.
My question is the following statement.
Operating system 4.2 has sloppier
architecture than a Tijuana anthill.
Did you get peanut butter
in your Ethernet port again?
No. I got mayonnaise in the CD drive.
I see you're admiring our MyCube.
It's fueled by dreams
and powered by imagination.
What does it do?
- You should ask yourself,
'What can I do for it?'
- Okay, what can I do for you?
Please, I'm begging you!
- Sir, it's not even turned on yet.
But it's glowing.
- That light confirms that it's off.
I can't afford any of your products.
But can I buy some fake white earbuds
so people will think I have a MyPod?
Sure. Those are called MyPhonies.
And they cost $40.
I'll never get a Mapple anything.
KRUSTY: I hate this MyPod!
I can't watch movies
on a screen this small!
And the music today, don't get me started!
I said don't get me started!
Come on!
Isn't someone gonna get me started?
Let's go, Teeny.
Maybe somebody at Old Navy
will get me started.
Here, kid. You take it.
- Thank you, Krusty.
Don't thank me.
Thank the Jewish Clown Awards
gift basket.
I'm a Mapple person!
We're all Mapple people.
- Sorry.
ANNOUNCER: Attention, Mapple universe.
Prepare for a live announcement
from Mapple Founder...
...and Chief Imaginative
Officer, Steve Mobs.
Steve Mobs!
He's a genius!
He's like a God who knows what we want!
Greetings. It is I.
Your insanely great leader, Steve Mobs.
I'm speaking to you from
Mapple headquarters deep below the sea...
...with an announcement
that will completely change...
...the way you look at everything.
And that announcement is...
BART: You're all losers!
Huh?
You think you're cool
because you buy a $500 phone...
...with a picture of a fruit on it?
Well, guess what?
They cost 8 bucks to make...
...and I pee on every one!
I have made a fortune off you chumps,
and I've invested it all in Microsoft.
Now my boyfriend Bill Gates and I kiss
each other on a pile of your money!
Traitor! Your heart is blacker
than your turtleneck!
Who dares question the boss we fired
10 years ago and then brought back?
It was my brother, Bart!
Flay him with your earbuds!
Flay him, I say!
MyCube, take me away!
Loving you
is easy 'cause you're beautiful
Get him! Get him good!
Stupid angry mob, chasing me because
I shine a harsh light on modern society.
Now I know how Dane Cook feels!
Mmm. What's that exotic aroma?
Smells like a hamburger
cooked at a rug store.
Hello. Would you like some lamb?
Whoa! All these years
I've been petting lambs...
...when I should've been shoving them
in my mouth!
I'm Bart.
- I'm Bashir.
My family and I just
moved here from Jordan.
Jordan. That's on some map
somewhere, right?
Bashir, introduce me to your new friend.
Bashir, you didn't tell
me you had a sister.
Such a charmer.
Would you like to stay for dinner?
Hey, I never refuse food from strangers.
Okay. You're new to our school,
so here's the deal.
We call Skinner, Skin Rash.
Mr. Wiener is Mr. Whiner.
And Groundskeeper Willie,
Grounds Creeper Stupid.
That's not clever.
And I have so many aspects you can mock.
I'm poor. I'm dirty.
I can't read or write.
I think movies are real.
Okay, next.
Here's the food at the cafeteria
that will make you sick.
Coleslaw, tuna, all chowders and gumbos.
The only thing that's safe
is the pork chops.
My religion says I can never eat pork.
A different religion?
Do not tell anyone that,
because if the bullies around here
find out that you're different...
JIMBO: Who's different?
What's your name, sweat stain?
Bashir.
- Bash Here?
I love a kid that comes with directions!
Okay, Bash Here,
tell us where you came from
so we can punch you back there.
I'm gonna punch you extra hard
because I secretly think you're cute!
Whoa! Whoa!
You can't just wail on him because he's...
What religion are you anyway?
Muslim.
- Oh, boy.
You're the reason I can't carry
toothpaste on an airplane!
Ow!
Look, guys. Everyone's different.
Jimbo, you're Christian.
Dolph, you're Jewish.
And Kearney,
your family's in that cult Moe started.
I had to join. My mom's doing the savior.
I mean, the one true Moe.
- You're the one true Moe.
Help me, oh, mighty Moe!
- I can't.
I'm not really a God. I
was just acting crazy...
...to get out of jury duty.
Look at Lisa Simpson
over there by herself.
Not talking to us, her best friends.
Do we hate her?
Yes!
- Yes!
Lisa, we came to tell you that we...
Is that a MyPod?
- Yeah!
I've already downloaded
so much incredible music.
Check out Moon Dreams,
from Miles Davis' Birth of the Cool.
Or check out
this MyTunes exclusive episode...
...of Itchy and Scratchy.
Why?
Stop!
I love the nightlife
I've got to boogie
On the disco round
Marge, I installed all
the low energy bulbs.
MARGE: What have you done
with the old ones?
Disposed of them
in an environmentally-friendly manner.
Milhouse is looking good.
He's got contacts, changed color,
got a cool new catch phrase.
Dad, that's Bashir, my new friend.
Bart forgot this, sir.
- 'Sir'?
That's the kind of respect you'd have
to strangle out of an American kid.
You know, Bart never told me
he had a handsome teenage brother.
I'm really 38.
Thirty-eight waist I might believe.
Hey, Carl.
Got any idea what direction Mecca's in?
Why don't you ask Homer?
He ought to know
by dint of his son's new friend.
Hey, Bashir's great.
If Derek Jeter married Mariah Carey,
it wouldn't last,
but I bet they'd have a kid like him.
Homer, this is serious.
This Bashir kid is Muslim,
and therefore up to something.
Well, I can't believe that till I see...
...a fictional TV program
espousing your point of view.
All right.
For the last time, Fayed.
Where did you hide the nerve gas?
Under your Statue of Liberty's dress!
And she loved it!
Oh, my God. What can I do?
Well, if you want to stop Bashir
and his war on American principles,
you could discriminate against
his family in employment and housing.
Yeah, that's pretty patriotic.
But I got a better idea. Invite them over.
A little dinner, a little dessert.
Then you Jack Bauer them into giving you
all their secrets.
I guess I have no choice.
Homie, it's very open-minded of you...
...to have Bart's Muslim friend's
Muslim family over.
Here's the plan, Marge.
You keep them talking.
I'll be listening and quietly judging.
The doorbell will tell you
when they're here.
So, how did you two meet?
We met while studying at Jordan
University of Science and Technology.
Interesting.
Why just the other day, I was reading
that science is used to make bombs.
Now bait the trap.
Why don't I get us dessert?
I made us a little cake. Care to cut?
Watch this, Lenny.
Not now! I got soap in my eyes!
No. Thank you.
What's the matter?
Don't like the taste of freedom?
Dad, these people are my friends.
Don't fear them just because
they have a different religion,
a different culture
and their last name is bin Laden.
Young man, you do not respect us
by disrespecting your father.
I like the way you Italians think.
- Shut up, old man.
I think it is time for us to go.
That's it! Ruin a perfect evening!
You're teaching Bart
a terrible lesson of intolerance!
I'm sorry.
It's just so fun and easy to judge
people based on religion.
Well, I want you to go over
to their house and apologize.
But we're the more powerful country
for a few more years.
Okay. I'll apologize.
Don't eat that, sweetie. It's poison.
'I am sorry I suspected you of being
soulless murderers of innocent children.
'I hope we can move past this and...'
Dynamite? They are terrorists!
Must leave quietly.
So far, so good.
Marge, I was right!
Everybody is whatever I think they are!
I saw them unloading dynamite!
Homer, I'm sure you didn't see anything.
Go to sleep.
All right, sweetie.
But if I wake up tomorrow,
we'll discuss it.
Hi, Homer!
You rubbed. You must like me!
You really, really like me!
Good morning, Ramadan!
Come to Crazy Fayedi's!
Our prices are Hussein!
Here's Genie!
Now do Flanders!
- No.
Now I will destroy
your decadent western society.
No!
Usually that ends the dream.
The power of dreaming has convinced me
the threat is real!
Delivery for Lisa Simpson.
It's a gift from Mapple!
Such beautiful packaging.
I never thought a company
could be my soul mate.
It's my first MyBill.
$1,200?
But I only downloaded 1212 songs.
I gotta prove the genie was right.
Off to work.
Sometimes I wish you would quit
that awful business.
But I love blowing up buildings.
Oh, my God!
Safely and legally
in order to make room for new buildings.
Darling.
I think you're working much too hard.
Yes. I am killing myself.
But it is all for the profit.
And after the explosion,
I will be in a better place.
That corner office
with the downtown view.
Oh, it's you. What do you want?
I want to apologize for being
such a jerk at dinner.
And I thought the best way to do that...
...would be to come to your house
and poke around.
Mr. Simpson, I accept your apology.
Goodbye.
Wait, wait, wait, wait! I read somewhere
your people are hospitable to guests.
Is that true?
- Yes.
Praise be Oliver.
- That's Allah.
We'll look it up in the Corona.
So, now that we're alone,
death to America, right?
Homer, why are you really here?
- Look at that!
We're out of almond paste!
Don't get up! I'll grind
the almonds myself!
A computer.
I'm in.
They're gonna blow it up!
Homer, I don't hear almond grinding.
Just listen! I'm grinding them now.
Ow!
My finger!
Here comes the ambulance!
My, you're a handsome fellow.
Just get in the ambulance, Mr. Simpson.
We'll see to your finger.
Why, thank you.
My finger!
Everyone, get out!
Run for your lives!
Run for your...
Stay where you are.
Bart!
Boy, don't blow up this mall.
It has the cookie store
that gives free samples!
I can't believe your dad gets paid
to blow stuff up.
Actually, Bart, my job is about math
and engineering.
Every calculation is to make sure
the explosion is safe.
Did you factor in one bald idiot?
- No, I...
USA! USA! USA!
Dad, it was an empty building.
It was supposed to come down.
What about the bridge?
- That was supposed to open tomorrow.
Do we really need a bridge there?
The Duff brewery is on that island.
I'll save you!
That banner has really paid for itself
over the years!
We accept your apology.
Lisa, add another name
to our Christmas card list.
Next to our Jewish friends.
Where is Lisa?
She said something about the bottom
of the ocean and 'be back in a month.'
ANNOUNCER:
Welcome to Mapple headquarters.
The cost of this journey
will be added to your bill.
Come on. Come on. Yes!
Sixteen million results!
Mr. Mobs, there's
a surface dweller here to see you.
MyTunes user Jazzgal62.
Lisa Simpson. Send her in.
Lisa! It's insanely great to see you.
Mr. Mobs, I sort of downloaded
too many songs onto my MyPod,
and I don't have the money
to pay for them.
And do you think you could consider
a reduced payment plan?
I'm sorry.
I know our posters say,
'Think differently,'
but our real slogan is, 'No refunds.'
Can't you open your Mapple menu
and click on the 'compassion bar'?
Oh, please?
Lisa, how would you like
to work for Mapple?
Would I ever!
Think differently.
English - US - SDH