D'oh!
And so in summary,
there are only two real commandments,
and the other eight are just filler.
I knew it.
- Yeah.
And now I have some exciting news.
Tomorrow we'll be blessed with a visit...
...from the highest ranking clergyman
of our Presbylutheran faith,
His Holiness, the Parson!
The Parson? He's coming here?
Oh, my God! She fainted!
Let's go get smelling salts.
HOMER: Suckers!
Springfielders have
camped out all night...
...to get a glimpse of
the most saintly person...
...to visit our town...
...since Mother Teresa stopped here
to gas up her Vespa.
And I'm selling all sorts of
faith-based knickknacks.
Let's take a look.
I'd commit arson for the parson.
Clergymen can kiss my apse.
All kinds of gems.
Surprisingly, none of them have sold.
Except for this one.
There you have it.
News has never been softer.
What's that? The Parson is here!
Oh, my God! It's him!
The earthly embodiment of the elected
chair of the National Congress of Deacons!
Well, well, well. Hello, everybody.
I hope you didn't go
to all this trouble for little old me.
Parson! Parson! Give us a quick
official church position on family.
Well, in these modern times,
family is more important than ever.
You just made my moustache tingle.
Settle. Settle down.
Now, now. I am just a man like any other,
that has been chosen by God.
I have come here from our world spiritual
headquarters in Michigan City, Indiana,
to say, keep up the good work.
And now if you'll excuse me,
I'll do a little speakin'
with your deacon.
I love to go to church
It's where I like to be
I get a day in of praying
And still tee off by three
Calm down, Tim.
He's just your old roommate
from Texas Christian.
He's like the pope of this thing!
This would be like Mary Kay visiting you
when you were selling her cosmetics!
That is, if you had stuck with it.
You asked me to quit
because I was making more than you.
Not now. He's here.
Welcome, Your Holiness.
You'll love what we've done
with the church.
There's fresh wax on all the pews.
Sounds to me like somebody put on
more than just one coat.
Maybe.
Tim, is there somewhere that we can talk?
Of course. My office.
- Perfect.
Walking to your office
Is what I like to do
Maybe while we're at it
We'll peek in at your pews
Nilla Wafer?
I'll take two if you don't mind.
Tim, I'm here because of a problem
with your last recertification.
When we tried to charge the filing fee
to your credit card, it was declined.
Oh, yeah.
The bank put on a security hold after they
saw a charge from an offshore poker club.
Helen had bought a fireplace poker
from Nova Scotia.
She says it shifts logs better than
American pokers, but I disagree.
We'll get through it. We always do.
Well, love conquers all, huh?
I remember when she was
Helen Schwartzbaum.
In fact, I remember when she was
Harold Schwartzbaum.
You what?
- I've said too much.
But for the three months
it took your card to go through,
you weren't certified.
Anything you officiated during that time,
funerals, baptisms, even bingo,
well, it just didn't count.
Well,
I'm sure the Lord is understanding.
No, he's not!
I'll notify those affected right away.
Tea time.
What's going on?
- Helen, I was briefly uncertified.
So all those graces you said were a lie?
That food might as well have been
regurgitated by Satan himself.
Regurgitated by Satan
He couldn't keep it down
Old 666, he got sick, sick, sick
And that's how volcanoes were born
Due to a bureaucratic snafu,
I wasn't an official minister
when we laid your dear Estelle to rest.
So, she's still alive?
I'm afraid not.
Good. Because I left her ashes on the bus.
Mmm.
So, Captain, when I blessed your vessel,
it didn't count.
Maybe the next one!
So I'm afraid I wasn't a minister
when I blessed your tin roof shanty.
So that's why that ghost
keeps a-comin' to the window.
MAILMAN: Afternoon.
- Fly away, ghostie!
Go back to your haunted cornfield!
Reverend Lovejoy, you deliver pizza now?
We didn't order a pizza.
But you forgot the pizza anyway.
Marge, the pizza place screwed up again!
You remember when I remarried you two
after Homer got that divorce?
Like it was yesterday.
Kirk and Luann split up.
So, Homer, fearing we would do the same,
preemptively filed for divorce.
But then you re-married us
and we were as solid as ever.
And I think Apu got lucky with my sister.
Well, I'm afraid that joyous occasion...
...fell during a time
when I wasn't actually a minister.
Since that time,
you two have not been legally wed.
You don't get it, Padre.
My old lady and I have a thing going on.
We don't need a piece of paper
to keep it real.
Who are you calling an old lady?
- I need that paper quick!
So, you and Mom aren't married?
Does that mean I'm a bastard?
You were born while they were married.
So, legally, no.
But in the sense someone calls you one
when they're angry, yes.
It's not a big deal.
We'll just go to City Hall
and get married there.
I think it's romantic.
You can pretend you're newlyweds
starting a life together.
Yeah, instead of exhausted zombies
running down the clock.
Why, you little bastard!
That's the angry one.
MOE: Hmm.
This isn't the most romantic place
to get married.
Sweetie, any place I'm marrying you
is the most romantic place in the world.
Watch your back!
Half a corpse coming through!
Marge, this time I'm gonna give you
the wedding you deserve.
Let's get out of here.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
That's the line to get out.
MARGE: Ah!
Hello?
- Hello. It's me, Lance Romance.
Your first mission
is to look out the window.
Whatever you say, Lance.
Oh!
Whoa!
BILL: This is Bill and Marty saying,
''Marge, go down to the basement.''
Homer, what's going on?
The violin, pants with a crease? Why?
Marge, you deserve a wedding day that,
unlike our children,
was planned in advance.
So, will you marry me in style?
Yes, Homer! Yes!
Did you hear that, Santa?
She said yes! Yes!
Now back to your cold, airless tomb.
SANTA: Ho, ho, ho.
Oh! It's beautiful.
But that's an awful lot to pay
for a dress I'll only wear once.
Marge, a woman only gets one chance
at a second remarriage.
The choice is yours.
You can look like a fairy princess
or a pig wrapped in rags.
Uh... A princess?
- Fine. We'll do it your way.
This one's a little gay, isn't it?
Well, the last time I checked,
pirates weren't gay.
How'd you check?
Check out this rocket ship cake, Marge!
That's for a child's birthday.
We're going to get this one.
Maybe we could bury the rocket ship
inside the cake.
And that would be a big surprise
because I'd forget about it pretty quick.
No rockets! You can pick the frosting.
Chocolate!
- We'll take lemon.
Okay, I want white roses at the altar,
red roses along the aisle,
and blue roses in the centerpieces.
- There are no blue roses.
I want to talk to Howard!
- Howard died 10 years ago.
Well, did he take
all the blue roses with him?
My father was a lovely man.
He took very good care
of my mother and me.
All right, people, I want every table
to have two baskets of bread...
...but only one plate of butter.
That will stimulate conversation.
What if we...
- There is no 'we' in wedding!
But there is, Marge.
The first two letters.
I can't believe you're ruining
the second Thursday before the wedding!
Homer!
I can't believe you told Lenny and Carl
they could bring dates.
'Cause they're not even coming
to the wedding.
Why not?
Because their RSVP cards
arrived one day after the deadline!
Marge, maybe you should take a break
from wedding planning.
I think you're becoming a bridezilla!
Bridezilla?
A combination of bride and Godzilla?
How could you say that?
More like you're a King Wrong!
Mmm.
No matter what I do, Marge yells at me.
If she's like this now,
what will she be like
after we get married?
Oh!
Okay! Okay! Everyone, back off!
I want to see myself.
A pimple? Not on my day, you don't.
Okay, it's go time. Dim the lights.
Cue the band.
And release the groom!
Homer, that's you!
We are now 11 seconds behind schedule!
Homie?
I can't believe Homer
left me at the altar.
Marge, have a shrimp puff.
Wipe your tears
with a monogrammed napkin.
MARGE: Oh!
I know it is hard,
but smile for the cameraman
from Gary's Magic Moments.
You have my deepest sympathy.
HOMER: What's going on?
What's with all the darkness?
Hello? Marge? Where am I?
What the...
I'm chained up like a common bicycle!
Who would do this to me?
It would have to be someone
who could afford a chain.
DEEP VOICE ON SPEAKER:
You're going to be here awhile.
But I have to marry Marge!
As of now,
your pathetic little life means nothing!
Just so you know, you're making
a pretty bad first impression!
It's all my fault.
Homer wanted to serve
those little cocktail hotdogs.
But, no! I had to have spring rolls!
They taste like nothing.
I don't understand.
Dad would never miss an open bar
with chicken wings.
Plus, he loves Mom and us,
yadda-yadda-yadda.
Hey, I found something!
Sideshow Bob!
- Sideshow Bob?
He ruined the wedding,
getting his revenge on us at last!
Because he knows that if Mom and Dad
don't get married, I'll never be born!
I've got some wedding registry items
for Mrs. Simpson.
I'm afraid I'm just Ms. Simpson now.
Interesting nuance.
I'd like to hear more about it
but company policy forbids chitchat.
I miss you so much.
DEEP VOICE: To remove that chain,
you need the key to the lock.
You idiot.
How am I ever gonna find the key to the...
Here it is.
To get the key,
I have to lick through a lollipop?
How awful!
What the...
- The lollipop is made of hot sauce.
Oh! Whose side are you on?
Sideshow Bob, drop that knife
and give back our dad!
I'm working on a bust of Krusty
and using this knife to aerate the clay.
Anyone for a peppermint tea?
- Not for me.
But the monkey
needs to keep his strength up.
We're gonna drop him out of a blimp
tomorrow and see what happens.
Don't worry. Nothing's gonna
happen to you, Mr. Teeny number seven.
Bob, did you take any breaks yesterday
to kidnap our dad?
Impossible. I was with Bob the whole day!
Then we watched the deluxe DVD
of The House of Sand and Fog.
At night,
we slept in the same bed for warmth.
Then we woke up, had a little nosh,
watched The House of Sand and Fog again,
with commentary.
The director was an ass.
Fine. But how do you explain this?
Nice of you to think of me.
However, 'SB' could be anyone.
Scott Baio, the Sultan of Brunei,
the former Polish secret police,
the Sluzba Bezpieczenstwa. Or...
Marge, I miss you!
I miss you so much.
Wait till he finds out
the key isn't the key,
but just a hotter sauce.
Hmm?
- Hmm?
I'm gonna say this for the last time.
Bart, if this is one of your pranks,
very funny.
Maybe we should let him out soon.
- Not till Marge dumps him for good.
Hey, lame-o.
Ready for some fun with fire ants?
What's fun about fire ants?
They're... Oh. You're being sarcastic.
Wow. You're the smartest guy
in that room.
Thank you. That's very...
Oh! More sarcasm.
Just see that my fiancée,
Marge, gets this,
my wedding vows.
'Marge, I hope this day is as perfect
for you as the day we met was for me.
'You always find the one grain of sugar
in the saltshaker that is I.
'With each marriage,
I get a little better.
'Maybe after a thousand,
I'll be worthy of you.'
I miss you. I miss the kids.
God help me, I even miss your sisters!
Poor guy.
- He loves her so much.
Excuse me.
But I have been waiting 45 minutes
for you to slide my license over to me.
Closed!
Okay, you are hereby
banned from my store.
You will have to shop at the Kwik-E-Mart
across the street from me!
You know, the much nicer,
much newer one.
Good day to you!
Mom! Mom! We know where Dad is.
He's right here.
- I'm not sure what happened.
I was kidnapped, then tortured,
then I fell into a
surprisingly sound sleep.
When I awoke, I felt refreshed.
Then I was blindfolded,
and two sobbing trolls
threw me out of a van onto our lawn.
I'm just happy you're back.
Now let's get that chain off you.
Won't it dry up in a few days
and fall off in the bath?
I've missed your nonsense.
Now there's no evidence
to tie us to the kidnapping.
And we've got a one-year lease
on that torture room.
So maybe we can put
a tanning bed in there.
We know it was you, Selma Bouvier!
Would you kids like cookies?
Let your Auntie Patty make some cookies.
We don't want your cookies.
What she means is,
we'll eat your cookies later.
If you don't want us
to tell our mom what you did,
you're gonna have to pay.
Pay? Pay for what?
Ask her. She's the brains.
I'm the thing that's not the brains.
And with the inking and
application of this...
...stamp, you are
officially married. Next.
I'm sorry, honey.
I wanted so badly to give you
a fancy wedding.
Homer, one thing I've learned is that...
...you don't need a fancy wedding
when you're marrying the man you love.
Just what I always wanted!
A rocket ship wedding cake!
We emptied our 401s for this?
Zoom. Zoom.
Oh! Blue roses!
Yes. It took a lot of
frantic genetic engineering,
but enjoy.
No! You're a plant now!