D'oh!
Care to try our new sciencewater?
MARGE: The label is all in lower case.
It's like drinking e.e. Cummings.
And each of our flavors
is named after a real word!
Nourish.
- Mmm.
Vitality.
- Oh!
Purple.
- Ooh!
Potato Lime.
- Mmm.
I Love the '90s.
- Oh.
New Car Smell.
Excuse me.
I'm feeling a little over-hydrated.
That's normal.
It just means your
bladder's full of science.
Now if you'll excuse me,
our company just went bankrupt.
Gotta find a place to tinkle!
Language!
Schools have bathrooms.
And I'm a woman,
so my going in unattended
won't cause a panic.
Hey, Mrs. Simpson.
- Janey.
That's Bart's class.
Lousy teachers.
Lousy hangover.
This school has really gone downhill.
That's an awfully crowded classroom.
Three, two, one.
Okay, children,
I've just been granted tenure,
so I'm gonna sit back
and let Ralph teach for awhile.
Class, in what year was one plus one?
The answer is the Amazing Ralph!
The only person getting
an education here today was me,
in how bad it is!
Mrs. Simpson, let me pour you a drink.
Scotch? Vodka? Gin?
I got everything you want.
I want my kids in a decent school!
Hey, I want the 'check engine'
light on my dashboard to shut off,
but that ain't gonna happen.
Aah!
And because of cutbacks,
they were combining math with P.E.
They were playing dodgebook!
Look at this.
Springfield Elementary's rating is so low,
it's more than two standard deviations
below the norm!
I can't understand that math reference
because I went to Springfield Elementary!
My cousin goes to a much better school.
He lives in Waverly Hills.
Their school system's the best!
Their auditorium and their gym
are two different rooms.
We can't afford to move to Waverly Hills.
Their house prices have commas in them.
As it is, our lawn
is just green-painted cement.
I just wish I could go
to a school like that even for one week.
'Tis better to have learned and lost
than never to have learned at all.
What if we got a small apartment there?
We wouldn't have to live in it,
but we would
have a Waverly Hills address.
Mom, that's brilliant!
We could go to a school
where special doesn't always mean bad...
...and where the teachers
don't have to moonlight as telemarketers.
As you know,
the music of Air Supply is timeless.
And now their 50 biggest hits
are on four CDs.
Wait, wait, wait.
You're putting us in a new school?
What about my friends?
Oh! Elementary school friends,
those are forever!
You're always
gonna be friends with Milhouse!
Stand by me Oh, stand by me
Oh, stand now, stand by me Stand by me
I need to rent an apartment
in the worst part of Waverly Hills,
the crappier the better.
So cheap, eh?
- Ahso sheepay to you.
I can't afford this place.
It's way too fancy.
Sometimes there's not a train going by.
Four walls?
I was thinking
more of something in a two or three.
No windows, no parking
and a man died here.
Play it cool, Homer.
Don't let her know it's perfect.
Yeah...
Well, I'm looking
at a lot of murder sites right now.
Where's the bedroom?
- Right here.
Tempting, tempting.
Where's the bathroom?
In the Ethiopian restaurant...
...at the end of the block.
- I'll take it!
Waverly Hills
That's where I want to be!
Gimme gimme Gimme gimme
Squatting in Waverly Hills
Waverly Hills
Get education fraudulently
Gimme gimme Gimme gimme
Mooching off Waverly Hills
Well, welcome to Waverly Hills.
Your children can
start school immediately.
Thank you.
- Now,
you'll be getting a random visit
from the inspector sometime this month.
The what?
- It's just a formality...
...to make sure you actually live here.
Some people use the address
just so their kids can go to our schools.
I can see them now with their
bald heads and their blue-haired wives!
How I despise them.
Yeah. Well, here's our inspector now.
Call it, friendo.
Heads! I mean, tails! I mean, on its side!
Well done.
Now let me validate your parking.
That's not enough.
Thank you.
- Oh!
Goodnight, Marge.
It's so kind of you to live there
so our kids can go to a better school.
When do I get to move back home?
You just have to stay there...
...until that psychopathic
school inspector...
...makes a surprise visit.
You can come home when the heat's off.
The heat is off.
The hissing from the radiator is a snake.
Please just stay there
till Bart graduates high school.
That's another 20 or 30 years!
Where am I?
Wow! Your first day at the new school.
Lisa, have fun. Bart, don't.
Look at this place.
It's everything I've ever dreamed of.
On campus stables!
Field trips to Europe!
Oh, my God.
Look what they serve in the cafeteria.
Welcome.
I'm your new principal, Dr. Bettelheim.
Ooh! A doctorate!
Wait! Don't matriculate those students!
Principal Skinner?
We need Lisa Simpson
at Springfield Elementary.
She's our top student and she writes the
fun facts in the morning announcements.
Skinner!
Bettelheim.
Superintendent Chalmers!
What are you doing at another school?
Seymour, as superintendent,
I supervise every school in the district.
So, you're overseeing other people?
I'm sorry if you
misunderstood our arrangement.
What am I supposed to tell our children?
They already know.
And they're happy for me.
Hey, neighbor. Welcome to the jungle,
also known as,
'Royal Waverly Apartments.'
Brought you a housewarming present.
That was great!
You mind if I use that at work?
It's yours, my friend.
- Hey, are you into poker?
Well, I love to play,
but I'm not very good.
Also, I always forget
to cash my chips back in for money.
This man crush just got bromantic.
You make words into dudes!
Guy five!
- Yeah!
Hi, newbie. I'm Caitlin with a 'C.'
This is Kaitlyn with a 'K.'
And this is Kate Lynn, two words.
I'm Lisa, one word.
So, Lisa, what's your favorite
Alaska Nebraska song?
Mine's Touch a Star.
Mine's Make It Yours: The Star Song.
Who's Alaska Nebraska?
Only the greatest 16-year-old
singer /actress in the world!
Do you even know how lame you are?
I should warn you.
By using the term 'lame,'
you're violating
the Americans with Disabilities Act.
Ew! That makes you even lamer!
B-plus?
- Nice work.
But I always get A's!
At my old school, I got so many A's,
the teachers didn't even check my work!
Maybe that's why you got so many A's.
Oh, my God. You've been challenged.
Well, Lisa, let's see how you respond.
Bart, at this school,
I'm not a brain, I'm not popular,
I'm not anything!
Not to worry.
At this school, we've got a clean slate.
In fact, I'm establishing
my cred right now.
CLANCY: Got you!
Hey!
- Come on!
Take this as a warning, kids.
Bart Simpson is the ultimate bad boy.
Befriend him
and you'll wind up just like him,
a rebel who does
what he wants when he wants.
Wow. Come on, tough guy. Let's go.
GIRL: He's so bad!
Okay, I held up my side of the bargain.
Now you have to go to Ralphie's
birthday party.
A deal's a deal.
- And you'll stay till we cut the cake.
Fine. I want one gift bag now,
and one when the party's over.
- Fine, you got it.
BIG TONY: You wanted a powwow, Chief?
I know you been dealing drugs
at the high school.
But I'll look the other way
if you come to Ralphie's party.
I ain't gonna pin no tail on no donkey!
Look, just come to the party.
It's gonna be fun.
Batman's gonna be there!
Batman?
I ain't messing with no caped crusader.
ALL: Wow.
I wonder what he did?
I heard he burned down his old school.
- I heard he killed a groundskeeper.
Oh, my. That's a bit rough.
Now to turn my sis from loser
to schmoozer.
Qué pasa, ladies?
You're that bad boy.
- What do you want from us, bad boy?
Don't tell anyone but my sister Lisa
is best friends with Alaska Nebraska.
Get out of here!
- No way!
You so lie!
She didn't even know
who Alaska Nebraska was.
Duh! She said that
because she respects Alaska's privacy,
just as I have no doubt
you guys will respect Lisa's privacy.
We're approaching
bandwidth overload, sir.
It's gossip at Waverly Elementary.
How juicy is it?
- The juiciest!
Hi, Lisa.
- Hi, Caitlin.
She knows my name!
- No, she knows my name!
Bart, your plan worked.
My plan was to lie, lie like hell,
and that's what I did.
Well, well.
It seems like someone
forgot about a previous engagement...
...at the bowling alley from 2:00 to 4:30!
Get him and string him up!
'You have the right to be delighted.
'If you do not have a gift,
one will be provided for you.'
HOMER: It's open.
Marge, I'm glad you came!
There's a kegger down the hall.
We can go as soon
as I desecrate this corpse.
I'm sorry, Marge. Where are my manners?
Did you want to taunt my kill, also?
Press the X button.
I'm doing it!
I'll get us some brewskis.
Cup, m'lady? Or would you
care to funnel it down thy throat?
Definitely a cup.
Foam wasn't spilt in a day.
Dude, your date is hot.
- Does she have a sister?
Two, actually. Twins.
Twins!
I was an astronaut for a little bit.
So many rules.
Your hair smells nice.
Listen. I got a place down the hall.
- Let's go.
So were you two in the same accident
or what?
We don't need a bed.
We're not gonna be sleeping.
Woo-hoo!
We're not the only ones
having a good time.
What in God's name was I thinking?
Maybe you could over again.
I'll cook you
my special microwave burritos.
I stop the oven...
...when the middle is
still a little bit frozen.
You know what a girl likes, mister.
So can I see you again?
How about you, me
and my wife have a two-way?
Hi.
Lisa, I re-graded your paper
from the other day...
...and you got an A.
- Really?
My kid's a huge Alaska Nebraska fan.
If she could somehow get
an autographed photo or t-shirt,
that would be A+ in my book.
Did you just wink at me?
Oh, look.
There are pumpkin stickers on the floor.
They must have fallen off
your homework for next week,
which you don't have to hand in.
I didn't think I'd get
a fresh start like this till junior high.
Even the Ralph of this school
speaks French.
I love tapas.
It's like appetizers for a meal
that never comes.
Try the flan de leche de cabra.
Be sure to dig around in the gunk.
Homie!
A key to your apartment.
And I've got a present for you.
But you'll have to wait
till we're back at the apartment.
Why can't I have it now?
You got your present here.
Basic fairness dictates... Oh!
Caitlin, hi.
Do a reading at your bat mitzvah?
Now my bat mitzvah means something.
By the way, I was wondering.
There's this Alaska Nebraska concert
this weekend,
and the tickets are all sold out.
Well, if it's sold out,
even Alaska Nebraska's best friend
couldn't do anything about that.
Can't build more seats.
Then get us backstage passes.
Surprise!
I redecorated!
Where are my video games, my X-Box?
My Wii?
You don't need a Wii now that I'm here,
because you and me make us.
You know, you're starting
to remind me a lot of my first wife.
We can talk about that
after brunch with my mother.
Miss Nebraska,
your purified water
and fried chicken skins are here.
I am so tired of fans in my food.
Alaska, we've never met,
but everyone thinks I'm your best friend.
Wait, wait. Let me guess.
I'm supposed to give all your best friends
front row seats and backstage passes.
Could you?
- First, riddle me this.
What's your favorite episode of my show?
You have a show?
Look, can you please, please help a poor
little girl who was just trying to fit in?
It's what half your songs are about.
You know what?
I was a little girl who
didn't fit in, either.
So you know what I did?
I got a new nose, I got famous,
and now I date the starting point guard
for the L.A. Clippers.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I have to go meditate and smoke.
Wait. I want to ask you something.
Could you tell I lip-synched
that whole speech?
You know what?
I was a little girl who
didn't fit in, either.
So you know what I did? I got a new nose.
I...
That's amazing.
I know. Security.
You know, I think
those shirts should say 'Insecurity.'
Because if you feel you have
to put what you are on your shirt,
then I feel sorry for you.
Do you feel sorry for me? Guess not.
Where have you been?
We have mirrors to hang!
I went to a movie.
- Without me? How'd you get there?
I drove.
- Without me?
Sometimes I think
this 50-square-foot apartment...
...isn't big enough for the both of us!
Fine! You can have your key back!
I got it halfway.
It went back.
City inspector.
I'm here to verify that this is
the residence of Bart and Lisa Simpson.
D'oh!
Hello, friendos.
Here comes Lisa
with our backstage passes.
Yay!
- Yay!
People, I'm not who you think I am.
I'm just a transfer student
who wanted to make some friends.
Yes, I lied to you.
But you only liked me because of a lie.
So if you think about it...
Get the liar!
Those are last year's shoes!
Kill her!
- Also, it's Lisa!
Kill her twice!
Go, Dog. Go with pages missing.
Lego spaceship, poorly assembled.
Clearly this is the home
of elementary school children. Too bad.
I was looking forward to killing you
and making it look like a suicide.
Thank you, friendo.
I am not your friendo.
- But I thought...
You said...
Mom! Dad! I have to leave Waverly Hills
and never come back!
I gotta get back, too!
I just remembered I was playing
hide and seek with Milhouse.
Three weeks?
This has gotta be some kind of record!
I can't leave my bachelor pad.
My bros will miss me.
- No, we won't.
Your comments
when we watch movies aren't funny.
Why do you watch comedies
if you don't want to hear more jokes?
Please. I just want to go back to a place
where I'm ostracized for being me,
not for who I pretend to be.
What do you think, Marge? Maybe we've
outgrown our first apartment.
Yeah. A house in the suburbs
does sound pretty nice right now,
although I am gonna
miss our little love nest.
Get a room!
HOMER: Come on, boy. Be cool.
- But...
Be cool or you're grounded.
Waverly Hills
That's where I want to be!
Gimme gimme Gimme gimme
Squatting in Waverly Hills
Waverly Hills
Get education fraudulently
Gimme gimme Gimme gimme
Mooching off Waverly Hills
English - US - SDH