The Simpsons
D'oh!
Sir, we're two minutes
from landing at the billionaire's retreat.
Ah! My favorite week of the year.
Sophisticated financial discussions
with my fellow plutocrats.
Food fight!
Take that, Ted Turner.
In your face, founder of Facebook!
Skinny dip!
Yee-haw!
MAN: Gangway!
'Men.' The room for me.
Nice prank, Simpson.
I dare you to dump that bees' nest
on those second-grade babies.
Why would I want to?
Because I said, 'I dare you.'
Kearney, can you read it back?
'Nice prank, Simpson. I dare you to...
'dump that bees' nest
on those second-grade babies.
'Bart: Why would I want to?
Jimbo: Because I said, 'I dare you.'
'Kearney, can you read it back?
'Kearney, reading: Nice prank, Simpson.
I dare you to...'
The point is, Simpson,
a dare has been placed on your nards!
My nards accept!
Stingamajigs!
Save yourselves!
Huh?
Where are the bees?
No bees?
- Dare annulled.
Can I appeal?
- Yeah. Appeal to other guys,
Captain Wuss!
Other than the birth of my kid,
this is my happiest moment.
All the bees are dead!
Aye, lass. The bees are dying,
and not just here. All over the world.
From Glasgow clear to Edinburgh.
And no one knows why.
I've lost a lot of wee friends of late.
Willie, I didn't know
you were an apiarist.
From context, I can tell
that means beekeeper.
'Tis a tragedy, Lisa.
No man should outlive his bees.
They're stinging God now.
And the call from the SEC...
...was coming from inside
their own brokerage house!
Jeff Bezos wet his pants!
I did not.
That was apple juice from before!
I fold.
- I raise a million dollars.
And to sweeten the pot,
my assistant, Smithers.
If you lose me, sir, may I say
what an honor it's been to...
Bets don't talk. They see and raise.
Well, if we're betting people,
I got a whole herd of them.
My professional basketball team,
the Austin Celtics.
Well, they're hardly worth a Smithers.
But we don't have all night.
Can you beat nine high?
Damn! Eight high!
So I own a basketball team, do I?
Take good care of them, Burnsie.
Don't let the forwards
mix with the guards.
And if they're acting sluggish,
slip some steroids into their cocaine.
Mmm-hmm.
Fortune Four Lotto numbers are nine...
Knew it.
- Seven...
Duh.
Three...
- What?
And...
- Boring.
Dad, we have to do something!
All the bees are dying!
Oh, no! No bees? Ooh!
Now who will sting me
and walk all over my sandwiches?
But, Dad, bees pollinate flowers.
Flowers.
The painted whores of the plant world.
No bees means no honey.
Synthetic honey, just like you remember.
Honey?
Thank you.
D'oh!
I never dreamed the future could be scary.
Let's go, Lisa.
We've got some worms to save.
- Bees.
Worms, bees, ticks,
fleas. Let's go, go, go!
I'm glad you called me.
I know I'm not the first scientist
in the phone book.
That's Associate Professor Aaron Ableman.
How I hate him.
Thundering thorax!
It's just exactly what I feared!
In there. Close. See these red dots?
This bee has been felled by bee measles.
Or as I call it, beesles.
Animals can get sick?
I'm going to talk to the girl from now on.
You're the nerd.
- What we need to do now...
...is find enough uninfected bees
to start a healthy colony.
This pheromone should attract them.
Marry me, and I'll support you for life.
You're not a bee! This thing is useless.
There's one on Lisa.
Hold still, sweetie. Daddy will kill it.
And this time, no screw-ups.
Stop! Stop! It's an uninfected queen!
How do we catch her without hurting her?
Unfortunately, the best method
is to allow her to sting you.
Yeah. Much like that.
Now squeeze around the stinger...
...to keep her attached,
and a colony of bees...
...will soon form around your face.
Now just keep them there
until the colony is healthy and thriving.
How long is that?
Long enough that you will be known
as Springfield's crazy bee girl.
She likes the stingers!
Marge, remember when we were
talking about our worst fears?
Mmm-hmm.
And mine was snakes, and yours was...
Never being a grandmother.
Really? I thought
it was Lisa with a beard of bees.
Well, whatever. Brace yourself.
President Lincoln, you've come back!
And you got rid of that hat!
You've got my vote!
Lisa, I don't like this at all.
It's not for long.
But until they find a suitable habitat,
this beard is the only
hope for these bees.
Relax, Mom. I'll mold them
into a shape you know and love.
Stop Milhousing your sister!
Now take it off before they sting you.
Actually, bees rarely sting
when they're in a cluster.
They only attack to defend their hive.
I don't know.
All it takes is one troubled Ioner.
Please let me keep them
for just a little longer.
Okay. One night.
So let's see how my burly-bottomed
ball handlers are faring.
Smithers, we're leading two to nothing.
Run out the clock,
boys. Run out the clock.
Oh, yeah! Three points!
Big three in the Big D for the Big C!
Mark Cuban, that's me!
Who is that man? And why isn't
his enthusiasm being punished?
That's Mark Cuban, sir.
He's the most flamboyant owner
in the league.
I'm out of my mind!
How odd. His money seems to have
bought him happiness.
I'd like to meet him, Smithers.
So you made your money in nuclear power?
I can't remember how I made my money!
If you're really a billionaire,
give me the secret billionaires handshake.
Smithers, turn away.
Hey!
So tell me, why don't you
recoil from the public...
...like a normal billionaire?
Hey, why own a basketball team
if you're not gonna have any fun?
'Fun'? Is that how it's pronounced?
I've only seen it written.
- Hold that thought.
No one's paid attention to me
for 10 whole seconds.
It's time for this peacock
to show his feathers.
You know, the feathers with the big eye...
...that trick them
into thinking that's my front?
Said feathers are what I'll flaunt!
Mom, maybe you shouldn't have put
so much syrup on the pancakes.
The secret is not to swallow the stingers.
Dad, don't eat the bees!
- They're just drones, Lisa.
They only live for like
five minutes anyway.
And they only have haploid cells,
not diploid, like me and Bart!
Yeah!
- Listen, Lisa,
I was trying to think of a way
to help your bees.
And I remembered this abandoned
greenhouse outside of town.
Which used to be a beautiful
thriving greenhouse...
...till I was hired to run it.
Your bees will have plenty of room
in this old greenhouse.
Plus, there are flowers.
And it's near a prison,
so they'll have a place to sting people.
Oh, Mom, it's perfect! Go live your lives!
Get off my face!
I miss them.
Now you know how I'll feel
when you go to college.
You'll always have Bart,
always.
But he'll be gone a lot,
repairing refrigerators.
Always.
ANNOUNCER ON PA: Ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome your new fun-Ioving owner.
You've seen him on the cover
of the December 1943 issue...
...of Collier's Magazine,
Montgomery Burns!
Silence! Now let's make some noise
for everyone's favorite basketball team,
whom I have renamed
the Springfield Excitement!
I knew it!
Now I would like to sing
our national anthem.
My country 'tis of thee
Austria, Hungary
Obey your king...
...Sir, the Archduke is dead.
What? The Archduke is dead?
And the empire is destroyed.
Then what happened?
- World War I.
Then what?
- World War II.
- A postwar period.
Then what?
- The Cold War.
Then what? Then what?
Then what?
- The European Union.
A European union? Good heavens.
MR. BURNS: Ladies,
hold on to your husbands.
It's time for the saucy antics
of Springfield's own
Basket-Belles!
Enough of this vulgarity!
Back to your brothel, harlots!
Now enjoy your game and
the madcap antics...
...of the freewheeling
title holder of this asset,
me!
Hip-Hop hooray! Ho!
Hey! Ho!
Hey! Ho! Hey! Ho!
You drew a picture of my morning
But you couldn't make my day...
Sir, were those real bullets?
- Yes. Was that a real gorilla?
No.
- I see.
Sir, your escapades,
while well intentioned,
seem to be driving away our fans.
We have to turn this business around.
Time to think outside the boxiola.
What would Mark Cuban do?
I'm out of my mind!
That's not much help.
Build a new arena, state-of-the-art!
New arena.
That's it, men!
Pave and tar the way God intended!
Mr. Burns, you can't do this!
I can, I shall, and in the future,
I will have done!
I cannot be stopped.
Kill his acorns and make him watch.
First, one announcement.
I regret to inform you...
...we are not offering childcare tonight.
I don't know who that guy was
you were leaving your kids with.
Now without further ado,
let's get ready to referendum!
There's only one place in town
where the bees can survive,
and Mr. Burns wants to tear it down.
Please, people. You didn't listen to me
about the snail darter.
You didn't listen to me about the osprey.
And you didn't listen to me
about the javelina!
The feisty pig of the desert?
Apparently not feisty enough.
Future generations will judge us
by how we cared for the tiniest creatures.
I am not just asking you to save the bees.
I am asking you to save your souls!
Excellent speech. Just excellent.
I no longer wish to build my
magnificent new basketball stadium.
You don't?
- Heavens no.
No skyboxes. No kiss cam.
Nor will we have the chance to marvel
at number-one draft pick
Muk Mu, the human North Pole.
No. I'm afraid he'll be on the
first kayak back to Ketchikan.
ALL: No!
- Please don't take our freak!
I love you, Muk Mu!
Muk Mu! Muk Mu!
- Muk Mu! Muk Mu!
All those in favor of building
this decadent monument to excess,
say aye.
- ALL: Aye!
Nay.
I know it's not your fault, Muk Mu.
You're a gentle, loving soul.
What's wrong with your bees, Lisa?
Mr. Burns took away their sanctuary.
And now they aren't strong enough
to survive on their own!
I'm going home.
Give me the keys to my bike lock.
Are you sure?
- Give me the keys!
Okay, okay. I don't know why I had them
in the first place.
I'd do anything to
cheer up my little girl.
Really? Listen, Homer. In the back room,
I got these super tough Africanized bees.
I saw this ad in a gentlemen's magazine
for excited African honeys,
and that's what they sent me.
If we could combine them with Lisa's bees,
it would make them strong enough
to survive any environment.
But how are we supposed to
combine the DNA of two strains...
...of the same species?
Actually, Homer...
You and me?
- No. The bees!
Oh, yeah, yeah. That's what I meant, too.
I have no inclination.
Got the queen?
Yup. And she's ready for a night of
anonymous sex with multiple partners.
Now let's give 'em some privacy
while they get down to 'buzziness.'
Come with me, my love
To the sea The sea of love...
...If they was me,
they'd be done by now.
Wow, this must be important, Dad.
I've never seen you walk up
an incline before.
Sweetie, I have a very special
surprise for you.
My bees?
Your bees died days ago!
These are their angry mutant descendants!
And they're tough enough to
live in any environment.
They sound awfully mad.
Are they dangerous?
Hmm. I'm not sure. Let me check.
Are you guys dangerous?
A simple 'yes' would've sufficed!
Don't worry, Lisa.
Where else are they gonna go?
To that new stadium
that looks exactly like a hive!
Welcome to the American dream.
A billionaire using public funds...
...to construct a private playground
for the rich and powerful.
And now, so our skybox owners
can really enjoy the game,
I shall let in the sky!
Stop! I am one of you!
We've been invaded by a swarm
of killer bees.
My microphone is no microphone at all.
It's bees!
Am I being badly stung? Yes. And it hurts.
Our bullets are useless!
Okay, they're useful on me.
Oh! They've found a home!
You've won this round.
But when next we meet,
the beekeeper will be the beekeepee.
Help me, Muk Mu!
So that's how I was outfoxed...
...by a little girl and
her halfwit companion...
...when my beautiful stadium
was declared a bee sanctuary,
and I had to take a third-quarter
write-down of 804 million dollars.
Wait a minute!
Someone crunch the numbers!
He's only worth $996,036,000!
He's not a billionaire at all!
Wait, wait, wait!
It's only a matter of four million.
I'm sure I can find that somewhere.
I have $50 here in my wallet.
Mark, can you get me off the hook
for old times' sake?
Can't do it, Monty.
Don't worry.
You'll feel a lot more comfortable...
...in the millionaire's camp.
No! No! Just kill me now!
Howdy do!
I own a minor league hockey team!