The Simpsons.
Aren't you glad we
got out of the house
and came downtown
for a little culture?
Heh. They're butchering
the classics.
Could that bassoon have
come in any more late?
Oh, come on, Homer.
There's lasers.
You like lasers.
Laser effects,
mirrored balls...
John Williams must be
rolling around in his grave.
Deviliciously satirical.
I wonder if anyone
else got that.
We're outta here.
Whoa. Careful, now.
These are dangerous streets
for us upper-lower-
middle-class types,
so avoid eye contact,
watch your pocketbook
and suspect everyone.
Three-card monte.
Whoo-hoo! Easy money!
Homer, these games
are fixed.
Then how come
that guy's winning?
Whoa... I, like,
totally won again.
Way to go, bro.
He looks and acts
just like the dealer.
I think they're related,
or at least in cahoots.
Just pick the red card.
It's totally not hard.
20 on this one, my good man.
Sorry, dude.
Black.
Homer, he cheated you!
Surely, you don't blame me.
It's people like you
who are ruining our downtown
promenades and piazzas.
How dare you prey on the greedy
and stupid like this.
Buh-bye.
Somebody stop him!
He's getting away!
Come on! Come on!
No! Marge!
Uh, I must warn you...
um... sometimes ordinary people
g-get, uh, uh,
a surge of adrenaline.
Yee...!
See?
Cuff him, boys.
We're putting
this dirtbag away.
Huh. I'll be back on the street
in 24 hours.
We'll try to make it 12.
Marge, are you okay?
I think I'm okay.
It was scary, but,
in a weird way,
it was also
kind of exhilarating.
Yes, it is exhilarating
to see the police
get their man
and save
a hysterical woman.
Oh, for crying out loud.
Easy now, sweetheart.
Homey's here.
Hey, Mom, is this
how you caught him?
Face it, Lis,
you're too puny to...
Lisa, unhand your brother.
Yeah, like that
really hurt.
Mom, was catching that guy
the most incredibly exciting
thing you've ever done?
Well, it was
pretty exciting.
But celery soup's
pretty exciting, too.
Mm... mm...
Strange. Regular ham
doesn't thrill me anymore.
Hmm. I'm crossing over
to deviled ham.
Whoo!
Marge!
Hey, Mrs. Simpson,
I just got
the new issue of
"Sponge and Vacuum."
Thanks, Benevenstanciano.
Death sports.
All right, get in there.
You're going down.
I want a piece
of him.
You think you're
pretty hot, huh?
Well, we got everything
we need on you.
Excuse me.
What? What? What? What?
This better be about pizza.
Actually, I'm interested
in becoming a police officer.
Welcome aboard.
You did what?!
I borrowed your
nail clipper.
What's the big deal?
Nothing. I'm just
a little edgy
since your mother told me
she wants to be a cop.
Cool. Will you bring me along
when you do evictions?
You got it, little buddy.
Marge, you being a cop
makes you the man!
Which makes me the woman!
And I have no
interest in that...
Besides occasionally
wearing the underwear
which, as we discussed,
is strictly a comfort thing.
Homer, there's no reason
for you to feel threatened.
You'll always be
the man of this house.
Aw, thanks, honey.
All right,
you scrawny beanpoles,
becoming a cop is not something
that happens overnight.
It takes one solid weekend
of training to get that badge.
Forget about the badge!
When do we get
the freakin' guns?!
Hey. I told you,
you don't get your gun
until you tell me
your name.
I've had it up to here
with your "rules"!
Heh. Women always have
trouble with the wall.
Can't ever seem
to find the door.
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
You missed the baby.
You missed
the blind man...
Oh, sorry, Simpson.
Now you'll have to do
the course again.
I was trying to get this
magic eye thing to work.
Ah, look at that! A pony!
Hey, everybody!
Mom's home.
They didn't have my size shirt,
but you get the idea.
Wow, Mom, I never
pictured you
as any kind of
authority figure before.
Marge, I want you
to take care
of yourself out there.
You've become
very dear to me.
Oh, Homey,
of course I will.
Mom, if someone shot at the mayor,
would you have to
throw yourself in front of him
and take the bullet?
I suppose I would.
What if they shot
a Coke machine?
No.
- A TV?
- No.
TV with a picture of
the mayor on it?
Whatever you do, Mom,
we'll be proud of you.
Well, thank you, honey.
As long as it's constitutional.
Homer, give me
my pepper spray.
Aw, Marge. One squirt and
you're south of the border.
Mmm... incapacitating.
All right, settle,
people. People, settle!
People! Wood and Van Zylen,
stake out Donutland.
When they fry up a fresh batch,
call it in.
Keneally and Earhart,
back 'em up.
Fitz and Garcia, it's your turn
to sleep in.
And, Simpson...
Seeing how this
is your first day, you're
inexperienced and vulnerable.
Your beat
is Junkyville and Bumtown.
Hello, Mr. Hutz.
I'll have you know
the contents of that
dumpster are private.
You stick your nose in,
you'll be violating
attorney-dumpster
confidentiality.
I just wanted to say hello.
Hello.
So, you are the new
cop on the beat.
Okay, I know the drill.
What will it be...
100? 200?
200.
No, no. I mean, nothing.
I don't take bribes.
Yes, of course you don't.
I will just leave
this money on the table
with my unseeing back to
the money, on the table.
Apu, no.
That's better.
This is why
I can't bear
to be in this house!
I got a report on a domestic
disturbance at this address.
Yes, indeed there is.
There's an inflatable
bath pillow
that mother and I
both enjoy.
She claimed it was
her day to use it.
I maintained she was mistaken.
We quarreled.
Later, as I
prepared to bathe,
I noticed to my horror
that someone had
slashed the pillow.
Mm-hmm. Who called
the police?
We both did.
Look, why don't you two
settle down.
I'm sure you can get
another pillow.
Well, I could send it back
to Taiwan for repair.
But why should I have to?
I've done nothing wrong,
and I don't give permission
for my face to be on TV.
I want it blurred.
So Mom,
what are you gonna do
with your day off?
I just want to
relax and forget
that I'm part
of that thin blue line
which stands between
civilization and chaos.
Bart, it's illegal
for you to operate
that class nine vehicle
without pads and a helmet.
- But, Mom...
- It's for your own safety.
Take that,
safety boy.
This padding's
so easy on the knuckles,
I could punch all day.
I just hope they have
Us magazine in heaven.
He said it was his day
to use the tub pillow.
I can't go to the library
anymore, everybody stinks.
Don't stop talking
on account of me.
I may be a cop,
but I'm still your friend.
So, how are you,
Mrs. Krabappel?
Law-abiding.
I'm done.
Moe! I've never seen
you here before.
Well, these days my roots
don't stay
so chestnut on their own,
Officer Simpson.
You don't have
to call me officer.
I'm not on duty here.
Finished.
It looks nice.
It's a good length for you.
Mom's police tape
isn't a toy, Dad.
Shush, dear.
You'll wreck Daddy's fun.
Bringing in the sheaves.
Bringing in...
Oh, my Lord!
Something horrible
has happened!
Fooled you, Flanders!
Made you think
your family was dead.
Did you get it?
- They're not, though.
- No?
- But you thought they were.
- Yeah.
That's why
it was so funny.
- But they're not.
- That's a good one.
And that's the drunk tank,
and this is Mommy's desk.
Mom, I know
your intentions are good,
but aren't the police
a protective force that
maintains the status quo
for the wealthy elites?
Don't you think we ought to
attack the roots
of social problems
instead of jamming people
into overcrowded prisons?
Look, Lisa... it's
McGriff the crime dog.
Hello, Lisa.
Help me bite crime.
Ruff, ruff.
Hey, great news, guys.
I picked up a nudie deck
for our game.
"The Girls of the Internet."
Ooh, I'd go on line
with them any day.
Hey, hey, we've
offended Herman.
No. I'm just going out
for some fresh air.
Geez, that guy sure
likes his fresh air.
None of that for me.
Oh, yeah... yeah.
Hey, Homer,
you sure it's okay
to smoke Cuban cigars
and gamble here
now that your wife's a cop?
Are you kidding?
Being a cop husband
is one mighty sweet deal.
This police radio entertains me
with other people's miseries.
We get a free funeral
for Marge... God forbid...
And I can run background checks
on whomever I want... Mohammar.
Homer, please, please.
Ix-nay on the Ohammar-may.
Hey, hurry up
with the cards, Lenny.
I've got you clocked
at two miles per hour.
Come on, put that away.
Those radar guns
give you cancer.
All the more reason
to hurry up.
Hey, what could be going
a hundred miles per... Oh!
Illegal gambling in my house?
Your house? Your house?
It's so glamorously decorated,
I thought I was in Vegas.
You guys lied to me.
You said it was Vegas.
We'll be going.
We don't want no
trouble here, officer.
Marge, you chased away
all my poker buddies.
I didn't mean to.
You've become such a cop.
Not that long ago, you were
so much more to me.
You were a cleaner of pots,
a sewer of buttons,
an unplugger of hairy clogs.
I'm still all those things.
Only now
I'm cleaning up the city,
sewing together
the social fabric,
and unplugging the clogs
of our legal system.
You're cooking what
for dinner?
Everywhere I look,
someone is breaking the law.
Dog, no leash.
Man, littering.
Horse not wearing diaper.
Car parked across
three handicapped spaces.
- Homer!
- Hey, Marge.
How's my little piglet?
Homer, I'm on duty.
That's okay. I'm supposed
to be working too.
You have to
move your car.
I'll just be
a second, Marge.
I'm going to get some beer
for those kids over there.
I'm gonna pretend that
I didn't hear that,
but you have to
move your car now.
I'll be right back.
Now keep your eyes peeled
for a real cop.
That's it. I'm gonna
write you a ticket.
- Come on, we're family!
- You're breaking the law.
I'll make you a deal...
You rip up that ticket,
and I'll give you back
your hat.
- Hey!
- Whoo! Whoo!
Homer!
Taking an officer's cap
is an arrestable offense.
Ooh, what are you gonna do about it?
What are you gonna do?
Ooh, I'm officer Marge.
I'm going to arrest you.
Ooh... What?
Oh, Marge, not here.
Hey, you're not
really arresting me?
You have the right
to remain silent.
I choose to waive that right.
All right, Simpson,
you're free to go.
Let me just finish
this last lobster tail
and raspberry torte.
All right, Hans,
time to go.
But he ate
my last meal.
Well, if that's the worst thing
that happens to you today,
consider yourself lucky.
Are you really allowed
to execute people
in a local jail?
From this point on,
no talking.
I'm sorry I had
to arrest you, Homer,
but what I did was right.
Someday when you really
need it, you'll be happy
there are dedicated cops
like me out there.
I have nothing more
to say to you, Marge.
I'm drawing a line
down the center of the house,
a la "I Love Lucy."
You stay on your side,
and I'll stay on my side.
Boy, when Marge
first told me
she was going to
the Police Academy,
I thought it would be
fun and exciting, you know,
like that movie...
"Spaceballs."
But, instead, it's been
painful and disturbing
like that movie
"Police Academy."
Homer, I'm worried
about the beer supply.
After this case
and the other case,
there's only one case left.
Yeah, yeah. Barney's right.
Yeah.
Let's get some more beer.
Yeah. What about some beer?
Yeah, Barney's right.
All right, guys, pipe down.
I got some more in the garage.
I'll get it
for you, Homer.
Hmm. I wonder why he's so eager
to go to the garage.
The garage?
Hey, fellas, the garage.
Ooh, la-di-da,
Mr. French man.
What do you call it?
A car hole.
You're late, Herman.
Surely, you don't mind
waiting for merchandise
of this quality, Mr. Jericho.
Huh. Looks like
good stuff.
But, of course, I'll
have to sample it first.
- These are fabulous.
- Yeah.
Who would suspect that
they're counterfeit jeans?
And what better place
to make the buy
than in a cop's garage
where no one would
suspect a thing.
Herman, I had to come out here
to see what's so funny.
A counterfeit jeans ring
operating out of my car hole!
I'm gonna tell everyone.
Wait here.
Not so fast.
Okay.
Maybe you should
just stop entirely.
Herman, how could you?
We've all thought about
counterfeiting jeans
at one time or another,
but what about the victims?
Hardworking designers
like Calvin Klein,
Gloria Vanderbilt,
or Antoine Bugle Boy.
These are the people who saw
an overcrowded marketplace
and said, "me too."
Advance on him, men.
I don't think that's
a very good idea.
Oh, no.
It's Gloria Vanderbilt,
out for revenge.
No. It's Officer Simpson,
of the police.
Herman, your beef
is with me.
Leave the girl out of this!
Okay.
Homer!
It's too late for me, Marge.
Sell the jeans
and live like a queen!
Is Bart home?
Just taking Maggie
for a stroll.
Well, I guess I am putting up
the Halloweenie decorations
a little early.
Criticism accepted.
Marge!
Bust him, Mom!
Go back to bed.
Don't make me
come up there.
Looks like your wife
is embarking
up the wrong tree.
Freeze!
Every mother knows
the secret entrance
to her son's tree house.
Oh, Marge, you saved my life.
I'm sorry
I teased you.
You're a really
good cop.
I'm proud of you.
So long. Got to catch the 501.
He's getting away!
You blew it, Marge!
I don't think so.
Oh, foiled by my own
shoddy merchandise!
That's my ambulance.
I called for it four hours ago.
- Marge, how did you know...
- That the pants would rip?
- No. What I was wondering...
- Years of buying pants
for two active children
and a full-seated husband
has given me a sixth sense
for shoddy stitching,
which these jeans
have in spades.
That's some
nice work, Simpson,
but we can't hold him...
There's no evidence.
Yes, there is. There's a garage
full of counterfeit jeans.
Uh, they've, uh,
mysteriously disappeared.
- Looking good, boys.
- That's it.
There's too much corruption
on this force.
I quit.
Sorry to lose you,
Simpson.
I don't think
they're coming back.
Well, that does it.
That does it.
I'm looking at his cards.
Ah, crap. I fold.
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.