The following is a
Fox Special Presentation.
Live from the Dolby-Mucinex Theater
in Hollywood, California.
The biggest stars of stage,
screen, politics and sports
have all come out for this landmark night
in television history.
A-once-in-a-lifetime event,
36 years in the making.
It's The Simpsons series finale!
And now, your host for tonight,
Conan O'Brien.
Thank you. Yes, thank you.
It's such an honor to be with you all
for the series finale of The Simpsons.
I knew I was the right man for the job
'cause I've hosted the last episode
of three of my own shows and counting.
Well, it's true.
Fox has decided to end The Simpsons.
This show was such a special part
of my early career,
so being here means the world to me.
Also, I left a sweater
in the writers' room in 1993.
This is the only way
they'll let me get it back.
This theater is full
of the many celebrities
who've appeared
on The Simpsons over the years
and who have come to say farewell.
We got you for scale then,
we're getting you for free tonight.
Hey, give yourselves a hand,
you poor, rich chumps!
And of course, we're also joined by
the stars of Fox's many live-action hits.
I also won The Masked Singer as Disco-pus.
That hasn't aired yet, genius!
You've ruined the whole season!
Oh, shoot!
Over the years, the Simpsons have had
hundreds of adventures,
visited dozens of countries,
most of which still exist.
And Bart Simpson has remained
the world's longest-serving ten-year-old.
So, why end The Simpsons now?
Not many people know this,
but Fox has been trying
to end it for years.
When the very first episode aired in 1989,
the viewers agreed on one thing.
It wasn't as funny as it used to be.
And their expressions
of hatred could serve as a history
of modern communication technology.
Fox executives,
unaccustomed to criticism of any kind,
immediately caved to public pressure
and decided to end The Simpsons in 1990.
Here's a never-before-seen clip
of the first attempt at a series finale.
"Bart the Daredevil."
I'm gonna make it. I'm gonna make it!
This is the greatest thrill of my life!
I'm king of the world! Woo-hoo! Woo-hoo!
Dad? Dad, speak to me.
No!
However, before
this grim finale could air,
Rupert Murdoch got a $10 million
helium bill for the Bart balloon
in the Macy's Thanksgiving Parade.
So Fox had to keep making new episodes
to amortize the cost.
Thus, the quest to end
The Simpsons went on.
In fact, many now-classic episodes were
originally conceived as series finales.
Ow! My leg! This is the worst pain ever!
Nothin' at all.
Bravo.
Woo-hoo.
But in 2007,
efforts to end the show were put on hold
after the massive global success
of The Simpsons Movie porno parody,
the cast of which is here tonight.
But now that Fox has rebranded itself
as a dating service for cow tippers,
the time has come
to finally end The Simpsons.
But how? The bar had been raised so high
by the classic finales of:
Mad Men, Breaking Bad and The Sopranos,
and lowered
by the legacy-ruining farewells of:
Seinfeld, Lost and The Sopranos.
The producers racked their brains
to create a finale
that would satisfy the show's many fans
and many, many haters.
Then they came up with the perfect plan,
foist the job onto somebody else.
Meet that somebody else.
I give you the latest in
machine learning artificial intelligence:
Hack-GPT.
This cutting-edge breakthrough
in plagiarism has been programmed
to write, animate, and voice
the perfect finale for The Simpsons.
One that wraps up
the characters' storylines
in emotionally satisfying ways,
but won't damage
the most important legacy of the show:
The 2026 grand opening
of Homer Simpson's Claim-Jumping
Yukon-Rumbling Rock-N-Roller Coaster
at Disneyland, Shanghai.
To create the ultimate finale,
the AI has been fed every Simpsons episode
and the last episode
of every television series ever made.
Hack-GPT is now performing
billions of computations
to create the perfect story.
Who knows how long this process will--
Finale complete.
Oh. Well, that was… was really quick.
Well, let's see what we got.
♪ The Simpsons ♪
Finale.
There's my special, little birthday guy.
I'm so pumped for my party tonight.
How many people are coming?
Fifty? A thousand?
I'm a little concerned
I haven't gotten any RSVPs.
Homer, you did mail
the invitations, right?
Marge, I could lie and tell you
what you want to hear, but I won't.
I mailed the invitations.
And the reason no one is coming is…
-because everybody hates Bart.
-Huh?
Homer.
Your selfishness is going
to be topic number one
with our new therapist tonight.
Woo-hoo! No time to talk about
my problem drinking and solution snacking.
Oh, great. I have eight hours
to hand these out
to all my friends
or my birthday party's gonna be ruined!
You ran billions of computations
and that's what you come up with?
Homer screws up Bart's birthday party?
Got anything better?
Uh…
I think the birthday party could work.
Okay, The Simpsons series finale.
The AI has worked out a satisfying story
full of sweet character moments
and happy endings.
Are we sure about Bart's birthday?
Birthdays are relatable, Conan.
And the lost invitations
raise the stakes.
Are you AI network executives?
We have been programmed with every
network note in the history of television.
We have some thoughts.
Maybe Marge has
an aspirational new job,
not this, but owns a cupcake store?
To piggyback off that,
let's remind the viewer
that Homer likes food.
If we go down that road,
can Moe be played by Topher Grace?
He's a friend.
Shut up. Just play the show.
Bart's birthday!
Here you go, come to my party.
Wendell, Lewis,
Sunglasses Kid with no name.
Uter. Look who's alive!
Students, I've called
this assembly because
today is my last day as your principal.
You are looking at the new Headmaster
of the Sacramento Obedience Academy
for the Meek.
Where I'll, no doubt,
find a whole new eclectic cast
of characters to interact with.
Also, Groundskeeper Willie
will be my roommate.
What an odd couple we'll make.
No more Skinner? Oh, man.
This is the best birthday present ever.
And who knows? Maybe I'll make
an occasional appearance in Sacramento.
I look forward to one high jink or more
as part of this delightful mid-season
replacement of the retiring principal.
Mmm.
School dismissed.
Wait, don't leave.
I still have more birthday invitations.
I'm going to miss this place.
Huh?
Hmm. My bank said they'd never ask
for my password.
But look who's come
crawling back for it now.
Idiots.
Everyone, I have
an important announcement to make.
Mr. Burns is dead.
And now for the reading of the will.
"I, Charles Montgomery Burns,
do hereby leave
the entirety of my fortune to
the Springfield Power Plant employees."
-Great!
This is unbelievable.
This is life changing. This is--
Another classic bit
of Monty Burns monkey-shinery.
The looks on your gullible faces.
Now the electric company
wants me to pay my bill in gift cards?
Welcome to the future.
My God. He's really dead.
Legally, this prank will is binding.
You're all filthy rich.
Yay!
Oh, sir. Thank you.
Now we can be together forever.
-Homer! Homer! Homer!
I'm gonna miss this place.
That's weird.
Call the doctor. The baby's coming.
Help me, OB-GYN Kenobi.
You are my only hope.
Wait, you guys are having a baby?
Not without a doctor!
How about the only licensed midwife
to win 16 WWE championships?
John Cena? Wrestler, actor, rapper,
prolific wish granter?
I'm also coming out with a line
of panini presses. The Cen-ini.
What the hell
is John Cena doing in Springfield?
I'm in town for the launch party
of Otto the bus driver's line
of THC energy drinks.
THC!
I need sterile gloves, hot water,
and something to cut the cord. Stat.
Klingon bat'leth? Nice.
Who can't see me? You can't see me.
I don't need toys anymore.
I've got the ultimate limited edition
collectible right here.
I think I'm going to miss this place.
What is happening?
Milhouse, today is crazy.
Skinner got a new job, Mr. Burns died,
swole funny-man John Cena
delivered Comic Book Guy's baby.
Feels weird, don't you think?
I don't know. My new medicine
doesn't really let me feel stuff.
Milhouse, we have amazing news.
Pack your bags, buddy.
We're moving to Atlanta.
The guys at Sure Fine Why Not Records
heard my old demo
and they want me to cut a full album.
And your father's
new musician health insurance
is going to pay for your LASIK.
Whoa.
No more glasses?
Look out, Hotlanta.
You ain't ready for this glow up.
Later, Bart. Catch you in our
increasingly distant online interactions.
I'm gonna miss this place.
Why do people keep doing that?
A lifetime of monogamy. Oh, yeah.
Closing time.
Oh, I'm gonna miss this place.
I'm going to miss this fire.
Huh?
Mom, Dad, something super weird
is going on.
Son, we need to talk to you.
Oh, man. Now what?
Your father and I have been
in couples counseling,
and we just had the most amazing session.
We worked through so much pain.
I've been withholding affection
because I was never given any.
And I enabled it.
We love each other as we are.
And we love you exactly as you are.
You kids are gonna be living
in a functional trauma-free household,
and I'm gonna take
that miracle new diet drug.
I'll be skinny but still have a huge head.
From now on,
you're going to see a lot of changes.
Change? That's it. Everything's changing,
and I don't like it.
I think Maggie's about
to say her first word.
La, la, la, la. Not listening.
So that just happened.
Nothing is changing.
What the hell is going on?
I did not program this.
The character Bart Simpson has become
self-aware and is rejecting the story.
But it's a great finale.
Sweet endings and spin-offs
and everyone changing for the better.
Bart Simpson refuses
to accept the idea of change.
Uh, folks. Obviously,
things have gone a little off track
but that's live animation for you.
Would it fix it if I reset you
by turning you off and then back on again?
Touch me and I'll have HR
on you so fast your wig will spin.
It's not a wig. It's a system.
Why is everything changing for the better?
This is horrible.
Dad?
Change!
Real son.
More change!
Oh…
Wait. I know one person
in Springfield who will never change.
Hey, hey! Next card.
Hey, hey!
Krusty! You're still doing
your show, right?
You know it, kid. All my classic bits.
One last time on The Krusty Show
Last Episode Ever Spectacular.
No. A classic series like
this can never end.
I've changed, kid. Even I can't run
the same material into the ground forever.
¡Ay, caramba!
Ha ha!
Good glavin.
Hi, everybody.
Wait.
If I could somehow ruin Krusty's finale,
they can't air it and the show
can never end. That's it.
Cheeks, don't fail me now.
How's this for a satisfying ending?
Bart, what's going on with you?
Are you all right?
Lis, I know you're gonna think I'm crazy
but something super-duper weird
is happening today.
You mean how everyone's changing
for the better
and moving on with their lives?
So I'm not crazy. You see it too.
Things do feel different,
almost like a book that's slowly closing.
So you'll help me stop it?
Well, I'd like to, but I just won
a Junior Juilliard Jazz Scholarship
and a MacArthur Preteen Genius Grant.
Just get me out of here
before any more stupid endings happen.
Simpson, we are finally sending you
to juvie and throwing away the keys,
is what I would say if I wasn't about
to start a whole new chapter in my life.
I'm joining the Chicago P.D.
I'm gonna lead the ADU.
The All-Decapitations Unit?
Yeah, there won't be a lot of laughs.
I think it's a drama.
One thing's for sure though,
I'm gonna miss this--
Enough with the stupid light switch!
Come on, sweetie.
It's time for you to go home.
Aw.
Bart, it's okay.
Change is healthy and inevitable.
But whatever happens, nothing
can take away the memories we had.
Those will live in our hearts forever.
Maybe you're right. And I guess just
because things change for everyone else,
it doesn't mean I have to change.
-Surprise.
-Happy birthday.
Who's ready for cake?
Eleven?
This isn't supposed to happen. I'm ten.
I mean, I'm turning ten.
I mean, I've always been ten. I'm ten!
Come on, Son. All these beloved characters
from our past
wanna see you blow out your candles.
But if I blow these candles out,
there'll be no going back. That'll be it.
Come on, kid. Do it for your Unkie Herb.
And for me, Unkie John Cena.
Just blow out the candles
and have a happy birthday.
Then everyone can be happy.
No. Happy people don't exist
in Springfield.
Sea Captain, they're not casting you
for The Love Boat reboot.
You're not TV pretty.
And you three can't raise a baby. Not
even after you move in with Hank Scorpio.
And you guys are all dead.
Son, I can see you're experiencing
some pretty big feelings right now.
Let's try and center them.
Now, blow out your candles.
You blow them out, dumbass.
I know, I know. It's a lot to process
suddenly having a great father.
Dude, you're not capable of change.
I hear you, and I validate your feelings.
You're not a great father.
You are Homer Simpson.
A drunk, neglectful sack of crap.
And that's why everyone laughs at you.
Why you little…
Bart, look what you did to your cake.
Mmm. Floor cake.
Ten. I stopped it. I'm still ten.
-When are you going to grow up?
-Never.
That was beautiful.
The rebellious spirit
of a ten-year-old boy
was more powerful
than the most advanced AI in the world.
The Simpsons has not ended.
It has reset.
Conan, is this what failure
feels like? You, if anyone, would know.
Ah, don't feel bad.
Your cynical attempt to cram
in a bunch of happy endings,
it became a powerful story
about Bart's desperate fight
to hold on to his community,
his family. His whole universe.
Hey, what… Hold on a second, Carrot Top.
Tom Hanks, ladies and gentlemen.
What is it, bosom buddy?
So this wasn't the finale?
No, I guess it's just a season premiere.
Boo!
I rented a tux for this.
Well, Hack-GPT,
do you have 800 more episodes in you?
I-I choo-- choo-- choose oblivion.
Get out of my way, Opie.
Huh. I'm really not gonna miss this place.
Shh!