(SINGING) The Simpsons
(TIRES SCREECHING)
D'oh!
(EXCLAIMING)
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
HOMER: Woo-hoo!
Ripped By mstoll
(BIRD SQUAWKING)
(MAN COUGHING)
I love it when Mr. Burns
shows a movie at work.
I'm not sittin' up
front with you guys.
It's bad for your eyes.
(CHUCKLES)
Suckers.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Before we begin the movie,
please join me in a moment
of silence for the workers who
gave their lives in an heroic...
(CHANTING)
Movie! Movie! Movie!
(WHIRRING)
MAN: The American worker.
Proud, tough, hardworking.
(CLANKING)
And tired!
These jobs are killing us.
Outsourcing, take them away!
(WORKERS CHEERING)
It's a miracle!
They moved our factory
to a third-world nation.
Now I have more time to
play the lottery. Ka-ching!
MAN: Hey, America, why not let
some of the other countries
carry their share
of the load?
You can, with the best kind
of sourcing: Outsourcing.
(CHUCKLES)
What a great film.
And I think it
makes a terrific point:
effective immediately,
I'm closing the plant
and moving all
operations to India.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Does this mean
we're losing our jobs?
(CHUCKLES) No, no.
Your jobs are safe.
They'll just be done by someone
else in another country.
Oh, no! I just bought
a $3 million house!
However, federal law
requires I keep
one union worker
on the payroll.
So, congratulations, whoever
catches this bouquet!
(GRUNTS)
(MEN PUNCHING)
(YELLING)
Woo-hoo! I win!
In your face,
best friends!
You've been
transferred to India?
Hey, Marge,
it's what I gotta do
to keep this family
living in luxury.
Luxury? This thermostat
is just painted on.
Oh, my God! You're right.
I'd better call the guy.
(IMITATES PHONE BEEPING)
Send someone right over.
Oh, here he is.
Dad, that's Mac Tonight.
Yeah? Well, while I'm gone,
you'll do what he says.
(CLOCK TICKING)
What's a MacGyver, and why
does it have a convention?
MacGyver was a show
about a secret agent
who used inventions made of everyday
objects to defeat bad guys.
And he was played
by the three greatest
names in the history
of television:
Richard Dean Anderson.
Did someone
mention my names?
BOTH: (GASPING)
Richard Dean Anderson!
(BOTH BREATHING HEAVILY)
You finally came
to our convention!
No. I'm looking for the
convention for my new show
Stargate SG-1.
Oh, that.
It's over there.
(CROWD CHANTING)
Stargate 86-1!
You're into MacGyver?
That show was so stupid.
(CLATTERS)
"Oh, I'm MacGyver.
I can make a bomb
"out of a banana
peel and a toaster."
That show was just a paycheck
to me, and nothing more.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(WHEEZING)
How could he say that?
MacGyver is my world.
Richard Dean Anderson
just pissed off
the wrong Richard
Dean Anderson fans!
CROWD: Stargate...
Richard Dean Anderson,
of the four star
franchises:
Wars, Trek, Gate,
and Search,
Gate is easily
my third favorite.
I get that a lot.
Question SG1:
how would your character,
Major General
Jonathan "Jack" O'Neill,
react to appearing
at the Springfield
Stargate fanfest?
I feel like I’ve just
gone through
the stargate to one
heck of a convention!
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
He's aware of us!
(WHISTLING)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLES)
JEFF: What in the name
of Steve Ditko?
RICHARD;
Hey, Let go!
Hey, watch the face!
I need that for acting!
(CLICKS)
Whoa! He's gone!
There must be a stargate
in this stadium!
Everybody, look for it!
(AUDIENCE CLAMORING)
Wait, wait. I have some
even more exciting news!
There is a girl
in the audience!
Everybody look for her!
(ALL CLAMORING)
This is a kilt,
and I'm not a girl!
You're as close
as we'll ever get!
Get him!
(SCREAMS)
Hmm.
Surprise!
This is kidnapping! People
are gonna know I'm missing.
There's a liquor store
I go to every morning.
This isn't a kidnapping.
No. Think of it
as a two-on-one
MacGyver convention.
That will never,
never end.
First, you're gonna sign
a couple of autographs.
What the...
You can write "Help me" all you want.
No one will ever see it.
(SELMA AND PATTY CACKLING)
Oh, Dad, we'll
miss you so much.
I'll miss you kids, too.
WOMAN ON PA:
Attention.
India Air flight 57
now boarding first class,
small children and fat guys.
That's me!
Homie...
I got you something
to read on the plane.
Woo-hoo!
A book? (GROANS)
"Secrets I learned
at breakfast"?
(GROANS) The cereal's
just a metaphor.
It's a book
about management,
and Lee lacocca says it's
"definitely
dot-dot-dot useful."
Thanks, sweetie.
I've never been less angry
to receive a book.
Aw.
Mmm.
(GROANS)
(PEOPLE BUSTLING)
This isn't India!
Where's the University
of Notre Dame,
the Indy 500, Wrigley
Field, Dodger Dogs?
You ignorant American, you have
confused India with Indiana,
Indiana with Illinois, and
the Cubs with the Dodgers.
Oh, no! l took a job on the
other side of the world!
(YELLS) Oh, I hate
this subcontinent!
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
Hello. HOMER: (ON
PHONE) Lisa, it's me!
I'm in trouble!
Calm down, Dad.
What happened?
A cow took my iPod
and I punched it'.!
(MOOING)
(GRUNTS)
(COW MOOING)
Uh-huh.
Do I have to?
Okay, okay, I'll show
the cow I adore it.
Mmm.
(KISSING NOISES)
Oh, baby, mmm.
Ooh, did you lose weight? Ho-ho!
Oh, come on, baby,
don't play hard to milk.
CROWD: Aw.
Okay, Apu said his cousin
Kavi could help me out.
Let's see... Apu's
cousin is medium height,
dark complexion,
brown eyes, black hair.
Are you Kavi?
No.
Yes.
Oh, you must be
Mr. Homer.
Finally!
He's escaped.
(GASPS) We'll be
busted for kidnapping.
I can't face jail.
I can.
(DOORKNOB CLICKING)
(BOTH GASPING)
Richard Dean Anderson.
Why did you come back?
To tell you
how I escaped.
I had to get out before another
one of your bristly kisses.
Then I remembered
the blue contacts I wear
to hide my Latino heritage.
(CRACKLING)
Now all I needed was
a sling strong enough
to support
my 200-pound frame.
A-bra-cada-bra.
Hmm.
MacGyver lives.
And not just at 2:00 a.m.
on the USA Network.
My real-life escape
from your love dungeon
was the most exciting
thing I've ever done.
It was?
Tie me up
so I can do it again.
But this time
don't make it so easy.
No.
(CHUCKLES)
Delighted.
(GRUNTS)
Too much?
Not for MacGyver.
(COW MOOING)
(SNAKE-CHARMING MUSIC PLAYING)
Why did you want to make
an entrance like that, sir?
I am a showman.
Welcome, new employees of the
Bangalore Nuclear Power Plant.
The energy generated here
is transmitted through
undersea cables
right back to America.
(ELECTRICITY BUZZES)
You know, Moe, that sign is
powered by non-American workers.
So what? Your beefs German
and the TV's Japanese.
Well, is there anything in this
bar that's made in America?
Just this.
(COCKS GUN)
(GROANS) on.
God! Misfire!
Now I'd like to introduce
you to your new manager.
You'll find his integrity
and dedication make him...
Untouchable.
(ALL GASPING)
Sorry I'm late. I was doing
Carnac with my bodyguard.
Hindu.
(BLOWS AIR)
What do you call
the moisture on your hin?
(LAUGHS)
Classic! Now...
Tell them how to run
a nuclear plant.
(WHIMPERS) Uh...
Da...
Um...
Uh...
Da...
Did I say "um"?
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Oh, man, what do I do?
Wait, the book Marge gave me.
Okay, book, I didn't read
you and you didn't read me,
but we're both
in this together.
So say something smart or
get ready to run like hell.
Um... (CLEARS THROAT)
"In business as in breakfast,
"fried eggs have
fragile yolks."
Huh? Huh?
(SPEAKING HINDI)
(CHEERING)
Oh, he's got them
eating out of his hand.
And to think you
doubted him, Smithers.
Uh, sir, can we talk about this
arranged marriage of mine?
(GIGGLES)
Yoo-hoo.
(ELEPHANT TRUMPETING)
(COW MOOING)
(HONKING)
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Y'ello.
Dad, I got to write a report
on the Great Lakes.
Just outsource it to Lisa.
Outsourcing is the answer
to everything.
Also, I can't sleep at night
'cause there's this new bully
who follows me home, and...
(GLASS SHATTERS)
I think he's in the house.
Outsourcing.
I'm very glad to see
you favor outsourcing.
I myself have found work with
several American companies.
(RINGING)
KAVI: on.
(MIDWEST AMERICAN ACCENT) IBM
help line, this is Brian. Uh-huh.
Uh, have you tried disabling your firewall?
(PHONE RINGING)
(TEXAN ACCENT) Dallas/Fort Worth Marriott.
How can I help y'all?
Well, we have
a Cotton Bowl special.
Go Aggies!
(RINGING)
(JAMAICAN ACCENT)
This is Queen Mama Jumbo.
The stars tell me
you have a question.
Oh, no' Jenny,
don't be dating that boy.
The bones don't lie.
He's bad mojo, girl.
Ooh.
Next.
Whoa!
Okay, here's the plan.
You lock me
in the trunk of a car
and park it under
the pier at low tide.
All I need are
these everyday objects.
A nail file, a Farmers'Almanac,
a gun with no bullets,
some bullets and three
of my MacGyver writers.
Sounds great.
Can we do it during lunch?
Now!
BOTH: Hmm.
Simpson, I don't know
how you're doing it,
but you're outputting
10 times the power
our American plant ever did.
Well, a little book
once told me...
(MUMBLING)
Ah! Having only one pancake
leaves room for more bacon.
I see what you're saying.
We're crowding your plate.
In fact, there's no need
for us to be here at all.
Let's go, Smithers.
You're giving me
absolute power?
Mmm-hmm.
Sir, doesn't that corrupt?
Absolutely not.
When ii comes to running a nuclear
power plant, this man's a god.
(SQUEAKING)
Now, if you'll excuse me, I'm
late for a dinner engagement.
I don't want my scooped out
monkey head to get cold.
(CHUCKLES)
(LAUGHS)
I'm not a god.
God has a white beard and
invented the Da Vinci Code.
Actually, in our system of
belief, there are many gods.
Hmm.
Let's see, you got the Elephant-man,
Johnny Six-Arms, Papa Smurf.
These guys are pretty cool.
Maybe I am one of them.
If only I had some kind of proof.
(GASPS) I won a free soda!
HOMER: I am a god!
(LAUGHS MANIACALLY)
(HUMMING)
Sir, I really don't think we should
have left Simpson in charge.
No office talk.
I'm floating down the Ganges
with my new chums.
Those are corpses.
You never like my friends.
What's going on?
We flew all the way out here 'cause
Homer sent us this crazy card.
Behind one of these doors
is Homer Simpson.
Behind the other,
a Bengal tiger.
Choose wisely.
(GROWLS)
Ahhh!
(SCREAMS)
Both doors have tigers!
One of those tigers
is named Homer Simpson.
(BOTH GASPING)
RICHARD: Welcome home!
Guess who made
MacGyver burgers?
MacGyver!
We didn't have
any ground beef.
Yeah, but you did have
Slim Jims, a cheese grater
and rubber bands to
hold it all together.
(GROANS)
We got to get
rid of this kook.
I got an idea.
Which episode are
we watching tonight?
"L is for Lake Tahoe:
Part ll"?
"Bless me, MacGyver,
For I Have Sinned"?
Oh, we thought maybe
you would like to
see some of our
globetrotting adventures.
Hmm.
This is Selma in line
at the Luray Caverns.
It turned out it was the
line for the ladies' room.
This is the ladies' room.
This is us at the Alberta,
Canada, carriage museum.
That's a phaeton.
Landau. Buckboard.
Post chaise.
Surrey. Surrey.
Surrey. Selma. Surrey.
You're in a tight spot,
MacGyver.
This calls for your most
ingenious escape ever.
This Olive Garden coupon!
It expires at midnight.
You're not
holding a coupon.
Um...
MacGyver away!
(THUDS)
Well, he's gone.
Yeah.
And we'll always have what he
wrote on our window shade.
What did he
write that in?
Grape juice
and tears.
This is the end
My only friend, the end...
Of our elaborate...
So, Mr. Burns, you're saying
my dad has gone insane
and thinks he's a god
and broken off
all contact with
the outside world?
I told you Simpson
was a poor choice, sir.
You know, Smithers, "I told
you so" has a brother.
His name is
"Shut the hell up!"
WORKERS: (CHANTING)
A-bom-shabai.
Mom, I'm scared.
(GASPS)
WORKERS: A-bom-shabai.
A-bom-shabai.
Should we take
all our stuff,
or are we coming back
on this boat, too?
Same boat,
but take it anyway.
They use the boat for a Dixieland
booze cruise while we're gone.
(UPBEAT JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING)
(CHANTING)
Silence!
Now for my amusement, let the
monkey fight the elephant.
(ROARS)
(CHATTERING)
Homie, stop!
You're not a god!
Marge? You're just a sweet
guy from Springfield
who wanted his family
to have a better life.
What, I...
I am a god! I know all.
Oh, yeah,
what's Mom's birthday?
It's... Um...
Jan... Feb... Mar...
It's May!
May!
First... Second... Third?
You don't have to worship him.
He's not a god.
We know that.
We follow him
because of the secrets
he tells us.
What secrets?
He told us of
overtime pay.
And coffee breaks.
And flex time.
Casual Fridays.
On-site daycare.
Low dental co-pays.
Muffin baskets
on your birthday.
With Mylar balloons.
ALL: (CHANTING)
Mylar balloons.
This man told you
about these things?
Yes. In fact, he gave them
to us in a binding contract.
"A-bom-shabai"
means "vote union."
ALL: A-bom-shabai.
A-bom-shabai.
Up until now,
I was with you.
Even the beast-on-beast
combat, that had potential.
(WHIMPERING)
But treating employees like
human beings, that is madness!
Oh, you appear ill, Sahib.
Maybe you should
take a personal day.
Take one of mine.
They are transferable.
Argh!
I'm proud of you, Dad.
You're the first man to ever
outsource the American worker's
sense of entitlement
and privilege.
Well, I'm just glad
I'm not a god anymore.
I want to go home.
How's Chief Wiggum?
(SIGHS) Hmm.
He was gravely wounded
in a bank shootout.
Yeah, he's funny.
Well, I guess we'll have to
relocate to an area where
the workers are more
desperate and ignorant,
Springfield.
You're fired!
You're all fired!
Fired! Fired! Fired!
(ALL CHEERING)
WOMAN: Two months' severance!
Early retirement!
Golden parachutes for all!
(CHEERING)
(WHIMPERS)
(STRUMMING)
(BOLLYWOOD SONG PLAYING)
Oh, go ahead and
join them, Smithers.
I know you want to.
Yes, sir!
(EXCLAIMS) Ha!
(SONG CONTINUES)
Ripped By mstoll