(SINGING) The Simpsons
Ripped by jasonnguyen2606
(TIRES SCREECHING)
D'oh!
(EXCLAIMING)
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
Children, your gym teacher,
Ms. Pommelhorst,
has a brief announcement.
This is very
emotional for me.
I am taking
a leave of absence.
I will return in the fall
as Mr. Pommelhorst,
your new shop teacher.
We're telling you children now so
you can adjust and not make jokes.
Looks like there'll be some
new wood in shop class.
Precisely the type of wordplay
I seek to discourage.
(CHUCKLES)
"New wood."
Now please welcome your new
gym teacher, Coach Krupt.
Today we're gonna
play a game
that's as old
as pain itself.
Bombardment.
I'm intrigued.
What are the rules?
Duck or die!
(GROANS)
(CHILDREN GROANING) Bombardment!
Deal with it!
Bombardment!
Life's a bitch, son.
Bombardment! Walk it off!
Bombardment! Bombardment!
(GROANS)
No! (WHIMPERS)
(GLASSES SHATTER)
I caught it! I'm safe!
(GROANS)
Son, are you okay?
I guess.
Bombardment!
(GROANS)
(MARGE HUMMING)
Hmm.
(GROANING)
Oh, sweetie, if someone's bullying
you, you should tell your teacher.
But it's the teacher
who's bullying me.
Well, tell your regular bully.
He won't like it one bit.
Marge, I ripped my pants.
The only pants that
understand my complex hiney.
That was your last pair!
How did it happen?
Uh, normal wear and tear.
(GIGGLING)
Ow! My ass!
Sir, your go-cart's damaged!
I paid for 50 laps.
And I'm gonna take them!
(TIRES SCREECH)
(YELPING) Ow...
Oh, I'll have to go to every
store in the Pants District
to find another
pair like these.
Aw, Homie.
Kiss rubber, loser!
(GROANS)
Hey! You cry like a
little girl, Amy!
Ahh!
Oh, come on now!
Those were just baby teeth!
(SOBBING)
Oh, how much longer
can this go on?
(GROANS)
I see you like reading.
How do you like Bombardment?
Bombardment! Bombardment!
(GROANS)
BART: "Bombardment! Bombardment!
"How do you like
Bombardment?"
Well, I'll show him!
(GRUNTS)
(CHUCKLES MISCHIEVOUSLY)
Time for the bombarded
to become the bombardier.
Why'd I put this in here?
My saxophone!
(HONKS)
Mmm! (STRUGGLES)
Oh, yeah. That's why.
You jerk! I'm telling Morn!
(SAXOPHONE HONKING)
Van Houten!
Here, sir.
But my doctor says
no more Bombardment.
Well, here's a second opinion.
(GROANS)
Muntz! Do your worst! I'm drunk!
Well, welcome to AA.
Always Attacking!
(GROANS)
Simpson!
Here.
Bart's got an ice ball!
What is your major
malfunction, Simpson?
You will defrost, drain,
and surrender that ball!
And then I will use it to bombard you!
Bombardment!
Kid power!
(GRUNTS)
(SHATTERS)
Hmm? (GASPS)
(SCREAMS)
Me shack! It's ruined!
Ye red rubber home-wrecker!
(GROANS)
(HAMMERING)
Listen. I'm real sorry
I busted your shack.
Let me make it up to you.
I know a ravine where
there's a rusted-out car.
Don't be tantalizing me
with tales
of ravines
and rusted-out cars.
I'll only be getting me heart broke.
(CAR HONKING)
That's my mom. I gotta go. I
finished nailing this board.
Oh, yeah.
You're outta nails.
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
(LIGHTNING CRASHING)
Poor Willie.
Would you like to spend
the night with us?
I don't need your charity, not as
long as I've got a pan over me head.
That's not a pan.
That's a colander.
Oh, so that's where
all my soup went.
Thanks for taking
me in, Missus.
Please accept this
in return.
It's my most
prized possession.
It's a sculpture made of
children's lost retainers.
Huh? Ooh...
It's lovely!
I like this part in here.
The way it, um, goes.
(HUMMING)
(GRINDING)
Willie, I hope I'm not
being too personal.
But you seem resigned to
a life of abject squalor.
My family's used to it.
Me grandfather used to get
sent down into the mines
to make sure it was
safe for the canaries.
Don't you ever hope
for anything better?
Something better?
For Willie?
(SINGING) All I want is
a place somewhere
And?
That's it.
Maybe you could aim
a little higher.
Well, let's see.
(SINGING)
Oh, to have me shack rebuilt
Get my rotten
teeth all drilled
Something on
underneath me kilt
Oh, wouldn't it be adequate
Matching shoes
for both me feet
Dining on untainted meat
A toilet what
still has its seat
Oh, wouldn't it be adequate
BOTH: Adequate
Adequate
Wouldn't it be adequate
Hmm?
You're right, Lisa.
I do want to better me lot.
To live like a normal...
Hey, that's great.
Goodnight.
Bart, Willie could
have a better life
if only someone
showed him how.
I bet I could turn him
into a proper gentleman,
and I will do it in time
for the school science fair.
You're on, Lise.
I think you'll find that deep
down anyone can be civilized.
Goodnight, Willie.
Goodnight. (GRUNTS)
(SNORES)
Hmm.
Willie,
in the next few weeks,
I'll be teaching you poise,
pronunciation, and posture.
Let's see you stand up
as straight as you can.
Well, there's a first time
for everything.
(GRUNTS) Argh!
(BONE CRACKS)
Ugh! I'm too far
off the ground!
Lisa, come up here
and help me down!
(WHIMPERS)
So how am I doing?
(SIGHS) Oh.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Mr. Simpson,
I appreciate how much
you love our
big blue trousers,
but I'm afraid we just
don't make them anymore.
Sales plummeted after
our disastrous Super Bowl ad.
MAN: Big blue pants.
When you no longer care if
you're attractive to women.
(BABY ELEPHANT WALK PLAYING)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
Mr. Stern, would you make those
glorious blue pants again
if I whipped up
public interest for them?
Of course. But how?
Do an advertising campaign
so fresh and exciting
I haven't even
thought of it yet!
Well, what have I
got to lose
besides the factory that's been
in my family for generations?
How long is this
commercial anyway?
I don't know. I've never
made it to the end.
(HAMMERING)
Okay. How do you
address an archbishop?
I'll kill ya! I'll kill ya
for what you've done to me!
(SIGHS)
Lisa, you're a sweet lass.
But it's hopeless.
Like my dad told me.
You'll never amount to anything!
(BAGPIPES PLAYING)
You were born trash!
And you'll be lucky if you
grow up to be garbage!
(BABY COOING)
Would you like
to cut the cord?
Let him cut it himself.
It's time he learned
life ain't one big party.
(SOBS) That was the last
time we really talked.
(SOBBING)
What the hell are
they doing in there?
Lisa bet Bart
she can turn Willie
into a proper gentleman.
(SCOFFS)
That's as unlikely as Kearney going
around the world in 80 days.
Eighty days?
Ample time to circumnavigate
the globe, booger breath.
You, sir, have a wager.
I shall hold the money.
To Istanbul!
Wrong way, dingus!
(MOANING AND KISSING)
Oh, yeah.
(GIGGLES)
(GASPS) Homie?
What's that?
Huh?
On the back of your head.
It's called
"headvertising."
It creates brand awareness without
relying on traditional media.
Well, it creeps me out.
(CLICKS)
Wow.
It glows in the dark.
It's not supposed to.
(SIGHS)
All right. Let's just
try one more lesson.
Repeat after me.
"What flows from the nose
does not go on the clothes."
"What flows from me nose..."
Oh.
It's no use!
I'm not very cultured. I
don't even have a last name!
Care to concede that bet?
No. Come on, Willie.
I believe in you!
Uh...
(IN POSH ACCENT)
"What flows from the nose
"does not go on my clothes."
Say it again!
(SINGING)
What flows from the nose
does not go on my clothes
(MEOWS)
I think he's got it
Oh, yes, he's got it
What flows from the nose
Does not go on my clothes
(IN NORMAL ACCENT)
Ahh! A talkin' mirror!
Where is that ghastly flow?
(IN POSH ACCENT)
The nose The nose
(NASAL VOICE)
And where should it not go?
Blue pants! Blue pants!
Dad, get your own song.
Fine.
(SINGING) I'm getting
blue pants in the morning
Ding-dong,
the zipper's gonna shine
Gee, Homer. if those blue
pants mean that much to you,
they must be the greatest.
I'm getting
two pairs today.
I don't get this.
This guy paints his noggin and
you guys are ready to buy pants.
Meanwhile, I've been
paying for that billboard
outside for a year now
and it's not yielded nothin'.
(MOE'S VOICE)
You don't have to look at me.
You don't have to
look at me.
Well, he does have
billboard money.
Talking billboard money.
Ahhh...
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
Ew!
But he might be
right for my friend.
Behold, the first machine that
accurately measures surprise!
Really? Huh.
(MACHINE BEEPING)
(CLEARS THROAT) Ms. Lisa Simpson.
Master Bart Simpson.
(WHISPERS)
G.K. Willington, Esquire.
And Mr. G.K. Willington Esquire.
I have the strangest feeling
I've met him before.
And you may meet him again
as your new father!
Hubba-hubba,
Mommy like!
If you ask me,
the Royal Shakespeare
Company's latest
season was much ado about nothing.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Ha! I get that reference.
And you can get me anytime
you want, handsome.
I would be delighted to
dine with you on the 12th.
You're a smash, G.K.
It feels so sublime.
lfeel like I...
(SINGING)
Could be indoors all night
Could use a fork and knife
And never soil my suit
I could be so polite
Start not a single fight
And still not
feel like a fruit
How very nice that
There's no lice in my hair
And my toenails
Mmm...
I don't bite
Now that I've
reached the stage
Where I'm not full of rage
I could be indoors
Indoors all night
(SEYMOUR CLEARS THROAT)
Ladies and gentlemen,
it's time to announce the
winner of the science fair,
though I must
note I'm surprised
Lisa Simpson didn't enter
a project this year.
That's where you're wrong,
Principal Skinner.
I did enter a project.
And it's been in plain sight
the entire evening.
(ALL GASPING)
(MACHINE BEEPING)
Mr. G.K. Willington
is not who he seems.
In fact, he's someone
you all know quite well.
Is it me?
I give you
Groundskeeper Willie!
(CROWD MURMURING)
Well, Mother,
aren't you glad
you didn't get more
intimate with him?
Who said I didn't?
Hmm. Maybe there's room
on my sports wall.
(GIGGLES)
Now you have a friend.
Good morning, Lisa.
What's the lesson for today?
How to smoke a pipe
while summoning a falcon?
Put the kettle on, Featherby.
I'll be home soon.
(SCREECHING)
Willie, there are
no more lessons.
You're a proper gentleman.
My work is done.
But I don't know
what to do with myself.
All I've ever been
is a groundskeeper.
And that job's taken.
Skinner dumped it on the next
lowest guy on the totem pole.
Oh, for goodness sakes!
How did I get up here?
I think this is the perfect
job for new you, Willie.
It requires
sophistication, tact,
and you get to meet
the highest class of people.
Good evening, sir.
I'm your maître d'.
Oh, that's the "D" for?
Dimwit? (CHUCKLES)
Laugh. jerk!
(LAUGHS)
Eh, I don't need your
charity titters.
Now say hello to my
girlfriend, Charity Titters.
Right this way, ma'am.
(GASPS) Oh. Thank you.
No, not now! Not now! Wait
till we get to the booth.
(MOANING AND KISSING)
Mmm.
(CHUCKLES)
I'm so glad you washed that
stupid logo off your head.
Well, it did itsjob. Everyone's
wearing blue pants now.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
Hmm.
(TURNS OFF TV)
I'd like to get into some
blue pants right now.
(GASPS)
What are those
doing there?
Earning us 100 bucks
a week, that's what.
Uh, except
the "Maine potatoes" one.
It's just a reminder
to myself.
(GROANS)
Hey, maître d'!
May I help you, sir?
These rolls are stale!
Bombardment!
Bring me some more!
And some iced tea for the lady, please.
Bombardment!
(SIGHS)
(SINGING)
I've a fancy suit
And a clean white shirt
But I miss the days
when tractor fumes
Blew up my skirt
I was freezing cold
And I slept in mold
But I long for
the shack where I lived
She was true to me
My old home of wood
And when I passed out drunk
From turpentine
She understood
(SNORING)
Life was so sublime
Well, boo-hoo
'Cause I'm hanging ferns
In the shack where you lived
If I had your voice,
I'd talk-sing everything.
So, how you doing, Willie?
I'm ebullient! I'm
bubbling with glee! I'm...
(IN NORMAL ACCENT) Bloody miserable!
I miss me crap shack!
(SOBBING)
Hey, that's my table.
Amscray!
(IN POSH ACCENT) Sir, there are
many other tables available.
None that has a view
of the yoga studio.
Yeah, baby.
Greet the sun,
downward dog.
(GROWLS AND BARKS)
Sir, there
is a child present.
Hey, when I'm off the clock,
kids can jump in the lake!
Now get out of my booth,
Duchess of Cornball!
Very well, sir. But my name is
(IN NORMAL ACCENT) Willie!
Now may I show you
the dessert tray? (GRUNTS)
Dessert tray?
That's a great gag.
Can I use it?
I'm taking it anyway.
(GRUNTS)
SEYMOUR: It is with great joy
and a sense of "once again everything
is back to where it started,"
that we welcome our once and
future groundskeeper, Willie!
(CHILDREN CHEERING)
Now let's all enjoy
some punch and cookies!
Willie, you can start
cleaning up now.
With pleasure.
(SINGING) Heaven
I'm in heaven
Willie, please express
yourself through mopping.
All right.
And when you're done, here are
the keys to your new shack.
(SIGHS) Ah!
It's just like I remember.
With one little difference.
Oh, you made that for me?
(SOBS)
I think I'll need
a moment alone.
I understand.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Argh!
(SHATTERS)
I liked it the way it was!
Ripped by jasonnguyen2606