The Simpsons.
Go, toothpaste, go!
Move your pasty
white butt.
Come on, shampoo!
You can do it!
Yay! I won your stupid
bathroom products race.
No fair, you only won
'cause you had
the inside track.
If the water was spinning
the other way...
It never spins
the other way.
In the northern hemisphere
water always drains
counterclockwise.
It's called
the Coriolis effect.
No way.
Water doesn't
obey your rules.
It goes where it wants.
Like me, babe.
Yes, Bart.
Why don't you
try it and see?
I know I've seen it
go the other way.
Faithful toilet.
You'll prove me right.
I'm a-singin' in
the show... Ow! Ow-ooh!
Hot! Yah! Cold!
No! Hot! Cold! Hot!
Oh! Who's! Doing! That?!
Oh, for Pete's sake, Bart,
use the plunger!
Bart, water will
only go the other way
in the southern
hemisphere.
What the hell is
the southern hemisphere?
Haven't you ever
looked at your globe?
See, the southern hemisphere
is made up of
everything
below the equa...
This line.
So down there in,
say... Argentina,
or Rand McNally,
all their water
runs backwards?
Uh-huh. In fact,
in Rand McNally
they wear hats
on their feet
and hamburgers
eat people.
Cool.
Hello,
southern hemisphere?
Which way does the water
go in your toilet?
Just a minute, I'll check.
Ah, nuts.
Please to repeat again
and I will translating
for the El Presidente.
Which way does
the water turn in your toilet?
Dice que el curso
esta cambiando.
Ay, caramba!
Los insurgentes ya van
a capturar la capital.
Necesito huir.
Ay!
I can't get a straight answer
out of this crazy hemisphere.
Eine minuten,
eine minuten.
Ach! Das wagenfone
est eine nuisancefone.
Buenas noches,
mein fuhrer.
Ja, ja.
Bart, you can't actually
call these places.
Don't you know
how expensive
international calls are?
Hello, operator.
I'd like to make
a collect call to...
Australia.
This is the
international operator.
Will you accept
a collect call from...
Uh, yes, this is
Dr. Bart Simpson
of the International
Drainage Commission.
It's an emergency.
If it's an emergency, then.
We understand some
drains in your area
have been malfunctioning,
sucking in people
and whatnot.
Willikers. That's awful.
Indeed.
We need you to check
your sinks and toilets
and tell us which way
the water is going.
And please...
Stand clear.
The fixtures...
they're all draining
clockwise, sir.
Oh. She was right.
Stupid Lisa,
science queen.
Well, why don't you just check
your neighbor's drains.
I'll hold.
Hey, Bart.
The bakery caught fire
and all of downtown
smells like cookies.
Want to go smell?
Yes. Yes, I do.
Hello. Sir? Sir?
I've returned from
the Koolamugery's place.
They're draining
clockwise too.
Draining?
I don't care
about that anymore.
Are we in any dange...
Burkina Faso?
Disputed zone?
Who called
all these weird places?
Quiet. It might be you.
I can't remember.
No, I'm gonna ask Marge.
No, no.
Why embarrass us both?
Just write a check and I'll release
some more endorphins.
900 dollar-adoos!?
Tobias!
Did you accept
a six-hour collect
call from the states?
It was an emergency call
from the International Drainage
Commission in Springfield.
Oh, my God!
There's nothing wrong
with the bidet, is there?
Hello?
Right,
I'm calling all the way
from Squatters Crag,
Australia.
And I want to speak to, uh,
Dr. Bart Simpson right now.
Uh... hold, please.
All right, but I don't...
Payroll,
Burt Stanton speaking.
Oi. I said Bart Simpson.
What kind of a company
is this?
Bart Simpson's office.
Thank the great good Lord.
Look, I was just say...
One moment please.
Who do they think I am?
Some stupid Aussie drongo?
Bleedin' yanks.
I ought to...
This is Bart Simpson.
Can I help you, ma'am?
Yeah... Hey! My name is
Bruno Drundridge, right?
You owe me $900, mate.
No, you owe me $900.
I... You... Ohh...
You're... You're just
some punk kid aren't you?
You picked the wrong guy
to tangle with here, mate.
I don't think so.
You're all the way
in Australia.
Hey, I think I hear
a dingo eating
your baby.
Yeah, well... Ooh!
Oh. Ah. That's it.
I'm going to report this
to me member of parliament.
Hey! Gus!
I got something
to report to you.
That's a bloody
outrage, it is.
I'm gonna take this
all the way
to the prime minister.
Hey! Mr. Prime Minister!
Andy!
Hi, mates!
What's the good word?
"Mr. Simpson, blah blah.
Misrepresentation
over a telephone, yadda yadda.
Sincerely,
some Australian Jerk."
Hey! I need that.
Office of the
Solicitor General?
Office
of the Prime Minister?
Hopping Mad Collection Agency?
What is all this stuff?
Nothing. Some stupid country
thinks I owe them money.
Uh-oh. Bart,
you better talk
to Mom and Dad about this.
Hey, guys. Just so you don't
hear any wild rumors...
I'm being indicted
for fraud in Australia.
That's no reason
to block the TV.
Oh, my.
Bart, did you trick
an Australian boy
into accepting a
$900 collect call?
Yes'm.
Hmm... There it is,
"Aus-tral-ia."
I'll be damned.
Look at this country...
"U-ar-gay."
Oh, my. Hello.
I'm Evan Conniver with
the U.S. State department.
"Undersecretary for
International Protocol...
Brat and Punk division"?
Unfortunately, Bart,
your little escapade
could not have come
at a worse time.
Americo-Australian-ian relations
are at an all-time low.
As I'm sure you remember
in the late 1980s
the U.S. Experienced
a short-lived infatuation
with Australian culture.
For some bizarre reason
the Aussies thought
this would be
a permanent thing.
Of course it wasn't.
I know those words
but that sign makes no sense.
Anyway, the down-under
fad fizzled
and the diplomatic climate
turned absolutely frosty.
Let's pretend we
didn't see that.
And Bart's childish taunting
agitated the Aussies further.
Oh, he'll agitate you.
Ho, ho, he sure will.
What can we do for you?
Well, it's too late
to merely pay back the money.
But as a sign of good faith
to our Australian "friends"
we'd like to imprison Bart
for five years.
That's tough but fair.
Boy, go with the man.
No, no, no! No.
I'm not gonna have my
son go to jail
over some silly tiff
with Australia.
You'll just have
to find some other
country to have
relations with.
You're sure now?
The prison train is sailing.
Okay. I'm not hearing
a lot of support for prison.
There is one other option.
They'll drop the charges if.
Bart makes a public apology
in Australia.
All Bart has to do
is apologize
and we get a free trip
to Australia?
I can handle that.
I'm an expert
at phony apologies.
- Bart!
- I'm sorry.
That's better.
Uh, we left at
1:30 p.m. Monday.
What time is it now?
It's 6:45 a.m. next Wednesday.
You may also be
interested to know
that's it's summer
here, not winter.
What does that sign say?
I thought they spoke
English in this country.
It says you
can't bring in
outside plants
or animals.
Any foreign creature
you bring in
could upset the
environmental balance.
Sorry, girl.
I don't want to get
in any more trouble down here.
I'll pick you up
on the way home.
Hey! Are you like one
of those English guards
who can't laugh
or smile or anything?
No, sir!
U.S. Marine Corps, sir!
Oh, yeah.
This is the life.
Boy, next summer,
can you commit
some fraud in
Orlando, Florida?
I'm way ahead of you, Dad.
Kno-ock.
Simpsons, I'd like you
to meet our ambassador,
the honorable Avril Ward.
Hello. Now, everything is
all set for Bart's apology.
Mr. Conniver will meet you at
the parliament house at 3:00 p.m.
Any questions?
Yeah. Do the toilets go
backwards in here?
No. To combat homesickness
we've installed
a device that makes them swirl
the correct American way.
Sweet land of liberty,
of thee I sing.
Hey, G.I. Joe,
your sign's broken.
We're already in Australia.
Actually, sir! The embassy is
considered American soil, sir!
Really?
Look, boy. Now
I'm in Australia.
Now I'm in America.
Australia. America.
- I get it, Dad.
- Australia.
America, Australia.
Homer, that's enough.
America, Australia...
Here in America, we don't
tolerate that kind of crap, sir!
"Australia was
originally founded
as a settlement
for British convicts."
Hmm, Lisa,
watch your camera.
You call that a knife?
This is a knife.
That's not a knife.
That's a spoon.
All right, all right.
You win.
I see you've played
knifey-spoony before.
Hey, give me one of those
famous giant beers
I heard so much about.
Something wrong, Yank?
No. It's pretty big,
I guess.
I'll just have
a cup of coffee.
Beer it is.
No. I said coffee.
Beer?
Cof-fee.
Be-er?
C-o...
B-e...
We'll meet you boys
back here for dinner.
Good luck, honey.
Bart, I'm sorry
I'm gonna miss
your public humiliation.
But the Woolumbaloo
Dirt Monument
is just too exciting
to pass up.
Hear ye, hear ye.
This session
will now come to order.
With the cooperation of
the U.S. Department of State
we have present today
one Bart Simpson.
I believe he has
something to say.
Bart?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for what
I did to your country.
- Bravo.
- Very good.
Well, you're
free to go, Bart...
right after your
additional punishment.
Punishment?
Well, a mere apology
would be bit empty, eh?
- Let the booting begin.
- Booting?
Aw, it's just a little
kick in the bum.
What kind of a sick country
would kick someone
with a giant boot?
Mr. Simpson, shush.
Disparaging the boot
is a bootable offense.
It's one of
their proudest traditions.
You sold us out, Conniver!
Stay back or I'll boot
your prime minister.
I'll do it!
So help me God,
I'll boot him!
He means it.
When will you
Australians learn?
In America, we stopped
using corporal punishment
and things have
never been better.
The streets are safe.
Old people strut confidently
through the darkest alleys
and the weak and nerdy
are admired
for their computer
programming abilities.
So, like us, let your children
run wild and free.
Because as the old
saying goes:
"Let your children
run wild and free."
Now, boy, run back
to the embassy.
Back to American soil.
I'll stop them.
Oh, no.
It's coming back this way.
That throwing stick
stunt of yours
has boomeranged on us.
Hey. We can get away
in their pouches.
Eew! It's not like
in cartoons.
Yeah, there's
a lot more mucus.
Mom, you said I could have
one souvenir, right?
Well, I want a didgeridoo.
That seems very noisy and
expensive for a souvenir.
Why don't you get
this nice cap?
It's clever,
just like you.
Get out. Get out.
Shoo, shoo.
Get out of here. Ugh!
These bloody things
are everywhere.
They're in the lift,
in the lorry,
in the bond wizard,
and all over the
malanga gildachuck.
They're like kangaroos
but they're reptiles,
they is.
We have them in America.
They're called bullfrogs.
What?! That's an odd name.
I'd have called them
chaswassers.
L-isa!
M-arge!
Oh, the Simpsons.
Well, they're not
getting back in here.
I can't believe
our government
would set up Bart
like that.
I must say,
I'm very angry
at the State department
right now.
Yes, but shh.
Mrs. Simpson, please.
We're about to reach
a breakthrough
with the Aussies.
Then it's agreed.
During the bargaining session
we each get two candy apples.
All right.
One candy and one caramel.
Oh, for the love of criminy.
Give me that.
I know Bart did something wrong,
but he's my son
and I'm going to
punish him myself.
Our countries may have
their differences
but as human beings
I think we can all agree
there's no substitute
for the discipline
of a loving parent.
He wants to talk to you.
Y-ello.
So we're in agreement.
She won't be allowed
near the phone again.
We did it.
We've worked out
a compromise
that will allow both nations
to save face.
We've argued them
down to a booting.
What?!
The prime minister
just wants
to kick you once
through the gate
with a regular shoe.
I believe it's a wing-tip.
No deal.
This is my son
we're talking about.
Sure, he's not perfect
but who is in this
work-a-day world?
No, Mom. Wait.
It's time for me
to bend over
and receive my destiny.
Thank you, Bart.
I promise I won't
make fun of you
later for this.
Show them what
American butts
are made of, son.
That's it, lad.
This is for the commonwealth
of Australia.
And this is for
the United States of America.
I'm glad you're okay, honey,
but I wish you'd chosen
a more tasteful way
to be patriotic.
I'm impressed you were
able to write so legibly
on your own butt.
All right, mates.
Let him have it!
Hey, do we get to land on
an aircraft carrier?
No, sir. The closest vessel is
the U.S.S. Walter Mondale.
It's a laundry ship.
They'll take you
the rest of the way.
Hey, look.
Those frogs are eating
all their crops.
Well, that's what happens
when you introduce
foreign species
into an ecosystem
that can't handle them.
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.