(SINGING) The Simpsons
Ripped by jasonnguyen2606
(TIRES SCREECHING)
D'oh!
(EXCLAIMS)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
HOMER: D'oh!
(CHUCKLES)
Oh, when is our food
going to get here?
I'm starved!
I'm so bored,
I figured out
where the wallpaper
pattern repeats.
See, it goes ship's wheel,
Popeye tattoo, Gilligan hat
fish with boobs
and back to ship's wheel.
LISA: What about
this swordfish?
Oh, my life's work ruined!
Arr, sorry
about the delay.
The chef is having a bit of a
problem with tonight's special.
(GRUNTS)
Meanwhile, I can send a busboy
out to get you something
from a better restaurant.
Red Lobster?
Not that good.
(ALL GROANING)
Until then, perhaps an old sea
yarn might pass the time.
(PUFFS)
Too bad I don't know any.
I know one about
the most important
sea voyage in
American history,
the journey
of the Mayflower.
Ah, yes, the ship that brought
prostitutes to America.
Not prostitutes, protestants.
Now who's being naive?
The year was 1620.
Hurry, my little puritans.
We must flee England and its
insufficiently puritanical ways.
Do you have your
shipboard entertainments?
I've got my
toy wood lump.
(GRUNTS)
What jolly fun.
(BELL CLANGING)
Finally, we shall bid
good-bye to England
and its drunken,
decadent sinners.
HOMER: Oh!
Out of my way, you
God-fearing buckleheads!
(MAN GROANS)
(SHRIEKS)
(GRUNTS)
Hide me!
Please, you got to help me.
If they find me,
they'll kill me.
LENNY: Has anyone
seen this knave?
He's wanted for daring
to question why we call this
the Jacobean era when the king's
name is James and not Jacob.
(PRAYING) Oh, Lord,
I beseech you...
Mother, we must
protect him.
Look, he's praying.
Oh, Lord,
please let the soldiers
kill this family
instead of me.
Noble sir, you may
accompany us
to America in my late
husband's clothing.
And I will make thee a hat
from construction paper.
So thou art a widow, eh?
Then the codpiece
holds no terrors for thee.
Good sir, I do not approve
of your fleshly gaze.
Hmm.
(PANTING)
Oh, baby.
Hmm.
MAN 1: Goodbye!
MAN 2: Don't come back!
(ALL PRAYING)
What kind of a booze
cruise is this?
Where's the hooch?
(CHUCKLES) We puritans have
no place for drunkenness.
Or colorful clothes
or dreaming or poetry.
So if you write a sonnet,
keep it under your bonnet.
(GASPS) Oh, no!
That was a poem!
(WHIPS)
Forgive me, Lord!
Then pour a little salt in the wounds.
(GROANS)
And I'm good.
I see you met our devout
leader Ned Flandish.
Stupid Flandish.
Uh, listen, since all the other
fun stuff is out of bounds,
how about a little Bible-thumping
in the crow's nest?
What do you say, Miss...
Constance Prudence
Chastity Goodfaith. D'oh!
My friends
call me Marge.
Oh. Marge Obedience
Temperance Sexwon't.
D'oh!
Back off, newbie!
We're engaged.
I didn't kill her
husband just so...
I mean, I... ldidn't
kill her husband.
We're not engaged.
Uh, it's really more
of an amiable concordance.
Oh! (CLICKS TONGUE)
Such language
from a woman.
(GASPS) Oh, no! I just
thought of you as a woman!
(GRUNTS)
Lord, we thank you for the
many ways you show your love.
The sun which bakes our lips
to the point of bleeding,
(CHUCKLES) and your hilarious
idea to surround us with water
that would kill us
if we drank it.
Now I've got to warn you,
even for this day and age,
I'm considered a bad husband.
She's going to marry him
'cause he wears boots
instead of
blackening his feet.
(SOBS)
Well, I'm sure the way to win her
heart is to be fat and crying.
Why, thee little...
(CHOKES)
(GRUNTS)
D'oh!
Oh, don't stop.
You're choking him just the
way his father used to.
MARGE: Good times.
(SIGHS)
Ooh.
Perhaps thou wouldst
make a good father.
May I escort you
to the railing'?
(HUMMING)
Oh, my God. Look at that
hand-on-hand action.
If I don't do something, soon
they'll be exchanging pleasantries.
Yes, the weather is fair.
Man! That guy sends my humors
from sanguine to bilious!
That's how we talk.
Weird, huh?
Time to think of
a plan most sneaky.
Anyways, I just wanted to let
you know that I'm throwing
a little party tonight
to celebrate
that only half of us
have died so far.
(SPLASHES)
Beer? I thought you guys
didn't drink on the Gayflower?
Stop calling it that!
Whatever.
I was saving this booze
to mess up the Indians,
but seeing what good pals we are,
I wanted to give you a taste.
Say, I know
a good drinking game.
Take a sip every time
a wave hits the ship.
(GULPS)
Oh, you're good at this.
Oh, Lord, thank you for this generous
rain and abundant lightning.
(LIGHTNING CRACKS)
(GROANS)
Obviously, kissing your ass
is getting me nowhere.
This storm's
blowing us off course.
And where's our crew?
I'll show you
where they are.
You don't want
to miss this, Marge.
MEN: (CHANTING)
Sin, sin, sin!
NED: (GASPS) Horseplay?
Roughhousing'?
Horsehousing?
And here's the knave
what's responsible.
(DRUNKEN LAUGH)
That's all I needed to hear.
(GROANS)
Homer, I can't believe I was
thinking of letting you
touch my elbow
through a cloth.
But, baby,
a man has needs.
(RUMBLING)
(ALL PANICKING)
(THUDS)
(GROANS)
Our captain's
be-head-bumped.
Oh, I guess we'll never
make it to the new world.
Oh, when we landed I was going to
denounce my sister as a witch.
I keep telling you
the ability to add
two-digit numbers
is not witchcraft.
Thirty-one plus forty-three?
Seventy-four.
ALL: Witch, witch, witch!
People, this is madness!
We can burn the witch later.
Right now I've got
to save this ship.
ALL: Hmm.
Hey, I've been driving
drunk since I was 12.
But first, who's going
to help me pee?
They're looking at me 'cause I
have the key to the stocks.
(WAVES CRASHING)
(GRUNTS)
Don't worry, Marge.
I'll see to it you
fundamentalist Christians
live to take over all America
by the 21st century.
Look! An albatross.
It can lead us to safety.
Man, that bird did it all.
Good guy.
(CHUCKLES) I just thought of a
name for where we're going.
New England.
Oh, that's real creative.
What do you call
your foot, "new hand"?
At least I'm pitching.
(KISSING)
Land, ho!
What did you call me?
(MOANING)
Great chief Wig-Gum,
we could never have survived
our first year in the
new world without you.
I almost regret what we Europeans
are going to do to you.
What, what are you
going to do?
Oh, give you the biggest
slice of pumpkin pie.
Also we're going to take
your land and wipe you out.
Who wants whipped topping?
Here's your bill. And will
there be anything else?
We haven't gotten
our food yet.
I'll look into it.
OLD SEA CAPTAIN:
What the...
(CHUCKLES)
Who else has a story?
I do.
Homer, you can tell
the third story.
Bart will tell the second,
which is usually the weakest.
Hey!
I'm just trying to take
the pressure off of you.
Well, one time I read
this boring comic book
about a ship
called the Bounty.
Ooh, like the paper towels.
Go on.
BOY: Hurry up.
Captain Bligh, there's a
message from admiral Nelson.
Thank you, Mr. Christian.
Mmm-hmm.
"Bligh eats dolphin boogers."
NELSON: Ha-ha!
Well, when you eat
as much dolphin as I do
there's bound to be a
booger or two in the mix.
Good morning, crew.
Welcome to day 718
of our voyage.
Today's announcements.
First of all, in an effort
to save water,
you will no longer
be given any water.
And because of
a drawing of myself
having romantic congress
with a merman...
(CHILDREN LAUGHING)
CAPTAIN BLIGH: I am dumping all
your mail from home into the sea.
(GRUNTS)
And I can assure you
there were cookies in there.
Good cookies.
The kind only a loving mother or
Milhouse's father could make.
My father's alive?
No, he died while baking.
It's all in the letter.
(ALL GRUMBLING)
I'm getting pretty
tired of that seawad.
This is nothing like
the recruiting brochure.
Hmm.
Maybe that's what
happens on the last day.
I warn you, Captain.
Push this crew too far
and there'll be mutiny.
Mutiny? On the Bounty?
(CHUCKLES)
What have you been smoking?
Opium.
Besides that.
Welcome to our
tropical paradise.
Enjoy our luaus, our
lagoons, and our ladies.
And remember, what happens
in Tahiti stays in Tahiti.
Because we have no way of
communicating with the outside world.
Tell me, has Robert Fulton
invented the steamboat yet?
Any day now.
Ooh.
Hip, hip
When you're on a holiday
You can't find
the words to say
I'm telling you,
I don't look like that.
Make another.
(SIGHS)
Yes, Lord Ugly-face.
And I wanna feel it too
Don't just sit there,
help me!
We'll be playing
and having fun
Bye-bye. Bye-bye.
Thanks for staying with us.
We appreciate you putting cloth
over our women's boobies.
You'll receive an updated bill
after you leave. Bye-bye.
I wish we were
back in Tahiti.
Why, yes, it was truly
an unforgettable vacation.
I order you to forget it.
(ALL GRUMBLING)
And while you're working, I
want to hear a sea chantey...
In a round.
(ALL SINGING) Row, row, row your
boat gently down the stream
(GUNSHOT)
Rounder! I hear edges!
Row, row, row your boat
gently down the stream.
Ow!
You're off-key.
(GROANS)
Make that song your own.
You don't sound like you've ever
been on a boat in your life.
(GUNS COOKING)
What the...
Captain, this is a mutiny.
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
Let's not be hasty here.
What if I introduce
a suggestion box?
We have a suggestion box.
You made it from the head of the
last guy who had a suggestion.
Yeah, but... I...
I warned you
there'd be mutiny.
Just start rowing, Willie.
And sing a round while you do.
(SINGING)
Row, row, row your boat gently
Row, row, merrily, merrily Bound
the down gently down the...
Merrily down the...
I cannot do it!
I'm only one man.
You'll sing or you'll mutiny.
And you're too much of
a spineless coward for that.
Swim faster or I'll have
you made into soup.
What are you going
to do, go underwater?
(LAUGHS)
I'd like to see that.
Ahhh!
You call this deep?
This is your new captain
saying, "Next stop, Tahiti."
(ALL CHEERING)
And we're going to
remove all evidence of
the previous regime, starting
with this stupid wheel.
(GRUNTS)
(SPLASHES)
Uh-oh.
Ahhh!
(ALL SCREAMING)
Well, I know you had your doubts,
men, but there they are,
the most beautiful
women in the world.
(PENGUINS SCREECHING)
Those are penguins.
Well, look at it this way. We're
going to discover the North Pole.
South Pole.
CHRISTIAN:
Oh, boy, do I suck.
JIMBO: Yeah.
(SIGHS) I'm starting to think the
Sea Captain isn't coming back.
He's out there
playing basketball.
(GRUNTS) Arr.
(LAUGHS)
In your face, Julio.
I'll be fetching
your food right away.
Six more games.
Well, I guess we have time for
my tale of moist adventure.
It takes place
in a dark time for mankind
when madness
and ignorance ruled.
The 1970s.
Rock the boat
Don't rock the boat, baby
Don't tip the boat over
Rock the boat
Don't rock the boat, baby
Disco Stu has some
troubling news.
(INDISTINCT MURMURS)
The ship's doctor has
reported an outbreak of...
Disco fever!
The only cure is to do a little
dance, make a little love,
get down tonight.
Wait a minute.
What was the second one?
And now let's welcome
the LeRoy Neiman of seamen,
your captain,
Montgomery Burns.
(APPLAUSE)
Ten-four, good buddy.
I'm Chevy Chase
and you're not.
Willy Stargell!
Yes, welcome to the maiden
voyage of the Neptune,
the world's most
unflippable luxury liner.
Help yourselves
to some pineapple
upside-down cake
and apple turnovers.
And you'll all be
getting free hats,
so make sure to
give us your cap size!
What a fascinating
cross-section of humanity.
You've got the lonely,
but lovable loser...
Hello, Angels.
Your mission today
involves going
undercover at
a wet t-shirt contest.
Just get you wet...
(CHUCKLES)
Uh, maybe not so lovable.
And you've got the elderly
Jewish couple
making their first
trip to Israel.
Our son, Shlomo is working
on a kibbutz in Haifa.
We're schlepping
him some kreplach.
We're Jewish,
all right!
What's our back story?
We're the band.
And we're on!
(SINGING) I think we're
heading for disaster
And most of you
will not be saved
Unless the captain
is attentive
We'll all be crushed
by a huge wave
Mmm, I love the sea,
Smithers.
No earthquakes,
towering infernos,
China syndromes,
apple dumpling gangs...
(WAVES CRASHING)
(ALL SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMS) My wig!
I mean, my natural hair!
Mamma mia! What a time
to be carrying the soup.
Whoa!
Cool! No gravity!
Oh, there it is.
(SCREAMS)
Hey, you schmuck,
get off of me!
Oh.
Goin' out with a sight gag.
Nice.
(GROANS)
(SCREAMING)
I got an idea.
Climb into my mouth.
(WHIMPERS)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLES)
No!
Catch me, Flanders!
(SCREAMS)
Lord, with you watching over
me, I shall feel no pain.
(SCREAMS)
(SIGHS)
Woo-hoo!
It's almost New Year's!
(COUNTING)
Ten, nine, eight...
Homer, the ship's upside down and
hundreds of people are dead!
...three, two, one...
Happy New Year!
(BLOWS)
My resolution
is to be more fun.
Attention, everyone!
I've spent the entire cruise
reading these
maintenance brochures
because as a lonely
single woman,
I've had nothing
better to do.
ALL: Aw.
"Aw"s are cheap.
I'm lookin' for some action.
(ALL WHISTLING)
I thought so.
It says here we should head
upwards towards the hull
before the ocean
starts filling the ship.
Don't listen to her!
She'll get us all killed!
The safest thing to do is to
resume our normal activities.
Now where is
the rumba instructor?
Okay, so that's left, left, right.
Come on, people!
(VOCALIZING)
So, now which way do we go in
this farkaktah flippity ship?
(GROWLS)
Homer, what should we do?
HOMER: Uh, give me a second.
I'm in the bathroom.
What? I have great
ass suction.
Now, how about
a little privacy?
(KEYS JANGLING)
My keys!
Whatever you do, don't look down.
I mean up!
(PANTING) I can't do this anymore.
It's too confusing!
Ahhh!
Not that confusing.
This hatchway is jammed!
Move aside!
I'll use my
Swiss Army Bone.
(GRUNTS)
(METAL CREAKS)
Okay, the engine room is just
through this flooded area.
Somebody has to
take the rope,
swim through
to the other side
and tie it off so we can use
it as an underwater guideline.
Stand aside!
I shall perform the necessary heroics.
Thank you.
You?
Yes.
All I need is some
inspirational music...
(CLICKS)
When she passed away
I cried and cried all day
Alone again
Naturally
(SOBBING)
All right, I can see
this is all up to me.
(GRUNTS)
Swim, fatty! Swim!
Oh, Homie! You did it.
(GASPS)
(INHALES DEEPLY)
Mmm. (GULPS)
(GRUNTS)
I've tied it off.
You're all going to make it.
(GROANS)
Tell the world
that I saved you all.
Don't tell me
what to do.
(KNOCKING)
I hear knocking.
We're saved!
(SCREAMS)
I don't know which
pains me more.
The flame or the irony!
(GROANS)
Can you believe
it's the irony?
Oh, my God, our boat is upside-down.
(BELL CLANGS)
You guys know
the way to Tahiti?
Way to go, genius!
You sailed into someone
else's tale of the sea.
At least I'm not gay
for skeleton Kearney.
Our ribs got tangled
75 years ago.
That's not gay.
CHRISTIAN: Right. You
keep believing that.
Ripped by jasonnguyen2606