The Simpsons.
This romance is so full
of heartfelt passion.
I can really identify
with this corn-fed heroine.
Homer, are you awake?
This is important.
Give me some sign
you're awake.
Wake up!
Huh? What's wrong?
House run away?
Dog's on fire?
Homie, do you think that
the romance
has gone out of our lives?
Wake up!
Marge, it's 3:00 a.m.,
and I worked all day.
It's 9:30 p.m., and you spent
your whole Saturday
drinking beer
in Maggie's kiddie pool.
Hmm? There you are.
Thought you could get away, huh?
Homer, young people
learn about love from adults,
and we've been setting
a terrible example
for our children and
the community in general.
I want us to
deal with the issues
raised by this book.
I knew we shouldn't have put
a fireplace in the bedroom.
How many times
can you laugh at that cat
getting hit
by the moon?
It's a new episode.
Not exactly. They pieced
it together from old shows
and it seems new
to the trusting eyes
of impressionable youth.
Really?
Ren and Stimpy
do it all the time.
Yes, they do, and when was
the last time you heard anyone
talk about Ren and Stimpy?
Children, your father and I
have fed you and clothed you,
but we've neglected
something more important.
It's time to learn
about love.
No need, Mom. We already
learned in school.
This is Fuzzy Bunny.
About a year ago,
he noticed his voice
was changing.
He had terrible acne
and had fur where
there was no fur before.
He also noticed
Fluffy Bunny.
Bor-ring.
Fuzzy went to the park,
the ice cream social,
the boat show,
and various other
wholesome activities.
And they never
ruined their fun
by giving in to their
throbbing biological urges.
Then came the big day.
Fluffy and Fuzzy
got married.
That night came
the honeymoon.
She's faking it.
I mean romance,
not love.
Mom, romance is dead.
It was acquired
in a hostile takeover
by Hallmark and Disney,
homogenized and sold off
piece by piece.
That's not true.
Romance is all around us...
In our neighborhoods...
even at our jobs.
All you have to do
is think about
your most cherished memories.
- Moe's Tavern.
- Hello, is Al there?
Al?
Yeah, Al.
Last name Coholic.
Let me check.
Phone call for Al.
Al Coholic.
A Jock Strap?
Is I.P. Freely here?
Hey, is there a Butts here?
Seymour Butts?
Ah, Homer Sexual?
Mike Crotch?
Uh, Amanda Hugginkiss?
Ah, Hugh Jass?
Ivana Tinkle?
I'm a stupid moron
with an ugly face
and a big butt,
and my butt smells,
and I like to kiss
my own butt.
No! No! No!
No, ask your heart
what its fondest desire is.
Chocolate.
Invisible cola.
Forbidden doughnut.
Sacrilicious.
Mmm. Snouts.
Mmm. Free goo.
Mmm. Something.
No. Think about people...
About moments in your life
that have been very romantic.
Oh, okay.
That's not the idea at all.
Okay. Well,
this story isn't ideal.
I've never told it
to you before.
I got a very thoughtless
birthday present
from someone
who shall remain nameless.
So I actually went
to the bowling alley
to spite him... or her.
I'm awfully sorry.
Entirely my fault.
It is nice
to meet you...
- Homer.
- Oh. No, no.
Homer is my...
ball's name.
I'm Marge.
Your fingers are so slender,
so feminine.
They're far too tapered
for the ball you're using.
You need something lighter,
more delicate.
Here, use my ball.
No. No, thank you,
mister, um... Brunswick.
Call me Jacques.
Jacques.
Marge.
May I ask you
a bold question?
Sure.
You've never
bowled before?
- Never.
- No.
- Then I will teach you.
Oh, I don't want
to trouble you.
Not at all.
I am a professional.
Roll the ball for me, Marge.
Let me see your form.
All right,
but I'm not very good.
I can hit that
one pin all right,
but the rest of them
don't even wobble.
I can help you, Marge.
Pick up the ball.
Pick up Homer.
Pick him up.
- Now, throw.
- But...
Throw, damn you.
You're a very
good teacher.
Here we are.
You didn't have to
drop me off.
But I wanted to.
Marge, do you know
how beautiful you look
in the moonlight?
Oh, Jacques,
I'm a married woman.
I know, I know.
My mind says stop,
but my heart
and my hips
cry, "proceed!"
Marge, darling, I want
to see you tomorrow.
Meet me tomorrow
for brunch.
- What's brunch?
- You'd love it.
It's not quite breakfast.
It's not quite lunch.
But it comes with a slice
of cantaloupe at the end.
You don't get completely
what you would at breakfast,
but you get
a good meal.
He seemed to know
a lot about brunch.
But it turned out he wasn't
interested in brunch at all.
Your laughter
is like music to me.
But if you laugh at what I
say next, I will die.
For I am about to say
something very serious,
perhaps shocking.
Marge, my darling,
I want you
to meet with me again.
That doesn't shock me.
Away from prying eyes
at my apartment,
the Fiesta Terrace.
Marge, speak to me.
Is Thursday okay?
Thank goodness
I drove down that
ironic street.
I made the right decision
to stay with my Homie
and there was no harm done.
So if you kind of
mentally snip out the part
where I already had a husband,
that's my idea of romance.
Marge, I want you
to stop seeing this Jacques.
You can let him down gently.
But over the next
couple of months,
I want you to break it off.
Uh, okay, Homer.
That was
a close one, kids.
Okay, Marge,
as long as we're
traumatizing the kids,
I have a scandalous story
of my own.
Gentlemen,
I'd like you to meet your
new co-worker, Mindy Simmons.
I think she has a degree
in engineering or something.
Hi. How's it going?
- Pleased to meet you.
- Yeah. Ditto.
Hi. Huh?
Homer, what's
the matter?
Ain't you never seen
a naked chick
riding a clam before?
Got to go!
I made it the whole day
without seeing her again.
I mean, hello!
I guess we'll be
going down together...
I mean, getting off togeth...
I mean...
That's okay.
I'll just push the button
for the stimulator...
I mean elevator.
Think unsexy thoughts,
think unsexy thoughts...
Well, this
is my floor.
See you tomorrow.
I tried to avoid her,
but we were sent to
a nuclear convention
in Capital City together.
TV's there,
bathroom's there,
and there's your
king-sized bed for...
Hubba, hubba.
Stop that. I love my wife
and family.
All I'm gonna use this bed
for is sleeping, eating,
and maybe building
a little fort.
That's it.
Homer.
I got a really wicked idea
that could get us
into a lot of trouble.
Mindy. We have to fight
our temptation.
No, Homer.
Let's do it.
Let's call room service!
Someone is charging room service
to the company, sir.
Well, we'll just see about that.
Fly, my pretties.
Fly!
Continue the research.
Thanks for poisoning
the planet, bastard!
Get bent.
No more Chernobyls!
- Go to hell!
- Ah!
I was doing my best
to resist her,
but at dinner, the fortune
cookie predicted doom.
This was a really nice
night, Homer.
Yeah, yeah.
What's wrong?
Oh, yeah.
Like you don't know.
We're gonna have sex.
Well... we don't have to.
Yes, we do.
The cookie told me so.
Well, desserts
aren't always right.
But they're so sweet.
Homer...
you know how I feel,
so... it... it's up to you.
Look in your heart.
I think you'll see
what you want.
Oh, baby.
This was
a wonderful idea, Homie.
What happened to Mindy?
Yes, what did happen to her?
She hit the bottle pretty hard
and lost her job.
Hmm. Good.
Does anyone else
have a love story?
Yes, I do. And just like
your love stories,
it's tragic and filled with
hurt feelings and scars
that will never heal.
It started,
appropriately enough,
with an innocent boy being
embarrassed on Valentine's Day.
Poor Ralph.
Here you go, Ralph.
You choo-choo-choose me?
Happy Valentine's.
It was an unusually warm.
February 14,
so the children walked home
without jackets.
Can I walk you home...
valentine?
Sure, I guess.
That valentine
sure was funny.
Glad you liked it.
It says,
"choo-choo-choose me"
and there's a picture
of a train.
Yeah, nice gag.
Uh... so...
do you like... stuff?
The doctor said I wouldn't
have so many nosebleeds
if I kept my finger
out of there.
Well, here's my house.
Oh, no.
It's a package from Ralph.
Oh, a Malibu Stacy
convertible.
"Look in the tunk."
He must mean trunk.
Tickets to
the Krusty anniversary show!
It's the Krusty The Clown
29th Anniversary Show!
Hey!
Thank you! Thank you!
Lisa, do you want
a bite of my ice cream?
No, thanks.
Send it this way, boy.
- Whoops.
- Aww...
Oh... nothing
gets chocolate out.
See?
Now for my favorite part
of the show.
What's that say?
"Talk to the audience"?
Oh, God, this is always death.
All right.
Oh, no. Please don't
show me with Ralph.
- What's your name, son?
- Ralph.
And is this
your girlfriend, Ralph?
Yes. I love Lisa Simpson,
and when I grow up,
I'm going to marry her.
No!
Now you listen to me!
I don't like you!
I never liked you!
And the only reason I gave you
that stupid Valentine
was 'cause
nobody else would!
Watch this, Lis.
You can actually pinpoint
the second
when his heart
rips in half.
And... now.
Lisa, not all romances
turn out that way.
Bart, do you have
a love story
that doesn't end
in heartbreak?
Yes, I do.
The only girl I ever loved
invited me up to
the tree house.
She had something
very important to tell me.
I'm so happy.
I just had
to tell someone.
I have a boyfriend.
You won't be
needing this.
Wait. That did end
in heartbreak.
Thanks for opening up
old wounds, Mom.
Well, as Jerry Lee Lewis
would say,
"There's a whole lot
of frowning going on."
Mom, doesn't any love story
have a happy ending?
Of course.
Remember when...
your aunt Selma got married?
Oh, oh, good.
Soon I will kill you.
Wait, wait. That's no good.
I know. Your grandfather.
Remember?
It all started
on an outing for dinner.
Say, I've got a neat idea.
Why don't you go in
and pick up my mother
and we'll all go out
to dinner?
I'll be back in a jiffy.
That's not my mother.
I'll be back
in a jiffy.
Can I come too?
They hit it off
right away,
but there
were rivals
for the fair
lady's hand.
My favorite song.
This is so nice.
I can't remember
when I felt this young.
I really can't.
Say, sport,
mind if I have the next dance?
What the...
Don't sneak up on a...
Oh, you...
No need for the blown gasket,
Charlie.
I'll have her back
in one piece.
But, in the end,
just when things
looked worst,
true love triumphed.
Do you, Jacqueline Bouvier,
take this man
to be your lawfully
wedded husband?
Oh, Monty,
my favorite song.
I specifically requested
no romantic music.
Mrs. Bouvier!
Honey, are you sure you want
to be Mrs. Montgomery Burns?
Wouldn't you rather be
Mrs. Abraham J. Simpson?
No.
I don't want to be either.
Hot diggety damn!
That's good enough for me.
That doesn't seem
like a happy ending.
That seems more like a detached
tale of modern alienation.
I give up.
Did anybody learn anything
about love tonight?
I learned it screws
everybody up.
There's that side of it,
but there's also...
Help me out here, Lisa.
Sorry, Mom. I've decided to
save my love for someone
who's guaranteed
not to reject me.
Soon, Corey, soon.
Well, kids, I tried.
But maybe you're right.
Wait a minute, Marge.
Love isn't hopeless.
Look, maybe I'm no
expert on the subject,
but there was one time
I got it right.
Gee, Artie...
Artie, wait. I don't know.
I mean,
it was a beautiful evening.
- Let's not ruin it.
- Just this...
Artie, please.
Come on, kiss me.
- Oh, Artie...
- Please?
No, really, I mean it!
Now stop it!
I'm sorry, Marge.
Take me home, Artie.
Marge, I would
appreciate it
if you didn't tell anybody
about my busy hands.
Not so much for myself,
but I am so respected
it would damage
the town to hear it.
Good night.
Yeah, right.
Shut up!
I'm over as far as I can go.
All right! All right!
I'll walk in the mud!
- Homer?
- Marge?
- Yeah. You want a ride?
- Sure.
You know, Homer,
when I got home,
I realized who I should have
gone to the prom with.
Who? Oh.
Hi, prom date.
Marge, pour vous.
Why so glum?
I got a problem.
Once you stop this car,
I'm gonna hug you
and kiss you,
and then I'll never
be able to let you go.
Ah, your first kiss.
But not the last.
Mmm... Homie.
- Mmm...
See, kids?
That's what I meant
by romance.
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.