(SINGING) The Simpsons
(TIRES SCREECHING)
D'oh!
(SCREAMS)
Ripped By mstoll
Children, we have a special
treat today. Willie!
(CHILDREN CHEERING)
(ALL GROANING)
(ALL GASPING)
WOMAN;
Welcome to Diversity Tales.
(ALL GROANING)
Enjoy your
multicultural hooey!
(LAUGHS)
WOMAN: It was the
Feast of the Sea Lion
Who Would Not Share.
Come, Brother Titi. Let us
collect cha-cha sticks.
I will make a headdress
for the wedding
of Earth Turtle
and Moon Mongoose.
You don't need
a headdress.
Your most beautiful costume
is your self-esteem.
(WOMAN READING)
What is this crap?
This is worse than
Wheelchair-Nocchio.
Yeah? Well, if you
don't like the movie,
feel free to stare out the window.
(LAUGHS)
(CAR POPS)
Hey, crypt keeper, I like
your Dodge Scare-a-van!
(ALL LAUGH)
How dare you mock
my mobile-a-mobile?
It was the first
car to outrun a man.
A caveman!
(ALL LAUGHING)
I thought of that because I
slept in a cave last night.
(HUFFS) Of all the...
I will not be lampooned by school children!
Kill them, Smithers!
Uh, you could just
buy a new car, sir.
Well, whatever's easier.
A new car? May I
suggest an Oldsmobile?
Mr. Bums sucks!
(LAUGHING)
I won't forget who mocked me!
I'm taking your picture!
Now hold perfectly
still for 78 minutes.
(SNORING)
(HOMER HUMMING)
Doo-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo!
Simpson!
Charge!
I mean, yes, sir?
I just bought a new car.
A nice foreign number.
The Lamborgotti Fasterossa.
A Lamborgotti Fasterossa?
That's the car I think about
when I make love to my wife.
Yes. I need you to pick up my
car at the factory in Italy
and ship it
directly back to me.
I'll save thousands
in taxes.
You're sending me to Italy?
Yes.
Can I take my family?
Sure.
Do I have to
hang outwith them?
It would be nice.
(GROANS)
Oh.
Mmm? (STRUGGLES)
Hey, that guy in first class is
taking a TV out of his armrest.
What's in you?
(GRUNTS AND GROANS)
A bunch of stupid cables.
(GRUNTS)
Hey, Brandine! The kids
just got a new playhouse!
Cletus, you are the most wonderful
husband and son I ever had.
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
What's with the Canadian
flag on your backpack?
Well, some people in Europe
have the impression
that America has made some stupid
choices in the past, oh, five years.
So for the next week,
I'm from Canada.
Uh, I think Dad may
blow your cover.
That flag is mine!
Don't mess with Texas!
Shock and awe, losers!
Shock and awe!
Your car, she's coming
off the assembly line.
(MACHINE WHIRRING)
This car is the ultimate marriage
of design and technology.
Ooh, marriage!
Now we have to drive
it straight to Rome
where it will be shipped to Mr.
Burns in Springfield.
Gee, I wish we could explore
a little more of Italy.
Marge, are you encouraging
me to be irresponsible?
Why don't you encourage him to
get us some health insurance?
Why you little... (GRUNTS)
(CHOKES)
(BOTH CHOKING)
Ow! D'oh!
(GRUNTING)
(BOTH GROANING)
So, first time in Italy?
HOMER: Wow.
I've seen photos of this.
But you can't really experience
it until you're here!
A McDonald's where
you can get booze!
(GULPING)
Dad, don't you want to turn
around and see the tower?
Eh, there's a picture
of it on my cup.
When Mount Vesuvius
erupted,
people were overcome
by volcanic ash so fast
that they were frozen in
whatever position they were in
at the moment
of their death.
Savages.
We've passed the Ponte
Vecchio Bridge three times.
I think we're lost.
Let me check the navigation system.
(CLICKS)
Says here we should turn left
at a fat chick in a tutu
being fed by a midget.
That's a DVD of
a Fellini movie.
(CARNIVAL MUSIC PLAYING)
I get it. The midget
represents dwarves.
Dad, cheese truck!
(ALL SCREAMING)
(GASPS) Mozzarella!
Parmigiano! Provolone!
Pecorino! Gorgonzola!
Fontina!
Taleggio! Bocconcini!
(CLATTERS)
(ALL SCREAM)
LISA: Mortadella!
(CRASHES)
Don't worry. We got
the cheese insurance.
It doesn't cover
mortadella.
(GROANS) No!
(ALL GRUNTING)
Stupid Italy! I wish
you'd never been unified
by Victor Emmanuel ll!
If only you'd stayed a loose
confederation of city states
trading with each other
and occasionally warring.
Maybe there's a mechanic
in this Tuscan village.
(LIQUID SPLASHING)
Hey, do you know anything about
fixing sports cars? Scusi?
It's a Lamborgotti
Fasterossa XT 550
with ABS
Sport Tech Package!
(SIGHS)
Americano?
Americana? What the hell
could that mean?
Why can't you people learn
to speak my language?
I learned to eat your food!
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
Hey, she says the mayor
speaks English.
I honor you
and your country.
(GASPS)
"Kentucky"?
In Italian
this means "whore!"
(GRUNTS)
Excuse me, Mr. Mayor? They
say you speak English.
Indeed I do.
ALL: Sideshow Bob!
(GASPS) The Simpsons!
(ALL SCREAMING TOGETHER)
BART: Sideshow Bob?
Of all the regioni in all the
villaggi in all of Italia,
you had to be
I! mayors of this one!
I can assure you I'm as sorry to
see you as you are to see me.
How did you wind up here?
Yes. Tell us your story.
But ii better have a beginning,
a middle, and an end.
And you'd better make us
root for the protagonist!
My tale begins after I had once
again attempted to murder Bart.
Okay. So far
I'm rooting for you.
I needed a fresh start,
but where?
Not in this lifetime!
Damn it!
Never!
Now cut that out!
Ah, Tuscany. Fortune is
finally smiling upon me.
(GRUMBLING)
I left my past
behind and moved
to the small
village of Salsiccia.
Acceptance came slowly.
It's pronounced “buongiorno.“
Your mouth is getting lazy
on the second syllable.
Here. Let me guide you.
But that all changed
when the grape harvest began.
(CROWD GRUNTING)
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
(ALL GASPING)
(SINGING) These feet are
made for stomping
And that's just
what they'll do
One of these days these feet
will make chianti out of you!
Ready, feet? Start stomping!
(HUMMING)
(CROWD CHEERING)
it was the biggest
harvest ever.
(CORK POPS) Never had I
felt such acceptance.
The next spring, the contadini
elected me their mayor.
But! won more than
the love of a town.
Roberto, amore!
This is my bride Francesca.
And my son, Gino.
Holy moley!
I always thought you were, you
know, out, loud, and proud!
Well, I experimented
in college, as one does.
Yeah. I never
went to college.
Stop the presses.
Hello. I'm Marge.
This is my husband Homer,
my daughters
Lisa and Maggie,
and my son
Bart Simpson.
Bart Simpson?
The name Roberto cries
when he has the bad dream.
Bart Simpson! Bart Simpson!
Ban Simpson!
I make like my daddy! I cut, cut...
(CHUCKLES)
Yes. Ban and I used
to go fly-fishing together.
Die, Bart! Die, Bart!
(GRUMBLING)
You shall all slay
for dinner
and tell me more
about my wonderful Roberto.
(SIGHS) He makes love like a
man who just got out of jail.
Mmm. (KISSES)
(CHUCKLES) Yes, yes,
you crave my skillful touch.
Now go. Take the boy. And shut the door.
I'll rock your world anon.
Simpsons, I beg of you,
please don't destroy the new
life I've created here.
Surely even the most heinous
criminal deserves a seventh chance!
Bob, you haven't told
your wife
about all the terrible
things you've done?
Yeah. I tell Marge
everything.
Not necessarily in words,
but in body language.
You know, sneaking
around and such.
Bob, your family
will find out the truth.
Sooner or later,
you'll try lo kill me again.
Watch. I'll prove it.
Come on, Bob. Slice,
dice, and serve on rice.
(CHUCKLES) You little scamp.
You know, you'll make some
murderer very happy one day.
But it shan't be me.
Bart, Bob
is a family man now.
You can't be a bad person
if you have a family.
And literature is filled
with tales of redemption
from Jean Valjean, to the voice
of Buzz Lightyear, Tim Allen.
All right, Bob,
we won't tell your
beautiful new family
that you're a homicidal
psychopath
if you fix up our car.
Now, I can't undo
the past.
But I can try to
make it up to you.
My humble little
town is at your service.
Questi sono i miei amici,
i Simpsons!
(CROWD CHEERING)
(WHISPERS) Dad, don't
act like Mussolini.
Ooh, I thought I was
doing Donald Trump.
Hmph-hmph!
Here's a cute fact.
This sausage shop has been
grinding the same family of pigs
for six hundred years.
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
Prego.
Si, si.
Ooh.
(GOBBLING)
And he kisses you
with that mouth?
(MUFFLED)
I love you, Marge!
(KISSING NOISES)
(LAUGHING)
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
(CHILDREN GIGGLING)
(LAUGHING)
He's so wonderful. They
must miss him in America.
Uh, well...
(GUNS COCK)
Eat justice, Sideshow Bob!
Chief, I tried to warn you. Sideshow
Bob hasn't lived here for months.
Oh, God, am I sorry!
(CHUCKLES SHEEPISHLY)
Oh, hey, is that
a Penn State banner?
Because, um,
my cousin went there.
Did you know him?
Mark Wiggum? Fat kid?
Played a lot of Tetris.
(GLASS CLINKS)
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
We are here to honor my old
friends, the Simpsons.
Tomorrow they return to America,
taking with them my gratitude,
my friendship, and my heartfelt
wish that they never return.
And now, mangiate!
No wine for her!
She's only eight!
Marge, don't be
so Olive Garden.
Yeah, this is Italy. Look, the
town drunk is two years old!
(SINGING) Hey, mambo
Mambo Italiano!
(BURPS)
(GULPS)
Bob, your generosity and abbondanza
have touched our hearts.
(CHEERING)
Bravo! Bravo! Bravissimo!
Ooopsie.
I'll just get it
outwith more wine.
See? lt's fine.
Go on. Go on with the thing.
Hmm.
It's obvious why Bob is a vaunted
pillar of your community.
Yeah. But he's a wanted
killer in our community!
(LAUGHS)
He deserves to be
hailed at this wingding.
More like jailed
at Sing Sing!
Time for bed now.
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
Drunken children
tell the ugliest lies.
(CHUCKLES)
Mmm. (GIGGLES)
(SCREAMS)
(CROWD GASPS)
(SCREAMS) Sideshow Bob!
Sideshow Bob?
(SPEAKS ITALIAN)
BOTH: Hmm?
Roberto, is this true? You
tried to make the murder?
But darling, the boy
drove me to murder
by exonerating a harlequin
who I framed for robbery
at the Kwik-E-Mart!
Oh, it all sounds
so stupid.
You have brought shame upon our
humble, Mafia-controlled village!
You are welcome
in Salsiccia no more!
(GRUNTS)
(BLEATS)
(SNARLS)
Uh-oh.
He's getting that
stabby look.
Simpson family,
I hereby swear a vendetta!
"Vendetta" means "vendetta!"
(ALL SCREAMING)
Boy, that Sideshow Bob goes from
zero to murder awfully fast.
At least this time it was
Lisa who ruined Bob's life.
(GROANS) I feel so sick.
(CHUCKLES)
It's called
a hangover, sweetie.
And it's an unavoidable
part of life.
MR. BURNS:
Simpson! Simpson!
Where is my roadster? You
were due back a month ago.
Mr. Burns, we may be experiencing
some technical difficulties.
Ah...
(HUFFS)
Sideshow Bob!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(GASPS) Dad, you're driving
on an ancient Roman aqueduct!
What am I supposed
to use it for?
Transporting water
to distant urban centers?
Uh-oh.
Lazy Romans!
(ALL SCREAMING)
(BANG)
ALL: Huh?
HOMER: Everyone remember
where we parked.
(WHIMPERS)
(GRUNTS)
Come on!
(CRYING)
Why do I keep
trying to kill them?
Roberto!
Francesca,
you've come to me!
Well, you've caught me
at the right time
because I swear never to raise
this hand in vengeance again.
Hey, no, Roberto.
If the Simpsons
have dishonored you,
they have dishonored
our family.
And we shall take
revenge as a family.
Vendetta! Vendetta!
Vendetta for mi papa!
Ah! Revenge is a dish
best served
family-style.
(EVIL LAUGH)
(CRYING)
We're in a foreign city,
with no car,
being stalked
by a killer.
I feel like I'm in
The Bourne Identity.
(BRAKES SCREECH)
Hey, Krusty's in an opera
here in Rome.
He can save our lives.
Come on, let's go!
(GROANS) Oh!
Opera? They have that
here, too?
(GROANS)
Let's see... Uh-huh.
I ain't doing that.
That's not funny.
Here we'll change "wealthy merchant"
to "nudist with big rack."
This needs punching up.
That's coming out.
Two acts?
Krusty, you gotta
help us!
I don't do "gotta."
Sideshow Bob has sworn
a vendetta against us!
Vendetta? What's that?
An Italian vending machine?
Ahhh! That's my opening joke,
and my closer, and my saver,
and my topper! (SOBS)
Please help us, Krusty.
We don't want to be the first
Christians to die at the Coliseum.
I'll tell you what.
Put on these costumes.
Go on the stage
and mix in with
the crowd scenes.
He won't kill you in front
of all those witnesses.
Can I be the
Phantom of the Opera?
Dad, the Phantom
isn't in this.
But I do a great
impression of him!
(HUMS)
l am the gayest
super villain ever!
Beware my scented candles!
Ooh. Scented!
(SINGING)
No more Rice Krispies
We are out of Rice Krispies
(SOBS)
(AUDIENCE GASPS)
Hey, don't blame me.
I didn't write this crap.
I can't believe what that clown
is doing to Leoncavallo!
And they call me
a murderer!
Vendetta! Vendetta!
I don't wish to brag.
But he's evil at an
eighth grade level.
Vendetta! Vendetta!
Let's see.
What else we got here.
So I had this
beautiful tour guide, right?
And I tell her,
"I wanna see your Naples."
She slapped me!
(LAUGHS)
We call it Napoli!
Yeah? Well, it sounds like
you're all taking a Napoli!
Know you're out there!
I can hear you being greasy!
Ahhh!
(SINGING OPERA)
(APPLAUSE)
That's so beautiful.
That's Sideshow Bob!
I know. And he's magic!
This is no act! They're
actually trying to kill us!
(AUDIENCE GASPS)
(CONTINUES SINGING OPERA)
(AUDIENCE SIGHS)
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
(EVIL LAUGH)
Quick! Get in!
Krusty, you saved us!
Well, I need someone
to help me
smuggle antiquities
to America.
Everyone break off a piece
and hide it on your person.
Hide it well.
Vendetta! Vendetta!
Vendetta!
Farfalla!
Farfalla vendetta!
GINO: Farfalla vendetta!
Oh, Homie,
isn't Venice romantic?
This gondola ride
was a wonderful idea.
(SINGING)
When a wife looks like that
And her husband's so fat,
that's immoral
When she kisses that jerk
While I do
all the work, that's...
Hey, knock it off!
Mi scusi.
No speak English.
(SINGING)
When a big tub of lard...
Ripped By mstoll