(SINGING) The Simpsons
(SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
(HORN BELLOWING)
(PLAYING DIFFERENT TUNE)
(HONKING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
D'oh!
(EXCLAIMING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Ripped By mstoll
Oh, my God! Everything
we own is in that house!
ANNOUNCER: How often have you
driven by a fire and thought,
“How can this
benefit me?“
Well, think no more
and drive on down
to the Smoke Damage
Outlet Store!
Where there's smoke,
there's bargains!
We've got
fire-damaged furniture,
smoke-damaged
smoke detectors,
action figure puddle, something
we think was an air conditioner,
and boxes and boxes
of “you-figure-it-out. "
Ooh...
ANNOUNCER; Come in today and
meet Smokin' Joe Frazier!
I'm only here because
my name had “Smoke" in it.
ANNOUNCER: Oh, come on. That has
nothing to do with it, Smokin' Joe.
I can send people
to your house. Bad people.
(HUMMING)
Come on! We're going
to that store
before the next commercial
makes me do something else.
Buy the suit off my back,
only $9.95.
Stop, drop, and save.
(CHUCKLES)
(MURMURS)
I've never noticed
that sign before,
and I'm a very
good noticer.
They must've just
made this a toll road.
They can't charge me for
something I use everyday.
What's next?
A spatula tax?
Well, what choice
do you have?
Voilà! Which is
French for ta-da!
Boy, you sure
showed them.
Hey, if she's not paying,
I'm not paying.
And if you’re not paying,
Of course you're not.
We're in the same car.
Oh, I just wanted us
to start talking again.
QUIMBY: No one is using
the tollbooth.
(SNORING)
Damn it. We need those 75¢ to
de-python the town fountain.
(HISSING)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
Get those cheapskates through
that toll by any means necessary.
Got it.
No survivors.
No shooting!
But it's already cocked.
All right, shoot it
in the fireplace.
(CHUCKLING)
(CLANKING)
What the Hello Kitty?
Tire spikes?
Oh, they blocked
my shortcut.
I'm trapped like
the "L" in a BLT.
We've gone over
the spikes, Tim!
We're gonna have
to come up with 75¢!
Don't worry.
This one's on Jesus.
Oh, be cool for once.
(BRAKES SCREECH)
Do it, Marge. Today 75¢,
in five years, 80¢.
(LAUGHING HYSTERICALLY)
Assuming voter approval.
No!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Oh, boy.
My tires have been
severely damaged!
The prophecy
has been fulfilled!
Seymour, get out
and change the tires!
I don't have
four spares, Mother.
You don't have
four anything.
(SINGING) I fell into
a burning ring of fire
I went down, down, down
And the flames went higher
And it burns, burns, burns
The ring of fire
Kent Brockman here
atop Mount Springfield,
where the melting icecap has
revealed a discovery so gruesome
we'll give you a moment to get
the children out of the room!
That's long enough.
Here it is.
A frozen mailman somehow buried
in ice several decades ago.
For further analysis,
here's the one scientist
who's always home
when we call,
Professor John Frink.
Uh, based on
the ice core samples
and the size of the
mailman's bell bottoms,
measure that there,
we have determined
he was frozen
sometime in the 1960s.
Swinging for all
except for me.
I was making napalm
to drop on Da Nang!
The post office has
promised to deliver
every letter in
this 40-year-old mailbag.
So get ready, Mr. Largo.
(CHUCKLES)
You were accepted
to Julliard.
Ah! I got into Julliard?
I could have been second chair
with the Cincinnati Pops!
RALPH: I'm C3-D2!
Shut up! Shut up!
Shut up!
Here you go, pally.
What's this? A letter from 1966?
(LAUGHS)
This says I ain't
allergic to pollen.
So I could've gone to the park
and played with other kids!
I gotta make up
for lost time!
(SINGING) Sitting in a rocking
chair eating baby crackers
Tick-tock, tick-tock,
tick-tock, banana
A-B-C-D-E-F-G Wash those
June bugs off of me
Yeah, I got a 40-year-old letter
here for Mrs. Abraham Simpson.
My grandma? I haven't
seen her in years.
She ran away.
Ran away from all this, huh?
What a fool.
Hey, Grampa, we got a
letter for Grandma.
Open it up. This may be my last
chance to invade her privacy.
"My dearest Mona,
"you've just left my arms
to return to your husband, Abe,
"and already I ache for you."
Mona cheated on me?
I don't know how
she found the time
with her late night
pottery classes
and supermarket trips
that took all weekend!
Lisa, I'm not sure that letter
is age-appropriate reading.
Why can't the government edit
our mail like other countries?
(MURMURING)
Uh-oh.
"I know I'm just a lifeguard but
I want you to run away with me.
"If you don't reply
to this letter,
"I'll know that you've
chosen to stay with Abe.
"But I know in my heart that the
baby you're carrying is mine."
(ALL GASP)
"Love always, M."
That's ridiculous!
That was my baby
in her belly!
Look how happy
we were.
What the...
(GROANS)
Homer, that means your dad
might not be your dad.
I don't care what
that letter said.
This man raised
me single-handedly.
When I think of all the
things he's done for me...
The many times he...
Lifeguard, huh?
Mmm...
So this guy might
be my real father.
And his name
starts with
Moleman? Mister Burns?
(GASPS)
M. Night Shyamalan?
That would be a twist worthy of
his increasingly lousy films!
Of course
I'm your father!
Here. Mush up your face
and you look just like me.
See?
Yeah, but that also works
with the dog's butt.
Oh, hello, handsome!
Well, this whole
fatherhood issue
could be resolved
with a simple DNA test.
Aw, nertz to that!
Homer, l fed you and clothed
you until you were 13!
If that's not a father,
I don't know what is!
I'll be waiting
for your apology
on the "old man bench"
at the mall!
I sit by the trash so people
have to come up to me.
Finished your soda, eh?
Oh, your hair's looking
sharp from the back.
Homie, what's wrong? Did those
pork chops give you a tummy ache?
The only tummy ache
is in my head.
I can't stop wondering
who my real father might be.
(SINGING) If you're lost, you
can look And you will find me
Time after time
If you fall I will catch you
I'll be waiting
Time after time
If you're lost, you can look
And you will find me
Time after time
(GASPS) There's only one
lifeguard whose name begins with
Mason Faibanks.
His hobbies are philandering,
writing letters,
and making up
for lost time.
"Okay, until you're sure this guy's
cool, stick to your cover story."
"Oh, that sounds hard."
"Just do it!"
Can I help you?
Uh, yes, I'm a reporter
with a local paper.
I'm doing a story on people
who wear sweaters.
Do you mind if I ask
you some questions?
I'd be delighted.
But I must warn you I don't
wear a sweater every day.
Interesting.
(CLOCK TICKING)
So I infer from
all the knickknacks
you're some
sort of fruitcake?
(CHUCKLES) No. Actually, I salvage
valuables from sunken ships.
Some call me
a treasure hunter.
Oh, that is so cool!
Ooh, a dish
of shrunken heads!
Those are raisins.
So you don't have
any shrunken heads?
Well, my hat size
is a number six.
(SCREAMS)
That is small, right?
It's smaller than average.
(SCREAMING)
And this is
the lady in my life.
Uh...
You know
it's a boat, right?
Indeed I do.
I loved a real woman a long time
ago but, uh, it didn't work out.
(GASPS) Well, uh, I'm sure
my listeners would love
to know the story
behind that name.
Listeners? I thought you
worked for a newspaper.
No. Uh, I said I worked
for a radio station.
980 on the AM dial, but
number one with our viewers.
Viewers? Wouldn't that be
for a TV station?
Ah, well, l...
I think you're my pappy!
What?
I found this letter you wrote
to my mom, Mona Simpson.
Dear God! I always dreamed
this day would come.
And now that it's here,
there are so many feelings,
I...
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
Oh, possible Daddy!
Mwah!
I'm sorry. I got a little
carried away there.
Perfectly all right.
Here's your gum back.
ANNOUNCER: Springfield Public
Access Television presents...
The Bully Corner, with
Jimbo, Dolph, and Kearney.
Good evening,
dumbasses.
Tonight, our guest is Oscar
nominee William H. Macy.
Welcome.
Thanks for having
me on, guys.
You know, these public access shows
remind me of independent film.
Special people,
not special effects.
Big hearts,
not big budgets.
Very well put!
Now get him!
(ALL GRUNT)
Hey!
So tell us, what's next
for William H. Macy?
Besides bleeding.
(GRUNTS)
WILLIAM: You know
Neve Campbell?
(ALL GRUNTING)
Marge, I found
my real father!
His name is
Mason Fairbanks!
He has a knife just for cheese,
and he talks like this.
(BRITISH ACCENT) "Homer,
please do that in the loo."
Oh, Homie, you just
met this British man.
It's too soon to get
so emotionally invested.
Hmm, honey,
you've given me a lot
to think about tomorrow,
when we're on daddy's boat!
(FOG HORN BLOWS)
Mr. Fairbanks,
looking at your boat,
I gotta say Grandma
bet on the wrong horse.
Now, Bart, over the years, I've come to
learn that the most valuable treasure
is right here
on this map.
These waters are home to a treasure
lost hundreds of years ago.
The famed emeralds
of Piso Mojado.
You know, if I was born
three months later,
emerald would be
my birthstone.
Yes. Fate has a strange
sense of humor.
The emeralds were nestled in
the bosom of a Spanish galleon
returning home
from the Caribbean.
(THUNDER CRASHING)
We must pray to
Santa Maria to save us.
(PRAYING IN SPANISH)
(THUNDER CRASHING)
One of you
was not praying!
It was me! I was thinking
of a joke I heard!
Why you little...
(CHOKING)
And now that treasure
is somewhere down there.
Wow. That story
had everything.
Action, treasure,
water, a guy...
Would you like to come
to our house for dinner?
I'd be delighted.
I've dined with the Prince of
Wales and with killer whales.
But only the latter knew how
to chew without humming.
(ALL CHUCKLING)
(ALL GASP)
Mmm...
Listen, old timer, I'd like
you to meet Mason Fairbanks.
You! First you stole my wife and now
you're trying to steal my family!
Perhaps I couldn't
have stolen anyone
had you given them, uh,
what they needed.
I was busy telling young
people to get a haircut!
Mason, come see my room!
Homer, look what
this is doing to Grampa.
We have to settle this question once
and for all with a paternity test.
I'll take any test
you want.
Eye test, pap test,
memory test, memory test,
Vinny Testaverde,
Ferrari Testarossa.
Grampa, stop.
Never!
President's
Physical Fitness Test,
Sealtest ice cream,
Testors airplane glue.
HOMER: Ahh...
Now, Homer,
I'll compare your sample
to the ones from Grampa
and Mister Fairbanks.
And then, bingo!
Who's your daddy
will become abundantly clear.
I've prepared a T-shirt for you
that covers either eventuality.
(LAUGHING)
I have the results.
Oh, God.
Whatever happens, Abe,
I hope we can be civil.
Aw, poop in your fist!
At least I can make both.
Oh...
Homer's biological father
is Mason Fairbanks!
(ALL GASP)
Who's Mason Fairbanks?
This guy.
Whoo-hoo!
See, Abe?
We're still visiting you
even though we have
no biological obligation.
You've said that
three times already.
Well, then you think
of something.
I guess Homer
couldn't make it, huh?
No. But he told us
to say "hi."
Hi.
So what setting
is that fan on?
Medium.
Hmm.
I would've guessed low.
You would've
guessed wrong.
Today I'm filled with joy.
Searching for treasure
with my long lost son.
My dream for each of you is that you
find the happiness I feel today.
And my dream is to someday
wear a real wetsuit
instead of one that
is just painted on.
Missed a spot.
There we go.
These waters contain some of Mother
Nature's most stunning creatures.
(LAUGHS) That's what you get
for being luminous, jerks.
Homer, look!
The treasure
of Piso Mojado!
(STATIC CRACKLES)
Hey, guys.
We found the treasure.
When I get to shore, I'm
bringing it right to the bar.
We'll see you soon, Homer. We
got somebody else coming in.
SEYMOUR: This is W-A-3-Q-I-Z.
Do you read me?
AGNES: Seymour, isn't it about
time you made a real friend?
Mother, please. I'm communicating
with my fellow hams.
AGNES: How do I talk? Push
this button here? (STATIC)
You're all losers!
Oh, which way
did Mason go?
That must be him over there.
D'oh!
What do I do?
(BUZZING)
(SCREAMS)
(DINGS)
(SIGHS)
(BUZZING)
(SCREAMS)
(GROANS)
Daddy... Daddy...
(ABE CHUCKLES)
Grab Daddy's keys.
(GIGGLES)
(CHUCKLES)
Grab Daddy's keys.
(GIGGLES)
I love that little guy.
(ENGINE STARTS)
What the heck...
(TIRES SCREECHING)
HOMER: I drew
this picture of you.
Aw, it's beautiful.
Homer, on your wedding day,
I want you to have this.
It may not be much.
But it's all I've got.
That is so sweet.
(SHRIEKING)
I gave you everything
and it still wasn't enough.
(MUMBLES)
Daddy... Dad...
(GROANING)
(MUMBLING)
Dad, you've been in
a coma for three days.
They had to feed
you through a tube.
Oh, Homie, I always believed
you were gonna make it
no matter what that pushy
casket salesman said.
Well, Homer, now that
you're alive again,
I'll leave you
with your real family.
Wait. Can we have
a moment in private?
Of course.
As I lay dying on
the ocean floor,
I remembered everything
you've done for me.
To hell with
that stupid DNA test
and its 99.99997% accuracy.
You're my dad
and I love you.
I love you, too, Homer.
BOTH: Oh...
And now there's something
I've gotta tell you.
I really am your father.
(GROANING)
But how?
ABE: After seeing how happy you
were with Horatio-Homewrecker,
I made a decision.
I switched the names
on the DNA samples.
Then I put my name first on
the fist for a new heart.
(LAUGHING)
My old one's fine
but you never know.
Only a true father would
lead his son to believe
he belonged
to someone else.
Aw, Dad!
Oh, Homer.
Now why don't you
stay for dinner?
It would be
my pleasure, son.
Send up two hams.
Hey, this one's cold.
(GRUNTS)
Listen, l wanted to ask you
if you could do something
my former father
never did for me.
Anything, son.
Teach me that the stove is hot.
Very well.
(HOMER SCREAMS)
MASON: No, Homer.
Mustn't touch.
(HOMER SCREAMS)
MASON: I said no, Homer.
MASON: All right, nap time!
HOMER; (WHINING)
But I'm not tired.
Ripped By mstoll