The Simpsons.
Looks like you
got a leak.
Could you start
fixing it pretty soon?
The basement is
getting awfully flooded
and I think
the cat's down there.
Yeah, I probably won't be able
to get the parts I need
for two... three weeks.
And that's if I order them
today, which I won't.
Oh, dear.
Emergency call.
Gotta go.
What should we do
until you get back?
Put a pan down there.
Oh, it didn't work.
Lousy traffic jams.
The traffic report will
get me out of this one.
This is Arnie Pie.
Looks like we got
a little accident
that's backing
traffic up
as far as
this reporter can see.
Hi, Dad.
Hey, how come you guys got
such great parking places?
It's a secret.
Shh! Shut up.
All right, Econo-save,
you just made the list.
Hey, will you guys
help me fix my...
Hey, how come you guys
got better chairs than me?
It's a secret.
Shh! Shut up.
Hey, you guys want
to go bowling tonight?
Nah, we're busy.
Yeah, we got things to do.
Like what?
It's a secret.
Shut up.
So anyway, Lenny and Karl
are never around on Wednesdays,
and they don't tell me
where they go.
It's like a conspiracy.
A conspiracy, eh?
You think they might be involved
in the Kennedy assassination
in some way?
I do now.
Anyway, I'm going to follow them
tonight and see where they go.
Oh, Homer, don't start
stalking people again.
It's so illegal.
Remember when you were stalking.
Charles Kuralt because you
thought he dug up your garden?
Well, something did.
I don't want you
stalking anyone tonight.
Oh, okay, have it
your own way, Marge.
I'll be back in a minute.
I'm going outside...
to...
stalk...
Lenny and Karl...
All I had to do is
follow the yellow drip road.
There's our
secret meeting place.
- Yes, let's go inside.
- Sounds good.
Whoop.
I can see everything.
And they're none the wiser.
- An intruder.
- He will pay the ultimate price.
Yes, the ultimate price.
Get out of here.
I saw weird stuff
in that place last night.
Weird, strange, sick, twisted,
eerie, godless, evil stuff,
and I want in.
We don't know what
you're talking about, Homer.
And you can't join
the Stonecutters
because it's too exclusive.
Well, it was a real nice secret
organization we had once.
Stonecutters, eh?
How do I join?
There are only two ways
to gain membership.
Be the son of a Stonecutter...
Next.
Or save the life
of a Stonecutter.
Hey!
I saved your life.
That egg sandwich could have
killed you by cholesterol.
Forget it, Homer.
While it has been established
that eggs contain cholesterol,
it has not yet been proven conclusively
that they actually raise the level
of serum cholesterol
in the human bloodstream.
So one of those
Egg Council creeps
got to you too, huh?
You got it all wrong, Homer.
It's not like that.
You'd better run, egg!
Why don't people
like me, Marge?
Everyone likes you.
You're a wonderful person.
Why don't
those stupid idiots
let me in their crappy club
for jerks?
I'm sure it's nothing
personal, Homer.
It is.
It's been happening
to me all my life.
Hey, Billy! Hey, Joey!
Come on in.
There's plenty of room.
- Sorry. Not you, Homer.
- Why not?
But you let in Homer Glumplet.
It says "No Homers."
We're allowed
to have one.
I felt so left out.
Kids can be so cruel.
We can?
Thanks, Mom!
Ow, cut it out, Bart!
I'd give anything to get in
to the Stonecutters.
What do they do
there, Dad?
I'm a member.
What do they do?
What don't they do?
Oh, they do
so many things, they never stop.
Oh, the things they do there...
My stars!
You don't know
what they do there, do you?
Not as such, no.
I'm a Stonecutter.
Dad, remember
those self-hypnosis classes
we took to help
us ignore Grampa?
Do I ever.
It's five years later,
and I still think I'm a chicken.
- I'm a chicken, Marge.
- I know, I know.
Maybe we should be listening
to him, now.
I'm a member.
- Huh? What?
- What? Huh?
You're a member of
the Stonecutters, Grampa?
Oh, sure, let's see.
I'm an Elk, a Mason,
a communist.
I'm the president
of the Gay and Lesbian Alliance
for some reason.
Ah! Here it is!
The Stonecutters!
Oh! This is it!
My ticket in.
They have to let me join
if I'm the son of a member.
I'll take this
communist one too.
Coming through.
Can't throw me out.
My father's a member.
- I'm in. I'm in.
- Okay, okay. Homer, you're in.
Just don't point
that thing at me.
Ah, thanks, Lenny.
When am I going
to be initiated?
As soon as Number One gets here.
Number One?
What kind of stupid
wiener name is that?
Hello. My name is Number One.
And so forth.
We call each other by number,
not by name.
Carl is number 14.
I'm number 12.
Burnsie is number 29.
You outrank Mr. Burns here?
Sure, watch.
Hey, 29, get over here.
Thank you, sir.
May I have another?
Patience, Monty.
Climb the ladder.
Is he the leader?
Of this chapter.
There are chapters
all over the world.
And it has been foretold
that someday
a chosen one will...
Okay, okay. I didn't ask
for your life story.
Let the initiation begin.
All Stonecutters must take
the leap of faith.
If you survive
this five-story plunge,
your character will be proven.
Happy landings.
I think
I have to do it again.
My blindfold came off.
This ritual is called
"Crossing the Desert."
And this we call
"The Unblinking Eye."
Hey, have you ever noticed
that the "Crossing the Desert".
Is a lot like
"The Unblinking Eye"?
It's exactly like
"The Wreck of the Hesperus."
And now the final ordeal.
"The Paddling of the
Swollen Ass with Paddles."
And by the sacred parchment,
I swear
that if I reveal the secrets
of the Stonecutters
may my stomach become bloated
and my head be plucked
of all but three hairs.
Um, I think he should have
to take a different oath.
Everyone takes
the same oath.
Welcome to the club,
number 908.
You have joined the Sacred Order
of the Stonecutters
who since ancient times have
split the rocks of ignorance
that obscure the light
of knowledge and truth.
Now let's all get drunk
and play ping-pong.
'Cause he's already
kind of heavy, you know, and...
Well, to be honest
I never got around to ordering
that part for you.
So it's still going
to be a couple of weeks.
Oh, really?
Yes.
Really?
Yes. Yes!
But what if I were
to shake your hand
in this wise?
Wah-wah-weh!
Whoa. I didn't realize
you were a member.
So long, suckers.
Same old space, huh, Dad?
Yep, but they gave me
these roller blades
so I can glide
to the front door.
Whoa. Whoa.
Whoa!
Sweet.
Jealous?
Well, no.
We've got the same chair.
You're jealous.
Your membership pack.
What's this?
Put that sticker on your car
so you won't get any tickets.
This other one keeps paramedics
from stealing your wallet
while they're
working on you.
Oh, and don't bother
calling 911 anymore.
Here's the real number.
I still don't believe
all the Founding Fathers
were Stonecutters.
That's because you trust
your stupid school books.
Here's what
really happened
at the signing of the
Declaration of Independence.
And a nation is born.
Now let us party
like 'twas 1799!
Quaff! Quaff! Quaff! Quaff!
Quaff! Quaff! Quaff!
Please, sir,
you're destroying
my establishment.
We just created
the greatest
democracy on earth,
you low-life commoner!
You want to see how Davy Crockett
really died at the Alamo?
You must be 18.
Homer, a man who called himself
"you-know-who"
just invited you
to a secret "wink-wink"
at the "you-know-what."
You certainly are popular
now that you're a Stonecutter.
Oh, yeah.
"Beer busts, beer blasts,
keggers, stein hoists,
A.A. meetings,
beer night."
It's wonderful, Marge.
I've never felt so accepted
in all my life.
These people look deep
within my soul
and assign me a number
based on the order
in which I joined.
Who controls
the British crown?
Who keeps
the metric system down?
We do.
Who leaves Atlantis
off the maps?
Who keeps the Martians
under wraps?
We do.
Who holds back
the electric car?
Who makes Steve Guttenberg.
A star?
We do.
Who robs cave fish
of their sight?
Who rigs every Oscar night?
We do.
We do!
Thank you.
Tonight we are here
to commemorate
our glorious society's
1,500th anniversary.
And in honor of this
momentous occasion,
we're having ribs.
Uh-oh. I need a bib.
If I slop any on my shirt,
I could lose the respect
of my beloved brethren.
So let us rejoice
and enjoy our meal
in the shadow of the hallowed
sacred parchment.
- Homer.
- Huh? Oh. Yeah.
- Thanks, Lenny.
- This is terrible.
This is just appalling and outrageous.
What? Did I miss something?
Oh, God!
No! Homer, no!
This is outrageous!
You can't do that. No!
You really are stupid!
And the official
Stonecutter underwear, too.
Please don't kick me out.
This society's everything
to me.
Please give me another chance.
I've learned my lesson!
That's it!
- How can we punish him further?
- Get him out.
- Oh. Sorry.
- Homer Simpson,
for your continuing
and baffling desecration
of our beloved sacred parchment,
you are hereby banished
from the Stonecutters
forever.
And as a final humiliation,
you must walk home naked,
dragging behind you
the Stone of Shame.
The mark!
Oh, that.
It's just a birthmark.
And I'll thank you
not to stare.
He's the chosen one.
You are the chosen one
whom the sacred parchment
prophesied
would lead us to glory!
Now, to the top
of Mount Springfield
for the coronation!
- Remove the Stone of Shame.
- Woo-hoo!
Attach the Stone of Triumph!
Wow.
Mental note: Don't overdo this.
Peekaboo!
I always wondered
if there was a god
and now I know.
There is,
and it's me.
You're not
a god, Homer.
Remember, Dad,
all glory is fleeting.
- So?
- Beware the Ides of March.
- No.
- Dad, I know you think you're happy now,
but it's not gonna
last forever.
- Everything lasts forever.
- Don't you see?
Getting what
you want all the time
will ultimately leave you
unfulfilled and joyless.
Remove the girl.
Dad, you're not
with your Stonecutters now.
There are no lackeys around
to carry out your every...
Another strike
for the chosen one!
- Hurrah!
- Whoo-hoo!
- Well, that's just an excellent break.
- Most assuredly.
- Absolutely.
- Whoo-hoo!
I'm out.
No, no, no,
no, Homer.
You have the royal,
um... sampler.
Oh, I win again, don't I?
Whoo-hoo.
You know, I think you guys
are letting me win.
No! No, no! No! No!
From now on, I want you
to be honest with me.
I mean, I'm not perfect, right?
Run.
The Grand Exalted
Leader requests
a moment of your time.
Class dismissed.
Yay!
Lisa, you were right.
My happiness is fading.
You're experiencing
spiritual emptiness
because your power
has isolated you
from other human beings.
What do you mean, isolated?
Well, maybe you could reach
out to the community
and help other people.
Hmm, I could help others.
I'll get a bunch of monkeys,
dress them up,
and make them reenact the Civil War.
Dad, that doesn't
help people.
Couldn't hurt,
unless the monkeys
started hurting people,
which they almost
certainly would.
Brothers! Brothers!
Brothers, I've learned
a wonderful lesson.
Helping others
makes our own lives better
and makes us better people,
so instead of just shooting
pool and drinking beer,
let us Stonecutters
use what we have
to help the less fortunate.
He's gone mad with power
like that
Albert Schweitzer guy.
Whee!
Ooh, for the love of God!
Somebody get
the jaws of life!
Higher!
Oh, I'll give you higher,
my filthy little urchin.
Oh. You've won this round...
Oh, thank you,
Mr. Simpson.
It looks so much better.
A beautiful sky blue.
You were right, Lisa.
I've never felt
so spiritually fulfilled.
And with my brothers,
the Stonecutters, behind me,
this is the beginning
of a better world for all of us.
- We got to kill him!
- Take it easy, Moe.
Let's hear from
the Stonecutter World Council
- before we act too rashly.
- Kill him!
- Kill the fool!
Afraid I have to disagree
with Orville, Jack, and Mister.
Can't we just do something
to his voice box?
We might as well face the truth.
As long as we're Stonecutters,
he will control our lives.
Maybe, but maybe we don't want
to be Stonecutters no more.
Hey, this much better than
the old Stonecutter hall.
Silence!
I now call to order
the first meeting
of the Ancient Mystic Society
of...
No Homers.
Hey, fellas, can I join?
Sorry. No Homers.
Loyal Stonecutters!
Let us begin our reenactment
of the Battle of Gettysburg!
Homer, you can't
just keep hanging out
with these
colobus monkeys.
Somebody's going
to get parasites.
Oh, Marge, kids,
I miss my club.
Oh, Homie.
You know, you are a member
of a very exclusive club.
- The Black Panthers?
- No.
The Family Simpson,
which has just five members.
And only two of those members
have special rings.
- Yeah!
I meant our wedding rings!
You know, Marge,
you're right.
The Simpson Family is
the best possible club
I could belong to.
Ow! Ah! Ack! Ah!
This club better
be worth it!
Ow! Ee! Ah!
All right, all right.
It's Lisa's turn.
Who controls
the British crown?
Who keeps
the metric system down?
We do, we do.
Who keeps Atlantis
off the maps?
Who keeps the Martians
under wraps?
We do, we do.
Who holds back
the electric car?
Who makes Steve Guttenberg.
A star?
We do, we do.
Who robs cave fish
of their sight?
Who rigs every
Oscar night?
We do.
We do!
Shut up!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.