(SINGING) The Simpsons
(SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
(HORN BELLOWING)
Ripped By mstoll
(PLAYING DIFFERENT TUNE)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
D'oh!
(SCREAMS)
MAN ON TV: Next on Fox,
Carmen Electra stars in Boobs.
About a class of remedial reading
students and their teacher
who wants to be
taken seriously.
Oh, I thought it was
about her boobs.
(CLICKS)
Tonight on Jock Center,
a slugger on 'roids,
Tiger Woods is annoyed,
and North Korean
missiles deployed.
But first, the commissioner
of pro football
has announced plans
to expand the league.
Owners will meet soon to award
a new team to one lucky city.
Well, it's a cinch Springfield
wont be that lucky city.
Yeah, the only
thing we're known for
is leading the country
in heart attacks.
(GROANS)
Ha! (GRUNTS)
Oh, I've had enough
of your stinkin' thinkin'.
I, Homer Simpson,
will personally bring
the new pro football
franchise to Springfield.
(ALL LAUGH)
(MOTORIZED LAUGHING)
(LAUGHS)
God, we have fun.
Homie, snagging a pro football
franchise is a big project
requiring a lot
of follow through.
And that's not your
strong suit, big guy.
I'll show you all.
I'm gonna spearhead the hell
out of this expansion bid.
(ALL LAUGH)
(BABBLING)
(DRILLING)
(HAMMERING)
(TYPEWRITER CLACKS AND DINGS)
(LOUD CLATTERING)
(CRASHING)
(SIREN WAILING)
(CHILDREN SINGING)
Ring around the rosy
Homie, you've been
down here for a week.
I really think you need...
(GASPS)
What the Hellmann's
Real Mayonnaise?
Marge, meet pro football's
newest team,
the Springfield Meltdowns!
Plus, I designed
a state-of-the-art stadium.
We'll fund it with
corporate naming rights.
It's the Duff
Beer-Krustyburger-Buzz Cola-
Costington's Department Store
Kwik-E-Man-
Stupid Flanders Park.
So Homer do good?
Homer do great.
Uh, maybe Homer brush teeth first?
(GROANS) Oh.
Gentlemen, I've narrowed our choice
of expansion cities down to two,
Springfield...
Yee-haw! I own slums there!
...and Los Angeles, which
has sent us this videotape.
I love LA
Oh, hi, I'm Rob Reiner, director
of When Harry Met Sally.
"I'll have what she's having"
was one of the lines.
I'm here to tell you why you
should choose LA over Springfield.
LA has the beach,
a thriving music scene, and
the beautiful Getty Museum.
Springfield has
Apu Nahasapeemapetilon.
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(LAUGHS)
Hollywood takes in
talented actors
and writers from
all over the world.
Springfield takes in
garbage from other cities.
But don't just
take my word for it.
Some of Hollywood's
biggest stars
have taken the time
to sign waivers
allowing celebrity impersonators
to sing in this video.
Enjoy.
(ALL SINGING)
LA makes great movies
And awesome TV shows
Springfield don't make nothin'
'Cause Springfield blows
Springfield blows
Yes, Springfield blows
(INDISTINCT TALKING)
I'm sick of LA.
They got earthquakes, wildfires,
Benniffers, Brangelinas,
and that potty mouth
Sarah Silverman.
To hell with all of them!
I didn't kill my husband lo
get control of his franchise
to give a team
to Los Angeles!
Then Springfield it is!
Yee-haw!
(ALL MURMURING)
Now if you'll excuse
me, I gotta go
tell my gay grandson
I still love him.
This is Kent Brockman live at
Duff Beer-Krustyburger-Buzz Cola-
Costington's Department Store-
Kwik-E-Mart-Stupid Flanders Park.
In just one hour the commissioner
of football will arrive
to sign the contracts
necessary to make Springfield
the home of pro football's
newest team, The Meltdowns!
I've got Melt mania.
I've got Downs syndrome!
In honor of
the commissioner's visit,
the city has been
re-painted in the team colors
and all the streets
whimsically renamed.
Touchdown Avenue?
Delightful!
Who you talking to?
Your imaginary girlfriend?
Argh! Isn't your mother
a well-known whore?
(GASPS)
You win this round, Mel.
It is my honor to introduce
the commissioner of football,
Mr. Bud Armstrong!
(CHEERING)
There, uh, seems to be
some delay.
Um...
Did I ever tell you people about
the time I met Lloyd Bridges?
LENNY: Yeah, you
passed him in the airport!
Yes, but which airport?
CARL: Hartsfield in Atlanta!
(HUFFS)
Ugh, this map says things like Oak
Street and Evergreen Terrace.
But all I see are
Two-Point-Conversion Avenue
and Off-Season Knee
Surgery Boulevard.
I'd better call
and ask for directions.
I'll just Blackberry my assistant.
(PHONE BEEPS)
Oh, my God.
Oh, what a day.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
Who are ya?
What do you want?
What year is it?
Who are ya?
I have to borrow your phone. Oh, I
also need to use your bathroom.
As you can tell,
I've been crying.
MAN ON TV:
Tonight on 48 Minutes
we look at America's number
one problem, (TICKING)
criminals who prey on the elderly
people who watch this program.
I'd go to some
geezer's house
and ask to use their
phone or their bathroom.
Well, I'm done with the bathroom.
(SIGHS)
Now, I'm going to make
that phone call. Oh.
Then I'd steal
their wallets, jewelry
and pictures of
their grandkids.
I made a collage of these
and when you step back, it
looks like my face. (LAUGHS)
(HUMMING)
If I knock him out,
I'll be a hero
and people will listen
to my loose brain nonsense.
(BEEPING)
(HUMMING)
(GROANS)
(CHUCKLES)
By the shores
of Gitche Gumee,
by the Shining
Big-Sea-Water,
stood the Wiggum of Nokomis.
I'm sorry, did I just say "Wiggum"?
(CHUCKLES) I meant "wigwam".
Let me, uh, start again.
(CROWD GROANING)
lt's so strange that the
commissioner didn't show up.
Maybe, he's thinking of a
new shape for the football.
(ALL GASP)
Not so tough
when someone hits you
from behind with
a golf club, are ya?
Grampa, that's
the commissioner of football!
(STUTTERS)
What the... You...
I thought he was
trying to steal my jewels
and all them pictures
of Bert and Lucy!
I am never coming back
to this city!
And neither is the league!
(GASPS) You mean...
That's right.
The Springfield Meltdowns
Football Club shall never be!
You're a useless old man. Name one
thing you do for this family!
I watch the baby.
Where is the baby?
You left me with a baby?
Hey, Abe, thanks for losing
us our football team!
Thanks to you, we have
a $100-million stadium
we can only use
for farmers markets.
Nobody loves you
when you're old and gray
Nobody needs you
when you're upside-down
Everyone's hollering
about their own birthday
Everybody loves you
When you're six
foot in the ground
You're the only
smile I got.
(GROANS) on.
Abe, I know you've been
real depressed lately
on account of everyone hating
ya, including me. (SPITS)
But I thought you might
want to call this number.
A doctor? I already got
enough doctors touching me
and poking me
and squeezing me up here
and jiggling me
down there!
And that's just
the receptionist!
Abe, Abe, Abe!
This doctor helps old people
to kill themselves.
Euthanasia?
No way, l want to die
with dignity,
like slipping in the shower and
then they find me two weeks later
swelling up so bad they don't
know if I'm man or sofa!
Just go for a visit.
There's a Howard Johnson's next door.
You'll get some pie.
Hmm.
Mmm.
Mr. Simpson, you are a good
candidate for assisted suicide.
Aw, I think you're cute, too.
But killing yourself
isn't as easy
as putting on an ugly
sweater like you did today.
I want you to carefully think
about this for 24 hours.
Oh, I see.
You want me to reconsider
whether or not
I really should
give up my life.
Yeah, and we're cleaning out
the death machine today.
Lotta gunk gets stuck in it.
(CLOCK TICKING)
Okay.
If I get a single phone call in the
next 24 hours, I'll keep on living.
If you go, can I have your
blanket and your liver?
Blanket, sure.
Liver, never!
Homie, you should
give your dad a call.
You can't stay
mad at him forever.
Yeah, you're right.
(PHONE RINGING)
Y'ello? (GASPS) You want my
opinion on current movies?
Well, first of all,
they're all perfect.
Also, when's the Cap'n Crunch
movie coming out?
And will it be R or hard R?
(CLOCK TICKING)
Oh, that's it.
It's time for me to die.
I'll just get mad about one
thing in the newspaper then go.
"President visits Europe."
On my dime? (HUFFS)
l am so honored that you've
chosen me to murder you.
You'll be following in the footsteps
of Socrates, Virginia Woolf,
Ernest Hemingway, Hunter S.
Thompson and Fred Kanickee.
Who's Fred Kanickee?
My appointment before you.
Nice guy.
Just a little screwed up.
Now, it is time to hook
you up to the diePOD.
As you surrender your body,
what music and visual imagery
would you like to experience?
I want to hear
the Glenn Miller Orchestra
and I want to see
cops beating up hippies.
Uh-huh.
(TURNS KNOB)
Hmm.
(PENNSYLVANIA 6-5000 PLAYING)
One minute to go.
Hands off the stiff,
Manfred Manslaughter!
(CHUCKLES) The voters just
overturned the assisted suicide law.
(GRUNTS)
I'll kill you all!
When the law is reversed.
I'd like to see you try!
CLANCY: I think you know my
brother-in-law, Fred Kanickee?
DR. EGOYAN: Oh, boy.
(GASPS) I'm dead.
I never felt so alive!
And I got my
16-year-old body back.
Woo-hoo!
(CARS HONKING)
MAN: Look out!
(MAN SHOUTING)
MAN: Idiot!
Now, let's see.
Am I in heaven or hell?
Mmm.
That's odd. You'd think
they'd come back as the cows.
Charlie Chaplin?
They sure put you to work.
You said it. And you can talk.
Good for you.
What. .. (STAMMERS)
You're all dead, too?
So who went berserk?
Fatso or the little guy?
We're not dead
and neither are you.
I'm not?
I guess if you want to
commit suicide around here,
you gotta do it yourself.
ALL: Suicide?
Grampa, killing
yourself is a sin.
God wants us to die
of old age,
after years of pain
and reduced mobility.
I ain't gonna kill myself because
I just learned something.
The brief time
I thought I was dead
was the happiest
I've ever been
because I was finally
living without fear.
And dagnabit, that's the way I'm
gonna live the rest of my life!
I am, I am
I am Superman
And I know what's happening
(ALL GASP)
I am, I am
I am Superman
And I can do anything
You're all gonna die
in a pointless war.
Huh?
We're here tonight
to discuss possible uses
for this football stadium,
including
the solid gold statue
of Mike Ditka
with diamond eyes.
I suggest we use the stadium for
the ancient art of the toreador.
Bullfighting!
CROWD: (CHEERING) Yes!
No, wait, wait! Bullfighting
is a cruel pseudo-sport.
Lisa's right!
It is a cool super sport!
Everyone in favor of bringing
bullfighting to Springfield,
say, olé.
CROWD: Olé!
So ordered!
All we need now is...
Uh, er...
(STAMMERING)
A matador.
If it's all the same to you,
I'll take on those bulls!
Grampa, no!
Grampa, sf. If the bull
dies, the crowd goes wild.
If Grampa dies,
the crowd goes wild.
Either way, we make a fortune
on souvenirs and snacks.
Uh, can we bring
outside food?
Not even gum.
Is the practice bull ready?
Hell, yeah! (SNORTS)
Olé.
Ooh, a penny.
This is my lucky day.
Ahhh!
(TIRES SCREECH)
Yep, my lucky day.
(SCREAMS IN PAIN)
(WHIMPERS)
(SINGING) How many bulls
must my grandfather kill...
Aw, she's so cute.
We'll bring you the
bull's heart, sweetie.
(CROWD CHEERING)
MARGE: Well,
I had my doubts.
But Grampa sure looks
manly in those leggings.
And I don't know
who's more handsome,
the bull taunter
or the bull stabber.
(HORN BLOWS)
(SNORTS)
(GRUNTS)
And the corrida
de toros has begun!
COMMENTATOR: The bull
charges at Grampa Simpson.
(BULL GRUNTING)
(CROWD GASPING)
And he avoids the toro
with a masterfui veronica!
This old man has no fear,
like the fear I feel that I
have left the iron on at home.
(SCREAMS) Have I? Have I?
(SNORTS)
And another
veronica and another.
That last veronica means
everyone here today
has won a free side
of rice and beans
at the Springfield
Taco Pronto.
Tired of waiting two hours for a taco?
Go to Taco Pronto!
(CROWD CHEERING)
(SNORTS)
(LOWING)
(CHEERING)
(CROWD JEERING)
(CROWD CHEERING)
Grampa, I think you should
give up the bullfighting.
Forget it! I'd look pretty
stupid in this outfit
walking around
fighting oysters!
But you just got
a new lease on life.
Why would you want to use it
to hurt poor helpless animals?
Listen, I'm 83 years old
and for the first time in my life,
people are cheering for me.
I was always cheering for
you, Grampa, till now.
Oh, how does she always
know how to get to me?
(CROWD CHEERING)
Grampa Simpson's
movements are tentative
as if he's distracted.
Distracted as if
by a moral dilemma,
a moral dilemma
posed by a young boy...
No, a girl. A girl named Linda.
Ne, Lisa!
The flutter of
the cape tells all.
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
HOMER
Hurry up and kill n.
I have to be at
the opera by 7:00.
(CROWD JEERING) MAN: Come on!
Kill it! Come on!
(GRUNTS)
I don't get what
he's doing and I'm smart.
Not book smart
or street smart
or brain smart,
but somethin'.
(GRUNTS)
(BULLS GRUNTING)
(GASPS) He has released
the bulls from the stadium.
Thank God I am up high.
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
(SNORTS) (GASPS)
Please, no. I have a wife
and three girlfriends.
(GRUNTS)
(LOWING)
(GAS PS)
Grampa must've
set them free.
(STRUMMING)
(CROWD PANICKING)
(BULLS GRUNTING)
Oh, Gil's back on track. He's got
a new job and a new red suit.
(HUMMING)
Ahhh!
If you let me go,
I give you free large pizza
pie with purchase of same.
Offer not good Tuesday through Sunday.
We're closed on Monday.
(BULLS GRUNTING)
Ahhh!
Santa Maria!
(SCREAMING)
Thanks for setting me
straight, sweetie.
De nada, Grampa.
(SIGHS) It sure is
peaceful up here.
(BULLS GRUNTING)
Uh-oh.
(SHUTTER CLICKS)
I would like to name
the following friends of mine
as members of
the Communist Party.
You're just here to
test the microphone.
Fred Wilson, my brother Bill,
Dom DiMaggio,
the paper boy, Howdy
Doody, Joseph Stalin...
Ripped By mstoll