(SINGING) The Simpsons
(SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
(HORN BELLOWING)
(BEEPING)
Ripped By mstoll
(PLAYING DIFFERENT TUNE)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
D'oh!
(EXCLAIMING)
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
(SPRAYING)
Are you sure we can
make money doing this?
What if nobody wants their
address painted on the curb?
Duh! Nobody wants their
address painted on the curb.
We do it without asking,
and then they have to pay.
What are you punks doin?
(COCKS GUN)
Answer me, or I'll drop ya
like a bad cell phone plan!
Sorry. This thing
goes off on its own.
Anyway,
you were sayin"?
Ignore that.
We painted your
address on the curb.
And since you didn't tell us
not to, you owe us 10 bucks.
Wow. A number
on the curb?
That really classes
the joint up.
Yep, things are
finally going my way.
I struck oil! I struck oil!
(VOCALIZING)
I struck oil!
(LAUGHING)
Uh, when do we
tell him that's not oil?
Ah, let him
have his fun.
Oil! Oil!
Only $10 to paint my curb
like a common whore?
Well, I'm happy to pay
for a three-digit spray.
Tell you what. I'll give you another
$100 if you paint my garage.
Wait a minute.
That's not a scam!
That's honest work
for honest pay!
ALL: No!
I'll throw in some
Christian comic books!
Please!
Somebody take them!
Screw you.
I'm never gonna pay.
Well, then we're gonna
leave you one digit short.
(NELSON GRUNTS)
Fine. I'll finish
it myself.
And don't think I'm gonna
screw it up, because I won't!
(HOMER LAUGHING)
Dad, all you had to do
was paint one number.
Now no one’s gonna
be able to find our house.
But, sweetie,
I just wanted to tell
the '74 Oakland A's
how I felt about them.
Look, that guy remembers us!
(BRAKES SCREECH)
Hey, Sal Bando, give him a
'74 A's "thank you honk."
(HORN HONKS)
My work here is done.
(HUMMING)
(DOORBELL RINGS)
(GASPS) I'm needed
at the door!
I have a delivery for a Scott
and Brenda Weingarten,
74 Evergreen Terrace.
74? Oh, sorry.
There's been a mistake.
Oh, no problem.
I'll just ship these juicy,
mail-order steaks back to Omaha.
Uh, on second thought,
I am Brenda Winecooler.
(LAUGHING)
Dad, isn't it wrong to open
or eat other people's mail?
Son, all our mail has ever
brought me is bad things.
Bills, jury duty,
Entertainment Weekly.
Now, for once, I'm getting
rich-person mail.
You wouldn't take that away
from me, would you, son?
Oh, Dad, no one can
rationalize like you.
Okay, Weingartens,
what else is in your mail?
Oh! Marge, do you wanna go to a
wedding of a couple we never met?
Strangers
getting married?
I wouldn't miss it
for the world.
Mark and Tracy, I remember the
first words I heard you say,
"l do."
Your cousin Scott
is so sweet.
But didn't you say
he was blind?
That's what I heard, but he's
so confident in his movements.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(ON TV) This is Kent Brockman
in the Springfield Keys,
reporting to you from the
middle of a hurricane.
The lid from my coffee
cup is long gone.
(GROANS)
I'm scared, people.
Truly scared.
(CHUCKLING)
Take that, liberal media.
Homer! This says I've won
Homemaker Magazine's
"Clean for a Day"
contest! Mmm.
"A highly skilled professional
will come to your home
"and clean it top to bottom
while you relax."
But how could I have won?
I don't subscribe
to this periodical.
Marge, I don't have to sit here
and listen to your insane ravings
about me getting
other people's mail.
Hi. I'm Brenda Weingarten.
(SCREAMS)
(VACUUM CLEANER WHIRRING)
LISA: Mom,
what are you doing?
Cleaning up before
the housekeeper comes.
This is a total stranger who
cleans houses for a living.
Who cares
what she thinks?
Don't be
so naive, Lisa.
Those people all
talk to each other.
You know what I found in
their dirty clothes hamper?
Dirty clothes!
I found a hair
in the drain.
Not a fine upstanding head
hair, but a curly-wurly!
ALL: (CHANTING)
Untidy! Untidy! Untidy!
Mmm-mmm.
Now, this is a house
that's ready to be cleaned!
(GASPS)
(DOORBELL RINGS)
(GASPS) That's her!
Don't answer it yet!
I don't want that judgmental
bitch in my house!
(GASPS) Maple syrup mixed with
baby spit-up and shoe scuff?
This is going to take my
whole arsenal at once!
(GRUNTING)
(INHALES DEEPLY)
Et tu, Zud?
(GASPS) She's opening
her eyes!
Oh, my head feels like it was
punched by a boxing man.
How many fingers
am I holding up?
Two.
Very good.
Now I'll put them
back in the jar.
Now I have a question.
Who are you people?
She doesn't recognize us!
(ALL GASP)
You monster! What have
you done to my face?
When will Marge
remember us?
It's hard to say, with
retrograde amnesia such as this,
the patient could forget
years and years of her life.
You just have to keep jogging
her memory till it works.
Aw, jogging?
I didn't say
you should be jogging.
Sweet.
Although you
should be jogging.
On, jogging?
Marge, I'm gonna
take care of you
until your amnesia
goes scram-nesia.
I got you flowers...
Mmm.
...fluffy pillow, and a nice,
relaxing private room.
(SNORING)
Oh, you're sweet.
I'm lucky to have such a kind, uh...
Uncle?
I'm your husband!
What?
I am.
We're the same age.
But you're so much
more ravaged than I am.
(LAUGHING)
I do eat a lot of crap.
I'm Lisa.
I'm eight years old, and this
might sound presumptuous,
but I'm your favorite.
Oh, you seem sweet, but I
could never have a favorite.
Well, talk to me
in a week.
Hi. I'm Bart.
I'm 10 years old and a
professional motocross jumper.
Can you buy me
a motocross bike?
I may have lost my memory,
but I'm not an idiot.
(CHUCKLES)
Great news, Marge,
we're going home.
Yes, the insurance
company said
you're as well as
they're gonna pay for.
(LAUGHING)
Oh, I can't wait to see what
kind of home we live in.
Oh, it's great.
Like somebody barfed
a two-story pile of puke.
Why, you little...
(CHOKING)
(GRUNTING)
You strangle
your child?
(CHUCKLING) Yeah,
but he's cool with it.
Right?
(SWALLOWS)
It hurts
when I swallow.
Why, you little...
(GRUNTING)
(CHOKING)
Mmm...
Now, the doctor said
a tour of the town
could help bring
back your memory.
I say Bing cherries
are the most delicious!
I say maraschino!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Who are those freaks?
(LAUGHING) Those "freaks,"
as you call them,
are some of our
closest friends.
Maraschino isn't even
a kind of cherry!
It's a way
of preserving them!
Sounds like Duffman took the wrong
side in this chicken fight.
Oh, yeah!
(BRAKES SCREECH)
Why is that drug addict
driving a school bus?
Whoa, I may be wasted, but I still
care about the safety of these kids.
Hmm?
Hmm... Hmm...
See that ball of fire?
That's the sun.
It goes by many names.
Apollo's Lantern,
day-moon, Old Blazey.
The important thing
is never to touch it.
I know what
the sun is!
Yes, now you do.
(PACIFIER SQUEAKING)
I know that sound!
Maggie!
My sweet little angel!
Mmm... Mmm!
The sound of the baby
must have triggered
a primal
mnemonic response
in Mom's brain!
Lisa! My little know-it-all!
Hey, guys, guess who just
became lactose-tolerant?
Milhouse!
You're Bart's best friend!
(GASPS)
I remember Bart!
Oh, I can't believe you
remembered me through Milhouse.
He's not even
my best friend.
Who's got
amnesia now, Bart?
Mmm, mmm, mmm.
lt's so great to have
my children back.
I better get ready.
I'm next.
(EXHALES)
(SNIFFS)
All right, Marge, time to
remember Admiral Awesome!
Mmm...
Nope. I'm sorry, Admiral, but
you're still a stranger to me.
Oh. Why do you remember
them and not me?
I don't know.
Maybe there's something unpleasant
blocking my memory of you.
Hi-diddly-ho,
Simpsons!
Oh, hey, Ned. Isn't today
your cat's birthday?
I remember, 'cause she shares
the date with Patti LaBelle.
(GROANS LOUDLY)
Okay. All it'll take to
unlock your memories of me
is one of these
blasts from the past.
Here's me fighting
with former President Bush.
Me fighting with
current President Bush.
And here's me showing a
bag of apples who's boss.
I'm sorry.
You seem like
a colorful character,
but I just don't
remember you.
Well, maybe if we snuggle, it
might rattle some memories loose.
What's "snuggling"?
When a man and a woman
love each other very much,
they usually
get together...
Mr. Simpson,
I don't even know you!
I'm not making
love with you!
But what if we...
(INAUDIBLE)
You're describing how
to parallel park.
(SOBBING)
You used to love my non sequiturs.
(SOBBING CONTINUES)
Why can I remember everyone
in town except my husband?
Simple. Your brain
is trying to save you
from your backed-up
toilet of a marriage.
Have you been talking like
this for my entire marriage?
Oh, no. No.
We've always honored
your choice.
I don't know. l should
give Homer a chance.
But on the other hand,
I feel nothing for him.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(GASPS)
This is horrible!
We've got to tell Dad.
Oh, no! Bart and Lisa are gonna
tell me something horrible!
(SIGHS)
What?
"Buy the police department
a hang glider," you said.
"Fight crime from above,"
you said.
Yeah, and you said
you're only 180 pounds.
Shut up
and look for crime.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
Mr. Simpson?
Marge, if I can't
make you remember me,
then I'll make you fall
for me all over again.
The heart is
the symbol for love.
Uh!
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(SINGING) That Homer
Simpson, he's quite a guy
He paid me 10 bucks
so I would lie
The truth is
he's not so great
He is the one man
I truly hate
So beautiful.
I wish I could
understand Italian.
I've had a lovely evening,
Mr. Simpson.
Just wait, we're coming to the site
of our most romantic night ever.
It was the plywood
castle that we first...
Well, you know.
Know what?
(GASPS)
No! I'm not the kind of girl who makes
love on a putt-putt golf course!
Oh, you loved it,
especially when the windmill came
around and whacked your butt.
(PURRING)
Oh, that sounds horrible!
No. It was the happiest
night of my life.
The warm spring air,
the swings I took in the
batting cage afterwards.
Don't you remember,
darling?
No, and I hope
I never do!
The best thing that ever happened
to me was forgetting about you!
(GRUNTING)
You know, I still think
about you all the time.
Birthdays over,
Seymour.
But, uh...
I'm sorry
you have to leave,
but I just can't think
of another way.
I know.
Wait, I thought of
another way. I stay.
Goodbye, Mr. Simpson.
Uh!
Dad, we don't want
you to leave.
(SOBS) My grades
will suffer.
In fact,
they're already suffering.
Look at this garden of "Fs."
You planted them all.
Marge, I realize you've
made up your mind,
and I want you to know that
I deeply respect your...
Boo! That works for
hiccups, not amnesia.
I know.
I just thought maybe...
Boo!
Oh.
(GROANS)
Boo.
(COUGHING)
How long you gonna be
bunking with me, son?
Well, the rest of
your life for sure.
Why are we having
dinner in Shelbyville?
We found a place here that's
serving up just what you need.
A mixer?
I don't know.
l am still
technically married.
All we're saying is go in
and chat with these guys.
And if you want a quickie
annulment and remarriage,
we've got all
the paperwork right here.
Why don't you sign
a bunch now?
For fun.
Welcome to speed dating,
you exciting, lonely people.
Every five minutes,
I'm going to blow this horn...
(AIR HORN BLOWS)
...and each man will move
one table to his left.
Excuse me.
Is this how you met
your husband?
No, I met him through friends
like a normal person.
Now, speed date.
(AIR HORN BLOWS)
(STAMMERING) I want you to know I'm
coming from a very fragile place.
My wife left me...
(SOBS)
...five years ago.
Oh, that's so sad.
Why did I kill her, why?
(AIR HORN BLOWS)
Hello there.
Yeah, hi.
How you doing?
So, uh, let's get
right to it.
I don't drive
a Lexus, okay?
I don't have a Learjet or some
big beach house in la-la land.
l am just a nice man
who makes a decent living.
So I guess I should probably
just go shoot myself, huh?
Hmm?
Oh, don't get
quiet on me.
Please, I hate when
they get quiet.
(AIR HORN BLOWS)
Ta-da!
I know what you're
thinking, but don't worry,
I'm old enough to date.
(CHUCKLING)
(WHISPERING)
Dermabrasion!
MARGE: I think
he's a male gay.
(AIR HORN BLOWS)
Ah!
I have to admit something,
I feel a little silly.
Oh, me, too.
I can't believe anyone ever really
finds anyone at these things.
Yeah, I was dragged here
by my older brothers.
We used to be quintuplets,
but three of us drowned.
(GRUNTS)
I really know where
you're coming from.
(AIR HORN BLOWS)
Oh, l guess
we have to move on.
Do we? We're adults. Why don't
we just go get a cup of coffee?
I'd love to.
(CHUCKLING)
Ooh-la-la.
I smell romance.
It's a perfect night
for love.
Would you pretty ladies care
to join us for some champagne?
Go suck a rat,
Assanova.
(CLOCK TICKING)
(PHONE RINGING)
(GASPS)
That might be Marge!
Don't answer it.
Savor the sound.
(CONTINUES RINGING)
Oh, boy...
Marge?
Homer, I don't want to
alarm you, but right now
we're looking at your wife yukkin'
it up with a good-looking guy.
He just touched her arm and
now they're being quiet.
But it's not
an awkward silence.
Yeah, it's more like a "nothing
needs to be said" kind of silence.
(SCREAMS)
I just think the best thing
a person can do
for the world is to
be clean and polite.
Wow, that's what
I would have said.
Well, I would have said, "Polite
and clean," but wow, still.
Oh, no! He's Marge's,
and my, dream man.
I've got to make a play for her
now Or I might lose her forever.
Uh!
(SPITS) D'oh!
At least she found someone
who can make her happy.
Oh, Marge, l feel like the two of
us can say anything to each other.
You really mean that?
I do.
I've got amnesia
and I have three kids.
Wow. My first thought
is "respect,"
both for your mental illness and
your ability to get back into shape.
My second thought
is "goodbye."
You idiot!
Ah!
Do you know what
you just gave up?
Who the hell are you?
The wisest, wettest
man you'll ever meet.
Go on. You just walked
away from the sweetest,
most beautiful woman
a guy could want.
In 10 years, she never had the last slice
of pizza and she's never complained.
Every election,
she wishes she could vote for both
guys because they both seem nice.
And there's alight inside her that
makes everyone else look better.
And you blew her off.
Dude, she's got
three kids.
(GASPS)
Really?
Well, she's still great.
Hmm.
MARGE: Mr. Simpson.
I may not know
much about you,
but you sure know a lot of
wonderful things about me.
And that means
a lot to a woman.
I still don't
remember you.
But for the first time since this
happened, l wish l did, Homer.
I'm so happy we're together again.
Want to get a drink?
You drink?
Uh, yeah, I started when
you were in the hospital.
Oh, I was so worried.
Recently I tried this
thing called beer, and...
(GASPS)
I remember everything!
You get drunk
all the time.
Oh.
But do you also remember
that you're an enabler?
Oh, of course I do.
That's why we're
such a great team.
(TIRES SQUEALING)
MARGE: You've been drinking
today, haven't you?
HOMER: l sure have,
partner.
MARGE: I remember him.
HOMER: What about her?
MARGE: No, I don't know.
And her?
Oh, and her.
And her'!
Uh-huh. And him.
Well, what about him?
Mmm, I don't
recognize that name.
Yeah. I have their
baseball cards.
Oh, I know all them.
Look at all those people.
You know them?
Wow. She still
works here?
Yeah, she's over
in post now.
Oh, I always liked
that guy.
Not me.
But we can't get rid of him because
he's friends with Richard Sakai.
Oh, and there's a familiar name.
And another one. Wait.
Whatever happened to that
guy from the network?
Did he get married?
Oh, he ain't
getting married.
(CHUCKLES)
He has commitment issues.
Ripped By mstoll