Tonight on Million
Dollar Listing: Springfield.
We once again have only
one house in this whole town
worth a million dollars.
I keep telling you,
I don't want to sell.
This area has
a great school system
and I'm thinking
of starting a family.
My children, fight each other
to the death for my love.
I'm here in
the sculpture garden,
and we can't keep
the buyers away.
Maybe it's the fresh-baked
morphine cookies.
Open concept dungeon,
four panic rooms,
hot and cold running oxygen.
Good old reality TV.
Snappy editing, no content.
Homer.
Marge.
What the...?
I'm hosting book club tonight,
and I was thinking,
maybe you'd like to go to Moe's
until we're done.
You want me to go to Moe's?
I do.
How drunk can I get?
Stinking or falling down?
Uh, how about "sociable"?
What I'm hearing
is wedding drunk.
Wedding drunk, cash bar.
Fine.
So, who liked the book?
Not me. It was a farewell
to my Saturday.
Hemingway is so clichéd.
This book about Italian
ambulance drivers was...
...boring, boring, boring.
There wasn't enough
smoking in it for me.
May I speak mah piece?
What's your problem, Daisy May?
Couldn't make it through
the audiobook?
Well, ah thinks
it's a classic of style
that's more than a war story
and more than a love story.
With deceptively simple prose
as lean and sturdy
as a half-ton marlin.
I-I mean...
my eyes was bewitchefied with
all them squiggels and squirms.
Well... I-I best git.
I left
all my kids with a nanny.
You free Saturday?
Then, the hillbilly woman
made a comment
that was profound
and insightful.
She's secretly smart.
Uh, Helen, please do not
gossip in church.
Did you hear about Brandine?
Well, it would be nice
to hear something other than.
"Let me go, I have a family."
Well, I tried
"you're under arrest,"
but you just laughed.
We got some nice wigglers.
They pair well with a hook.
Mm, I'll take a box
of Napa Valley reds.
Hey, Spuckler.
I just want to warn you.
Your wife isn't the woman
you think she is.
Just what does you mean?
She's smart.
Jeopardy smart.
Celebrity Jeopardy!?
Regular Jeopardy.
You do not tell a man
he don't know his wife.
That's like telling a man
his gun's not loaded.
You let him find that out
at the worst possible time.
Well, you should know.
When your wife left
the book club, she dropped this.
Liberry has two R's?
- Your bait, sir.
- You just keep your worms.
I gots me bigger fish to fry.
Go on, git.
What a senseless waste of worms.
Men receiving credit
for women's work in science
has been dubbed
"The Matilda Effect,"
with such victims as
Lise Meitner,
Rosalind Franklin,
and Jocelyn Bell Burnell.
How many pumpkin stickers
will it take for you to stop?
Here, have the whole sheet.
This is really important.
Each of these heroines
was nonplussed
at their lack
of recognition and...
Sorry, Lisa.
I don't think you're using
that word correctly.
Nonplussed? Ha.
I'm pretty sure I am.
It means perplexed.
It does.
As in,
"The teacher was nonplussed
by the impudence of a student."
When I grow up,
I want to be a big word.
Lisa, you get in the back
of the class and keep quiet.
Do I get an "A"?
An "A" for "aggravation."
An A's an A!
Cletus, darling,
I-I made your favorite.
Sorry, but I'm in no mood
for porcu-pie right now.
Brandine, tell me true.
Are you actually smart?
Have all your yups
just being yeses in disguise?
Aw, don't be silly.
Why? The only three R's I know
are racoons, Red Bull
and the rhythm method.
Please, I needs to know.
Brandine, who is you?
Darling, I'm afraid
I'm guilty of concealing
a significant self-improvement.
Guh-what??
It started a few years back
with some books I read
that fell off a passing tornado.
It was like entering a universe
I never knew existed.
I went to the ballet.
And I completed
my self-education
at the Springfield Athenaeum.
- The what?
- Athenaeum.
- Museum.
- The what?
- Pica-ture palace.
Got it.
Oh, good lordy.
I'm starting to worry
there's more layers to you
than a skunk
and tomater sandwich.
Brandine, I'm sorry.
But I-I can't have
a stranger as my woman.
Remember your vow.
You promised to love, honor,
and never grow in any way.
Well, you're right about that.
I'll leave now,
but I'll be back
for most of the children.
That's fair enough.
All right, which ones of y'all
want to stay with me?
And remember, you go with her...
You gots to wash your hands.
Whoa, you mean like every week?
- Sorry, Ma.
- Can't do it.
Say bye-bye to your mama.
Or would you prefer
a "bon voyage"?
Cletus Delroy Spuckler,
you are lower than
a gopher's basement. Goodbye.
Young'uns, turn away
if you don't want to see
your daddy cry.
We've seen you cry.
But we've never seen you yodel.
All right, then.
Brandine!
Are you here for further
book club discussions?
I'm here because
I got nowhere else to go.
I've been rejected by a man
who thinks it's funny
to light his farts.
- You can light them?
- No, Homer, no!
Hey, whoa!
Wasn't me.
Ms. Spuckler? I brought
some books you might like.
You're a smart girl, Lisa.
Which means life will be harder
than a month-old biscuit.
So, about Cletus, um...
I just have to ask, sorry.
- What do you see in him?
- What do you mean?
Don't you think maybe
you could've done, um, better?
You mean, like you could've
done better than Homer?
What? What?
What?
People think I could've done
better than Homer?
Yes.
I never knew
anyone felt that way.
Reality check in aisle five.
Disco Stu needs
to buy some glue.
Also, Marge, please get a clue.
Enough. Enough.
I'll tell you
how I fell for Cletus.
It was one of those
magical nights
when the world was young
and everything was golden,
including his tooth.
We were seated
at the same hay bale
at my sister's shotgun wedding.
- Um, is this bale six?
- It is.
Do you ever look at someone
across a crowded pasture
and your knees went all weak?
Not from rickets or scurvy,
but from sheer infatuation?
Oh, I ransacked my brain
for le mot juste,
but all I could find was...
Derr.
Derr yourself.
In that moment,
twenty years of being
the middle child
in a family of 37
fell away like high-heeled shoes
on a wedding night.
Uh, you know,
I'm pretty sure we's cousins.
Second? First?
Kissing.
You ever driven
a tractor before?
No, sir.
These blades massage the soil
to make it ready
for what is sure to follow.
Churn that soil.
Churning. Always a-churning.
Until you just plant that seed
in there real deep.
You do this with all your dates?
Now, if I did, don't you think
this field would be plowed?
This is just for you, darling.
You're ruining my marijuana!
That night, I knew the next
shotgun wedding I went to
was gonna be mine.
Oh, look who it is,
Little Miss Google Noodle.
This isn't fair.
There's four times
as many of you.
She's trying to teach us
to multiply.
Get her!
Yoink.
Hello? What is this?
Fight over
who beats me up first?
Someone's nonplussed.
Correct usage.
Are you a real kid
or did the voice
in my head come to life?
Lisa Simpson,
I'd like to modestly ask you
to join our League
of Extraordinary Geniuses.
A club for smart kids?
But I've never noticed any other
names on the online honor roll.
And I refresh it hourly.
We hide in the shadows.
Which is scary, so we bring
little flashlights.
Eh, just you, Myles.
To avoid suspicion,
we figured out
how to be good at sports.
We don't wear our glasses,
even though we really need them.
Hold on. That food
is not fit for students.
Starve a landfill,
feed a teacher.
So you pretend to be dumb?
Absolutely. To survive.
Like a brightly-colored bug
who is actually poison inside.
The Dasymutilla Occidentalis?
Don't tell anyone you know that.
If you do, the bullies will
pounce on you like an...
Arilus Cristatus?
Who said that?
- Ar...
- Shh. Quiet.
Name one more genus and species
and you will be silenced.
Engage the Idiot Shield.
Wheel. Of. Fortune.
Wheel of Fortune's on.
Let's get home.
And that's how I realized
wheelchair ramps
are bitching skateboard jumps.
Thanks, Americans
with Disabilities Act.
I miss
my rotten little apples.
Especially the babies:
Moderna, AstraZeneca,
and the twins,
Johnson & Johnson.
Well, I just wanted to say,
this is the best
possum potpie I ever had.
I know what you're
thinking, Lisa.
But if God didn't want us
to eat possums,
he wouldn't have
made them look so delicious.
I'm just thinking about a club
I may join at school.
This one recruited me.
Aw, that's wonderful.
And Maggie, how was your day?
I feel so bad for Brandine.
Homie, will you go
talk to Cletus?
For you, baby, anything.
Sorry. I didn't fix the light
switch like you asked me to.
Well, maybe tomorrow?
For sure maybe.
Homer, do you think
people look at us and say,
"Why does she stay with him?"
Why does she stay with him?
Lord, why does
she stay with him?
Oh, yeah!
Why does Mommy stay with...
Don't tell her you can talk.
I don't think
I could've done better,
but it seems every other person
in town thinks so.
You're not going to listen
to everybody, are you?
No, I'm not.
Just hang the blanket
over the window
so I can get to sleep.
We don't have to do that anymore
because I fixed the blinds.
Ooh, a shooting star.
That's the water heater.
Cletus,
you and Brandine have
to get back together.
Broken marriages are contagious.
This is not about if'n or not
I love Brandine. I do!
But she refused to tell me
who she was.
Does she now think
hill folk are a-a joke?
Well, some of it's funny.
I mean, that long underwear with
the back door for the butt?
When it flaps open...
I mean, come on.
You just follow me.
Aw, sheet.
Brandine didn't just lie to me.
What she done is made a mockery
of my forebearers who possibly
did include four bears.
I want you to look at me
not as a hick, or a bumpkin,
but as a human being.
With feelings.
Just like you.
Oh, my God. You're right.
I don't know
how to feel right now.
I'm worried about your marriage.
I'm worried about my marriage.
Homer, no matter how you feel,
there's a country song
that expresses it perfectly.
No, that's not quite it.
Here we go.
It's like they're singing just to me.
Oh, why is it so catchy?
Are you leaving?
I'm going home.
Marriages aren't perfect.
I've even forgiven him
for blowing a jug in his sleep.
Well, that's great,
because my new friends
have given me the same tip.
"Hide your intelligence."
No, not you. You're too young.
You have everything
ahead of you.
Show 'em how smart you are.
- Really?
- A-yup.
You hear that, brain?
You're free.
Veni, vidi, vici!
Whoa, slow down there, poindexter.
Attention.
I have some announcements
regarding the cafeteria menu.
Several items are misspelled.
"Gren beans"
should be green beans.
"Tater tats" are tater tots.
"Healthy" should be not healthy.
Also...
You have to listen.
I'm wearing a necktie.
I am not bemused.
Uh, excuse me,
Principal Skinner?
Uh, I just wanted to say
that I think you meant
you are not "amused"?
"Bemused" means bewildered.
What is she doing?
Revealing her intellect.
Oh, the fool.
This isn't a magnet school.
We don't even own a magnet.
That's because I swallowed it.
Never again will I hide
my intelligence.
I am smartacus.
Unsurprisingly,
I also am smartacus.
I am smartacus.
Well, sort of smartacus.
Well, perfect attendacus.
Sitting downacus.
It's time to squelch this wave
of love of learning
and show them who's boss.
They are, loser.
I declare half a day.
Still too much.
Okay, no day.
Who wants their lunch
money back?
Not me.
It's fish stick day.
This is it, Brandine.
Kill your brain.
Take your medicine.
Mama!
Oh, hi, kids.
Look at how
some of you have grown.
Where's your pap?
He's been doing
a lot of thinking.
About you and him.
Can't go on like it has.
He said he's going to
a govement building
to get something
so he can start a new life.
No. I got to stop him.
- It's too late.
- Wha...?
Signed and sealed.
I got me a liberry card.
Oh, Cletus.
And my first book.
Yeah, man,
this looks like a toughie.
We'll get through it together.
- Homie?
- Marge, never again will I be the guy
about who people say,
"Why is she still with him?"
I fixed the drapes.
And the light switch.
Oh, nice.
But you'll have
to do more than that.
I also cleaned
the lint trap in the dryer.
And?
Four things?
Okay, Marge. I admit it.
You could do better,
but I couldn't.
Every day you give me
something awesome to shoot for.
Though I may occasionally
fall short,
because you are so great,
I will never stop trying.
I love you, Marge.
I love you, too.
Finally,
just in case I needed it.
I got Elton John back.
And he's here,
ready to play for you again.
Oh, Homie. I never needed that.
You mean I learned
226 songs for nothing?
I don't think they'll be
needing you guys either.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I want to tell y'all
about an American classic
that details a wealthy lifestyle
far beyond my reckoning.
It's called
The Grapes of Wrath.
- It's about a middle-
- American family what drives
to California for a better life.
For a much better treatment
of this subject,
I recommend National
Lampoon's Vacation,
now available on Hillbilly Plus.
Y'all come back now, you hear?
Captioning sponsored by
20th CENTURY FOX TELEVISION.
FOX BROADCASTING COMPANY
And FORD.
We go further, so you can.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org