I come bearing
an important communiqué.
It's from the marching band
director at Springfield High.
Oh, did he get his swollen head
stuck in a French horn?
Uh, there's no mention of that.
But it seems one of the band's
most important musicians
injured his middle toe doing
a high step in double-time.
That's footwork suicide!
They need
a replacement sax player,
and they've requested...
Lisa Simpson.
Me, in the high school band?
Yes, yes, a thousand times yes!
One yes would suffice.
Pack your sax, Lisa,
you're moving up to high school.
Three days a week after school,
otherwise you're still
in second grade.
I finally get
to play with people
who respect music theory
and tradition.
Teenagers!
Class, we have
a new baritone sax player.
Direct from
Springfield Elementary.
Largo's losers.
Hi. Hello.
Now, if you'll turn to page 12
in your marching band songbook.
The theme to Hawaii Five-O?!
Wow!
Yeah, Mr. Orlando is cool.
We do 50-year-old songs
instead of 100-year-old songs.
Shauna Chalmers,
thank you for joining us.
I'm gonna call you James Corden,
because you're
a late, late show.
He totally relates to us
on our level.
- Burnout.
- Waste case.
Third-chair slacker.
Shut up, woodwinds.
Okay, from the top.
Okay, cut.
Apparently Supertramp
isn't giving us the rights
to "Goodbye Stranger."
No...
Shauna! I didn't know
you played drums.
And I didn't know some tiny band
dork was gonna talk to me.
It's me, Lisa Simpson?
You babysat for us.
Last Saturday night.
TikTok is dumb.
Well, anyway,
your drumming's really good.
Wow.
Dear diary,
today I got a compliment
from a rando about something
I don't care about.
I have a diary, too!
People were playing eighth notes
like it was nothing.
Band kids are the coolest kids
in high school.
No fair.
Lisa gets to go to high school?
I was supposed
to be King of the Burnouts
before she even got there.
Well, son, I guess Lisa's
just unusually bright.
She gets it from me.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no!
I left all my sheet music
at school.
I have to go get it.
- Shauna!
- I'm Shauna!
Did you stay late to practice?
No way. As if.
You're practicing. Being stupid.
You don't need to.
You're great at it.
I'm jealous.
Shauna, we share
a passion for music.
Do you want to jam?
Yeah, jam this stick in my eye
if this conversation
goes on another second.
Fine! But I'm not afraid
to admit that music
means something to me,
unlike you.
You're Shauna.
Hey!
I'm sorry if
I was mean back there...
little weirdo.
I really don't know
how to take that.
Well, maybe we can talk about it
tomorrow at my house...
when you come over to jam.
I'd love to!
Where do you live?
Okay, stalker.
Oh, hello, Lisa Simpson.
And how are you
this fine evening?
Dad, stop interrogating people,
you fascist!
Wow, you're really rude
to your dad.
Thanks. That's actually
the reason I got into drums.
To drive him crazy.
But then I...
Turns out,
I really like playing music.
It takes the suck out of things.
It does take
the suck out of things.
I just said a light swear.
Well, sounds like you
girls are having fun.
How would you know?!
Yes. Well, uh,
dinner's almost ready, dear.
Lisa and I are eating
at the mall.
I've been hand-rolling
gnocchi all day.
Stop touching my food.
Food-toucher.
Look at all this science stuff.
Are you building a Frankenstein?
'Cause if you are,
you have to tell me.
Ah, yes.
Uh, you're here to pick up Lisa.
She's at the mall with my,
uh, challenging daughter.
Eh, tell me something, Simpson,
do you like beer?
Hmm, I never thought about it.
Well, I've been brewing
my own Belgian ale
in the style
of the Trappist monks.
It's a,
it's a stupid hobby really.
That is stupid.
I buy my beer in a bar.
I-I'm sure you do.
But, uh, just take a sip.
This is the most delicious drink
I ever drank
that could get me drunk.
You made this?
Yes, I did. If you'd like,
I could show you how to brew it
using these simple ingredients.
Beer has ingredients?
What the hell?
You have so much to teach me.
Okay, worked there,
got fired there.
Got unfairly accused
of shoplifting there.
Oh, shoplifted
a ton of stuff there.
Wow, you've really lived.
In this end of the mall, sure.
Cool!
A selfie machine.
Ooh, A Prom Before Dying.
I read that book.
It's about two teenagers
who fall in love despite
only having 45 minutes to live.
Sounds stupid.
Let's go see it. It's on me.
Shauna's so great.
She's like a fun, older friend
who's mean to me for no reason.
But somehow I really want
to hang out with her.
What do you call that?
Um, she seems young for a movie
with adult themes.
You have to let her in.
I'm her big sister.
That's it... big sister!
Now let's go watch teenage
sickos make out, then croak...
little sis.
You've made a very fussy enemy.
Well... later, losers!
That's what Shauna and I
call people who aren't us.
Isn't that cute?
Hmm, I'm not sure
Shauna's the best influence.
She always seems
like she's so over it.
Even when "it" is
something nice.
Yep, teens are garbage.
Anyway, I'm off to 'Mers.
Don't you mean Moe's?
No, Chalmers.
Now there's a different
sad, old man getting me drunk.
Oh, man.
Art thou as hammered as I?
Yes, verily, but, Homer,
Trappist brewing
is about more
than just drinking the beer.
It's about the traditions
of the Belgian monks
who created this divine quaff.
See, that's what I like
about home brewing.
You're there when it enters
the world, so full of promise.
And you know that if you pour
your heart and hard work
into it,
it won't tell you it's pregnant
just to mess with you.
Simpson!
I think it's time for you
to brew this next batch
on your own.
You think I'm ready?
Oh, I sense
great drunkenness in you.
Mm. I didn't think
he'd transform on page one,
but I'm not complaining.
My horror-romance!
Messing with parents
is the best.
Wow, Shauna, you're so good!
I've been thinking, you should
try out for lead drummer.
They would never give that
to me.
Even if I wanted it,
which I don't.
Why won't you shut up
about this?
Mmm, these Cheetos are cheesy.
Shauna, listen,
the last thing I'd ever do
is imply that you care,
but I think you're a star.
And stars are meant to shine.
So if you won't do this
for yourself,
will you do it for me?
I think I have
cheese dust in my eyes.
Fine, I'll do the audition.
But only to shut you up.
Yes!
Mind if I celebrate
with a sax solo?
Oh, that'd be great.
Sarcasm noted.
Huzzah, big brother!
Thank you, petit frère.
Next audition...
Shauna Chalmers?!
I am so out of here.
Shauna!
Shauna, that was great!
I won't tell anyone
how hard you practiced.
Like I care.
Thanks.
Um, Shauna, I'm sorry
to bother you,
but I'm Trevor McBride,
star quarterback.
Cool bio, Jock Cousteau.
What do you want?
Well, um,
I couldn't help but noticing
that you blew my mind tonight
with your drumming.
I'm having a pool party
at my house tomorrow.
- Do you want to come?
- Mm.
Of course, your band friends
are invited, too.
Sure. I guess.
"Sure" and "I guess"?
Crushing it!
I don't know. I've never been
to a teen party before.
Don't worry, you'll be
with your big sis.
Whatevs, it's all good, NBD.
What am I saying?
It's a huge BD!
Oh, I forgot to mention.
Everyone has to bring
a beer to get in.
Huh, I think I have
a hookup for some brews.
Hmm. Warm caramel color,
the foam is
immaculately bubbled.
Beautifully brewed,
Brother Homer.
Today, you have truly become
my padre from another madre.
I wish only to be worthy
of our humble labels.
Daddy?
I know I've been kind of
a B-word lately.
That stands for Brenda.
She's this total bitch I know.
So Lisa and I want
to apologize by, like,
putting on a little show
for you.
Shauna, that is
so thoughtful and-and...
Just shut up
and come in the house!
You're so embarrassing!
Both of you!
Sorry, Shauna.
Awesome! This beer is exactly
where the chick
said it would be.
Her name is Shauna!
Learn three things
about her that don't have
to do with her looks,
or you're off the team!
Wonderful. Shauna and I
are finally connecting.
We're just like
the Gilmore Girls.
And I'm Lorelai.
I'm so happy for you.
What?
- Bravissima! Yes!
- Yeah!
- Wonderful, wonderful!
- Yeah! All right!
Welcome to the pool party, ladies.
We've got pizza, burgers...
Possible and Impossible...
And hella soda,
courtesy of my parents.
Love you, T-Man!
Oh, my God!
It's a little girl
with a saxophone.
So cute.
Play us a song, Saxophone Girl.
Okay, sure.
I don't care what people say.
I just think music is one
of the coolest sounds out there.
Want to kiss about it?
Duh.
Trev,
Mom and I are going to one
of those fun escape rooms
in another city.
Is it okay with you
that we won't
be back for seven hours?
Oh, don't worry
about them, Brian.
It's almost nightfall.
That's when teen pizza parties
generally break up.
Bye.
Well, party's over.
Now let's make
two separate recycling piles.
The beer...
is here!
Uh, this is like
one of those TV shows
I'm not supposed to watch.
Our beer, someone stole it!
But I brewed that
with the malt of my loins.
Oh, God,
please don't let Shauna have
anything to do with this.
I'm gonna check
her social media.
She lets you follow her?
Of course not.
I follow her as "Rodrigo,"
a goth teen from Argentina.
Oh, dear God,
that so-called pool party
is a bona fide rager!
Our homebrewed beer is
inebriating these minors.
We have to go save them.
The beers I mean,
from those awful teens!
Excuse me, have you seen Shauna?
Big sister?
Cool, it's a metal beer bong.
Thanks.
Hello, emergency?
I'd like to report
the abandonment of a minor.
The minor is me!
Hurry, this party is
out of control!
What are you doing?
Did you just narc out the party,
you party narc?
Where were you?!
I was with Trevor, getting some.
- Some what?
- Some smooches.
- Duh!
- Your turn.
You give me that!
Oh, no, this is terrible.
Homer, we need to get
every one of those bottles,
or my superintending days
are over.
You abandoned me.
And I was really scared.
I thought big sisters were
supposed to take care of you.
And I thought little sisters
weren't supposed
to be stupid, snitchy babies.
I am not a stupid, snitchy baby!
It's worse than we thought, Chief.
This party's not just epic.
It's legendary.
Now, who could have given
these teens so much beer?
Uh, good evening,
Your Eminences.
May God be with you.
Chief, those are no monks!
You two are under arrest
for subjecting these kids
to the best night
of their lives.
Well, there goes my career
and my pension.
Oh, and also
I'm going to prison.
Chief?
I just breathalyzed
all these teens.
They're all blowing 0.0.
Dear God, they're already dead!
This beer contains no alcohol.
Simpson, you-you glorious idiot.
You forgot to add the yeast.
What forgot the who?
No fermentation means
no intoxication.
Mwah!
Your incompetence
just saved our cowls.
Attention teens,
you are not drunk.
Repeat... not drunk.
Please examine
your outrageous behavior
through a lens
of newfound self-awareness.
Please use this experience
to better understand
the pressures you're all under,
and have more compassion
for your friends,
teachers, parents,
and most of all,
yourselves. Over.
You bungling brewmasters
are free to go.
My career.
It's saved.
Yes.
Whoa, Rodrigo
from Instagram is crying
at our party!
Let's comfort him.
All right, yeah...
Yes, all right.
Sweetie, what are you doing
at a teenager party?
Shauna brought me!
But I never want
to see her stupid face again!
- Dad...
- Mm.
Oh, Lisa.
It's been a week now.
Are you still upset
about Shauna?
I really did think of her
like a sister.
Well, you still have
your real sister.
Well, your father and I
are headed out.
We're gonna spend
some Mommy-Daddy time.
Marge, did you get
the hotel room?
Because I got the chants
and the incense.
Ave Maria.
That must be the babysitter.
Oh, hello.
You look... well.
Thanks.
I thought I might see you here
at the house you live in.
What's going on here?
Well, whatever it is,
the awkwardness is...
...delicious.
So, how's the marching band?
I can't believe
they made me quit
when that kid's toe healed.
I hate Western medicine.
Oh, I quit, too.
I started a punk band, where I'm
the drummer and the singer.
Just like Phil Collins!
Okay, got to go.
We're called
Brenda and the B-words.
I never would have done it
without all that
stupid confidence you gave me.
Wow, that's actually
really nice to hear.
Shut up, it wasn't meant to be.
Anyway, I brought my drums.
You want to jam?
I'd like that.
Oh, dear God, no.
Captioning sponsored by
20th CENTURY FOX TELEVISION.
FOX BROADCASTING COMPANY
And FORD.
We go further, so you can.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org