The Simpsons.
Zounds! I did thee
mightily smitely.
"Zounds" is
a Renaissance English word
short for "God's wounds."
But "Smitely,"
that's pure Flanders.
Please call a doctor.
Oh, these Renaissance Faires
are so boring.
Oh, really?
Did you see
the loom?
I took loom
in high school.
Meh.
Yon meat 'tis sweet
as summer's wafting breeze.
Can I have some?
Mine ears are open
only to the pleas
of those who speak
ye olde English.
Sweet maiden
of the spit
grant now my boon,
that I might sup
upon suckling pig
this noon.
Whatever.
Oh, I've eaten
eight different meats.
I'm a true Renaissance man.
I'll go to the first aid tent
and tell them to plug in
ye olde stomach pump.
Alight your gaze
on yonder fabled beasts of yore.
Behold the rarest
of the rare,
the mythological
two-headed hound
born with only one head.
Ooh. And here
out of the mists
of history,
the legendary esquilax...
A horse with the head
of a rabbit
and the body of a rabbit.
Oh, it's
galloping away.
Here, bunny, bunny.
Here, bunny.
Here, esquilax.
I've been waiting
for you, Lisa.
How did you know my name?!
Your name tag.
Would you like to
know your future?
Sorry, I don't believe
in fortune telling.
I should go.
What's your hurry?
Bart, Maggie and Marge
are at the joust
and Homer is heckling
the puppet show.
Wow. You can see
into the... present.
Now we'll see what
the future holds.
The death card?
No, that's good.
It means
transition, change.
Oh, that's cute.
The happy squirrel!
That's bad?
Possibly.
The cards are vague
and mysterious.
They seem to
be revealing
the story of
your first love.
Do you want me
to continue?
Guess so.
It's... It's coming to me.
Yes, I see an eastern university
in the year 2010.
The world has become
a very different place.
I can't wait
to see that play.
- Hey, watch it.
- Watch it.
That man is instantly
the most annoying person
I've ever met.
A soy-based snack
will calm me down.
Him again!
Hello. I need "Ecosystem
of the Marsh" by Thompson.
The last copy was just
signed out by, um...
Hugh Parkfield.
Oh, there he is.
No!
It couldn't be.
Thanks for holding my book
while I tied my shoe.
That's the book I need.
You'll probably take
forever with it too.
I can read faster than you.
I read at a 78th grade level.
Right here.
- Finish this page?
- Ages ago.
- I'll get a dictionary.
- Why?
You'll see when you get there.
The word "stochastic."
"Pertaining to a process
"involving a
randomly determined
sequence of
observations."
Hmm. First
they hate each other,
now, all of a sudden,
they love each other.
It doesn't make
any sense to me.
Of course not.
You're a robot.
I've never met anyone
who so understood
the magic of Jim Carrey.
He can make you laugh
with no more than frantic
flailing of his limbs.
I can't believe
how much we have
in common.
We're both studying
the environment,
we're both utterly humorless
about our vegetarianism
and we both love
The Rolling Stones.
Yes, not for their music,
but for their tireless efforts
to preserve
historic buildings.
Lisa, I can't bear
the thought
of being apart from you
all summer.
Come back with me
to Parkfield Manor.
I'd love to.
Can we get vegetarian meals
at your parent's house?
Yes, we can, Lisa.
That is good because
eating animals is wrong.
So very wrong.
When will the
world learn?
I don't know.
I just don't know.
I love these
new planes.
Yes, it's a good thing
they reevaluated
those wacky old designs.
Beautiful dinnerware,
Mrs. Parkfield.
Thank you, Lisa.
They were made
for the finest
family in Britain.
I don't know
how we ended up with them.
Uh-oh. Should I laugh?
Was that dry British wit,
or subtle self-pity?
They're staring at me.
Better respond.
Oh, it's good to hear
a boisterous American laugh.
And I love
that painting.
Judging by the clothes,
I'd say 17th century.
Actually, Lisa,
it's just Uncle Eldred.
I get me brain medicines
from the National Health.
This place
is so enchanting, Hugh.
I love it here.
I wanted this
to be perfect for you.
I know you Americans
like everything to be...
fireworks.
Oh, blast!
Go to plan B.
Yes, I will.
Isn't it wonderful?
Master Hugh
has found a true love.
Hi, Mom.
Lisa, hello.
How are you doing
in England?
Remember, an elevator
is called a "lift,"
a mile is called
a "kilometer,"
and botulism is called
"steak and kidney pie."
Guess what?
Hugh and I are getting married.
All right!
Lisa, that's wonderful.
If only your father
was still with us...
but he left for work
a few minutes ago.
Mom, remember
when I was little
we'd always plan
my dream wedding
and you always promised to...
you know, well...
keep Dad from ruining it?
Oh, don't worry, honey.
I guarantee
your father will behave.
Mom, it's a picture phone.
Oh, this? This?
Oh, no, I've just got
a touch of the rheumatiz.
Mom, picture phone.
Hi, Mom.
That's great news about Lisa.
Well, listen,
I better get back to work.
They're finally
paying me for this.
Oh, yeah!
Yes, but the international
market is my focus.
Whoo-hoo!
Ah, Marge, that's great news!
Hey, hey, there with
the personal calls, Simpson.
Oh, uh, but Mr. Milhouse
my little girl's
getting married.
Lisa?
Oh... My one true love.
It's not you, Milhouse.
I just don't plan
to ever get married.
I think I'll write your
performance evaluation now,
Simpson.
Oh, I got to call everyone
and tell them the good news.
Maggie! I need to use the phone!
Will that girl ever shut up?
Okay, Marge,
I'll plan everything.
We can have
the reception at Moe's.
Wait! Why not have
the whole wedding there?
We'll do it
on a Monday morning...
There'll be fewer drunks.
Homer, don't take
this personally
but I've obtained
a court order
to prevent you from
planning this wedding.
Well,
these seem to be in order.
I'll be out back
in the hammock.
"Mr. Smithers plus guest."
Huh! There's only one person
I would want to bring.
Oh, Mr. Burns,
we'll thaw you out
the second they
discover the cure
for 17 stab wounds
in the back.
How we doing, boys?
Well, we're up to 15.
Now turn to
the next problem.
If you have three Pepsis
and drink one
how much more refreshed
are you?
You, the redhead in
the Chicago school system?
Pepsi?
Partial credit.
We've been invited
to the wedding
of our only graduate to
read at an adult level.
It must be Lisa Simpson.
Because, of course,
Martin Prince perished
in that science fair explosion.
Not quite perished,
my lady love.
Although some days,
I wish I had.
Hey, I remember you.
Mayor Quimby, right?
Uh, no. Look at this license...
Mohamed Jafar.
Quimby, after this fare
get your indicted ass out to
the convention center.
I cut the ribbon
at that convention center.
Just a couple more blocks
to my house.
Lisa, darling,
don't worry.
I'm sure I'll get along
with your family.
You've so thoroughly
prepared me for the worst.
As long as they're not
squatting in a ditch
poking berries
up their noses.
And if they are?
Here they come!
Raise the flag!
Oh, Lisa!
Yo, Hugh!
Here's a little bit
of U.S. hospitality.
What do you think of that?
Dad!
Now throw compost on it.
Enjoy.
Still warm.
You can be the first
to try out
the new guest bedroom I built.
Remember, if the building
inspector comes by
it's not a room,
it's a window box.
Oh, Hugh, thank you.
You've been just wonderful
through this entire ordeal.
Lisa,
I love you so much
I'm willing to go
through anything.
Are you okay?
I'm fine, Lisa.
Fortunately,
the compost heap
broke my fall.
Be a dear, run a bath.
Homer, Bart, Maggie,
company eating rules, huh?
Oh, right.
Anyway, Hugh,
there's more to my life
than just the wrecking ball.
I also crush cars into cubes.
And on the side, I promote
local tough man contests.
Basically, I'm getting out
all my aggression
till I go to law school.
So, Hugh, have you heard all
the latest American jokes?
Here's a good one.
Pull my finger.
Oh, yes, we have that one
in England too, Mr. Simpson.
I said, pull my finger!
Mom, we've got my wedding dress
fitting this afternoon.
Maggie, if you're
not doing anything,
why don't you
come with us?
Maggie, don't talk
with your mouth full!
Me and Bart will take Hugh
out on the town this afternoon.
Hugh should take it easy
because of his fall.
Oh, Lisa, please.
The only thing bruised
in that fall was my spine.
I'll be delighted.
Great. There's only one thing
I ask in return.
- Certainly.
- Pull my finger!
So, this driving
on the left
makes you feel
more at home, huh, Hugh?
And tonight,
the following celebrities
have been arrested...
while Heather Locklear
Fortensky
remains at large.
Remember, if you see
any celebrities
consider them dangerous.
You know, I rather
like this pub.
Oh-ho! An English boy, huh?
You know, we saved your ass
in World War II.
Yeah, well we saved
your ass in World War III.
That's true.
Hugh, there's something
I want you to have.
My dad gave me
his cufflinks to wear
on the day
I married Marge
and they brought
us good luck.
I couldn't imagine
a happier marriage.
We don't have many
traditions in our family
but it'd mean
a lot to me
if you kept
this one alive.
Well, I'd be honored.
To...
wear those... things.
Hey, watch those
virtual darts!
I'm trying to play
virtual pool.
Ow! Why you!
Hey! Hey!
No fighting in my bar!
You know,
Fox turned into
a hard-core sex
channel so gradually
I didn't even notice.
Eesh!
Marge, it's so great
to have the whole family
together under one roof.
I never realized
how much I missed it.
Listen to the murmurs
in the next room.
The house is full
of life again.
Keep it down in there!
All right, Dad!
I'm sorry I left you alone
with Homer and Bart.
No, no, honey.
We had a fine time.
How did you get that gash
on your forehead?
Oh, that was when
we hid in the dumpster
after the fire alarm
went off
in the pornographic
magazine warehouse.
Oh... You are so good
to put up with all of this.
Oh, don't be silly, Lisa.
Everything's fine...
Really.
Now go to sleep.
We have a big day
ahead of us tomorrow.
A big, long day.
Lisa, I can't believe
it's your
wedding day already.
Mom, I feel kind of
funny wearing white.
I mean, Milhouse...
Oh, Milhouse doesn't count.
Okay, I've got
something old,
that's my pearl necklace.
Something new
is the wedding dress.
Something borrowed
is this antique brooch
from Hugh's mother.
Now I just need
something blue.
Here.
Oh, Mom, thanks.
Hi!
Wow, Lisa,
looking at you
makes me want
to get married
for a third time.
I met a really
nice exotic dancer
the other night
at Hugh's bachelor party.
Hugh didn't have
a bachelor party.
We had one in his honor.
I had one in his honor.
I went to a strip club.
Well, here goes nothing.
Mom, Dad, meet...
Homer Simpson.
- How do you do?
- How are you?
Nice to meet you.
You know what's great
about you English?
"Octopussy."
Man, I must have
seen that movie... twice.
Yes...
Yes!
Well, that's not too bad.
Hey, Krabappel.
You get in the way
of that bouquet,
I'll stuff that sun hat
down your neck.
Smithers, take me home.
I'm not fully defrosted.
Nonsense.
Just sit down
and rest for a moment.
Here you go.
Oh, no.
We've got a little
situation here.
I can't feel anything
below my cummerbund.
Ooh-la-la!
Hi, Dad.
You look great,
sweetheart.
Thanks.
Little Lisa,
Lisa Simpson.
You know, I always felt
you were the best thing
my name ever got
attached to.
Since the time you learned
to pin your own diapers,
you've been smarter than me.
- Oh, Dad.
- No, no. Let me finish.
I just want you to know,
I've always been proud of you.
You're my greatest
accomplishment
and you did it
all yourself.
You helped me understand
my own wife better
and taught me to be
a better person
but you're also my daughter.
I don't think anybody could have
had a better daughter than...
- Dad, you're babbling.
- See? You're still helping me.
Hey, Dad, did you forget to
give those cufflinks to Hugh?
- Uh... no.
- Well?
I found them on
the nightstand this morning.
I guess they weren't
his cup of tea.
Don't worry about it.
But you've been going on
about these all week.
I'm sure he just forgot.
Lisa! We're not
supposed to see
each other
before the wedding.
It's tradition.
What about
my family's tradition?
Surely, you don't want
me to wear those
in front of my parents
and their friends?
But you promised
my dad you would.
I was just humoring
him, darling.
Actually, he frightens
me a bit.
I know they look
a little silly
but his feelings will be hurt
if you don't wear them.
Fine.
I must say,
you were right.
This has been quite trying.
You know, I've attempted
to enjoy your family
on a personal level,
on an ironic level,
as a novelty, as camp,
as kitsch,
as a cautionary example...
Nothing works.
Frankly, I'll be quite relieved
when we get back to England
and we won't have
to deal with them.
Are you saying we won't
see my family again?
Well, possibly
your mother will come
when the children are born.
I can't believe
I'm hearing this.
I don't want to cut
my family out of my life.
Oh, really?
But Lisa, you're better
than this place...
You're like a flower that grew
out of a pot of dirt.
That's a horrible
thing to say!
Oh, come on, you complain
about them more than anyone.
Maybe,
but I still love them,
and I don't think
you understand that.
And now,
to sing "Amazing Grace".
Miss Maggie Simpson.
She's quite a hellion
but she does have
an incredible voice.
Stop everything!
The wedding has been
called off.
Uh, this is very sad news
and it never would've happened
if the wedding had been
inside the church with God
instead of out here in the
cheap showiness of nature.
Who wants cake?
The next day,
Hugh goes back to England
and you never see him again.
Wow! Now that
I know all this
isn't there any way
to change the future?
No, but try to look surprised.
I thought you said you'd
tell me about my true love.
Oh, you'll have
a true love
but I specialize in foretelling
the relationships where
you get jerked around.
Lisa! Lisa!
Where were you?
You missed the most
incredible thing!
Hi, Dad.
I ate seven pounds of fudge!
Wow!
The man at the stand
said it was a record.
Wow, what else
did you do, Dad?
I rode the teacups.
Then I got a little sick
and I had to sit down.
But then I rode them again...
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.