(SINGING) The Simpsons
(SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
(BEEPING)
Ripped By mstoll
(PLAYING DIFFERENT TUNE)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(HONKING)
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
D'oh!
(EXCLAIMING)
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
Welcome to Matinee of Blood
and Commercials.
I am your hostess, Booberella.
I hope you enjoy our
Labor Day Marathon of Murder
because soon, you have
to go back to school.
(DEMONIC LAUGH)
School!
Back to school?
Oh, my God. I've wasted
the whole summer.
There are so many things
I still want to do!
You think
you're behind?
Hmm...
Mmm... Hmm.
If it weren't
for my trick knee,
I'd do them both right now.
I've gotta squeeze a whole summer
of carefree fun into one day.
Win baseball game.
You're up, Simpson.
Be careful.
That kid on the pitcher's
mound is really 22.
(INAUDIBLE)
Son, you have time
for the pizza party?
Sure. Why not?
(INAUDIBLE)
BART: Mmm-hmm.
(READING)
(SINGING) That's Grease
Sit on it, Springfield!
Yeah!
(ALL CHEERING)
See summer blockbuster.
(ROARING)
Get outta my face,
you raggedy maggots.
Oh, so, that's why everyone's
been saying that all summer.
No, not yet. I have to
have a summer romance.
I'll never forget you.
Mmm.
Gotta go.
Mmm-hmm.
(SIGHS)
I just had
my first kiss.
When you get to third base,
I'll buy you a beer.
Mmm-hmm.
Well, now it's time
for my summer activity.
You all promised we
could go to a museum.
BOTH: Oh!
I'm so glad you picked the
Museum of Natural History, Mom.
Well, I'm so glad there's a
show we women can enjoy.
Weaving? Homer,
you're my father.
You're supposed to protect
me from things like this.
All right.
Just this once
you can take a drink out
of my special water bottle.
(GASPS)
BOTH; What?
Sorry, loom-wads.
New exhibit's in town.
BOTH: Whoo-hoo!
Weapons!
Bart, it's still history.
Not if I spend the whole time
running around like this.
(IMITATING GUNFIRE)
Die, weapons, die!
Don't start
the exhibit without me.
(BOTH IMITATING GUNFIRE)
(BOTH GASP)
HOMER: Oh,
look at that line.
Time to do
what I do best,
ruin it for everybody.
Hey, Flanders. Thanks
for saving our place.
But wait, wait. Hold the
phone there, Homer...
Oh, dude.
I was totally here.
You calling me a liar
in front of my kids?
Because I'd take a bullet for
you, man, right in the mouth.
Ah... Ah...
Oh, fine.
Take the cut.
Ned Flanders
is doling out cuts?
I for one wish
to partake of said.
(HUMMING)
Hey, if Boner here is getting
cuts, I want 'em, too!
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
Disco Stu slides
in front of you.
Hey, that rhymes.
(GRUNTING)
(CHUCKLES)
Tell you what.
If we turn around, it'll feel like
we're at the front of the line.
BOTH: Yay!
Oh, no you don't!
I'm everywhere.
ANNOUNCER:
IMAX 3D Films presents...
Nunchucks:
Cool But Useless.
The nunchuck was invented thousands
of years ago by a Chinese monk.
Artifacts of the time indicate
that this incident was hilarious.
Wow!
This 3D is amazing.
You can actually feel the face.
(GROANING)
Go ahead, Maggie.
You're allowed to touch
the deadly weapons.
Oh, it's a mugger! I'll hand
over all my hugs and kisses.
Okay, be cool. I've got
some candy in my purse.
(LAUGHING) Ow!
(GROANING)
Stop!
Come on, Milhouse. Do you want
to play in the NBA or not?
Bart, my arm's out
of its thing.
That means it's working.
(STRAINING)
(CRACKING)
Whassup?
(SCOFFS)
You're leaving already?
(STAMMERING) We haven't
even gotten in yet.
Sorry' Flanders,
but when you get in,
you can use my audio tour
narrated by Melanie Griffith.
GRIFFITH: This room's nice.
Let's go into the next one.
This room's nice, too.
(GROANS)
GRIFFITH: This room's nice.
This room's nice, too.
This room's nice.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Sorry, folks.
The weapons exhibit
is now closed for the day.
BOTH: Yay?
Sorry. No "Ya?"
But you can all feel free to
enjoy the rest of the museum.
(GASPS) Evolution.
(GASPS)
(SCREAMS) Excuse me.
How can you put up an exhibit
on the origin of man,
and not have one
mention of the Bible?
Oh, we do.
My most cherished
beliefs' a myth?
Daddy, was Mommy
a monkey?
I can't remember.
No one was
ever a monkey!
Everything is what it was
and always will be.
God put us here
and that's that.
But you said
a stork brought me.
Yeah, that was God
disguised as a stork.
Who brings baby storks?
(SCOFFS) There's no
such thing as storks!
It's all God!
Please bless Daddy
and Roddy...
Stop praying
to that stork!
They're telling people we're
descended from a pack of apes
even though there's nothing
about it in the Bible!
Ned, you've gotta take this
thing with a grain of salt.
(CHUCKLES)
I mean, come on.
Tim, this controversy could
put more meat in the seats.
Well, our membership
has been dwindling
since those Episcopalians
put in those vibrating pews.
(WHIRRING)
(ALL SIGHING)
Evolution is
the hot button issue.
We need to mobilize
our flock.
They'll be hanging
on your every word.
(GASPS) I'll be
a white Al Sharpton!
(CHUCKLING) Mmm.
Why does every church
meeting end this way?
We want you to teach alternative
theories to Darwinian evolution.
You mean
Lamarckian evolution?
No. The Adam
and Eve one.
Ha! And what if
I say no?
I believe you leased
your Camry
from Christian
Brothers Auto?
(GASPS) No! That was
a once-in-a-lifetime APR!
Class, starting today,
we will be presenting
an alternative theory
on the origin of man.
Creationism?
But that's not science.
It is now.
Are oceans God's tears?
They sure are.
A-plus.
Ugh!
Now Lisa's the Ralph.
How can you teach the Book of
Genesis as a scientific theory?
Mmm. This helpful video
will evade all your questions.
Eyes screen-ward!
(NARRATOR READING)
Let's say hi to two books.
One, the Bible,
was written by our Lord.
The other,
The Origin of Species,
was written by a cowardly
drunk named Charles Darwin.
(GROANS)
This is slander!
Darwin was one of the
greatest minds of all time!
Then why is he
making out with Satan?
(MOANING)
Evolution is widely acknowledged
as scientific fact!
It's even accepted
by prominent conservatives
like George Will and the
late Pope John Paul!
That's something
to think about.
The George Will?
Lisa, you've said
quite enough.
Children, drown her out with
whistling and arm flatulence.
All I'm saying is...
(WHISTLING)
(FARTING SOUNDS)
(MARGE HUMMING)
(GASPS)
(GROANING)
(SIGHS)
What's wrong, sweetie?
They're making us learn
creation theory in school.
Today we had a test and every
answer was "God did it."
Well, l think it's good to give
both ideas a fair hearing.
Maybe they could learn
from each other.
But they're incompatible!
Lisa, lots of times two incompatible
things can both be true.
My son's a brat but
he's a special little guy.
Your father says
he's at work
but there he is jumping
on a trampoline.
(LAUGHING)
Morn, you really
have to choose here
between science
and belief.
Well, then I choose...
Uh...
(CHOMPING)
So according
to creationism,
there were
no cavemen.
Good riddance. Their drawings
suck and they look like hippies.
Dad, you're not really
reconsidering evolution, are you?
My mind is always
open to new ideas.
Onions in the peas?
What the hell?
(GRUNTS)
(GLASS SHATTERS)
(DOG HOWLING)
It is agreed
regular people can park
in handicapped spaces
if they're just running in
to buy smokes
or maybe some
Pop-Tarts for tomorrow.
The system works.
And if there's no
further business,
I hereby declare
this meeting...
I have an issue
I'd like to raise.
Curse my slow gaveling.
Last week, the unscientific
theory of creationism
was introduced
alongside evolution
in Springfield
public schools.
(LAUGHS) Now honestly,
the Bible's about
the same age as, uh,
the rest of our textbooks.
(LAUGHS)
Evolution and creationism
cannot coexist, people.
It is time to go back
to teaching one single truth!
Homer's son's
sister is right!
(INDISTINCT TALKING)
Class, the town
has spoken.
From now on, we're only teaching
one theory, creationism.
Now please, hand in your evolution
books to Groundskeeper Willie
while I beat
this ominous drum.
(PLAYING DRUM)
Ah, there seems to be
a note on your locker.
From a secret
admirer perhaps.
Mmm, don't make
me laugh.
Ha, ha, ha!
(READING)
“L.M.S”
Who could it be?
(VIDEO GAME NOISES)
Little Moe Szyslak?
Why does everybody
call me that?
Bunch of snot-faced
puke bags!
I'm so glad you
could all come.
I will be reading to you from The
Origin of Species by Charles Darwin.
Oh! I thought we were gonna
light spiders on fire.
We're over here.
(GRUNTS)
Y'all have a nice day.
"Chapter One. When we
compare the individuals
"of the same variety
or sub-variety
"of our older cultivated
plants and animals..."
Lisa Simpson.
You're under arrest
for the teaching of
non-Biblical science.
(GASPS) Ugh.
There are so many
worse crimes.
Why are you
persecuting me?
Uh, well, we only have the manpower
to enforce the last law passed.
You know, it's not
the best system but...
Well, in fact, it's, uh...
It's pretty much the worst.
(GUNFIRE)
You live. You die.
(CHUCKLES)
In the old days, we would've
been all over that.
(SNAKE LAUGHS)
This is Kent Brockman reporting
live from the trial of
God v. Lisa Simpson.
Defending Ms. Simpson is ACLU-appointed
liberal, Clarice Drummond.
I'm from New York.
(ALL BOOING)
And prosecuting
the case against Lisa
is humble country lawyer,
Wallace Brady.
As the little chicken said to his
mama, I just hope I don't cluck up.
ALL: Aw.
I think it's fair to say
if that man doesn't win,
I'm resigning
from the jury.
This is Kent Brockman,
juror number seven, saying,
"I'll have the roast beef
for lunch."
So, does this theory of evolution
necessarily mean that there is no God?
No, of course not.
It just says that God is an
impotent nothing from nowhere
with less power than the
undersecretary of agriculture,
who has very little power
in our system.
(LAUGHING)
Now, sir, you are a
scientist, correct?
Oh, that's right. I have a Ph.D.
in truthology from Christian Tech.
ALL: Ooh.
Move over, Carl.
I got a new hero.
Yeah. This'll last
about a day.
So as a scientist, what is your
take on this "devil-ution"?
(LAUGHING)
Pure hogwash.
If man evolved from monkeys,
there'd be evidence.
But when we look at the fossil
record, here's what we see.
A missing link.
(ALL GASP)
(CHUCKLES)
I believe, right now, this
gentleman's having dinner
with the tooth fairy
and the Easter bunny.
This is the break in the
case we've been waiting for!
I mean, he doesn't exist.
Evolution is just a lot
of that Hollywood hooey.
(ALL GASP)
Well, I've heard
enough for today.
I have to judge a wet T-shirt
contest in 20 minutes.
(SCOFFS) This trial is
the biggest load of...
Oh, for crying out loud!
Now, Bambi, who started that
forest fire that killed your mama?
Evolution?
My, my, my.
Poor Bambi.
Poor Thumper.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
I'm sorry, Mom.
I should have just gone with
the flow like you said.
MARGE: Hmm.
Well, I might as well see
what all the fuss is about.
Homer...
Homer, please.
I love it when you're not into it.
Oh, yeah, baby.
Oh, yeah. That's it.
Ignore me.
I'm not even here.
Wow. Darwin's argument
is incredibly persuasive.
And his ship was the Beagle,
which reminds me of Snoopy,
my favorite Peanut.
Aw...
Lisa, I think I have a way to
help you at the trial today.
So do I.
Milhouse will serve the time for
you while you flee to Mexico.
Your new name?
Senorita Ugly.
Honey, I appreciate the thought
but just leave everything to me.
Oh...
You can take off
the wig, Milhouse.
I'm Nelson.
(GASPS)
Now, Mr. Flanders, you're
familiar with the Bible, correct?
As familiar as
it's proper to be.
Don't worry, Lisa.
I've got the answer to
your problems right here.
Look, Homie.
I brought you a beer.
Thanks, Marge.
(STRAINING)
It's not a twist-off.
(CONTINUES STRAINING)
Come on.
And you are positive that man
and ape cannot be related?
As sure as I am that
Jesus hates hip-hop!
Come on, open.
I want what's in you!
(GIBBERING)
As a matter...
Want you...
Homer.
Stupid.
(GIBBERING)
Homer, I'm trying to...
Would you shut your yap,
you big monkey-faced gorilla!
(ALL GASP)
Mr. Flanders, you've sworn
to tell the truth.
Can you say that this man could not
possibly be related to that ape?
(GIBBERING)
You win, Lisa.
This court hereby rules
that the law forbidding the
teaching of evolution is repealed.
(GRUNTS)
Oh, wait.
It was a twist-off.
Oh, thanks, Mom.
Thank you, honey,
for opening my eyes.
I can't wait to see what
evolution will make next.
Maybe a bird
with a people face,
or a bear with pants on.
NED: Let's go, boys.
Your poor old
Popsicle's been licked.
Mr. Flanders, wait.
Hmm?
I want you to know
I respect your beliefs
and I can see how deeply
you feel about them.
I just don't think religion
should be taught in our schools,
any more than you'd want
scientists teaching at the church.
Well, l wish this
world would evolve
a few more kids
like you, Lisa.
What say we take
our worthy adversary
out for a hot fudge
fun-day?
(NELSON'S VOICE)
Cram it, ya God-wad.
(GIBBERING) Wha...
Ripped By mstoll