(SINGING) The Simpsons
Ripped by jasonnguyen2606
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
D'oh!
(EXCLAIMING)
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
BART: Checking out a cave
is gonna be awesome!
It'll be dark, with rocks
and mineral formations,
and plants that
have adapted to harsh...
Wait a minute.
This is a scam.
We're on a nature walk!
(GRUNTING)
Don't worry, Bart. I brought something
that'll keep you interested.
A nickel in
a water bottle.
Wow. Wow. Wow!
(LAUGHING)
Oh, he'll sleep tonight.
Where'd it go?
Oh, it's in the cap.
(LAUGHING)
MARGE:
"Local Anahoopi Indians
"believed this stalactite
was the finger of Tsisnajini,
"their God of pointing down."
(SCOFFING) Silly Indians.
Our God made their God.
It's so impressive.
I'm just gonna get a tiny chip
to put on my desk at work.
(FAINT RUMBLING)
(ALL GASPING)
(ALL SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
Save me, Tsisnajini!
(ALL GRUNTING)
(STRAINING)
I'm stuck!
And I have to pee!
Now I'm just stuck.
(ALL STRUGGLING)
Don't worry, Homer.
We'll get that fireman who cut
you out of that teacup ride.
That was two firemen,
a crane, and Snow White.
Why you little... (STRUGGLING)
(LAUGHING)
Oh, no! This chamber's
not on the map.
We could be stuck in here forever
if we don't find a way out.
Well, we better
start looking.
Don't leave me!
I hate to be alone!
Except when I'm watching TV.
Then leave me alone.
But right now,
don't leave!
I'll stay with you, Dad.
Will you tell me a story?
Sure.
Once upon a time
in a far off kingdom...
No unicorns.
Oh, all right.
Um, I'll tell you something
that happened to me last week.
I was walking home
from school
when suddenly
I heard...
(BLEATING)
Oh, hello,
Mister Bighorn Sheep.
(SNORTING)
I've read about you.
You're shy and you
rarely approach humans.
(SNORTING LOUDLY)
(LAUGHING NERVOUSLY)
And of course, you'd never
attack a fellow herbivore!
Mad beast!
Liberal midget!
(YELPING)
(EXHALING)
(SCREAMING)
Good Lord,
a wooly bully.
(BOTH YELLING)
LISA: Come on!
(BOTH PANTING)
(SQUEALING)
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Enter password.
Damn it, I forget.
Forgot password?
Enter place of birth.
Pangaea...
Correct Your password has
been e-mailed to you.
D'oh! (GASPING)
Whoa!
(BOTH PANTING)
(BLEATING)
(BOTH YELPING)
So long, sucker. Oof.
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
I mean, don't leave
an old man to die.
So long, sucker!
(SCREAMING)
(PANTING)
(STRUGGLING)
Maybe Mr. Smithers
will help us.
No. He's out getting
a spray-on tan.
He comes back orange
and stains the furniture.
The man's a walking
creamsicle.
Hmm...
You worked at Moe's?
Yes, and therein lies a
tale of woe and heartbreak.
One I couldn't
possibly recount.
I understand. I'll
just read a magazine.
Okay,
here's the story.
I belong to
a very exclusive club.
The Excluders' Club.
Hmm.
MR. BURNS: One day, while I was
savoring the exclusivity...
HOMER: Wait.
Wait, wait, wait.
Now you're telling
me Burns' story?
Yeah, it's like the play
within a play in Hamlet.
Huh?
Let's see.
It's like when you watch old
home movies of you watching TV.
Gotcha.
MR. BURNS: One day, a new
member arrived at the club.
Yee-haw!
Who's this
dried-up old apricot?
(GRUNTING)
I'm in oil. What's
your racket, Slim?
Nuclear power!
I make money
using my brain,
not sticking a pole in the
ground and praying for goo.
(LAUGHING)
You need to get your
hands dirty, Poindexter!
Dip 'em in
a little Texas crude!
(LAUGHING) Down in Houston, we
call that a Fort Worth shampoo!
Sir, I challenge
you to a duel!
You got it.
A bullet in the brain
at high noon.
(GASPING)
At my age,
that could kill me.
How about we settle things
with a scavenger hunt?
You're on, Twiggy!
(GASPING)
Sorry about that.
(SQUISHING)
Gentlemen, you will each be given
an identical list of 10 items.
The first person to collect all
items on said list is the winner.
And shall receive all of his
opponent's worldly possessions.
Yee-haw!
I'm gonna win me
a nucular plant!
Dream on, bitch.
Scavengers, scavenge!
Whoa! Hmm?
(SHRIEKING)
I'm bald!
MR. BURNS: I had but
one item left on the list.
A picture of myself
with a smiling child.
(GIGGLING)
What could be easier?
(ALL SCREAMING)
It's the boogeyman's
grandfather!
He's gonna
drink our bones!
Smile. Like this.
(STRAINING)
(ALL SCREAMING)
Yee-haw!
I won! Everything yours is mine!
(SIGHING)
Hi-yo, Smithers, away!
(GRUNTING)
MR BURNS:
With nowhere else to turn,
I spent the first
three days with relatives.
(OWLS HOOTING)
I had to get a job. And I
had to start at the bottom.
But to get to the bottom,
I had to work my way
up from Moe's.
Hey, bar boy.
This table's wobbly. Come
jam your foot under it.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Hey, bar boy, write a play where I
meet Henry Ford and Captain Kirk.
Hey, bar boy, dance
around like an idiot.
Like this.
"I'm so stupid.
I'm so stupid."
I'm a little busy.
Can I do it later?
Sure.
(LAUGHING)
You're gonna be all,
"I'm so stupid. I'm so stupid.
I'm so stupid..."
(ALL LAUGHING)
Burns sure will
look like a jerk later.
MR. BURNS:
At $5.15 an hour,
it would take an eternity
to make my fortune back.
And FICA wasn't helping.
D'oh!
But then, for once in my life,
things went my way.
I steamed the letter open with
Moe's cappuccino machine.
MOE: if you're reading this,
I am dead.
And you are about to learn
the stow of my treasure.
Treasure?
Moe has a
cappuccino machine?
(MARGE SIGHING)
We couldn't find
a way out.
But on the upside,
I found some cave paintings
and made them awesome.
(LAUGHING)
Boy, come here and
listen to Lisa's story.
It's about Moe's treasure.
Mmm...
Oh...
Soto continue...
...with the sad story...
MOE: ...of Moe's treasure.
It was the first day
of summer.
(WHISTLING)
I was heading to the
restaurant supply store
to buy some
urinal cake mix
when I was suddenly
sideswiped.
By love.
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
D'oh!
(GROANING)
There she was, the gorgeous new
girl in town, Edna Krabappel.
Oh, you poor man.
MOE: She had gossamer hair, limpid
eyes, and the rack of an angel.
I see you're new to town. Maybe
I could, uh, show you around.
I know a terrific tavern.
Ha! My ex-husband
was a drunk.
I hate bars,
saloons, nightclubs,
and most of all,
taverns.
Oh, yeah, me, too. That's why
I'm not a tavern keeper.
What do you do
for a living?
Me? Well, I, uh...
For a living, well...
There's, uh, all kinds
of things a fella can do,
such as hemming,
and, uh, hawing and...
But me, I'm a highly-respected,
um, therapist for alcoholics.
Oh...
MOE: I knew that in
order to win her love,
I needed to get rid
of the human garbage
otherwise known
as my best friends.
(GRUNTING)
BARNEY: on!
CARL: Come on!
(GRUNTING)
Barney, how do you
keep getting back in?
I'm a drunk. I don't know nothing
about how I do anything.
Whoa!
(FRANK SINATRA SINGING)
Fly me to the moon
Let me play
among the stars
MOE: For one sweet summer,
I was a true gentleman,
as a result of which, Krabappel
was letting me do her.
So, Mrs. Krabappel,
you got any plans?
In the fall, I'll be teaching fourth
grade at Springfield Elementary.
Oh, that's great.
Wonderful bunch of kids.
Lab partners don't treat
lab partners like this!
Shut up and
attract lightning!
Edna, you've made me feel love
where before there was only pain.
Come here, you.
Oh, jeez.
Hey, Moe, thanks to you,
I've been sober a week.
Yeah, me, too.
Yeah, we're all sober.
Uh, these are some of the local
alcoholics I told you about.
Don't pigeonhole us.
We have other vices.
I dress up like a baby.
Ah, come on, guys, let me give
you some counseling over here.
(GRUNTING) Listen, booze bags,
I got a good thing going here.
If you mess it up, I will out
the one of you that is gay.
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
So, uh, where were we?
I had to get Edna
out of Springfield,
make a fresh start
in a new town far away.
A place where we could play
bridge with our neighbors.
And if they're interested in wife
swapping, who am I to say no?
I mean,
I'm just the new guy.
But where would I get the
money to start a new life?
And then opportunity
strolled right in the door.
Yes, hello. I need directions to the
Springfield Natural History Museum.
I totally have a
donation for them.
Coins, money, gold!
See, this was back before Snake
became a notorious jailbird,
when he was an idealistic,
law-abiding young archeologist.
I was, like, excavating
this Mayan pyramid
and I totally unearthed
these gold coins.
And I'm all like, "Could you
be anymore pre-Columbian?"
Uh, you can't donate that
gold to the museum today
because, um,
it's closed
so they can clean under
the wangs of the statues.
Oh. Well, no problem.
I'll just spend the night in that
motel across the street there.
MOE: Love had handed
me an awful dilemma.
Should I rob this guy,
or rob him and kill him?
I decided to do
the right thing.
I've been robbed!
I'll take my revenge
on society,
by which I mean
convenience stores.
And who would suspect me,
Professor Jailbird?
MOE: Before we left town for
good, we had to make one stop
so she could tell the school she
wouldn't be teaching there.
Back in a flash,
my sweet little gargoyle.
(LAUGHING)
Aww.
MOE: I was the happiest
guy in the world.
But fate likes to play a little
game called "Up yours, Moe."
Moe, we need to talk.
About what? How nothing changed
when you were in there?
Not exactly. You see,
when I went inside...
(GASPING) Young man,
it's summertime.
What are you doing here?
I've got detention
all summer.
Why?
Because I'm a screw-up.
My sister's the smart one.
All I do is get in trouble.
Aw, sweetheart,
do you want to do better?
Oh, it doesn't matter.
Everyone's pretty much
given up on me.
I bet I won't even make
it through fourth grade.
(MOE HUMMING)
You'll make it
through fourth grade.
Because I'm gonna stay
here and be your teacher.
MARGE: Wait, wait, wait. There's
one thing I don't understand here.
You never had
detention all summer.
Oh, that load of crap?
(LAUGHING)
No, I was just
keeping her busy
while Nelson
stole microscopes.
Make with the story.
Well, my best
recollection of
Burns' paraphrasing of what
he read in Moe's letter
is that Krabappel told Moe...
I have to stay here
in Springfield
because boys like
Bart Simpson need me.
Sweet, misunderstood boys who
just need someone to recognize
the basic goodness
that's trapped inside them
and is desperately
trying to get out.
MOE: There was
nothing I could do.
Well, except go nuts.
You crazy skirt! Nobody
backs out on fake-good Moe!
I ought to...
(TALKING GIBBERISH)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(FRANK SINATRA SINGING)
In other words
I love...
(SOBBING)
MOE: If I couldn't spend the treasure
on Edna, I didn't want to spend it.
I just sat there playing
our song on the jukebox,
one gold...
"...coin at a time."
Oh, you poor man.
You're about to
get a lot poorer.
(GRUNTING)
Okay, I'll take your gold
and give you back all
your worldly possessions,
excepting
your nucular plant.
You don't get
that back
till you bring me a photo of
yourself with a smiling child.
(SCOFFING) What the hell
could that mean to you?
I'm obsessive compulsive!
Yee-haw!
One, two, three, four.
No nucular plant without a photo.
That's where we left off.
One, two, three, four.
So, without my
beloved nuclear plant,
I have nothing
to live for.
(ROARING)
(BOTH SCREAMING)
Hmm.
(SHIVERING)
Take me, a barren,
old thistle,
and spare this sweet,
young flower.
(BLEATING)
(GASPING)
My pearl necklace.
I must've lost it and you were
just bringing it back to me?
(EXASPERATED BLEATING)
How did you find this?
(RAMBLING BLEATING)
(SHOCKED BLEATING)
MR. BURNS: Ooh.
The sheep was
no danger at all.
I sacflficed my gorgeous
body for nothing.
This must be what it's
like to have a baby.
I want a photo of the hero who
risked his life to save me.
(GASPING)
A picture of me
with a smiling child.
I can get my plant back!
(GIGGLING)
100 Industrial Way!
Mr. Burns got
his plant back,
and I like to think I found a shred
of humanity in his withered soul.
(SNIFFLING) Oh, Dad. Did
my story make you cry'?
(SOBBING)
Well, it was very moving.
But the thing is,
bats are chewing my legs!
(SCREAMING)
(BATS SCREECHING)
Oh, why did I lead you down here
to find those stupid coins?
(ALL ARGUING AT ONCE)
MARGE: This wasn't just an innocent family outing?
Homer, you brought us to this
horrible place on purpose?
Oh, you didn't think
it was so horrible
when you were
falling down the hole.
That was the most
horrible part of all!
Well, I guess
I should explain.
Not long ago, it was my day
to take care of the baby.
So I was out in
the forest hiding.
(SNORING)
RICH TEXAN: (SINGING) Oh, the yellow
gold of Texas is what I wanna save
I will not pay no taxes
if I hide it in a cave
HOMER: I deduced
from his parody lyrics
that he was hiding
gold in the cave.
I figured he'd never
miss two or three pieces,
money which we could use
to pay for Bart's operation.
I need an operation?
That's a story
for another day.
I realized I could never find
the gold without your help.
So I made it this
week's family outing.
(GUN COCKING) I'll take
that gold if'n you please.
How can you take it?
We haven't found it.
It's right there
behind that rock.
No, to your left.
Texas left,
which is your down.
Oh...
I'll take that gold if'n you please.
(GUN COCKING)
MR. BURNS: Not so fast,
Shady Bird Johnson.
I'll take that gold.
MOE: Yeah, you'll take it.
And then you'll give it to me if
you know what's good for you.
(GUNS COCKING)
You guys have guns?
Well, so do I!
(IMITATING GUN COCKING)
Huh? Huh?
SNAKE: Yo!
Coolest entrance
gets the gold.
Um, is it okay that
I brought my son?
This is my day
with him.
Jeremy, there's a boy over
there you can play with.
Do you like Xbox?
RICH TEXAN: Looks like we
got us a Mexican stand-off.
(GUN COCKING)
(GRUNTING) If you all don't drop your
guns and behave, no one gets the gold!
And why do you really
want it anyway?
Moe, will the gold
bring back Edna's love?
It could, definitely.
Mr. Burns,
isn't it more important
that you got a child
to smile at you?
Honestly, no.
I'd rather have the gold.
Oh, absolutely.
I couldn't agree more.
I can see there's only one way to
turn you into human beings again.
(GRUNTING)
(ALL GASPING)
Lady, I ought to
fill you full of...
...gratitude!
(LAUGHING)
That gold was turning us
into monsters.
Well, I know a place where we
can atone for our misdeeds.
They're building a youth center in
Shelbyville and totally need volunteers.
Let's go there now.
Yes, let's.
I'll, uh...
I'll catch up with you.
(STRUGGLING)
And that's why
I didn't have time
to study for
my geography test.
Bart, do you expect
me to believe that?
That story is
the biggest load of...
Krabappel?
Making out with Moe?
But I thought you didn't
want to date a tavern owner.
At this point, all I want is
a man with a healthy libido.
Uh-huh. Well, this is where
it gets awkward again.
Yee-haw!
Moe can't catch a break!
One, two, three, four.
Can't catch a break.
RICH TEXAN:
And there's some producers.
One... two, three, four.
Four producers.
Ripped by jasonnguyen2606