(SINGING) The Simpsons
(SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
Ripped By mstoll
(HORN BELLOWING)
(PLAYING DIFFERENT TUNE)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
D'oh!
(EXCLAIMING)
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
(SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
(GROANS)
(BOTH SCREAMING)
(WHIMPERING)
Uh...
(BEEPING)
(SCREAMS)
(BOTTLE SHATTERS)
(GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
(SIGHS)
Hmm?
(SCREAMS)
NARRATOR: We now
return to Hunch.
There's your murderer.
Are you sure, Hunch?
How do you know?
Uh? Something about his
hair. I don't know.
How did we miss
that? Get him!
Hey.
Come on.
Ah, you did it again, Hunch.
Let's go grab a bite.
You know what I'm
in the mood for?
Could it be turkey?
But how did you. .. Ah!
It's amazing they've gotten
512 shows out of this premise.
Remember when we saw
Hunch's butt in the shower?
That was two seasons ago.
Now you can only
see butts on cable.
This is Kent Brockman with
an Isotope baseball update.
The 'Topes are in first place
since the acquisition of
homerun king, Buck Mitchell.
Uh!
Thanks to him,
Springfield is once again
overrun with
fair-weather fans.
The Isotopes are winning?
To the bandwagon!
Nothing beats a day at the
ballpark with my family.
Tickets! Tickets!
Who needs tickets!
Homer, we need
those tickets to get in.
Don't worry. I'll use the money I
make to buy tickets from a scalper.
And I'll sell those tickets
and we'll be rich. Rich!
We did it, baby!
We made it through the rain.
Tickets, $30, big game. Everybody
wants to see the game.
Oh, cop! Act like
you're in love with me.
(GROANS)
MAN: Peanuts! $5 peanuts!
You want to know
something, Bart?
Nah. I know enough.
I myself played in this
ballpark back in 1940-deuce.
That was during the war when
sushi was called liberty logs,
and no one had
ever heard of it.
But, Grampa, in 1942, they only
played women's baseball here.
Ha, ha. Let's just say one of the
ladies had some extra equipment.
I was the center fielder
for the Springfield Floozies.
The pay wasn't much, but it kept
me out of the war for a year.
Effie Lou is a man!
Get him. He could threaten
my record for lady triples.
That was a magical summer.
How'd I get here?
ANNOUNCER. Now, to sing
our national anthem,
Payola recording artist,
Tabitha Vixx!
MARGE: She's married
to Buck Mitchell.
I bet that's why she's here
tonight honoring America.
Oh, say can you see
By the dawn's early light
And now here's something
from my new album.
I'm trouble-istic
Stay away, boy 'Cause
you know I'm trouble-istic
Think you can control me?
You ain't being realistic
(GROANS)
MOE: Hey, Buck!
How does it feel knowing your
wife's turning on a creep like me?
Weird, I bet! Ha, ha!
Trouble-istic girl
makes your troubulations grow
Double trouble-istic
when you try to tell me, "no"
Trouble, trouble
Oh, yeah
Trouble
And the home of the
Brave
(CROWD CHEERING)
She just embarrassed me in front
of the entire Tornado Belt League.
Ahhh!
ANNOUNCER: So next up for
the Cosmos, Freddy Alvarado.
Freddy,
of course, the older brother
of the famous Wolf
Boy of Juárez, Mexico.
Here's the pitch.
(GASPING)
And Buck Mitchell
can't find the handle.
That's an E3 if you're
keeping score at home.
And if you are,
your loneliness saddens me.
It's okay, Buck.
Bad hop! Bad hop!
(CROWD CHEERS)
(CROWD GASPS)
Yank it off, Buck!
(CROWD CHEERS)
(CROWD GASPS)
You suck!
I concur!
Bart, hand me that
sack of batteries.
9-volt, double A,
D, D, D, cordless drill!
ANNOUNCER: Job himself never
had a tougher day
at the ballpark
than Buck Mitchell.
He's made six errors, struck
out twice and swallowed a bee.
(CROWD GASPS)
MAN: My fiancée!
(CROWD BOOS)
They're making a mockery out of
Amerisnet.com Troll Doll Night.
You know what to do, Duffman.
Oh, yeah. Time for the
Duff Triple-Malt Kiss-Cam!
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Duffman.
WOMAN: And then he kissed me
And then he kissed me
Look, it's a thing.
Next time I saw him I couldn't
wait to see him again
I wanted to let him know...
We both find public displays
of affection vulgar.
Come on, Doc. She's a fine-looking woman.
You don't want to work that?
I didn't know just what to do
So, I whispered...
Homer? Homer,
now we have to kiss.
The big TV is telling us to.
Look at that ugly old man.
That's you.
(WAILING)
Gimme a kiss, Homie!
Really? You'd kiss
an ugly old man like me?
Only if he'll kiss me back.
WOMAN: And then he kissed me
(CROWD CHEERING)
And then he kissed me
Yeah, Homer. Suck that face!
(LAUGHING) Remember when we
used to kiss like that, Carl?
With our
respective girlfriends.
Yeah. I wonder where
Jill and Kelly are now.
I heard Jill died. Kelly,
I think, is a prostitute.
Hmm.
What a game!
I got on the Kiss-Cam,
I participated in the wave
and I got to pee in a trough.
Marge, can we
get a trough?
For the last time, no!
Ohhh, iced tea.
(GROANS)
(SLURPING)
HOMER: Mmm.
Hey, that was my iced tea. I
just sweetened it to my liking.
(DOORBELL RINGING)
Oh, Buck Mitchell!
Ooh, the baseball-playing man.
I barely recognize you
without your costume on.
Evening, ma'am.
I couldn't help seeing you two
exchanging marital kisses tonight.
Yes, yes. The game you
played so horribly at.
Well, unfortunately,
my marriage ain't so good.
Oh! I never heard anything
about it on the gossip shows
or the blogosphere, or in my
supermarket checkout magazine.
(GROANS)
I was wondering if
you and the mister
could give us some
marriage counseling.
You know, in return,
I can give you season tickets.
Season tickets? I could
entertain business clients.
I might even land
the Henderson account.
Uh... Homer, can I see
you in the kitchen?
Sure.
That means she wants
to talk in private.
It's probably about you.
Homie, I don't think
our marriage is so Jim Dandy,
that we should be
counseling others.
Hey, we've gone
through more hardships
than the Jews and Charlie
Brown put together.
Hmm. Well, we have
managed to squeeze
a lot of fun out
of married life.
Ha-ha. That's just how I feel.
Whoo-hoo!
See, that's what I want, carefree
intimacy with no edge of resentment.
Buck Mitchell!
Buck, I guess
we can help you out.
We'll start tomorrow.
Hey, Buck, Buck, Buck.
It's me.
The weird guy
from the stadium.
Uh, there were a lot of weird guys
at the stadium tonight.
You know, I remembered you.
Buck, Tabitha, welcome.
We'll start your first
marriage counseling session
as soon
as Homer gets here.
Sorry I'm late. I was just
gathering my counseling equipment.
(STRAINING)
(WATER RUNNING)
Meh.
Uh...
Now, let's remember
no one's right
and no one's
wrong till I say so.
Ha! I think what Homer
means is
why don't you tell us what each
of you feels is the problem?
Well, I'm an old-fashioned guy, you know.
And when we got hitched,
I just assumed she'd give up her
international recording career
to focus on my minor league
baseball dreams.
Wow, I think we've really
hit on something here.
Unfortunately,
we're out of time.
How does that
make you feel?
Shut up. My
10:00's here.
Ha, ha, ha.
Oh, Homer, please.
Uh... Let's see here.
Uh!
Here's something the book's
previous owner underlined.
"Be honest with your partner
about what you're feeling."
I don't want to waste any more
time in a mismatched marriage.
Hmm.
"Try to frame criticisms of
your spouse in a positive way."
Well, I'm positively
sick of her
shaking her lady parts for
the whole world to eyeball.
Interesting. Interesting.
(PEN SQUEAKING)
Buck, you've got a beautiful
woman with a hot body
that any man
would fantasize about,
even while making
love to his own Marge.
Aw. Thank you, Homer.
Maybe we should stop here.
Good idea, honey.
Buck, would you mind signing a
couple of baseballs for my boy?
Uh. Yeah. Sure.
Just sign your name
above President Lincoln's.
Isn't it weird that our parents
are giving marital advice?
They're always fighting.
If you listen closely, you can
hear them arguing right now.
HOMER: And I say a monkey
can mow our lawn!
This house is spectacular!
You must've had
a great view of the riots.
I stole a rack of fur coats.
I sell one a year
to pay for Christmas.
You make me laugh, Homer.
Why? Because I'm fat?
Okay.
Tonight, we're gonna discuss little
ways to keep your romance alive,
make time
for each other,
an hour, an evening,
a mini-vacation.
Well, I am presenting
at the ESPY Awards next week.
And I'm receiving. Hey, we can
wait for our limos together.
Or, take the same limo!
BOTH: Ohhh!
(BOTH GROANING)
BUCK: Mmm. Oh, yeah.
Like I always say,
compromise is the key.
I always say that.
Let's compromise and
say nobody said it.
Uh!
ANNOUNCER: And here's
the pitch to Buck Mitchell.
It's going, going...
And like America 's credibility
on the world stage,
that ball is gone!
Booyah!
Buck Mitchell is back
and sluggier than ever!
With five
homeruns in two nights,
he's ended rumors
of early retirement
and inspired
rumors of steroid abuse!
But I've heard this turnaround
is due to the marriage counseling
of Marge and Homer Simpson,
seen in this file photo.
Homer, I'm proud of you.
You've prolonged
this celebrity marriage
at least through
playoff season.
After that, who gives a hobo's crap?
Am I right?
I'm a girl who loves a man
And we live in
sexy, marriage land
Sexy, marriage land
Oh, marriage
Sexy marriage land
Wow. I've got this sudden
urge to give her $5 bill.
That's it. We're
out of here.
Huh?
(CROWD CHEERING)
Hey, Tabitha, great show!
I liked that part where you
mentioned Springfield.
Did you know
that's where you are?
Hey, why don't you
stay and have a bite?
Ohhh, You're so hot.
If only I'd seen you
before I met my wife.
Oh, Homer, you're
sweet, but...
Oh, you're talking
to the chicken.
Don't tell
the hamburger in my car.
Listen, these shows
always tense me up.
While your fingers are greasy,
could you give me a neck rub?
Well, okay.
So, why didn't you marry one
of your crummy backup dancers?
Nah. They're day laborers. We pick
them up in the Home Depot parking lot.
Oh, yeah.
Ohhh! That's it, right there.
Ohhh!
Ohhh, yes! Yes. Yes.
It feels so good!
Ohhh, yeah.
Oh, yeah, baby.
TABITHA: Oh, Oh... Yes!
HOMER: (MOANING)
HOMER: Whoa! Thank God
I brought protection.
I used to be so
embarrassed buying these.
Homer Simpson? You're supposed
to be my marriage counselor!
I did workbook pages for you.
D'oh!
Oh, we're gonna have a lot to
talk about at your three o'clock.
There ain't gonna be
a three o'clock.
Cancellations
require 24 hours' notice.
Hmm.
And that's why Lou Gehrig was a
selfish crybaby who deserved to die.
Springfield,
let's hear from you.
MOE: Uh, yeah.
I got a question.
How come Buck Mitchell's game
is in the toilet, again?
Well, rumor has it
his marriage is failing
due to the inept counseling
of Homer and Marge Simpson.
Ugh. I knew it. I knew it! So,
do l win a Jock Squawk T-shirt?
Uh, no. Sorry.
It don't need
no writing on it.
It don't even
have to be clean.
Is this Moe?
What happened to that
bumper sticker we gave you?
Uh, it's holding in my hernia.
(STRAINING)
Dad, because you and Mom screwed
up Buck Mitchell's marriage,
some kids beat me
up at school today.
Yeah, they beat me up at work.
Look at the words
they wrote on my skull.
(GASPS) Oh, Papa.
I didn't want you to learn
that word this way.
Marge, we gotta get Buck
and Tabitha back together.
This is the most important
case of our careers.
Listen, bub. We are out of the
marriage counseling business.
And the only one
you should be giving
chicken grease
neck rubs to is me!
But not me, because I
think they're disgusting!
Oh! So, now we're judging each
other based on things we've done!
Real fair! Class act!
I'm going back to the stadium to
bring those two kids back together.
And I'll do it
with or without you.
Then I guess
you'll do it without me.
(WHIMPERING)
Oh, but I wanted to
do it with you!
Crossed arms mean no.
(STRAINING)
Ooh!
(EXHALES)
HOMER: (STRAINING)
MARGE: Mmmm-mmm.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Tabitha, what a coincidence!
I was just thinking
sad thoughts about you.
I came to tell you
I'm leaving Buck.
Uh? What? No! No!
What? Uh? No! Uh? What?
Buck and I don't
belong together.
Don't give up on Buck.
There must be
something about him
that attracted you
in the first place.
Well, yeah.
He was the first man who didn’t
just like me for my body.
He always complimented
me on my hair.
Ooh! Your standing lamp
is dirty, I'll polish it!
(MOANING)
Ohhh!
Cancel all my appointments.
Let's go.
ANNOUNCER: So, here comes Buck Mitchell
in a spot every kid dreams of,
where a sacrifice fly
could lead
his minor league
team to a wildcard spot.
(CROWD CHEERS)
And there's the Duff blimp.
With a special message
from Tabitha to Buck.
Said Zeppelin has
a whole lotta love.
It's working.
Buck's buying my fake message.
And you said it
would never work.
No. l said, "Duffman
will do what you want!
"Stop kicking and
punching Duffman!"
I'm whacking
this for you, baby!
ANNOUNCER: And he sends one
into the slug-o-sphere.
It going, going...
(AIR HISSING)
My sister's friend!
(STRAINING)
Tabitha! Tabitha! Oh! This is
the worst blimp crash ever!
TOO SOON!
Where are ya, sweetie?
Uh... Uh... She was here a minute ago.
She must be pooping.
Hey, you're lying.
This whole stunt was a lie.
Get him.
He ruined mini bat day.
CROWD: Yeah! Get him!
Leave him alone.
All he did was try to help a
young couple find their way.
Does he really deserve
to get strung up for that?
(MOURNFUL ORGAN MUSIC PLAYING)
(CROWD LAUGHING)
Cut that out.
Duffman, gives
the people what they want!
Weren't you just
tied up in the blimp?
Three Duffmen
are working the game tonight.
Don't tell the children.
It's disillusioning!
Duffman! Duffman!
Marriage is hard work.
But it's worth it when you've got
someone wonderful like I do.
CROWD: Aw!
Buck, I love you, too,
and I'll take you back if you can
guess tonight's attendance.
CROWD: D! C! A! B! A! A!
B! No, A!
Let's see, um...
B. No, no, no, A.
No, no. Oh, man, man!
It's C, as in,
"keeping together. "
Which is what I want to do.
Well, Homer, it looks like my
marriage is going into extra innings.
Great. But enough of
the baseball analogies.
They sicken me.
No problem.
Now, m'lady, your
carriage awaits.
Ah, ain't love grand, Tito?
Hey, man, I don't care! Bandits
just kidnapped my mother!
Just found out.
Ripped By mstoll