(SINGING) The Simpsons
(SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
Ripped By mstoll
(HORN BELLOWING)
(PLAYING DIFFERENT TUNE)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(HONKING)
D'oh!
(EXCLAIMING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(BONANZA THEME PLAYING)
(NEIGHS)
(WHISTLING)
Well, well, Bart Simpson
in trouble again.
School hasn't
even started yet.
What can I say?
I missed you, Myra.
How's things
with you and Frank?
That bum.
He says his divorce
will be final next week.
So why is
she pregnant again?
Ouch! You hang in
there, beautiful.
So where's the Skin-man?
He's out admiring
his "new" car.
SEYMOUR: Ah, 1995.
A fine year for Camrys.
No one would ever guess you
spent three months in a lake.
(BART GASPS)
Ay, caramba!
Thank you, Satan.
Just think, Milhouse.
From now on,
we'll always be "those kids who
got into the steam tunnels."
(CLANKING)
(GRUNTING)
(STEAM HISSING)
I gotta warn ya,
we could get in trouble.
I don't mind. Trouble's
a form of attention.
(CREAKING)
MOE: Gentlemen, the moment
has finally arrived.
I'm renting a party bus and taking
all you regulars to Las Vegas.
Nevada?
That's right.
(ALL CHEERING)
Moe, why are you
being so generous?
You're usually so stingy
and rat-like.
Yeah, well, you remember that
time I tried to hang myself
and the rope broke?
Well, I sued the rope company
and I got a huge settlement!
And a new rope!
ALL: Wow.
Hey, nice rope.
You could hang a cow
with that thing.
These steam tunnels
are awesome!
It's like we're in the
school's lymphatic system
and we're the lymph!
Oh, my God!
My dad had a long talk
with me about this.
But you can't believe it
till you see it!
The cafeteria
loading dock!
Look, we're having
pizza tomorrow!
I'm gonna eat
a lighter breakfast.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Well, we made it
to the valve room.
Now we can leave
without touching a valve.
What a tale that'll be!
Hey, we can't leave here without
turning one little valve.
Yeah. It'd be like
going to Amsterdam
and not taking a walking
tour of famous doors.
(STEAM HISSING)
Hmm. That's odd. We only turn
the heat on for Parents Night.
What the F-minus?
(STEAM HISSING)
Steam!
Grover Cleveland's second term
was, if anything, more uneventful.
(STEAM HISSING)
(GASPS)
(SCREAMS)
Look! A new kid! Get him!
(GROANING)
(STEAM HISSING)
(CROAKING)
(ALL SCREAMING)
(BAND PLAYING)
(STEAM HISSING)
Our instruments are rusting!
We're going a cappella,
people!
(SCATTING)
I've got two kinds
of wet in my pants!
(HUMMING)
Oh, it's so hot.
I need a drink.
(STEAM HISSES)
(SCREAMS)
No water fountain
outwits Willie!
(SCREAMS)
Maybe I'll just have a soda.
(HUMMING)
(SCREAMING)
Mmm, this wood is more buckled
than a pilgrim's hat.
But who's responsible?
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(GRUNTS)
Don't bother struggling.
I've got your scruff!
Can I cut a deal?
I'll give you Milhouse.
I don't want Milhouse.
Sounds like my parents'
custody hearing.
Myra, can you help
me out here?
Forget it. This used
to be a croissandwich.
Now it's a ham
and cheese car crash.
Yes, thank you, Myra.
To highlight the seriousness
of Bart's offense,
Superintendent Chalmers will
be joining us by video uplink.
And joining me
by video uplink,
State Comptroller Atkins.
Can we move this along?
I 'm attending an important
conference here in Scottsdale.
You're in Scottsdale? I'm in Scottsdale!
At the Hyatt! Room 381!
Get outta here!
I'm in 502.
Hey, do you guys have any
ice buckets down there?
No. We've been
using shower caps.
Skinner!
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
You made that TV show
really mad.
Yes, but you won't think it's so
funny when we send Bart here!
"Upward Bound,
the toughest behavioral
"modification camp
in Northwest Oregon."
It's the only place cruel
enough to straighten Bart out.
They use a proven concept.
Tough hate to turn around
foul-mouthed hooligans.
Then they send them home
quietly ticking away.
Mmm.
This camp's got it all.
Climbing some
kind of rope thing,
wearing a backpack,
high five-ing the black kid!
It's the perfect thing
to straighten you out!
(GROANS)
Got it!
(REWINDS TAPE)
(BART GROANS)
Now I have a ring tone for
my brand new cell phone.
No wires at all.
Except this one.
Hey, check it out!
I made it partially risqué!
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Hey, guys. I have to put the boy
on a plane to soul-crushing camp.
Then I'll be back
to go to Vegas.
Dad, if you take
me to Vegas,
I'll teach you how
to cheat at blackjack.
Boy, you don't need to cheat
when you got a system.
What's your system?
I don't tell your mother
how much I've lost.
One child to Portland!
(CHUCKLES)
He's your problem now!
It seems he was
our problem before.
(BEEPING)
Your son is on
the "no fly" list.
(NERVOUS CHUCKLE) Why,
there must be some mistake.
There's no mistake. It seems the
last time he flew unescorted...
PILOT: (ON PA)
Welcome to Atlanta.
Please keep your seatbelt fastened
until we have come to a complete stop.
(BEEPS)
Nobody tells Bart
Simpson what to do!
(BUZZING)
(STATIC)
PILOT: Thanks a lot, 33C!
Now we all have to go back to Minneapolis!
And I'm very tired!
ALL; Oh!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Well, Homer, looks like I
can't go to discipline camp.
Which is too bad,
because I think
this was the thing that would
finally straighten me out.
Oh, yeah?
You're going to that camp
because I'm gonna
drive you there!
Oh, yeah, that'll be way
more fun than Vegas.
(YELLING)
Oh, dang.
Homer ain't coming.
(NELSON LAUGHS) And Nelson
saw something funny.
(TIRES SCREECH)
(HORN HONKS)
Stupid Bart makes me
drive to Oregon.
Home of unspoiled forest,
birthplace of Matt Greening.
Dad, neither of us
want to go.
Why are you doing this?
Where's the old carefree Homer
who likes to cut loose?
You mean Fun Homer?
I'm afraid Serious Homer
has him locked up
till you're at your
snooty torture camp.
Fight back, Fun Homer!
Together we can win!
It's no use.
Oh, come on, Serious
Homer, let me out!
We'll get a monkey drunk
and push him down the stairs!
(GRUNTS) I'll kill you the way
I killed Intellectual Homer!
(MARGE HUMMING)
While the boys are gone,
we'll sell all their
useless junk
and replace it with
knickknacks and curios!
I already made up
a yard sale sign.
You know your father saved every
book report he ever wrote?
And every one
was Stuart Little.
Mmm... Mmm...
Not to mention this PowerPoint
demonstration he did just last week.
Ooh... Mmm...
(GASPS)
My Malibu Stacy heads!
(SOBBING)
Oh, no.
Bart blamed this
on the dog.
I didn't pet him
for weeks.
(SOBBING)
Oh, I'm sorry I doubted you, boy.
(BARKS)
Eh.
Come on, Dad.
We got a long way to go.
You can't stay mad
at me the whole time.
Boy, if you were half as
smart as you think you are,
you'd clean up your act.
Well, maybe pulling pranks
is the only thing I'm good at.
At least you have
something you're good at.
I'm 38 years old,
driving a crappy car,
with a son
who doesn't respect me!
And I'm one Snickers pie away
from losing my foot to diabetes!
Mmm...
Snickers pie...
(DROOLING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(BELL DINGS)
So, I see you're also
traveling with your son.
What boy prison
are you taking him to?
Actually, Justin and I are going to
the Oregon Shakespeare Festival.
Sir Peter Hall himself
is directing.
See, Bart? I told you
things could be worse.
I'm getting a sweatshirt
with Shakespeare's face on it!
Well, we better get back
to the Prius, son.
Ah, don't forget the menu
for our scrapbook.
(BELL DINGS)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Did you see that? They were
eating melon for breakfast.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
"Look at me.
I use a napkin."
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
Well, Dad, we may not
always get along,
but we'll never
be that lame.
I bet they're
from Massachusetts!
You know it's legal there
for a guy to marry his son?
(CHUCKLES)
(SIGHS) Well, I guess
it's tinkle time.
Ooh, don't forget to wash
your hands, Shakespeare!
(BOTH LAUGHING)
So, here for a snack before they
roll you back into the ocean?
Yeah. I'll have the smiley
face breakfast special.
Ah, but could you add
a bacon nose,
plus bacon hair,
bacon mustache,
five o'clock shadow made of
bacon bits, and a bacon body?
How about if I just shoved
a pig down your throat?
Uh-huh?
I'm kidding.
Fine!
But the bacon man
lives in a bacon house!
WAITRESS: No, he doesn't.
HOMER: Mmm...
You know who would really
like this place? Bart.
Wait a minute.
Where the hell is Bart?
(GRUNTS)
You little monster!
Huh?
Show your face
this minute! Mmm?
Mmm? Huh?
(CHUCKLES)
Bart, where are you?
Hmm...
Hey, Stavros, there's a guy in your
bathroom trying to dine and dash.
What? No one
dashie-dine on Stavros.
(CHUCKLES)
Why you little...
(STRAINED GRUNTING)
I'm stuck! Ow!
(THUD)
Someone's hitting my butt
with something!
Is frying pan!
Ow!
(GROANING)
Leave your ass, Homer.
Leave your ass.
Hmm, let me
get this straight.
I get all of
Bart's action figures,
Homer's treasured
"Mr. Plow"jacket,
and these Power
Rangers Underoos
which I am already
wearing for only $3.95.
That's right.
Give me five minutes alone with
your fridge and you have a deal.
(GRUNTS) Fine.
We've only brought in $5.
And that came from Mr. Flanders
buying back his own stuff.
(GASPS)
My LP of Dreamcoat?
(SINGING) How I love
my coat of many colors
It was red and yellow
And green and brown
And scarlet and black
And ocher and peach
And ruby and olive
and violet and...
...And lilac and gold
And chocolate and mauve
And cream and crimson
And silver and rose
And azure and lemon and
russet and gray and gold...
(FOOTSTEPS)
...And purple and white
And pink and orange
And red and yellow
And green and brown
Scarlet and black
And ocher and peach
My yard sale
is a failure.
I guess I'll have to give
everything to the Salvation Army.
We don't want it!
Oh...
Mmm, Dexonumb,
Somnodoze, Percolax!
Are these for sale?
I guess.
They're Homer's expired
pain medications.
Ooh, I'm in a lot of pain.
I'm breaking in
a new pair of flip-flops
and my thong notch
is on fire! How much?
Um, a dollar?
Per pill, right?
Uh, yeah.
I'll take a dozen of each.
Oh, wow! Drugs in a bottle!
I feel like Elvis Presley!
Whoa, this is so much safer than buying
my illegal drugs at the playground.
Bag or keister?
Surprise me.
Mmm.
Um, I'll take
all your estrogen.
That's a female replacement hormone.
Uh-huh.
It's for a friend, uh, who's trapped
in the body of another friend.
Oh...
So Lenny, how's it going in Vegas?
Pretty boring, I'll bet.
Yeah, kind of.
(SHOUTING EXCITEDLY)
(ALARM RINGING)
(LAUGHING)
Can't talk now, Homer. I'm
too satisfied in every way.
Oh...
Hmm?
(GASPS)
(LAUGHING)
I gotcha now, boy.
(SCREAMS)
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
(GASPS)
(BEEPING)
(SCREAMING)
Oh, I'm gonna
fall down. Oh!
Boy! Push down
on the bumper!
Then I can back the car up
and save myself!
Hmm. If I save you, what
are you gonna do to me?
Shower you with love
because this experience has taught
me just how precious you are.
I'll kill you!
I'll kill your whole family!
Kidding.
I'm kidding.
We can do that.
We have a special friendship.
I'm gonna double kill you!
Then I'm gonna bury you
in a shallow grave!
Then I'll dig you up
and kill you again!
That's the beauty
of a shallow grave!
You sweet little angel.
Oh, I'm gonna rip your head off!
And spit down your
adorable little neck
because I want to
smash your little
stupid head!
Oh, but I love you.
We'll go on a fishing trip.
But first, I'm gonna
put you on a sawmill!
Then punch your
little face out!
That's what I'm gonna do!
(HUMMING)
(DOORBELL RINGS)
I'm here for the (CLEARS
THROAT) yard sale.
But that was yesterday!
No. I mean the "yard sale."
What are you
talking about?
Can I buy some pills?
Well, maybe someone else can help
you but I am not a drug grocer!
(SIGHS) Oh!
(KNOCKING)
I'm out of drugs! See
how much money I made?
(GASPS)
Oh, Chief Wiggum. Uh, are you
still with the police department?
Save it, Ma Peddle.
Ma Peddle?
It's a reference to Ma Kettle, the
popular movie character from the '40s.
If you have to explain it,
it's not good, Chief.
HOMER: Well, boy,
you made the right choice.
I think this is the first step to a
new closer relationship between us.
Dad, I think you actually enjoy
seeing your own son suffer.
I don't enjoy it.
Being a father
is just a job.
Long hours, no pay.
And at the end, all you get is someone
yelling, “You screwed me up."
Well, maybe if you enjoyed me more,
I wouldn't be so screwed up.
Hey, I enjoy you plenty.
Talking time is over.
Mmm...
Don't worry,
Mr. Simpson.
We're gonna take his sass
and turn it into siss.
Thank you, Colonel.
I'm not a colonel.
This is a Boy Scout uniform
that I dolled up.
Come with me, son.
Now kiss your
childhood goodbye.
Whoo-hoo!
Vegas, here I come!
I miss you, Dad.
(GASPS)
Hey, Homer, you want
to eat my shorts?
(SHRIEKING)
(SCREAMS)
Don't gamble on
my love, Homer.
Oh.
Oh, I miss Bart. I can't leave
him in that awful camp.
I'm coming, boy!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Oh, oh, great.
I'll get off here. Oh, no.
I bet this looks cool
from overhead though.
Oh, oh...
Whoo-hoo! Vegas, here I come!
Oh, right. Bart.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(GRUNTING)
Nicely chopped, Simpson.
Uh!
I've learned so much
in my three hours here.
I don't have to play
pranks to feel good.
I can just listen to the
gentle rhythms of nature.
(THUD)
HOMER: Stupid horse!
It's a "deer" crossing!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Wipe the blood off the windshield
and get in the car, boy.
Dad?
Son,
I'm doing something I should've
done a long time ago.
Taking you to Vegas!
I'm gonna order a steak dinner
and eat it on the toilet!
And don't you try
to stop us!
Actually, we were gonna call you, Mr.
Simpson.
Your credit card
was declined.
Try this one!
MARGE: Homer,
I hope you get this.
I'm in jail and I need
$10,000 bail.
Hurry!
(BEEPS)
HOMER: Ah, Marge, me
and Bart got in a fight
with this really
uncool pit boss,
and now we're in
Nevada State Prison.
Also, I don't know
where Bart is.
If you see him, say hey!
(BEEPS)
(SIGHING)
Well, Maggie,
I always knew it would
someday boil down
to just you and me.
I'll look for work
in the morning.
Ripped By mstoll