The Simpsons.
And now, to top off
our most propane explosion-free
science week ever,
our grand finale: The launching
of a weather balloon.
Go, weather balloon!
Hurrah for science! Whoo!
Hurrah for science? Whoo?
Well, I can't say
I approve of the whoo,
but the hurrah
was quite heartening.
Release the balloon.
No!
I don't think
I really captured the eyes.
Bart, if you have a failing,
it's that you're
always demanding perfection.
If you have a failing.
Whoever brings down
that balloon
doesn't have
to learn fractions!
Eh, careful, children.
That's my car.
Destroy that balloon.
Aye.
Tango 14,
we're being fired at.
I'm getting an exact I.D.
on the bogey now.
Iraqis again.
Launching sidewinder missile.
Missed him.
Launching second
sidewinder missile.
This is what happens
when you cut money
out of the military
and put it
into health care!
It's a good program!
Just give it a chance.
That's all I ask!
Hmm, it won't
come down for months.
Curse the man
who invented helium.
Curse Pierre-Jules-Cesar
Janssen.
Now to find out who did this.
Bart, empty your pockets.
Empty my pockets, you say?
Well, certainly, but I fail
to see how...
Blueprints of the dummy,
notarized photos
of you making the dummy,
and an alternate wording
for the banner... Buttzilla.
Race you to Utah,
Milhouse.
Okay.
I am going to punish you
for this, Bart.
And it won't just be
a simple caning this time.
Because you have impeded
science,
you must now aid science.
Yes. Starting tomorrow,
you will assist me
with my amateur astronomy,
taking down coordinates,
carrying equipment,
and so forth.
4:30 in the morning.
There's a 4:30
in the morning now?
Top of the hour,
time for the morning news.
But of course,
there is no news yet.
Everyone's still asleep
in their comfy, comfy beds.
Good night, everybody.
Mom, will you
make me breakfast?
There's a stuffed pepper in
the trash from last night.
Just rinse it good.
Come home, Lassie!
Here, boy!
Come on, girl!
Attaboy!
It's still dark.
Better use the generator.
Ah, there's nothing
more exciting than science.
You get all the fun
of sitting still,
being quiet,
writing down numbers,
paying attention.
Science has it all.
Is that the telescope we're
gonna be looking through?
Yes, but you won't
be looking through it.
I forbid it.
But you don't need a telescope
to enjoy astronomy, Bart.
There are all the constellations
you've heard so much about.
There's Orion, the Swan,
the Chariot Race.
Why don't they look anything
like their names?
Well, you do have
to use your imagination.
Look, there's
the three wise men.
Who names these things,
anyway?
Whoever discovers them.
I've been hoping
I could find something
that would be named
after me.
And you've never
found anything?
Once, but by the time
I got to a phone
my discovery
had already been reported
by Principal Kahoutek.
I got back at him, though.
Him and that little boy of his.
Anyway, that's why
I always keep
a cellular phone next to me.
Now, this morning,
we're gonna be mapping
a small square of sky
that's thought to be empty.
It's my hope that it's not.
So, what am I supposed
to do exactly?
Just write down my findings
as I give them to you.
Six hours,
19 minutes right ascension
14 degrees,
22 minutes declination...
No sighting.
Six hours, 19 minutes,
right ascension,
14 degrees,
23 minutes declination...
No sighting.
Six hours, 19 minutes
right ascension,
14 degrees,
58 minutes declination...
No sighting.
Did you get that one, Bart?
- Hell, no.
- Good.
My stars!
Give me the phone quick!
Check out 6-19-14-59.
No. No, there's no need
for that.
It's already named after me.
It's getting pretty close
to the ground.
Maybe I can catch it.
Don't touch
the telescope, Bart.
Even a slight change
in elevation
can destroy
a whole morning's work.
Whoo! All hands on deck!
Pirates off the port bow!
Hey.
Observatory?
This is Bart Simpson.
I see something in the sky
at 4-12-8
and the last number is seven.
Ah, got you,
my rumpy doppelganger.
I've got it. Hey...
What are you doing?
Give me that phone.
Congratulations, Bart.
You've just
discovered a comet.
No!
And then I sped away
without anyone seeing
my license plate.
Sounds like you had
a good day today, Dad.
Yeah, except I forgot
to go to work.
What did you do today, Bart?
What didn't I do?
"Boy discovers comet."
What?
"A young Springfieldianite
"has discovered a new comet
to be known as
the Bart Simpson comet."
Oh, honey,
I'm so proud of you.
But then, you've always
been proud of me.
Yes.
Won't you join us, Bart?
I guess so.
As the first student
at Springfield Elementary
to discover a comet,
we're very proud
to make you a member
of our very select group.
Welcome to Super Friends.
Welcome, super friend.
I am called Ham,
since I enjoy ham radio.
This is E-mail,
Cosine,
Report Card,
Database,
and Lisa.
Your nickname
will be Cosmos.
Well, I'm done eating.
Good-bye.
Good-bye, Cosmos.
Bye-bye.
Perhaps some night you
could show us your comet.
There it is right there.
I make it a point
never to turn my head
unless I expect
to see something, Bart.
Naturally, we can't see
your comet in broad daylight,
and without a telescope.
But you don't need
a stupid telescope.
It's right there.
Oh, no, no, no.
This isn't right at all.
It must be coming toward us
at a fantastic speed.
Don't you realize what's happening, Bart?
Your comet is gonna
collide with the earth,
and every living thing
in its path will be killed.
I knew you'd try
to find something wrong
with my comet, Lisa.
You've always been
petty and small,
right from the beginning.
We must alert
the proper authorities.
To the observatory!
We are the Super Friends!
Hey, shut up.
Dear God!
Warren, we've
talked about you
hogging the eyepiece.
Sounds like
the doomsday whistle.
Ain't been blown
for nigh on to three years.
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
Trouble a-brewing.
Fellow citizens,
when I learned
about the impending crisis,
I caught the very next plane
to Springfeld... Field.
First of all, yes,
there is a comet in the sky,
and, yes, it is going
to hit Springfield.
You, uh, don't need
to applaud that.
Now, here's what we think
the impact might look like.
Show them, Jerry.
Oh, dear God, no!
Fortunately,
we have a plan.
- Professor Frink.
- Good evening, ladies and...
Quit stalling!
What's the plan?
All right, just take your seat.
Just take your seat.
Now, working with former
Carter administration officials
and military men who were
forced into early retirement
for various reasons which we
won't go into here,
we have planned
this defense for the city.
As the comet hurtles
toward the city
our rocket will intercept it
and blow it to smithereens. Hey!
Oh, dear God, no!
And that will be the end
of our Mr. Comet.
Yay! We're saved!
Will you all stop worrying
about that stupid comet?
It's going to be destroyed.
Didn't you hear what the guy
in the building said?
- But Dad, don't you think...
- Ah, Lisa.
The whole reason we
have elected officials
is so we don't have
to think all the time.
Just like that rain forest
scare a few years back.
Our officials saw
there was a problem
and they fixed it,
didn't they?
No, Dad,
I don't think...
There's that word again.
Homer, what if this
doesn't work?
Well, then,
I have a backup plan.
See, while the unprepared
are still sitting around
twiddling their thumbs
and going...
Dad, the plan!
I'm getting to that.
So, anyway, they're going...
- Dad!
- So, anyway, we get in our car
and take the bridge
out of town,
while all the while,
they're still going...
Dad, they're firing
the rocket!
All right!
It blew up the bridge!
We're doomed!
It's times like this
I wish I were
a religious man.
It's all over, people!
We don't have a prayer!
And like Icarus,
the rocket foolishly soared
too high and lost control of
its servo-guidance mechanism
leaving us with some...
six hours to live.
So, let's go live now
to the charred remains
of the only bridge out of town
with Arnie Pie
and Arnie in the Sky.
With the bridge gone
and the airport
unfortunately on the other
side of the bridge,
a number of citizens
are attempting
to jump the gorge
with their cars.
It's a silent testament
to the "Never give up
and never think things out"
spirit of our citizens.
With our utter
annihilation imminent,
our federal government
has snapped into action.
We go live now,
via satellite,
to the floor of the
United States congress.
Then it is unanimous, we are
going to approve the bill
to evacuate the town
of Springfield
in the great state of...
Wait a second, I want to tack on
a rider to that bill.
$30 million of taxpayer money
to support the perverted arts.
All in favor of the amended
Springfield/pervert bill?
Bill defeated.
I've said it before,
and I'll say it again:
Democracy simply doesn't work.
Now, over the years,
a newsman learns
a number of things
that for one reason or another,
he just cannot report.
It doesn't seem
to matter now,
so the following people
are gay:
Turn it off.
Just a second.
What's everyone
so worked up about?
So there's a comet.
Big deal.
It'll burn up in our atmosphere,
and what's ever left
will be no bigger
than a Chihuahua's head.
Wow, Dad, maybe you're right.
Of course I'm right.
If I'm not, may we all be
horribly crushed
from above somehow.
Okay, if you're
that worried about it,
let's go down
to the bomb shelter.
We have a bomb shelter?
Homer Simpson takes
care of his family.
Flanders, open up!
Hi-dee-ho-a-rooney,
neighbor.
- What can I do you for?
- Get out of there.
- My family needs to use your bomb shelter.
- Homer!
Oh, I kind of figured
this might happen,
so I built the shelter
big enough for both our families.
No deal. Out.
Get in the shelter, Homer.
One more hour.
An hour?
I can't wait another hour.
What's keeping
that stupid comet?
There it is.
Well, howdely-doodely, neighbors.
Shouldn't you be in
your shelterinis by now?
We haven't got shelterinis.
We want in yours.
Oh, well, sorry.
The shelter's kind of full.
Really? Oh.
Well, we'll just go off
someplace and die then.
Thanks.
Wait!
You know, I may regret this
when our air runs out
and we can't whistle
or stay alive, but...
Oh, what the hey.
I can't... get the...
I can't get the door closed.
Somebody's going
to have to get out.
I'd get out,
but I don't know where I am.
Hey, somebody's touching me.
- I am.
- Oh, okay.
Okay, okay, let's figure out
who should stay.
Let's see. The world
of the future will need laughter,
so I'm in.
And they'll need somebody
to dispense drinks...
I.E., me.
And someone will have
to run the power.
You can do that, Homer.
Uh... Yeah.
I can do that.
Okay, let's start again.
We'll need laughter,
religious enlightenment,
gossip...
That's Mrs. Lovejoy.
Wait a minute, we all know the one thing
we won't need in the future...
Left-handed stores.
That's you, Flanders.
I'm terribly sorry.
Flanders is the only
useless person here.
If anyone dies,
it should be him.
I'm sorry.
Please forgive me.
So let's kick Flanders out.
Sorry.
Well, sir, sounds fair.
Toodle-oo, everybody.
I'll scream when
the comet gets here.
Oh, I'm coming
with you, Neddy.
No, sweetheart.
You... You stay
here because...
Okay.
I might go mad with fear
out there,
so, Todd, I want you
to shoot Daddy
if he tries to get back in.
Okay, Dad.
Okay.
Que sera, sera.
Whatever will be, will be.
The future's
not ours to see...
Hey, I got an idea.
We can play a game
to pass the time.
I'll make the sound
of a barnyard animal,
and you all try
to guess what it is.
- It's a pig.
- It's a cow, man.
- It's a pony.
- No, it's a goat.
You know,
one of them lady goats.
There are no lady goats.
A lady goat is a sheep.
- I believe she's right.
- You're crazy.
- Arr! What's it to you?
- What's it to me?
It's a pony.
Stop it! Stop it!
Can't you see this
barnyard noise guessing game
is tearing us apart?
Que sera, sera.
Whatever will be,
will be...
Say, Moe, was it a duck?
No, no! Shut up! Shut up!
Stop it, stop it!
I can't take this anymore.
I can't let that brave man
out there die alone.
I'm surprised and disgusted
by all of you.
Especially his children.
I'm going out there.
And it was a baby ox.
He's right, you know.
About the ox?
About everything, damn it!
Hey, Homer, wait up.
I want to die too.
- If you are going, I am going.
- Me too.
I'm outta here. Make way.
Radio reception
in there sucked.
When I was just
a little girl
I asked my mother.
What will I be?
Will I be pretty,
will I be rich?
Here's what she said to me.
Que sera, sera.
Whatever will be.
Will be.
The future's not ours
to see.
Que sera...
Run!
- Look!
- It's breaking up!
Cool.
We're saved.
Sure makes you appreciate
the preciousness of life.
Let's go burn down
the observatory
so this'll
never happen again.
I can't believe that extra-thick
layer of pollution
that I've actually
picketed against
is what burned up
the comet.
What's really amazing
is that this is exactly
what Dad said would happen.
Yeah. Dad was right.
I know, kids.
I'm scared too.
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.