(SINGING) The Simpsons
D'oh!
(SCREAMS)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Ripped By mstoll
(LOUD HAMMERING)
Oh!
(JACKHAMMER DRILLING)
(HAMMERING CONTINUES)
(SCATTING RHYTMICALLY)
Homer! Do something
about the noise!
(CONTINUES SCATTING)
It's 7:00 AM, what are they
cock-a-doodily doing?
Flanders, I can't listen to
your crap before my coffee.
Okily-dokily, here's some French roast.
Now, I'll go make toast.
Stupid best friend Flanders.
BART: A stamp museum?
(YELLS) oh!
Stamps?
Those are for snail mail!
Stamps rule!
I mean suck!
Well, they can't
just start building
in our neighborhood
without asking us.
Whatever happened
to "please" and "thank you"?
I think they
killed each other.
You know, one of those
murder-suicide deals.
(CROWD CLAMORING)
We have to stop all
this construction.
The noise is jiggling my grapes
to the bottom of the Jell-o.
What man would
want you now?
Two, four, six, eight, I hate
stamps, they aren't great!
Okay, how about this?
Seven, four, three, one...
Oh, wait, that's my pin number.
Everyone, forget that.
MAN: (SINGING)
Tell me over and over
And over again, my friend
Ah, you don't believe...
Whoa!
Again! Again!
Again! (CHUCKLING)
Again!
That's enough.
Don't you understand
what I'm trying to say?
Can't you feel the fears
I'm feeling today?
If the button is pushed...
"Come home from Iraq,"
my wife says.
"Fallujah's too dangerous,"
Whoo-hoo!
(WHISTLING)
Tell me over and over
And over again, my friend.
(ALL SCREAMING)
(THUDDING)
All right, Homer!
You beat those
stamp Nazis
with good old-fashioned
American complaining.
Homer, if it
weren't for you,
we'd be at the mercy of
weekend philatelists.
You know, why didn't you just
say "stamp collectors"?
'Cause I'm tired of dumbing
myself down for you.
The postal service is sending
a change of address card...
To itself.
The stamp museum
will now be built
on the site of
the Springfield cemetery.
The cemetery will be moved right
here, next to the Simpsons.
Instead of a stamp museum, we'll
be next door to a graveyard?
Look at the bright
side, Marge.
When I die, you can mourn
me from the bathroom.
That's multitasking.
Hmm.
Hmm. This is a little
too spooky for me.
I don't even like watching
the Count on Sesame Street.
One coconut, two coconuts,
three coconuts...
(LAUGHS WICKEDLY)
GO back to
your own country!
(CAWING)
(HINGES CREAKING)
(OWL HOOTING)
This stinks.
My room is the only one
that faces that cemetery.
Then the zombies
will eat you first,
and you won't have
to watch them eat us.
Thanks for making
me feel better.
Well, thanks for making me
feel better, knowing that your
screams when the zombies
chomp your brains
will warn me so
I can get away.
There's no such
thing as zombies!
Ugh, glad to hear you say
that, because the person
who doesn't believe
in zombies
is always the first
to get feasted upon.
(GRUNTS)
(assume)
Stop scaring me!
(SCREAMS)
Bart, don't you
have homework to do?
Yeah, and I could
really use your help.
I believe in science and reality,
not ghosts and monsters.
(YOWLING)
(SCREAMING)
Can I sleep with
you guys tonight?
Oh, sure you can, sweetie.
Just don't make
a habit of it.
Okay, just let me clear some space.
(GRUNTS)
HOMER: Out you go.
You, too.
(GROANS)
Mmm, so that's why I've been
smelling margaritas at 3:00 AM.
Hey, I love waking up
drunk in the morning.
(GROANING)
(MOANS)
Ow!
Lisa, honey, I know
last night was tough,
but all our kids
sleep by themselves.
We don't even hear Maggie
cry at night anymore.
Wait a minute, there's no
batteries in this thing.
I needed them for my
remote-control helicopter.
Tonight, I want you
to really try
to sleep in your own bed, because...
(WHIRRING)
Homer, stop that!
There's a little plastic man in your
hair, and I'm trying to rescue him.
(WHIRRING)
No soldier left behind.
Homer, can you
help me out here?
Lisa, honey, if you sleep
in your own bed tomorrow,
we'll do something special.
Just for you.
Well, I heard they finished the
stamp museum. That could be fun.
I can't believe it took us
40 minutes to get here!
Why can't they build a stamp
museum closer to our house?
Dad, you fought
tooth and nail
to get it away
from our house.
Lisa, when you've sustained as
many blows to the head as I have
consistency is something,
something that something...
I love you, Bart.
Isn't this Lenny's house?
Hey, Simpsons.
That'll be
40 bucks.
Oh, I thought it
was $20!
(CHUCKLES) Yeah,
that's per axle.
Park over there
in Carl-Four.
No early outs.
I can't believe you're
making money off this.
Oh, yeah!
Living next to the stamp
museum is making me a mint!
I bought a diamond
for my belly button!
You guys need water?
No one's gonna pay a buck to drink
water from your hose, so...
D'oh! Pay the man, Homer.
Wow, look at all these
worthy Americans.
(BEEPS)
My name
is Frederick Ives.
I invented the halftone
printing process.
Thanks to me,
Katherine Blodgett,
we have
nonreflecting glass.
Yeesh! Butter face!
And I'm Alexander
Graham Bell,
inventor of
the telephone.
You stole it from me,
Elisha Gray.
Read the patent
number, bitch!
"The Land of
the Wild Beasts?"
That's the first book I
read all the way through.
You read a book
all the way through? Why?
Milton Burkhart's work
has touched on every genre
from books to
films to advertising.
All right!
Commercials!
MAN: Once upon
a time, a bad boy
was sent to bed
without any dinner.
But then, something
magical happened.
Huh?
ls this the land
of the wild beasts?
No, this is the land
of the wild feasts!
The Hillside
Wrangler steak house!
I'm $4.99 Steak.
I'm All-You-Can-Eat Salad Bar!
Yo, and I'm Sneeze Guard.
Put it under glass, dawgs.
(RUMBLING)
And I'm Jumbo Shrimp!
Maximum two servings!
That's bull... (BLEEP) Man!
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
I love you,
Hillside Wrangler!
Tell us, Mr. Burkhart,
what led you to the magical
world of children's books?
I wanted to be a children's
book illustrator
ever since Playboy wouldn't
publish my cartoons
because they were too filthy.
(THUNDER CRACKING)
Groundskeeper Willie?
No, I'm his cousin,
Gravedigger Billy.
I've been digging
graves for 30 years,
and I've never
buried anyone alive.
If I did,
they'd ring this bell.
(DINGING)
(GASPS)
Well, that's just the wind.
Oh, that's just
a tree branch,
with a nice
watch on it!
(GRUNTING)
(YELPS)
(SHUDDERING)
MARGE: What a lousy party!
I don't care what
Apu was in a past life,
in this life,
he's a blabbermouth!
Oh! And that Dr. Hibbert
was so boring.
"Homer, we've got to get
that lump checked out."
"Homer, we must discuss
your test results."
"Homer, we've got
to find you a donor."
Blah, blah, blah.
LISA: I thought those
people were your friends.
(SIGHS)
Look who's sleeping
in our bed again.
I didn't know grownups said bad
things about other grownups.
You see, sweetie, when a mommy
and daddy are married for years
and have nothing
new to talk about,
they bad-mouth
their closest friends.
But I thought
it was wrong
to talk about people
behind their backs.
I spy with
my little eye
a girl who's not sleeping in
her room like she promised.
I know.
I'm sorry.
And I spy with my little eye something
with four legs that can't run.
Homer, we're not
really playing.
Oh...
ls it the chair?
Exactly!
Now, what has two
ears but can't hear?
Grandpa!
Tragically, yes.
What if we show Lisa we
can sleep in her room
without being
frightened'?
Okay, Marge.
But don't be surprised if a
snuggle monster shows up.
Well, I hope
he's accompanied
by the "how was
your day" monster
and the "foot rub" monster,
and the "let me just..."
Don't worry,
he's not showing up.
(CAWING)
(BOTH SHUDDERING)
Boy, Lisa's room
really is scary.
Now, Willie, the pot of gold
I saw is right down there.
All I see is an empty grave. Why
don't you fill it, you lazy bastard!
Finally! Back in the only safe
bedroom in the house.
What about
Bart's bedroom?
You know that race
car bed I made him?
Yeah.
The brakes are shot.
Ow, ow!
Ow, ow.
Lisa, honey, any chance you
could stop reading soon?
Okay, I'll watch TV.
(GROANS)
MAN: Now, Re-run Land takes you
back to 1965 with Bonanza.
See here, Cartwright, your boys
have been eating my apples.
That doesn't
sound like my boys.
I'll thank you to
keep a civil tongue.
(WESTERN MUSIC PLAYING)
Oh, Lisa, do you really
want to watch this?
Mom, I think
there's a danger this time
they might lose the Ponderosa.
Ow!
Learn to drive, boy!
(SIGHS)
We need professional help.
As a young child, did Lisa
receive a lot of nurturing?
Frankly, no.
Lisa kind of took
care of herself.
Our oldest, Bart,
was such a handful.
Did you bring
those home movies
of your daughter
I asked for?
Uh... This is
all I could find.
(CHUCKLING GUILTILY)
(CHUCKLING)
HOMER: Why you very little...
(GRUNTS)
(CHOKING)
Homer, stop that!
Who was filming
that scene?
Stationary camera.
I see.
Mr. and Mrs. Simpson,
to overcome her neglect
Lisa had to suppress
her childhood fears.
My ten-week program can help
her learn to be a kid again.
Well worth the $4,000.
Four thousand dollars?
Now, Marge, when our little
girl's happiness is at stake...
(GRUNTS) Run, Marge!
Start the car!
I'm not chasing
you, Mr. Simpson.
And you won't!
Unless you can
leap through fire!
(BLOWS)
I can't keep sleeping
in Morn and Dad's room.
Yeah, if Dad rolls over,
you're dead.
Mom showed me how to make a
retaining wall out of pillows.
But I'm going to conquer my fears.
Tonight.
(HINGES CREAKING)
(OWL HOOTING)
(STRAINED GRUNTS)
I changed my mind!
Can you please
open the gate'?
Hmm? I don't
work here.
I was just visiting another
security guard that died.
Bye, now.
(ANIMAL HOWLING IN DISTANCE)
(SHUDDERING)
If I can just spend the night
here, I'll never be scared again.
And, boy, you're free to
go home whenever you want.
(GASPS)
Hi, Dr. Nick.
Hi, everybody!
I mean,
I'm not Dr. Nick.
I'm Dr. Octopus.
Ha!
I'm going to get you, Spidey.
Then I will have upside-down
kiss with Mary Jane.
Huh?
Bye, Dr. Nick.
Bye, Lisa.
And remember, you have
a checkup next Thursday.
We don't go to you anymore.
We have a better doctor.
Oh, congratulations!
Boys, that grave robber
could be anywhere.
The most vital thing
is that we stick together.
Wait. Where did
everybody go?
Okay, this is it,
Clancy.
No squad car, no backup,
legs cramping in fear.
Sweat in my eyes and groin...
I'd better get out of
this damn cop uniform
before someone
takes a shot at me.
There we go.
Oh, hey, there's my Walkman.
(MUSIC PLAYING ON HEADPHONES)
You know, I actually
got into law school,
but I just
couldn't afford it.
Quiet, I hear something.
Yeah, that's my life
slipping away.
Okay, got to
keep calm.
If Scooby Doo has
taught me anything,
it's that the only
thing to fear
are crooked real
estate developers.
(CRACKING)
(HOOTING)
(SCREAMING)
(BATS SCREECHING)
Whoa!
(GROANING)
Where's Lisa, boy? This book's
going to solve all her problems.
Well, if you're
looking for Lisa,
she said she
was going to spend
the night in
the boneyard out back.
The cemetery? And you're
just sitting here'?
I figured the best
thing I could do
is monitor the news
for any reports.
You're watching cartoons!
Just the show for me!
Tim-Tom Tabby
is a curious cat.
Went to see
the queen in a velveteen hat.
Oh!
This is so boring!
(HAMMER CLICKS)
Shh!
(LAUGHS)
Hey, Mom, can we have
fried chicken for dinner?
BOTH: Lisa!
Don't worry,
we're not evil spirits!
Although,
if we were evil spirits,
we'd probably assume
the shape of your parents.
Homer!
Marge, we owe her the truth.
(SCREAMING)
There, there, dear.
Grandma will protect you.
But I ain't grandma!
(SCREAMING)
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
(GASPS)
Lisa, meet your new husband.
(CHUCKLES)
I made us a dream
house out of slime!
I don't know
howl reproduce,
but we'll have a great
time figuring it out.
(SCREAMING)
(SHATTERS)
(GROANS)
Where am I?
(ROARING)
(SCREAMING)
Welcome to the land
of wild beasts, little girl.
(ROARING)
Not scared. Not scared.
For God's sake, girl,
you're eight years old.
It's natural for you
to feel scared sometime.
But I'm too smart
to get scared.
Lisa, everybody
gets scared
no matter how old
or how smart they are.
In fact, I'm scared of her.
No, you're afraid
of intimacy.
That's because I know after
we mate, you'll eat me.
Your brother
didn't seem to mind.
You know, you
monsters seem scary,
but when you get
a little closer...
(LAUGHS) You're just funny.
(ALL MUMBLING)
But wait. How am
I supposed to sleep
with that spooky cemetery
outside my window'?
You could just draw the
blinds, you silly goose.
Or get a night-light.
My dad says
they're too expensive.
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
For God's sake,
they're four bucks apiece.
I could slime your dad,
just like I slimed
us a Paris honeymoon.
I think I'll be
okay by myself.
What is it about slime
that chicks don't dig?
Bye, guys. You've really
helped me a lot.
Bye-bye, Lisa.
Bye, Lisa!
See you soon!
We're always just
a concussion away!
Lisa, honey,
please wake up.
If you do, I'll get you a new pony.
New pony?
This is still part
of your dream.
Dreaming... Dreaming...
Now you're awake.
Oh!
Sweetie, we're going
to get you home
and straighten out all
these fears you have.
I think I'm going to be fine.
Let's get some breakfast.
Chief, it's light out.
You can open your eyes
and come down.
I don't want to, Lou!
I've got
a pizza bagel for you.
Let's roll.
Ripped By mstoll