[scoffs] If you ask me, any room
with Patty and Selma in it
is an escape room.
I know you don't like
Patty, Selma,
puzzles, or parties,
but try to enjoy Patty
and Selma's puzzle party.
Comrades, as your damaged
Soviet submarine sinks,
you must solve
a series of puzzles to escape.
Should you need help,
you can request
up to five hints.
[Patty and Selma chuckling]
We've escaped
from every fake dungeon,
zombie space station,
and unlicensed Hogwarts
in this county
with no hints.
Good luck and do svidaniya.
I escaped!
See you later.
[sonar pinging]
Lisa, search
the captain's locker.
Marge, torpedo bay!
Hint!
No!
No hints!
[Squeaky-Voiced Teen]
That door is painted on, sir.
You've used one hint.
You ruined our perfect
hint-free streak,
you Crisco-chugging
pistachio brain!
Yeah? Well, you're a...
a, a... Hint!
I don't know.
Something about her hair, maybe?
That doesn't count as a hint!
Yes, it does!
[Patty and Selma snarling]
-Separate.
-[Homer grunting]
[growls]
[hissing]
Homer, away.
Patty, tss, tss!
Selma, corner. Corner!
[all grumbling]
Why was I in another awards show
"in memoriam" package?
Oh, okay, then.
Then why did they boo me?
Herschella!
If you're wearing a robe,
cinch it.
Aunt Sadie!
My favorite aunt
who still talks to me!
To what do I owe
this barging-in?
Sideshow Mel asked me
to be a guest on your podcast.
I have a podcast?
Talking Krusty!
It's that thing where people
who worked on a TV show
talk about old episodes.
What do you call it?
A-a rewatch podcast.
Why has this been hidden
from me?!
[groans]
[laughter]
So, right in the middle
of the Game of Thrones sketch
where the thrones were toilets,
the cue cards went missing.
What a story!
Only in showbiz.
Why the hell didn't you tell me
about this show about my show?!
We begged you many times
to come on.
Shut up,
you backstabbing traitor!
Who the hell are you, Mustache?!
And who's the skirt
in the pants?
That's Wayne the Grip
and Jodie from Props.
They've been with the show
since day one.
What? You don't recognize
the people
who work on your own show?
Um...
Uh...
Eh? Uh...
[groans]
You're crying because they're
doing a podcast without you.
Now here's your chance!
So sit your butt in the chair
and make with the reminiscing
with your friends from work.
Yeah, my friends from work. I...
[chuckles]
Yeah.
[boing]
[Mr. Teeny screeches]
[sighs]
♪
We've solved every puzzle.
Why can't we find
the key to open the door?
We've never failed
an escape room,
and we're not starting now.
Forgive me, Selma.
Hint!
The bald man who hates you found
the exit key 20 minutes ago
and has been using it to scratch
his butt out of spite.
[blissfully]
Spite.
-[sonar pings]
-Your mission has failed.
The frozen sea
has claimed your bodies,
and your grieving children
will be sent to the gulag.
Happy birthday.
We're dead?
I'll kill you!
-Separate! Separate!
-[others arguing indistinctly]
[grunting]
We did it, boys.
We prayed our way out.
[Rod and Todd]
Yay!
Birthday ruined!
[sighing deeply]
Okay, so there we are,
in the finals of the kids' show
softball league.
-It is 110 degrees...
-[gasps] Huh?
...and we're playing those
psycho cheaters from Bluey.
They slide spikes up,
that's for sure.
[laughter]
And this is another activity
you missed out on
with your work family?
I wasn't invited.
That's on them.
Well, in our defense,
you don't seem like you want
to do things with the crew.
You don't look anyone
in the eye,
you address people
by their shirt color--
That's not true, Green Shirt!
Herschella Krustofsky,
you self-absorbed,
degenerate freak!
You're a lonely, sad narcissist
who has no connection
to his fellow man.
You're an empty
Hollywood elitist clown
who's gonna die alone
on a toilet
kissing your own headshot!
I don't know
how to connect with nobodies.
It's not my fault.
Listen up and listen good.
The problem is you!
[crying]
Oh, my God, you're right!
I'm the problem!
I worked with these good people
for 30 years,
and I haven't made
a single friend!
[crying]
If I can't change,
I'll never be happy!
[crying]
And we'll be back after
this word from 3 Day Clams,
fresh clams from the sea
to your door
in three business days.
[Sadie]
Listen up and listen good.
The problem is you!
-Brake!
-[grunting]
"The problem is you."
[chuckles]
What a catchphrase!
We could build an entire TV show
out of that.
Krusty's brash, no-nonsense,
"tell it like it is" Aunt Sadie
fixes broken relationships
in 30 minutes?
Exactly. Like Judge Judy
but we get the money.
All we have to do is choose the
heaviest metallic sound effect
for when the title slams in.
[clangs]
[Krusty]
Coming up
on The Problem Is You,
Aunt Sadie faces
her toughest challenge yet.
And I'm there, too!
What's hiding
behind those chuckles, hmm?
Another glass of rosé
will not fix this.
[Krusty]
And you won't believe
where the final finger points.
The problem is you!
Hmm... hmm...
Oh! Old Maid looks
20 years younger!
Dad, I thought
you hated family game night.
No.
I hated
extended family game night
with your evil, terrible aunts.
Can you please make up
with them?
We really need six people
to play
The Three Duos
of Half-Dozen Mountain.
Honey, if I could wave
a magic wand
and make Patty and Selma
not suck, I would.
But it's probably best we get
used to never seeing them again.
[doorbell rings]
[yelps]
Them!
Where's Marge? Is she okay?
She texted us she fell off
the roof cleaning the gutters.
I lied about that
to get you all here together.
I did clean the gutters, though.
And I did fall off the roof.
After all these years,
it's obvious I can't get the
three of you to stop fighting.
[tires screech]
But I think
I found someone who can.
Homer, Patty, Selma,
by the time I'm done with you,
you'll be as close
as a family can be.
[all shriek]
Marge, dear,
what's the who, why and how
of this family row?
Well, it's complicated.
I hate jerks,
and they hate cool guys.
End of story.
We didn't like each other
from the start.
But things got really ugly
at that fateful baby shower.
[Selma]
We wanted that day to be perfect
for our sister.
-And it was.
-[Patty] Until this idiot
botched the one and only job
we'd given him.
I got the cake!
[yelping]
We said a carrot cake!
I know. But chocolate is
me and Marge's favorite.
[hyperventilating]
Luckily I brought
a backup carrot cake
because I knew
the Impreginator here
would screw it up.
[Selma and Homer grunt]
You undermining land hags!
What's the matter?
You tell these traitors
that your favorite cake
is chocolate
and that you despise carrot cake
because it's a garden salad
with frosting!
It's fine. It's fine.
Please don't fight.
[moaning]
Mm-hmm. See? See?
I like both cakes.
No, she doesn't!
Eat wrong cake!
[grunting]
[Marge]
It was at that moment I realized
the only solution was to keep
my husband and sisters separated
from then on.
So, Marge, who was right?
What is
your favorite cake flavor?
It's neither! I like vanilla!
Only vanilla!
The less flavor, the better.
Vanilla is the opposite
of chocolate!
Carrot is the opposite of cake!
Marge ruined her life
when she met you!
Shut up! I've heard enough
of your bip-da-bip-da-bip!
You three disgust me.
May you walk
under a falling air conditioner.
That said, the problem...
is you!
[all gasp]
Me?
How can I be the problem?
I'm the Marge of this!
Oh, please.
If you actually wanted peace,
you'd stop interfering.
Let these three lunatics
work out their mishegoss
among themselves.
Why on earth
would I want them to fight?
So you could be the martyr.
You keep them separated
so they won't stop fighting.
God forbid they should ever bury
the hatchet and, who knows...
[chuckles]
become friends.
Because then St. Marge
doesn't get to run the show.
-[Marge] Aah!
-[clattering]
-[Santa's Little Helper howls]
-[Lisa] Hey!
-[glass shatters]
-[Snowball II yowls]
[Marge]
Lamp. [grunts]
That's the craziest thing
I ever heard!
I'm the nicest!
I love everyone!
Out! Out! Out, out! Get out!
I un-sign all the waivers!
Shh, shoo, shoo, shoo!
This is what showbiz is
all about, huh, Wayne the Grip?
The camaraderie.
Huh? Why do you know my name?
Please don't fire me.
I need to support my stepson's
illegal street racing habit.
Relax, my fruit-vaping friend.
I'm just like you--
a member of the crew family.
Really? You always seemed
like you couldn't stand
us below-the-line guys.
[groans]
What I can't stand
is that old-fashioned
Hollywood expression.
Why should there be
some imaginary line separating
the so-called "talent"
from the hardworking riffraff
like you?
If I could, I'd make it
so the line never existed.
[chuckles]
That's pretty cool of you, man.
You know, I'm hosting a crawfish
boil this weekend for the crew.
You should come.
You're inviting me
to your that?
Just watch out
for my friend Jimmy.
He will flick you in the nuts
if you're not looking.
I look forward to it.
Where does that judgmental
old clown-aunt
get off saying I'm the problem?
How can I be the reason
you three don't get along?
[chuckles]
That lady's off her rocker.
Thank you, sweetie.
You always know
how to agree with me.
Yes, I do.
[scoffs]
As if there were a world
where I'd be friends
with my worst enemies.
Hmm. Friends with Patty
and Selma.
What are you doing here, Homer?
This isn't you.
You're not this person.
So, here we all are.
If I could have stayed away,
I would have.
Part of me wants to run.
Part of me knows
I'm through running.
Do you think there's any truth
to what the mean lady said,
that we would be friends
if not for Marge?
I know I don't want
to believe it.
We need to figure out
if this is real.
I know a place where
we can explore these feelings
discreetly.
Patty and Selma,
welcome to Moe's.
Weird how the sunlight stops
at the doorway,
like it's afraid to come in.
Yeah, a scientist tried
to explain it one time
and went crazy.
[Moe]
Homer. Psst. Homer.
Hey, I said "Psst."
Who are these two goddesses?
They're Marge's sisters.
Midge has two hotter sisters?
Patty and Selma.
Pidge and Sidge?
Well, yeah, they're twins.
Oh, my God. Twins?
I always dreamed of hooking up
with twins.
Ever since I saw that old
commercial for the movie Twins.
Patty's a lesbian,
so I don't think--
And one of 'em has
zero interest in men?
I think I'm in love over here.
How could you keep this from me?
How could you do it?
[all murmuring]
All these years we treated
each other like garbage.
But it was Marge's fault.
I hope we can find it
in ourselves to forgive her.
Seeing as we're such great
people, we probably will.
To the three... amigos?
Four. You're so fat,
you count twice.
Zing!
-[all laughing]
-Twice.
Said the spinster with
a toilet brush for a head.
Zing!
[all laughing]
-Good one.
-Now that we're buddies,
our horrible insults
are just delightful zings.
Look, Homer, it's your head.
It's even got your IQ.
Zing!
[metallic scraping]
[Homer straining]
It's like I'm being crushed
by two sacks of wet mail.
[Patty and Selma]
Zing!
Did you have to audition
for this part
or did your agent
just get a call?
[whispers]
Zing.
38 minutes. No hints.
I stayed out of the way.
Homer?
[all yelp]
Marge!
[muffled] Dad, are you hanging
out with Patty and Selma?
-[laughing nervously]
-No, the thing is...
It seems like you guys
are friends.
-[stammering nervously]
-Wh-Why would I...
If you guys are getting along
without me,
the problem is me.
[clangs]
-Open. Open.
-[munching]
Friends.
[Patty]
Unlikely friends.
[Homer]
Remember, no splashing.
-[water splashing]
-[laughing] Oh, no.
Mom, you should go down
and join them.
No, I'd only cause trouble
because I'm the problem.
[worried grunt]
Of course you're not.
No, I am. It's fine, though.
Your father and my sisters
getting along was my dream
and it happened
and now my life is perfect.
Hooray for TV therapy.
Hooray, hooray, hooray.
So perfect that you're up here
watching them
while you refold laundry
that's already been folded.
Maybe I don't do things right
the first time.
Or any time.
[Marge groaning]
Bart! Mom has candy!
Candy, candy, candy,
candy, candy.
[groaning continues]
[sobbing]
I ruined everything.
Candy?
[tires screech]
[groans]
Krusty, you made it.
Like I'm not gonna
drive three hours
to be with my crew family.
You got a little water prison
for the kids. Nice.
Oh, it's a pool.
No, pools go in the ground.
Oh, you got to meet
my neighbors.
That's Phil. He's a cop.
Joe, cop.
Uh, cop, cop, cop.
Uh, I love law enforcement.
And laws.
Hey! Little help, K-dawg?
Oh! I can do this.
I bet on this sport.
[grunts]
[guests gasping]
[children screaming]
[crying]
Walk it off, Jayden.
Walk it off.
The dunes
are calling your name, bro!
[grunting]
-[laughter]
-[cheering]
My stepson's stepson,
he built this baby out
of boat parts!
So, no brakes or safety features
to weigh you down.
Smart.
Is there a helmet?
Statistically,
you're safer without one.
Got to do your own research.
Okay, I can do this.
Just take it slow and steady.
-[yelps]
-[crashes]
Hey, the CPR worked!
And when your heart stopped,
which heaven did you see?
Jet Ski paintball next weekend
at Concrete Lake, K-dawg!
You in?
Wouldn't miss it.
[announcer]
It's The Problem Is You
Season Finale Reunion Special!
[cheering, applause]
Welcome!
On our first hit season,
we solved a lot of problems.
And here they are now!
[audience cheers]
So, how's everybody doing?
Yes, well, when you find out
that you're the problem,
even though
you could have sworn--
and I mean with every fiber
of your being--
that it was the other guy,
it's very, well,
I don't know, freeing?
I don't know.
I was so controlling
of Percival.
But now I just let him
roam free.
Oh, Aunt Sadie,
you changed all our lives.
Once you helped Marge step back
from decades of sabotaging us,
it's been so good for her.
-Right, honey?
-That's right.
I'm gonna be honest.
There was a time when I thought
maybe we were doing
something wrong.
But we were
completely blameless.
Not me. I'm to blame.
The problem is Marge.
All those things that used to
bother me about Marge's sisters,
they just don't anymore.
I can remember, for example,
when I wouldn't be able to stand
the way he's breathing
right now.
Oh. W-Was I breathing loud?
I'm sorry.
Doesn't bother me either.
Good, because the cigarette ash
in your eyebrows
doesn't bother me.
I'm not sitting here, thinking,
"How could there be
so much of it?"
[Selma and Patty murmur]
Kumiko, tell me,
is your husband still skipping
the episode "previously on"s
even though you find them
helpful?
You want to know something else
that doesn't bother me?
That he only cuts his
fingernails on his left hand.
I'm a righty, so I can't use
the clippers with my left!
Again, it doesn't bother us.
[chuckling nervously]
Marge, you want to step in here?
You mean separate you?
Oh, no. No, not me.
I don't do that anymore.
You disgust me!
-Groom yourself!
-You first!
You don't yell at
a reunion show, you sick morons!
Look at these losers I cured.
Cheapskate-- fixed!
Daddy issues-- fixed!
Impotent--
came to terms with.
[Kirk sighs]
You fixed nothing!
You plaster over real problems
with an easy catchphrase.
These three have hated each
other since the moment they met,
and all you did
was give them a reason
to not feel guilty about it.
Don't talk to me about guilt.
I invented guilt!
No! It's my turn to yell!
And point and point and point!
You can't solve relationships
in 30 minutes.
It requires years
of constant hard work
and deep self-reflection
from all parties!
I didn't sign up
for self-reflection.
Now you want me
to work at my marriage?
Oh, I'm leaving you.
And I'm taking the pugs!
[overlapping arguing]
I'm Marge Simpson,
and the problem is not me.
I see it now.
The problem's not me either.
I was wrong to try
to form human connections
with the people
that work for me!
Well, I don't think
that's the lesson.
Why should I spend time
with anyone below the line?!
The line is there for a reason.
The line is an absolute good!
The line is life!
I always knew
that guy was a phony.
Hey, let's go rub our butts
on his sushi.
Don't you leave me!
I've got an hour to fill
with you mental cases!
[growls]
You need my yelling!
I'm so sorry
for your loss, Krusty.
Who said you could talk to me?
Oh! Here we go.
That's Jimmy!
Captioning sponsored by
20th CENTURY FOX TELEVISION
and FOX BROADCASTING COMPANY
and TOYOTA.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
[Sideshow Mel] If you're like me
and you love shellfish
and you're not in a hurry,
did you know that 94% of clams
are perfectly safe to eat
after three business days?
So the next time it's Wednesday
and you feel like having clams
on the following Monday,
visit 3DayClams.com.
Order a dozen littlenecks
and get a shucker for free.
Though with three-day-old clams,
they practically open
themselves.
One taste and you'll say, "Wow,
these clams are fresh enough."
Consult your physician
before ordering 3 Day Clams.
See terms and restrictions
at 3DayClams.com.
Delivery and/or food poisoning
concerns? Call 1-555-CLAM-HELP.
-Shh!
-3 Day Clams is not
an endorsement
of eating three-day-old clams.