The Simpsons.
Hey, kids, it's story time.
I'm gonna tell you the story
of Krusty's expensive new suit.
His sexual harassment suit!
Oh, boy...
Anyway, as part of
Krusty's plea bargain,
he has a new court-ordered
sidekick,
Ms. No-means-no.
Whoa, you're hot!
Let's get some dinner
after the show.
I have dinner
with all my employees,
right, Sideshow Mel?
We've never spoken
outside of work.
I'm surprised he doesn't try
to blame his problems
on his Percodan addiction.
It wasn't my fault.
It was the Percodan.
If you ask me,
that stuff rots your brain.
And now a word
from our new sponsor.
Percodan?! Aw, crap!
Bart, are you ready
for your history test?
You bet, Mom.
Ask me anything.
Okay. Who was George
Washington Carver?
Um... the guy who chopped up
George Washington?
Really? Wow.
Bart, you said you
were going to study.
Oh, my stomach.
You just don't want
to take that test.
No, I mean it.
It really hurts.
Mom, I think he's serious.
Kids are so naive.
Lisa, when you
get to be our age,
you'll learn
a few things.
Like when a sign says,
"Do not feed the bears,"
man, you'd better not
feed the bears.
Now get to school, boy.
Mrs. Krabappel,
I can't take the test.
I have a stomachache.
Well, that's a lame excuse
for an excuse. Ha!
Look, if you ignore me
and I die,
you'll get in a lot of trouble.
Read page six
of the school charter.
"No teacher
shall be held accountable
if Bart Simpson dies."
We're also absolved if Milhouse
gets eaten by the school snake.
Hey, cool,
there's a rabbit in here.
Mrs. Krabappel,
I'm done failing the test.
Can I please go to the nurse?
Gosh, Bart,
maybe you really are in pain.
Well, it would be cruel
not to let you go.
Now you may go.
Lunch lady Doris?
- Why are you here?
- Budget cuts.
They've even got
groundskeeper Willie
teaching French.
Bonjour,
you cheese-eatin'
surrender monkeys.
Look, my stomach really hurts.
All I can give you are these
chewable Prozac for kids.
Your choice...
Manic-depressive mouse
or the bluebird of unhappiness.
Superintendent Chalmers,
I'd like you to meet
our new school nurse,
lunch lady Doris.
Yeah, nice to see you.
Seymour, why is that student
lying unconscious on the floor?
Well, in many cases,
the floor is the bes...
Oh, look, here comes Lumpy,
the school snake.
Help! Help!
Oh, Lord.
Don't worry, son.
You'll be fine.
This boy's appendix is inflamed
and about to burst,
which will make it easier
to find once I get in there.
Man, these are primo seats.
I could really go
for a hot dog.
Homer, this is
an operation.
Hot dogs!
Get your
hot dogs here!
Whoo-hoo!
Okay, Bart,
I will count to three,
and you will be
sound asleep.
One, two, three.
Out like a light.
Scalpel.
Oopsie.
Maybe if I fiddle
with these knobs.
Hey, I smell gas.
Pleasant gas.
Night-night gas.
How's my special little guy?
How you feeling,
big brother?
Oh, this is wonderful.
You're alive.
No thanks to you, Homer.
Why, you little...!
Now, Homer, please.
The boy's just had
a very serious operation.
Oh, right.
Now, Bart,
I found the culprit...
A jagged metal cereal "O."
Wicked! I got this cool scar
and I get to miss
a week of school.
Dr. Hibbert, can I have
my appendix out?
- Yeah, me, too.
- I want mine out first.
Why not? Follow me, kids.
Nurse, prep these children.
I'm glad
you're okay, Bart.
Bleeding Gums Murphy!
Little Lisa,
it's good to see ya again.
It's been a long time.
My friends call me
Bleeding Gums.
Eww! How'd you get
a name like that?
Well, let me put it this way...
You ever been to the dentist?
- Yeah.
- Not me.
I suppose
I should go to one,
but I got enough pain
in my life as it is.
What are you here for?
My brother just had
his appendix out.
Is he gonna be okay?
Hello, I'm Dr. Cheeks.
I'm doing my rounds,
and I'm a little behind.
He'll be fine.
Lisa, I sure am glad
you dropped by.
You're the first visitor
I've had.
What about your family?
I don't really
have a family.
All I had was a little brother
who grew up to become a doctor.
He used to laugh at
the most inappropriate times.
Hey, I've got an older brother
that I'll never see.
He's a jazz musician,
or some such.
Oh, well. Bye-bye.
It must be awful to be
all alone in the world.
Well, I always had my music.
I learned at the feet
of Blind Willie Witherspoon.
I've been playing jazz
for 30 years,
and I just can't make
a go of it.
I want you to have
my saxophone.
This isn't a saxophone.
It's an umbrella.
So I've been playing
an umbrella for 30 years?
Why didn't anybody
tell me?
We all thought it was funny.
That's not funny.
Then I got my big break.
I was on "Steve Allen's
Tonight Show."
Now, a brilliant jazz musician
who's inspired me
to do some improv poetry.
"Twinkle, twinkle, groovy cat,
"how I wonder where you at.
"I really love
the way you cook.
Just like me
when I wrote this book."
"How To Make Love
To Steve Allen."
From the author of...
...and...
I cut my first
and only album:
"Sax on the Beach."
But then I spent all my money
on my $1,500-a-day habit.
I'd like another
Faberge egg, please?
Sir, don't you think
you've had enough?
I'll tell you
when I've had enough!
When was the last time
you worked?
In '86, when I did a guest shot
on "The Cosby Show."
Hey, kids.
Meet Grandpa Murphy.
But we have
three grandpas already.
This one's a great
jazz musician.
Oh, they all are.
You see, the kids...
They listen
to the rap music
which gives them
the brain damage
with their hippin'
and their hoppin'
and the bippin'
and the boppin'.
So they don't know
what the jazz is all about.
You see, jazz is like
a Jell-O pudding pop.
No. Actually, it's
more like Kodak film.
No. Actually,
jazz is like the new Coke.
It'll be around forever.
Wow! You've had
some career.
Although the moral
seems to be
that a lifetime of jazz
leaves you sad and lonely.
Well, before you
came to visit,
I would have agreed
with you.
This just in.
Krusty The Clown staged
a press conference today
to defend himself
against charges
that his products
are unsafe,
his theme park is
a deathtrap
and that he's
marketing videos
of Tonya Harding's
wedding night.
And I contend that those
tourists were decapitated
before they entered the
Krustyland House of Knives.
Next question.
What about that little boy
who got appendicitis
from eating your cereal?
To prove that this
metal "O" is harmless,
I will personally eat one.
See, there's nothing...
Ah, boy!
This thing
is shredding my insides!
Uh, Krusty, that wasn't
the metal one.
That was a regular
Krusty "O."
It's poison.
So, you all set
for your recital?
I sure am!
Look!
I stopped brushing my teeth
so I can play just like you.
Aw. Lisa, honey,
music comes from
what's in your heart,
not what's on your teeth.
Come on.
Let's jam.
Lift me,
won't you lift me.
Above the old routine?
Make it nice.
Play it clean.
Jazzman.
When the jazzman's
testifying.
A faithless man believes.
We can sing you
into paradise.
Or bring you
to your knees.
Jazzman.
Oh, jazzman.
Hey, Moe, what'll you give
me for an A.A. chip?
Barney, this is
a five-minute chip.
Eh. It's worth
the Pabst.
Baby, you are gonna
knock 'em dead.
Here...
Take this for luck.
Your sax!
Thank you so much!
Now, I have learned that most
of the orchestra
is having
their appendixes removed.
So, without further ado,
I give you the remnants
of the Springfield
Elementary School orchestra.
On saxophone,
Lisa Simpson.
On triangle,
Martin Prince,
and with a flute
up his nose,
Ralph Wiggum.
That's some nice flutin', boy.
They will be playing
"Stars And Stripes Forever,"
hopefully not forever.
This sucks!
Hey, Bleeding Gums,
I was great!
And I owe it all to...
What happened to Mr. Murphy?
I'm sorry. He passed away.
Lisa, honey, are you
gonna be okay?
Bleeding Gums
was my hero,
and I never got to
tell him how I felt.
Oh, I'm sure he knew.
And I'm sure that wherever
he is now, he's happy.
But he was the only person
who had the same love
for music that I do.
Thank you.
Oh, Dad,
why did he have to die?
Well, it's like the time
that your cat Snowball
got run over.
- Remember, honey?
- Yeah.
What I'm saying is
all we have to do
is go down to the pound
and get a new jazzman.
Oh, Dad!
Oh. I blew it again.
What?
Hey, Lis, you still upset
about that jazz guy?
If it helps,
I believe that after you die,
you can come back
as whatever you want.
I'll be a butterfly.
How come?
Because... nobody ever
suspects "the butterfly."
I didn't burn down the school.
It was the butterfly,
I tell you.
The butterfly!
He's crazy, boys.
Get the Taser.
Maybe I need
to talk to somebody
with a little more
age and wisdom.
Death stalks you
at every turn!
- Grampa.
- Well, it does.
There it is!
Death!
It's only Maggie.
Oh, yeah.
You know, at my age,
the mind starts
playing tricks, so...
Death!
That's only the cat.
That's Maggie again,
Grampa.
Oh. Where were we?
Death!
How come it won't
stop hurting?
Oh, Lisa,
it's normal
to be sad
when a friend dies.
And Bleeding Gums was
a good friend to you.
But nobody is really gone,
as long as we remember them.
Lisa, honey, if you really want
to preserve his memory,
I recommend getting a tattoo.
It preserves the things
you love.
"Starland Vocal Band?!"
They suck!
Death!
Isn't anybody gonna show up?
Well, Lisa,
we've waited an hour.
"Dearly beloved,
we are gathered here today
to bid farewell
to Blood and Guts Murphy."
No! It was
Bleeding Gums Murphy.
Ugh! Anyway,
"Bloody Gums Murphy
was quite
the sousaphone player... ".
Saxophone!
He was a jazz musician.
You didn't know him!
Nobody knew him!
But he was a great man.
And I won't rest
until all of Springfield
knows the name
Bleeding Gums Murphy!
And I won't rest
until I've gotten a hot dog.
Homer, this
is a cemetery.
Hot dogs! Get
your hot dogs here!
Whoo-hoo!
What do you do?
Follow my husband around?
Lady, he's putting
my kids through college.
Good news, Bart.
The Krusty-O Cereal Corp.
Has settled your case for $100,000,
less, of course,
my legal fees.
What kind of legal fees?
Well, for a case this complex,
I had to assemble a crack
team of lawyers:
Ronald Shaporo,
trial attorney.
Albert Dershman,
who can hold
three billiard balls
in his mouth.
How much of the hundred thou'
do I get?
Five hundred dollars?
- Yes, well, uh...
- Cool!
Glad you're happy.
Let's roll.
I can't believe it.
500 bucks.
Oh, just think what I can do
with that money.
$500 on red.
The winner is black.
Cool.
Mom, I want to honor
Bleeding Gums' memory,
but I don't know
where to start.
Maybe you could get
the local jazz station
to do a tribute to him, huh?
Jazz. They just make it up
as they go along.
I could do that.
That's "Mary Had
A Little Lamb."
Okay, then this.
That's the same thing.
You just replaced
"dees" with "doos."
Hi. I have a request.
I would like you
to do a tribute
to Bleeding Gums Murphy,
please.
Oh, I'd love to,
little sister,
but we don't
have his album.
What if I could find it?
Well, I'd spin it for you,
but, you know, ain't
no one gonna hear it.
Our broadcast range
is only 23 feet,
which makes us
the most powerful jazz station
in the entire U.S. of A.
Gee, your station
has a lot of problems.
Tell me about it.
Just look at
our morning guy.
Hello. This is Mole Man
in the morning.
Good mole man to you.
Today:
Part four of our series
of "The agonizing pain
in which I live every day."
$250?!
But I need that album
to honor the memory
of Bleeding Gums Murphy.
He's dead?
Well, why didn't you say so?
Where am I gonna get $500?
Now drive,
Smithers, drive!
Excuse me, my good man,
I have $500 to blow.
What have you got?
Behold! The ultimate pog.
I'll take it!
Lisa,
look what I've got.
Ta-da!
Bart, I can't believe it,
but why?
When I said
my stomach hurt,
you were the only one
who believed me.
Oh, thank you, but $500?
You'll never see
that much money again.
Oh, yeah?
Take a look at this.
I got the album.
Here. You can listen
to it on this.
I did the best I could,
Bleeding Gums.
Attention, all units.
Poison gas cloud
heading for...
Ah, that's nice.
Hey, it's getting cloudy.
Oh, boy.
That was for you,
Bleeding Gums.
You've made
an old jazzman happy, Lisa.
You must avenge
my death, Kimba...
I mean Simba.
Luke, I am
your father.
This is CNN.
Will you guys pipe down?
I'm saying good-bye
to Lisa.
We're sorry.
I don't want you to go.
Sorry, but I have to.
Good-bye.
Oh, what the heck?
Once more from the top.
Yay!
When the jazzman's
testifying.
A faithless man believes.
He can sing you
into paradise.
Or bring you
to your knees.
Jazzman.
Take my blues away.
Make my pain
the same as yours.
With every change
you play.
Jazzman.
Oh, jazzman.
One more time!
Oh, come on, Lisa.
I got a date
with Billie Holiday.
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.