The Simpsons.
We now return to the 1971 film.
"Goodtime Slim,
Uncle Doobie
and the Great
Frisco Freak-out,"
starring Troy McClure.
Slim, if we've got the bag
with the stolen diamonds,
then what happened to
the bag with our stash?
There's more than
one way to get high, baby.
Whoa!
Please, Marge.
How often can I see
a movie of this caliber
on late-night TV?
Is there something
wrong, Homie?
No. It's just that I've only
seen this movie twice before
and I've seen you every night
for the last 11 ye...
What I meant to say is...
we'll snuggle tomorrow,
sweetie, I promise.
Enchiladas!
Mom! Dad!
Don't turn on the light!
There's a U.F.O.
outside my window.
Seriously.
Oh, Bart.
It's just an old golf
umbrella stuck in a tree.
C-Can I sleep in there
with you guys tonight?
No.
Can I sit on the roof
with a baseball bat
- in case the U.F.O. does come?
- Yes, yes, yes. That's fine.
Good, good.
I hope you kept
the Homie fires burning.
Homer!
- Homer, wake up. Wake up.
- What?
We need to talk about
the marital difficulties
we've been having lately.
Marge, there's just
too much pressure
what with my job,
the kids, traffic snarls,
political strife
at home and abroad.
But I promise you, the second
all those things go away,
we'll have sex.
I simply can't
wait that long.
Maybe we should
get some help.
How about a book?
- Ooh, okay.
- A tasteful book.
Oh, all right.
Hey, Marge, this guy
looks like Apu.
Shh. I don't want
people to see us
looking at
these books.
Hi, guys.
What you looking at?
Uh... I'm just reading up
on artillery.
Yes, and I'm pursuing
my interest in...
This one's a good choice,
and it's not too smutty.
It's a book on tape
by Paul Harvey.
You know that nice midwestern
man on the radio
who's like
a pleasant version of Grampa?
Ooh. "Mr. And
Mrs. Erotic American."
Mom, Dad.
Look! This biography
of Peter Ueberroth
is only 99 cents.
And I found
the new Al Gore book.
"Sane Planning,
Sensible Tomorrow."
Yeah, I hope it's as exciting
as his other book.
"Rational Thinking,
Reasonable Future."
I'm getting
this book on U.F.O.'s.
Did you know they're real?
But there's a huge
government conspiracy
to cover it up.
Oh, that's just
a paranoid fantasy.
Mr. Vice President
someone finally bought
a copy of your book, sir.
Well, this calls
for a celebration.
Celebrate good times,
come on
I will.
Let's celebrate...
Hello, Americans. Paul Harvey here.
Did you know every
good American
is at heart
an erotic American?
It's true.
A famous couple...
I don't need to tell you
it was Dwight and Mamie
Eisenhower...
Offered this advice:
"Double your pleasure
with a bath... together."
Homie, I can't quite...
The faucet's jammed
into my back.
I'm stuck.
So am I.
Kids?
A romantic vacation
can provide titillation.
Sensual, sanitary seclusion
awaits you
at any of America's fine
AAA-approved motor lodges.
The Arabian Nights Room
looks nice.
The Pharaoh's Chamber
has a vibrating sarcophagus.
Sorry there, Fred and Ethel.
You should have made
a reservation.
We only got
one room left.
The toilet is overflowing
in the Caveman Room.
Oh, here we are.
The "utility room."
This isn't
very erotic.
I think it's an
actual utility room.
No, honey,
it's a romantic fantasy.
I imagine I'm the janitor,
and you're...
the janitor's wife
who has to live with me
in the utility room.
Don't mind me, folks.
Just need to get
the ol' wet-dry vac.
By now your new, improved love life
should have you flinging woo
like nobody's business.
So, to you,
Mr. And Mrs. Erotic American
I bid... good day.
Welcome home, son.
I broke two lamps
and lost all your mail.
What's wrong
with your wife?
Never mind.
You wouldn't understand.
- Flu?
- No.
- Protein deficiency?
Pneumonoultramicroscopic
silicovolcanoconiosis?
No.
Unsatisfying
sex life?
Yes, but please,
don't you say that word.
What? Sex!
What's so unappealing
about hearing your elderly
father talk about sex?
I had sex.
You're home safe.
Done my duty.
See you the next time
we need your signature.
Aw, you never want
to spend any time with me.
But I can help you
with your loving problem.
I got a home remedy
that'll put the dowsers
back in your trousers.
Legend has it
my great Grampappy
stumbled upon this recipe
when he was trying to invent
a cheap substitute
for holy water.
Here you g...
Hey!
Here you go, you ingrate.
Think of me when you're having
the best sex of your life.
Drink it.
Kids, here's $50.
Why not go to the movies
then take a cab
to your aunt's house.
Stay there. Phone call you later.
Now now now.
Whoa! Homie, what's...
Marge, I'll explain
to you afterwards.
What do you think
Mom and Dad are doing right now?
I don't know.
Here he is.
Rex Harrison
and Paul Anka
rolled into one.
That tonic really works.
You and Grampa
should bottle it
and go into business
together.
You want me to spend
more time with Dad?
What about my
new year's resolution?
You can make a lot of money.
Yeah! Where are my pants?
You threw them
out the window
in a fit of passion.
You said you were never going
to need them again.
Oh, hurry, Neddie,
they're awful.
You just be ready
with that garbage bag.
Ooh, mama!
This is finally
really happening.
After years
of disappointment
with "get rich quick" schemes,
I know I'm gonna get rich
with this scheme... and quick.
Sir. Uh, hello, sir.
Yes. You look like a man
who needs help
satisfying his wife, so...
I guess people
have some sort
of moral objection
to our sex drug.
Let me sell it,
you idiot!
Step right up, folks
and witness the magnificent
medicinal miracle
of Simpson and Son's
patented Revitalizing Tonic!
Put some ardor in your
larder with our energizing
moisturizing, tantalizing,
romanticizing,
surprising her-prizing,
revitalizing tonic.
I doubt very highly
that one elixir could boast
so many fantastic properties.
What say we am-scray
out of here
and have a wild wing-ding
at the cyclotron, doctor?
Anything you say,
professor. Whoa!
Ah, tonight we'll push
the twin beds together.
And I found something
for Milhouse
down at the mall too.
A pup tent.
Oh, boy.
Now I can sleep out in the yard.
Yeah! Every single night.
I've discovered that
the rejuvenating effect
people feel is actually
a mild form of poisoning...
No doubt a result of
the unsanitary conditions
in Grampa Simpson's bathtub.
Nonetheless...
What's going on?
Where are all
the grown-ups?
Who cares?
With no adults around,
I run this city.
Uh... carry on.
Listen to this.
"Unexplainable behavior...
"individuals acting
in a secretive fashion
"are often involved
with U.F.O.'s
"or other paranormal phenomena,
e.g., telephone explosions."
Jeez, if it's in a book,
it's got to be true.
Scary, no?
And this guy's
head of the Spaceology
Department
at the Correspondence
College of Tampa!
Will you cook
my dinner for me?
My parents aren't around
and I'm not allowed
to turn on the stove.
Hurry up!
We got a lot of tonic to sell
and a lot of towns to visit.
Frigid Falls, Mount Seldom,
Lake Flaccid...
Great. I'm gonna be stuck
in a car all weekend
with that wheezy windbag.
...and that's what's wrong
with Bart's generation.
Now, as for your generation...
And for the minimal outlay
of one dollar
you can take home a bottle
of liquid lothario.
Distilled Don Juan.
Catalytically carbonated
Casanova.
Lock old Rover in the shed
'cause man has a new best friend
in Simpson and Son's
Revitalizing Tonic.
I'm not convinced!
I've had bad luck
with aphrodisiacs.
All questions will be answered.
All fears will be allayed
with one incontrovertible
demonstration.
May I have a volunteer
from the audience?
Yes... you sir!
Now, sir, you've never
seen me before
is that correct?
That is correct.
Well, than, how come his face
is on the bottle?
You're the worst
shill I've ever seen.
You're a disgrace to the
medicine show business.
They didn't
start chasing us
until you turned on
that getaway music.
Okay, it's now painfully clear.
The adults are definitely
paving the way
for an invasion
by the saucer people.
You fool! Can't you see
it's a massive
government conspiracy?
Or have they gotten to you too?
Hey, hey, hey!
Stop it! Stop it!
Why are you guys jumping
to such ridiculous conclusions?
Haven't you ever heard of
"Ockham's razor"?
"The simplest explanation
is probably the correct one."
So what's the
simplest explanation?
I don't know.
Maybe they're
all reverse vampires
and they have
to get home before dark.
Reverse vampires!
Hey, wait a minute.
That's Amos Pierson's
moose farm.
Make a right here.
Ew... Why are we stopping
at this dump?
That's the house
you grew up in, son.
Wow!
Let's go find that
hot dog tree I planted.
Yeah, we lived here
till the bank
foreclosed in '63.
Farm went bust
after the cows
started giving
sour milk.
Something must have
spooked them good.
Nyah, stupid cows!
Na-na-na-na-na.
Oh, memories.
If this old place
could talk, it'd say...
There she is,
the old Radiation King.
You'd park yourself
right there
and watch for hours on end.
If I, uh, may, Helen,
I'd like to respond to that question
with yet another
flip remark.
Wow.
Look at me, er, Mom.
I am, er, President Kennedy.
Oh, Abe.
Maybe our Homer
could grow up to be
President someday.
You, President?
This is the greatest country
in the world.
We've got a whole system
set up to keep people like you
from ever becoming President.
Quit your daydreaming,
melonhead!
Dad...
How come you never
gave me any encouragement?
Maybe I could have been
something more than I am.
Like a travel agent
to a great scientist
or the inventor
of a hilarious
refrigerator alarm.
Who are you to complain?
You lock me up in a home
and give me
the same damn
shower safety seat
every Christmas.
Your whole life
you never said
one nice thing to me.
That's 'cause
you're a screw-up.
You're the screw-up!
Why, you little...
All right.
All right. That's it.
We're going home.
I'm sick of you
and your stupid tonic.
If I hadn't taken that
stupid tonic 38 years ago
you'd have never been born
and I'd have been happy.
You were an accident!
Get out.
I'm sorry I said that.
Out.
I'm going to get
out of the car
and I hope you'll find it
in your heart
not to drive awa...
Well, I'll be all right
as long as I can remember
my Army training.
Dang!
I'm sorry.
Hi.
Homie, are you really going
to ignore Grampa
for the rest
of your life?
Of course not, Marge.
Just for the rest
of his life.
He said I was an accident.
He didn't want to have me.
You didn't want
to have Bart.
I know, but you're never
supposed to tell the child.
You tell Bart all the time.
You told him this morning.
But when I do it,
it's cute.
So finally
we're all in agreement
about what's going on
with the adults.
Milhouse.
Okay. Here's what we've got.
The Rand Corporation
in conjunction with
- the saucer people...
- Thank you.
Under the supervision
of the reverse vampires...
Are forcing our parents
to go to bed early
in a fiendish plot to
eliminate the meal of dinner!
We're through
the looking glass here, people.
Kids, your daddy and his daddy
are involved in a very sticky
nutty, chewy, chocolatey...
Put it away, boy...
Situation,
and your daddy has realized
something very important.
A father should always
make his kids feel wanted.
Starting right now, I promise
to spend a lot more time
with you
and give you the attention
you deserve.
I can't breathe.
And just feast your ears on
this tantalizing testimonial
from my own flesh and blood...
The son who puts the fun
in Simpson and Son,
my son, Barney!
I used to be a fat,
disgusting slob.
That medicine seems to be
giving your son
a lot of gas.
I assure you his
belching is the result
of an unrelated
alcohol problem.
It just ain't the same
without Homer.
He knew how to drive a car.
Son, my dear son.
From now on, I'm going to be
a good and attentive father.
And for starters,
your old man is gonna
to teach you how to ride
your very first bike.
Dad, number one,
I know how
to ride a bike.
Number two,
I already own a bike
and number three,
that is a girl's bike.
You're no girl.
You're a boy.
A good boy.
You can be President.
Scratch that.
You will be President!
Dad!
I think Lisa
needs another push
on her new tire swing.
No, Dad,
I want to get down.
This tire is filthy
and the steel belts
are poking me.
- Whee!
- No!
No offense, Homer
but your half-assed
underparenting
was a lot more fun than your
half-assed overparenting.
But I'm using my whole ass.
Dad, it's just that
too much of your love
can really be...
scary.
Someday you'll thank me
for all this scary love.
Now I've got
to go somewhere
and do some
serious thinking.
I'm sure he meant to say
serious drinking.
That's what I assumed.
Here's where it all
started to go wrong.
How am I supposed
to be a good Dad
when I never had one myself?
Oh, Dad wasn't even around
on Christmas morning
when I actually got
to meet Santa Claus.
Some father.
Wait a minute.
Dad?
Oh... this photo is a blessing.
It eases my pain.
This tonic's caused me
nothing but trouble.
You've done all the damage
you're gonna do.
Oh, nuts!
- Dad!
- Son!
I'm a screw-up.
I burned down our house.
No, I'm a screw-up.
- You know what?
- What?
We're both screw-ups.
It doesn't matter.
What matters is
you were right
when you told me
I never said anything
nice about you.
So... are you gonn say
something nice now?
Well, I hadn't thought
that far ahead.
Oh, okay, here it goes.
I'm not sorry
I had you, son,
and I was
always proud...
that you weren't
a short man.
Aw, Dad!
What do you say
we roll on the grass, son?
I'm with you, Dad.
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.