The Simpsons.
Ah... this place is going
to smell classy all week.
To Homer...
The Wall Street genius!
Hey, Homer,
how come you got
money to burn,
or singe anyway?
Yeah Homer,
what's your secret investment?
Take a guess.
Uh, pumpkins?
Yeah, that's right, Barney.
This year,
I invested in pumpkins.
They've been going up
the whole month of October,
and I got a feeling
they're going to peak
right around January
and, bang,
that's when I'll cash in.
To Homer, and to Sergeant Pepper
who is growing out of
the middle of your back.
Uh, Barn, you got
to unwrap the plastic
before you smoke these.
To Homer. Yeah!
Way to go, Homer!
Homer, you knuckle-beak,
I told you a hundred times
you got to sell
your pumpkin futures
before Halloween, before.
Alright, let's not panic.
I'll make the money back
by selling one of my livers.
I can get by with one.
Oh, how am I going
to tell Marge we're broke?
I need a miracle.
My house is on fire!
Whoo-hoo!
Insurance to the rescue!
Hello, Homer.
Marge, we had a deal.
Your sisters don't
come here after 6:00,
and I stop eating
your lipstick.
This is a special occasion.
Patty and Selma just got promoted
at the D.M.V.
Yeah, Homer.
Let your wife have
a glimpse of success for once.
All right.
That's the last straw.
Time to take out
the trash, but first
I'm going to have
to ask you to leave.
I'm sorry.
Homer doesn't
mean to be rude.
He's just a very
complicated man.
Wrong!
When are you
going to wake up
and smell your
husband, Marge?
Granted, you got
some kids out of him,
but when the seeds
have been planted,
you throw away
the envelope.
I wish you wouldn't put
Homer down like that.
He may not be a
big success like you,
but I can
always count on him
to provide for the family.
Oh, sweet, trusting Marge,
I can't let you down.
I'll get some money somehow.
Hello. Vegas?
Give me a hundred bucks on red.
D'oh! All right,
I'll send you a check.
If only I could think
of an invention.
Something that would
really make money.
Must concentrate and work harder
than I've ever worked...
Congratulations,
Mr. Simpson.
This invention of yours
has made us all rich,
especially you.
It's simple yet ingenious
and it fits right
in the palm of your hand.
Every person in America
now owns one of these
and in many cases,
three or four.
Could I just get
a look at that?
Why would you
need to see it?
You're the genius who invented
the product in question.
But, uh, could I just...
Now don't worry,
you'll get to see it
just as soon as we unveil
our new ad campaign.
Let me see! Let me see!
Out of the way!
Homer! Homer, wake up!
There's still a few minutes
till our usual bedtime.
Ooh, my invention!
All my money problems
could have...
Money problems?
Homer, are we
in some sort of
fiduciary trouble?
Oh, Marge,
my loyal wife,
of course not.
And Lisa, my
little princess.
And who could forget
dear Rat Boy?
Rat Boy? I resent that.
Bart, I told
you before...
Stop gnawing
on the drywall.
What a day,
eh, Milhouse?
The sun is out,
birds are singing.
Bees are trying to
have sex with them...
As is my understanding.
It is a gorgeously
fabulous day.
Marvelous even.
So, uh, what's your
hurry to get to school?
Nothing.
What's your hurry?
That's enough, Bart.
Fun is fun,
but if we're late,
we're going
to get in trouble.
You're right, Milhouse.
Fun is fun.
Attention, students.
It's time once again
to choose a gym class
for the coming term,
so let's all prove
how adult we can be
by filing to the gym
in a calm and orderly manner,
even though it's first come,
first serve,
and the most popular sports
fill up fast.
Too many wee ones!
This gets uglier every year.
Any sign of Bart and Milhouse?
No. And if they don't
get here soon,
it'll be T.S. for them.
I don't feel right.
Do you hear that, Bart?
That was the tardy bell.
"Truant! Truant! Truant!"
They'll all say.
Aw, who needs him?
I can have fun
all by myself.
S'all right?
S'all right.
Sure Homer, I can loan you
all the money you need.
However, since you
have no collateral,
I'm gonna have to break
your legs in advance.
Gosh, Moe, I use these
all the time.
Couldn't you just
bash my head in?
Hey, hey,
are you a loan shark?
Do you understand
how finance works?
Now, let's
do this thing.
Oh, no.
It's P.E. sign-up day.
How could you forget?
They had signs posted
all over the library.
Better sign up for
something fast, man.
Baseball just
filled up... Ow!
So did tae kwon do.
There's only one class left,
but it happens to be
the coolest one of all.
Ballet?
Dancing is for girls.
Well, you should have
gotten here earlier.
Uh, I need another extension
on my mortgage payments.
I understand that Mr. Simpson,
but according to our computer,
your credit history
is not good.
It says here that you've been
pre-declined for every major credit card.
It also says that you once
grabbed a dog by the hind legs
and pushed him around
like a vacuum cleaner.
That was in the third grade.
Well, it all goes
on your permanent record.
I'm sorry, but if you don't come up
with that money by tomorrow,
the bank is going
to take your house.
Well, good luck finding it
because I'm gonna take
the numbers off tonight.
Well, we'll look for the house
with no numbers.
Then I'll take off the numbers
on my neighbor's house.
So then we'll look for the house next
to the house with no numbers.
All right,
you'll get your money.
You're my last last chance...
Bottom-of-the-barrel, hail-mary,
longshot-wish-you-would-do-it
but-probably-won't
final resort to lend me money.
We'll take care of you.
Yes, care.
Cut him a check
and get him the
hell out of here.
What a wonderful dinner.
What a beautiful family.
Someone get a picture of me
with my arm around this steak.
You're certainly in a good
mood tonight, Dad.
Well, Lisa,
I managed to solve
a little problem today,
and to celebrate,
I'm going to tilt my chair.
Mmm, slanty.
Patty, Selma?
What are you doing here?
We thought we'd stop by
unexpectedly for dinner.
Now bring us some extra chairs
like a good blubber-in-law.
Time to fertilize the lawn.
A couple of 500-pound bags
should do it.
Homer, be careful with
my sisters' heads.
Their necks are brittle.
That's okay, Marge.
Nothing's broke...
Except Homer.
What's that supposed to mean?
It means...
It means these two
fabulous babes
are staying for dinner.
Now, there's a stink
I could have done without.
This has been such
a nice, peaceful dinner.
It calls for a celebration.
I'm going to make
the most international coffee
in the house...
Montreal Morn.
All right,
you had your fun.
Now get lost.
Oh, our fun
hasn't begun yet.
We know something you
don't want Marge to know.
Now we own you
like Siegfried owns Roy.
I'm sorry. All we have
is Nescafe.
I'm very, very sorry.
Oh, Marge, Marge.
You're just in time.
Homer's getting ready
to give us a foot rub.
You are?
No! I... uh...
I'm giving them
a foot massage.
At least let me
have that.
You can start
with the corns.
Then you can move on
to bunion country.
Okay. Steady, Bart.
Taking ballet doesn't
make you any less of a man.
All right, girls.
Today we learn the dance
of the fairy queens.
You can either be
a fairy or a queen.
It's wide open.
Ah, and what have we here?
A young man maybe who thinks
he can be the next Baryshnikov?
I don't want to be
the next anything.
I'm only taking this stupid
class because they made me.
So, he has fire in the belly.
But it will take more than belly
fire to be the next Baryshnikov.
Look, Boris, I think
ballet's for sissies.
Ballet is for the strong,
the fierce, the determined...
But for the sissies...
Never.
Now, put on this fuchsiatard.
You, are a fairy.
Quitting time.
Let's go Homer.
On the way home,
we're stopping at Moe's
for a Zima.
Maybe I'll just stay
and work overtime.
My sisters-in-law
are at my house again.
Homer, quit wallowing
in self-pity.
Pull yourself together
and come get drunk with us.
Is something wrong,
Mr. Simpson?
I don't like wearing
tights, ma'am.
But so many of your
heroes wear tights.
Batman, for example
and... Magellan.
Look, I don't like this cootie platoon
and I never will.
I'm out of here,
and I'm out
of this stupid outfit.
Wait.
Joy of movement increasing.
Love of dance,
impossible to resist.
Toes twinkling!
Look at me, girls.
I'm doing ballet!
And I love it!
Hmm. Am I wrong,
or did it just get fatter
in here?
Request permission
to slink by.
Permission pending.
First...
light our cigarettes.
But you're already
smoking cig...
You're really pushing it.
Come on, Homer.
You can't spell "obsequious"
without "I-O-U."
I'll have to trust
you on that.
Well, Marge was always
a good speller.
Let's ask her.
No! Don't tell Marge.
I'll be good, I'll be good.
Just for that, you have
to crawl around on the floor
like the dog you are.
Yes, ma'am.
Now say "I am Homer Simpson,
the lowly dog"
in a dog's voice.
I am rrr-omer rrr-impson.
Good.
Jump, Homer, jump.
What's going on
in here?
Rabso-rutely rothing, Rarge.
- What's that paper?
- What paper?
Homer.
Is this projection accurate?
Did you borrow money
from my sisters?
I don't know Marge.
I can't be expected to keep track
of all my wheelings
and dealings.
He blew all your savings
on jack-o'-lanterns.
You told!
Sorry, Marge.
I never want to see
you again. You either.
Homer.
Homer, why didn't you tell me?
I was ashamed, Marge.
I failed you as
a husband and a provider,
and at best,
I was a B-plus dog.
I'll understand if you wanna sleep
on the couch tonight.
How's Dad today?
Not too good, Lisa.
Frankly, he's underneath
the table.
Nobody make me any breakfast.
A man so deeply in debt
doesn't deserve it.
But I like to make
you breakfast.
In that case,
I'll just have French toast
with double butter
and a side of bacon.
But no powdered sugar...
I don't deserve it.
Maybe a little powdered sugar.
See that?
I started to do, like,
a little arabesque,
but then I just
fully went for it
and pulled off
the demi-entrechat.
Not that I'm into
that kind of thing.
Bravissimo, Bart!
Next week,
class gives its first recital
and you, you will
dance the male lead.
Dance in front
of my whole school?
What is it with you and ballet?
I know you have
great conflict, Bart.
You love ballet,
yet you fear the boys
will laugh at you. No?
No. I fear the girls
will laugh at me.
I fear the boys will beat
the living snot out of me.
Hey Dad,
what you doing?
Daddy has very
important work to do.
He's looking
through the want ads
to find a part-time job.
Dad, that's a gag paper
we got at the carnival.
Oh. No wonder I didn't hear
about Bart being elected.
World's Greatest Sex Machine.
Aw, I'll never pay
off that debt.
Need money fast?
Got no experience?
Step up to elegance.
Become a limo driver at Classy Joe's.
That's it! I'll make money
with a chauffeur job.
Good thing you turned
on that TV, Lisa.
I didn't turn it on.
I thought you turned it on.
No. Well, anyway,
turn it off.
It is off.
You're gonna have to work hard
to win this crowd over.
Most of them are here
as part of detention.
Really big crowd.
We even bussed in troublemakers
from other schools.
That spiky-haired, masked dancer
is really something.
I wonder who he is.
He's graceful, yet masculine.
So it's okay for me
to enjoy this.
This reminds me
of the movie Fame,
and to a lesser extent,
the TV series
which was also called Fame.
Oh, wow. I can't believe
my very first passenger is
comedy legend Mel Brooks.
I loved that movie
Young Frankenstein.
Scared the hell out of me.
Um, thanks.
Hey, let's do that
2,000-pound-man thing.
I'll be the Carl Reiner guy,
and you be what's-his-face.
Homer, it's not that easy.
It takes the genius
of Carl Reiner
and the rhythm and timing
that only he and I...
Sir, today every country
has a national anthem.
Did they have national anthems
2,000 years ago?
Sure. Sure we had.
Of course we was caves.
But every cave
had a national anthem.
I'll never forget
my cave's national anthem.
What was that national anthem?
Let 'em all go to hell.
Except Cave 76.
Vat's with the si...
What's with the siren?
Evening, Simpson.
You got a short in your taillight.
Started blinking when
you made that turn.
Let's see your
Chauffeur's License.
Chauffeur's License, eh?
Mel, buckle
your borscht belt!
Since you're trying
to make a getaway in park
I'm guessing you
don't have a license.
Better head down
to the D.M.V.
These two broads
will help you out.
Wow. Officer, this man
is making me a little edgy.
Could you please give me
a ride to the airport?
Hey! Hey! You're Mel Brooks!
Sure. I'll give you a ride.
Thank you.
On the way, we can do
that 2,000-dollar-man thing.
You be Carl Reiner,
and I'll be Police Chief Wiggum.
Listen, why don't you play Carl Reiner
and let me play Police Chief Wiggum?
I hate Carl Reiner.
I haven't been moved like this
since the Joy Luck Club.
They love me. I'm accepted.
I don't need this mask anymore.
Behold, the masked dancer
is me, Bart.
It is I who have won
your acclaim.
Bart does ballet!
He dances
like girls!
Go ahead and laugh,
but I took a chance and did
something I wanted to do.
And if that makes me a sissy,
well, then, I guess I'm a sissy.
He's a sissy.
Let's rush him.
Yeah, let's get him!
Come on!
After him, go!
There he is!
There, right there!
Bart, use the ballet.
Leap, leap like
you've never leapt before.
Looks like he took
a pretty bad spill.
Well, as long as he's hurt.
Bart, I am so proud of you.
You've shown
a sensitive side of yourself
that can never be erased.
From this day forward,
we are kindred spirits.
Why did she
just leave me here
when I clearly need
medical attention?
Stupid driving test
at the stupid D.M.V.
where stupid Patty
and stupid Selma work.
Sometimes,
I think God is teasing me,
just like he teased Moses
in the desert.
Tested, Homer.
God tested Moses.
And try to be nice
to my sisters.
Very hard on me to have you
fighting all the time.
Oh, okay, Marge.
I'll get along with them.
Then, I will hug some snakes.
Yes, I will hug and kiss
some poisonous snakes!
Now, that's sarcasm.
Well, well, well.
Look who needs us again
to get his Chauffeur's License.
Look, all I ask
is that you be fair.
Oh! Did not adjust side mirror...
Minus one point.
Failed to check blind
spot... minus two points.
You won't be happy till my family
thinks I'm a loser, will ya?
You are a loser, Homer.
And we're winners.
Ya gotta learn that.
Oh, seat belt twisted...
Minus one point.
Nagging the driver...
Minus ten points for you!
Grazed a cone...
Minus five points.
Being a jerk...
Minus a million points.
- D-oh!
- One more wrong answer,
and Homer flunks another
of life's little tests.
And what's this? Ohhh...
Someone didn't fill in
a circle all the way.
Oh, boy.
Oh, that felt good.
Let me try.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, boy.
Oh, that was so sweet.
- So Homer, how did you do?
- Well, I...
Ladies, please don't
tell me you're smoking
in a government building
because that is precisely
the kind of infraction
that can cost a couple
of sisters their promotion.
- Uh...
- Yeah, oh, what?
- You mean, uh...
I'll never forgive myself
for this.
Wait a minute.
Those are yours, sir?
Yes.
I am in flavor country.
Both of them?
It's a big country.
Ladies, I apologize.
And you, sir, are worse than Hitler.
Homer, I'm...
I'm speechless.
You just saved our hides.
Please, on top of everything else,
don't make me picture your hides.
That's a wonderful thing
you did for my sisters.
I didn't do it
for them.
I did it
for you, Marge.
I'd kill for you.
Please ask me
to kill for you.
No, Homey.
You see?
This is the stuff
I've been telling you about
that you never see.
Homer...
We're... sorry.
If there's anything
we can do to make it up...
- Call off the debt?
- Or, say we could let you
pass your driver's test.
- Call off the debt?
- Uh... well...
Debt's off. Let's go, Marge.
Whoo-hoo!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.