The Simpsons.
"Wet cement."
Is there any sweeter sign?
Well, maybe "high voltage."
Hello, son.
You want to try this flying
motorcycle I just invented?
No time.
Okay.
This is for the ages.
Like Stonehenge, this site
will forever be a mystery.
Who was Bart
and how did he manage to write
his name in solid cement?
He must have been
much smarter
than his sister Lisa
about whom
we know nothing.
Say, let's bring him
back to life
by using technology.
Ay, caramba!
What's normal to him,
amazes us.
He will be our new god.
Oh, good. Somebody's shadow.
I'll just turn
and brag about my work.
Yi-ii!
Bart,
you've graffito-tagged
public property.
It was an accident.
I can't believe you vandalized
your own hometown, Bart.
What would
Jebediah Springfield say?
I think he'd be cool with it.
Homer, will you please help me
make a big deal of this?
What for?
Nobody cared when Bogart
defaced that sidewalk
in Hollywood.
Well, I'm just shocked
by this whole family.
Whatever happened to good,
old-fashioned town pride?
It's been going downhill
ever since
the lake caught fire.
Now just a darned minute.
This town is a part
of who you are.
This is a Springfield
Isotopes cap.
When you wear it,
you're wearing
Springfield.
When you eat a fish
from our river,
you're eating Springfield.
When you make lemonade
from our trees,
you're drinking Springfield.
Mom, when you give that lecture,
you're boring Springfield.
Bart, you have roots
in this town,
and you ought to show
respect for it.
This town is a part of us all.
A part of us all,
a part of us all.
Sorry to repeat myself,
but it'll help you remember.
This town is a part of us all.
A part of us all.
Wow. That does work.
Hey, gonna win some
this season?
Gonna try.
When it comes to catching trout,
nothing beats
the German light infantry.
Beautiful,
aren't they?
Yep. I'm going
to huck them at cars.
Hey, Milhouse, how's
the lemonade business?
It's clearly booming,
Bart.
I don't even want any.
I just bought a pity glass.
We've squozen
our whole supply.
To the lemon tree!
Thar she grows.
You know Milhouse,
I've been thinking.
This town ain't so bad.
Good friends,
lots of lemons,
numerous
angel sightings.
When you get
right down to it,
Springfield's a pretty
cool place to live.
Springfield sucks!
Hey, stop talking bad
about my town, man.
Why don't you make me?
I don't make trash.
I burn it.
Then I guess
you're a garbage man.
I know you are,
but what am I?
A garbage man.
I know you are,
but what am I?
A garbage man.
I know you are,
but what am I?
A garbage man.
Takes one
to know one.
Checkmate.
Hey, kid, stop wearing
your backpack over one shoulder.
We invented that.
- Copycats.
- Ah, you copied us.
Step over this line
and say that.
I'll kick your butt...
at Nintendo.
I just put a rock
in your crummy town.
That's a crud rock.
It belongs in crud town.
Look at the weak,
little baby.
You're stupid,
you stupid, weak baby.
Come on, let's
get out of here.
Hey, they're taking our lemons!
We can't spare a single one.
You just got citric acid
in my eye.
You'll pay for that,
Springfield.
Ah, some things
never change.
Hey, everybody,
an old man's talking.
Grampa's the name.
Did you know this tree
dates back to frontier times?
Wow! Frontier times!
Shut up!
It all began when
Jebediah Springfield
first came to these lands
with his partner,
Shelbyville Manhattan.
People,
our search is over.
On this site, we
shall build a new town
where we can worship freely,
govern justly,
and grow vast fields of hemp
for making rope and blankets.
Yes, and marry
our cousins.
I was just...
What are you talking
about, Shelbyville?
Why would we want
to marry our cousins?
'Cause they're
so attractive.
I thought that was the whole point
of this journey.
Absolutely not.
I tell you,
I won't live in a town
that robs men of the right
to marry their cousins.
Well, then,
we'll form our own town.
Who will come and live a life
devoted to chastity, abstinence,
and a flavorless mush
I call rootmarm?
The town of Springfield
was born on that day.
And to mark
that sweet moment,
our people planted
this lemon tree...
Lemons being the sweetest fruit
available at the time.
Those Shelbyville kids
think they're so hot.
But you know what?
They're not.
I really agree with you
on this one, Bart.
Class, please.
If you don't learn
Roman numerals,
you'll never know the dates
certain motion pictures
were copyrighted.
Everybody come quick!
Something's happened,
no time to explain.
No, children, no.
Your education is important.
Roman numerals,
et cetera, whatever.
I tried.
Are you sure
it wouldn't be faster
to just tell us
what happened?
No. I said there's
no time to explain,
and I stick by that.
The lemon tree's gone.
And the tracks appear
to lead into Shelbyville.
Oh, look, a clue.
A candy bar wrapper.
They're always eating
candy in Shelbyville.
They love the sweet taste.
We got to get
that tree back.
You mean,
go into Shelbyville?
We'll never make it out alive.
That lemon tree
is a part of our town,
and as kids,
the backbone of our economy.
We'll get it back
or choke their rivers
with our dead.
Where you going, Bart?
Mom, you won't believe this,
but something you said
the other day really got
through to me.
And now, I am going
to teach some kids
a lesson.
I choose
to take that literally.
Death to Shelbyville!
Yes, Bart's a tutor now.
Tute on, son!
Tute on!
Hey, Milhouse,
get your invasion supplies
and let's go!
- What the...
- Where'd he go?
Over here,
my friends.
Or is it
over here?
Yeah!
Okay, here's
how it goes.
I'm the leader,
Milhouse is my
loyal sidekick,
Nelson's the tough guy,
Martin's the smart guy,
and Todd's the quiet,
religious guy
who ends up
going crazy.
And now,
the time has come
to cross this line
into mystery and danger.
To step out of childhood
and become men.
If you get lost,
remember,
you can always find east by
staring directly at the sun.
Here's a tip.
Put a pinch of sage
in your boots
and all day long,
a spicy scent is your reward.
Oh, my gosh! Look!
The fire hydrants here
are yellow!
This place is starting
to freak me out.
Danger coming!
Behind us!
What is it, boy?
Is there something behind that wall
we should beat up?
No time to
check it out now.
We've got
lemonade to sell.
Huh. Radical.
They're getting
rich off us.
And that kid with the backpack
said radical.
I say radical.
That's my thing that I say!
I feel like I'm
gonna explode here!
It's almost lunchtime.
Do you know where
your brother is tutoring?
Tutoring? The only
thing Bart's teaching
is guerilla combat
in Shelbyville.
Well, do you have a number
where we can reach him?
No. Mom, Bart and some kids
ran off
to wage war on Shelbyville.
Homer! Come quick!
Bart's quit his tutoring job
and joined a violence gang!
Uh, the trail
has become indistinct.
Uh, I suggest we split up
to cover more ground.
Good idea.
Milhouse, you and me
will be Omega team.
Todd, you and Data
are team Strike Force.
Nelson, that leaves
you and Martin.
Team Discovery Channel!
Your wussiness
better come in handy.
I want some answers,
damn it!
Okay, folks, look,
I called the police captain
in Shelbyville.
He says he hasn't
seen our kids,
but if they show up
in the morgue,
he's gonna fax us.
Oh, man, I hate those
Shelbyville jerks.
Honey, I was born
in Shelbyville.
And it tears
me up inside.
This is my fault.
I tried to teach Bart
about town pride,
but the power
of my words
filled him with
a sort of madness.
Now, Marge, you can't blame
all of Bart's problems
on your one
little speech.
If anything
turned him bad
it's that time you let
him wear a bathing suit
instead of underwear.
And let's not forget
your little speech.
Isn't there anything
we can do?
Yes, there is!
Come on, everybody.
Let's go into Shelbyville
and get those kids
back ourselves.
I got an R.V.
We can use...
Flanders's!
Well, okay, but, you know,
just go a little bit easy...
Pile in, everybody!
No time to wipe your feet.
Okay, piglet,
start squealing.
Where did you
get the lemons
for this lemonade?
Uh, this is Country Time
lemonade mix.
There's never been
anything
close to a lemon
in it, I swear.
Hey, nobody hassles
my little brother.
Hey, no one manhandles
the bosom chum
of Nelson Muntz.
Spring forth,
burly protector
and save me!
Aw, geez.
I never hang out
with him... normally.
Hark to the tale
of Nelson.
And the boy
he loved so dear.
They remained
the best of friends.
For years
and years and years.
What are they saying?
Uh, I'm not sure.
I thought you said
you could read lips.
I assumed I could.
Aw, it's no use,
Milhouse.
If we're going to find
that lemon tree,
I've got
to go undercover.
What I need
is a new face.
You leave that
to the Baron and me.
Hello there,
fellow Shelbyvillians.
Wait a minute.
If you're from
Shelbyville,
how come we've never
seen you at school?
I don't go
to school.
Okay, what's
two plus two?
- Five.
- Story checks out.
We just got word there's
Springfield kids in town.
Curse those
handsome devils.
We're going up
to the bluffs
to paint "Springfield sucks"
in huge letters.
That way, whenever they
look into Shelbyville,
they will realize
that they suck.
Oh, radical.
Quit copying me!
You know, I wish
there was a Springfield
kid here right now.
I'd fill his mouth
with stink bugs!
No, not in my mouth!
...is what
the kid would say.
To the bluffs!
Well, a friendly Springfield
hello there, neighbors.
You know, we think
some kids of ours
may be missing
in your town.
Missing children?
Sounds like
Springfield's
got a discipline
problem.
Maybe that's why we
beat them at football
nearly half
the time, huh?
Quit stalling, kid.
Write "Springfield sucks"
in giant letters.
His can control
is excellent.
Yes. And that wig
makes him look
a lot like one
of the Beatles.
That's right!
The stranger
who walks amongst you
is me, Bart Simpson!
You know, Bart Simpson.
From Springfield?
He's from Springfield!
Get him!
I'll use these spray cans
as jet packs and fly to safety.
So long, losers!
You're dead.
Uh, hey, look!
Someone's attractive cousin.
Huh? Where?
So, he thinks he can
out-skateboard me, huh?
Launch me, boys.
Slow down, you sidewalk-surfing
cube-gleamers!
Wet cement.
I could sure use
that flying motorcycle now.
You had your chance.
Safe at last.
"Caution: Exit
through door seven only.
"All other rooms contain
man-eating tigers"?!
Roman numerals.
They never even tried
to teach us that in school.
Milhouse, what's seven
in Roman numerals?
I'll tell you, Bart,
but really you should end
each transmission
with the word
"over." Over.
Correction: The only
thing that's over
is that transmission.
Is this the untimely end
of Milhouse?
But Milhouse is my name.
But I thought
I was the only one.
A pain I know
all too well.
So, this is what
it feels like
when doves cry.
Milhouse? Milhouse?
Now what do I do?
Wait. I got it.
I got it!
I don't got it.
Okay. Think, Bart.
Where have you seen
Roman numerals before?
I know.
"Rocky V."
That was the fifth one.
So, "Rocky V" plus
"Rocky II" equals...
"Rocky VII"!
Adrian's revenge!
Oh, it's no use.
I'm never gonna find that tree.
This whole raid was
as useless as that yellow,
lemon-shaped rock over there.
Wait a minute.
There's a lemon
behind that rock.
The tree!
Oh! A car impound lot.
The impenetrable
fortress of suburbia.
We'll never get
the tree back now.
Keep your voices
down, boys.
We didn't come this far
to get found out.
Found 'em!
You kids are in big trouble.
Running away from home
like this.
But they stole our lemon tree.
I don't care
what excuse you've got.
Nothing's going to stop me
in the middle of this speech.
You're gonna... lemon tree!
That tree's
been in Springfield
since the time
of our forefathers.
Give it back, or we'll
bust in there and take it.
Bust in here and take it?
You must be stupider
than you look.
Stupider like a fox!
I'm okay.
Don't you get it, Springfield?
It's over.
You lose.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
all this talk
has made me hungry.
This is the darkest day
in the history
of Springfield.
If anybody wants me,
I'll be in the shower.
There's got to be a way
to get that tree back.
Hey, look!
A hospital.
Pull in there.
Oh, great.
Now I'm upside down.
Oh, dear.
Some thoughtless human being
has parked in a hospital zone.
And I think to myself.
What a wonderful world.
No one in history
has ever done
anything this clever.
I'll get the gate.
That's okay, son.
I'll take care of him.
Faster, son.
He's got a taste
for meat now.
Get out here, son.
There's a-doin's
a-transpirin'.
Let's shut the gate
and seal them in.
Gun it, Flanders.
It won't start.
Something's draining
the battery.
Sorry.
We made it.
Whoo-hoo!
Eat my shorts,
Shelbyville.
Eat my shorts.
Yes, eat all of our shirts.
Ooh, you lousy
Springfielders.
Shake harder, boy.
We did it.
All right!
And with that,
a mighty cheer went up from
the heroes of Springfield.
They had brought the sacred tree
back to its native soil.
And though Flanders
was stuck with the impound fee,
he could easily afford it.
More lemonade, Bart?
Absolutely.
Say when.
There are over 14 parts
of the lemon that are edible...
...and with that,
a mighty cheer went up from
the heroes of Shelbyville.
They had banished
the awful lemon tree forever
because it was haunted.
Now, let's all celebrate
with a cool glass
of turnip juice.
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.