The Simpsons.
Hey, Moe, you got
change for a five?
Yeah, sure thing, Lenny.
A snake in the cash register!
Great prank, fellas. Great.
Oh, I'm gonna be
sick tonight.
Hey, Moe, you want
to smell my flower?
Do I!
Oh! I'm burnin' up here!
Ooh, that's hot.
Taking advantage of my
alcohol-soaked clothes.
Oh, it's funny...
And it makes you think.
Oh, I need some coffee
before I black out.
Homer, pass me the sugar.
This is gonna be great!
- Geez!
- Oh, man.
Oh, there's sugar
all over the bar now.
That's not funny,
Homer.
Yeah. We were just
messin' around,
and you had to go
too far!
How many people want Homer
banned from this place for life?
- Yeah!
Aw, come on, everybody.
This bar is like
a tavern to me.
Sorry, Homer, you should have
thought of that
before you gave me
the old "sugar me do."
I'm taking your caricature
down from Mount Lushmore...
and I'm pulling
your favorite song
out of the jukebox.
"It's Raining Men"?!
Yeah, not no more, it ain't.
Joke's on them.
I'm still alive.
Cheer up, Homer.
Can't.
Okay.
What if you pretended
this couch were a bar?
Then you could spend
more nights at home with us. Huh?
I'm not going to dignify
that with an answer.
Look on the
bright side, Dad.
Did you know that the Chinese
use the same word
for "crisis" as they do
for "opportunity"?
Yes! "Crisitunity!"
You're right!
I've been wasting my life away
in that dump for years.
That's it! I'm going to find
a new bar to drink in,
and I'm going to get drunker
than I've ever been in my entire life!
Bart, where's my wallet?
Right here, Dad.
Thank you!
Wow. Classy.
Good evening, sir.
Would you please leave
without a fuss right now?
Okay.
Hmm... this looks like
a nice, friendly place.
Sammy, you're too old
to go on a date with two twins
on the same night you're
supposed to marry Diane
without Rebecca knowing.
Okay Carla,
I'll make you a bet.
If this affects
my major league comeback,
I'll sell the bar.
Woody, give me a beer.
I think you've had
enough, Mr. Peterson.
My chiropractor says I can't
carry you home anymore.
Just give me another beer,
you brain-dead hick!
I'll kill you!
I'll kill all of you!
Woah, settle
down Normy.
Gotta save those
pipes for karaoke.
I love you guys.
Wait a minute.
There's something
bothering me about this place.
I know!
This lesbian bar
doesn't have a fire exit!
Enjoy your deathtrap, ladies.
What was her problem?
Greetings, good man.
Might I trouble you
for a drink?
Oh, get out of here, Homer.
Homer? Who is Homer?
My name is Guy Incognito.
Oh, my God.
This man is my exact double!
That dog has a puffy tail!
Here, puff! Here, puff!
The last bar in Springfield.
If they don't let me in here,
I'm gonna have to quit drinking.
- Yay!
- Shut up, liver!
Ow... my liver hurts.
I'd like a beer, please.
Sorry. You got to be
a pilot to drink in here.
But I am a pilot.
Where's your uniform?
Um... I stowed it safely
in the overhead compartment.
Well, you talk the talk.
Here's a loaner.
We need a pilot, pronto.
Who wants to fly
to the windy city?
- I'll go.
- I'm your man.
Conditions are a little windy.
- Well...
- On second thought...
- You.
- But I...
Hey, you're not just
impersonating a pilot
so you can drink here,
are you?
Yeah. That's exactly
why I'm here.
You fly boys,
you crack me up.
But I keep telling you,
I'm not a pilot!
And I keep telling you,
you fly boys crack me up!
Hi. I'm Alan.
I'm your copilot.
Uh, yeah. Uh... hmm.
As a change of pace,
I'm gonna let you do
most of the work.
I think you're ready
for it, Alan.
And, um, I'll just
get us started...
Uh, we'll need that
to live.
If word gets out about this,
Quasi-Clown Airlines
will be a laughingstock.
In exchange for your silence,
I'm prepared to offer
your family free tickets
to anywhere
in the United States...
excluding Alaska and Hawaii,
the freak states.
Woo-hoo!
Good news, everybody!
Because I endangered lives,
we can fly anywhere we want!
- Alaska!
- Hawaii!
Mmm... I don't know, Homer.
We're right in the middle of
the busy housekeeping season.
But Marge,
you deserve a vacation.
It's a chance for you to clean up
after us in a whole other state!
I don't want to be a wet blanket,
but getting on a plane like that
seems like a hassle
coupled with a burden.
Come on Marge, I want to shake off
the dust of this one-horse town.
I want to explore the world.
I want to watch TV
in a different time zone.
I want to visit
strange, exotic malls.
I'm sick of
eating hoagies.
I want a grinder... a sub...
a foot-long hero!
I want to live, Marge!
Won't you let me live?!
Won't you please?!
So, Marge,
pretty sweet, eh?
Oh, I forgot to clean the
lint basket in the dryer.
If someone broke into
the house and did laundry,
it could start a fire.
Oh, great... I specifically asked
not to be seated next to a baby.
Wow! We must be
really flying high!
Those people down there
look all tiny and blurry,
just like the inside
of a cataract.
Attention, passengers.
Due to our policy
of overselling flights,
this flight
has been oversold.
In accordance
with F.A.A. rules,
the first two people
to the front
will be upgraded
to first class.
Okay, you two.
Come on, Bart.
They're going to pamper us.
Not literally, of course.
I come for the service,
but I stay for the leg room.
Flight crew, prepare for takeoff.
I think I'll go get
a picture of the plane taking off.
Marge, what's wrong?
Are you hungry?
Sleepy? Gassy?
Gassy? Is it gas?
It's gas, isn't it?
Homer, I've never told
you this before,
but I'm not a good flyer.
I have to get off the plane.
Let me off the plane.
I'm asking you nicely
to open the doors.
Take it easy, Marge.
How about if we dope you up real good?
Let me off!
Let me off! Let me off!
It's okay, Marge.
We don't need
to go on a trip.
We'll just wait for the
killer bees to come to us.
You know, I have this feeling
that we forgot something.
I'm sure it's nothing.
Mom, are you feeling
any better?
Yes, but I'd rather
not talk about it.
Permit me to solve
the mystery.
Your mother has a fear
of flying.
So much for the days when I could
say 'at least my mother's normal.'
Well, everybody's got
a fear of something.
Not everybody.
Sock puppets.
Where? Where?
Mom, are you sure you don't
want to discuss it?
Sure as sugar.
Lisa, the important thing
is for your mother
to repress what happened.
Push it deep down
inside her
so she'll never
annoy us again.
But if we don't encourage her
to vent her feelings,
they can come out
in other ways.
I just realized we never had
a wedding for the cat and the dog.
They've been living in sin.
Mom, you've been cooking
all night?
Judge, jury and executioner
all rolled into one you are.
See, Dad? I told you Mom
would have problems.
No, no, honey,
it's all right.
Really, I'm fine.
I'm all right.
Mother always said,
"Don't complain."
Be good. Behave. Behave.
Be nice. Smile. Be polite.
Don't make waves.
You heard
your mother's ramblings.
She's fine, so behave.
Marge, it's 3:00 A.M.
Shouldn't you
be baking?
In a little while.
Mom, can we talk to you?
Can't talk. Keeping myself
in a state
of cat-like readiness.
Uh... neat.
Anyway Mom,
maybe you should go into therapy.
No, I don't need therapy.
I'm fine,
and it's too expensive.
And I don't believe in it.
It breaks up families.
It turns wives
against husbands,
children against fathers,
neighbors against me.
You don't have to pay
some fancy psychiatrist
ten bucks an hour
to get top-notch therapy.
Hello, Radio Psychic.
You will die a terrible,
terrible death.
Ooh, I'm sorry. That was our last caller.
Okay, I'm getting
something now.
Huh... okay. You will die
a terrible, terrible death.
- But I...
- Thank you for calling Radio Psychic.
Do you have
a song request?
"It's Raining Men."
Now Marge, "Dear Abby" says
seeing films about air travel
can calm your fears.
Ooh, here are
some upbeat titles.
No thanks to the plane,
many of us are still...
Alive.
We certainly are.
Pass me another hunk
of co-pilot.
Dad, Mom's getting worse.
You have to take her to
see a real psychiatrist.
Look how tense she is.
She's fine.
Alright Lisa,
you got your way.
Your mom's going
to a psychiatrist.
She's going to tell
Marge to leave me.
It'll break up the family
and you'll have to live
with your grandmother
and pick beans.
Dad, I like
picking beans with Grandma.
Well, keep it up then.
Okay, I will.
Good. You do that.
Fine.
You'll be picking
many a bean.
Hope I do.
I don't believe it.
Principal Skinner!
Well, well, well.
I never thought
I'd win this easy.
Ha, this has nothing
to do with you, Simpson.
I have many, many issues with
my beloved smother... mother.
Bart, leave that man alone
with his pain and sit down.
Okay.
All right, how much
do you charge?
If money's a problem,
I charge on a sliding scale.
I can go as low as $30 an hour.
Keep sliding.
$30 will be fine.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
First, what are
your qualifications?
Well...
Oh, no.
I'm not here to take
a reading test.
I want to see some credentials.
I'm sorry, Doctor.
He's just afraid you'll blame
all my problems on him.
I'm not here
to blame anyone.
Marge, therapy can be an intense process.
We're going to delve deeply
into your subconscious
and we're not going to
stop until we've exposed
the root of your fear
of flying.
Don't worry.
This is a private sanctuary
where whatever transpires
will be just between us.
Whuh?
Oh, that's just Murray,
the window washer.
He comes every day
at 12:00.
But it's a few seconds
before 12:00.
Ever since you
started therapy,
all you can do is talk
about yourself.
Well, what about me, Marge?
I just left my first session,
and I haven't even opened
my mouth yet.
You see? You see?
"I just left my first session
and I haven't opened
my mouth yet."
Marge, there's no simple
explanation for your fear of flying,
but it can probably be traced
to some childhood trauma.
Think back.
What's the earliest memory
you have
of something bad happening?
That would have to be
my first day of school.
They got this thing
called a fire drill.
They use it to drill
a flaming hole
in your head.
And there's only
one big toilet,
and they make you
all go at the same time.
The kids at school
were even worse.
Ew! You like The Monkees?
You know they don't
write their own songs.
They do so.
They don't even play
their own instruments.
No! No!
That's not even
Michael Nesmith's real hat.
Kids can be so cruel.
But it's true.
They didn't write their own songs
or play their
own instruments.
The Monkees
weren't about music, Marge.
They were about rebellion,
about political and social upheaval!
Did you talk about
me in therapy today?
I don't think so.
Tell me the truth!
Don't tell her
I raised my voice! Don't.
Happy family,
happy family.
I keep having the same dream.
I am the mother
from "Lost in Space".
Ready for breakfast,
Dr. Smith?
Oh, being stuck on this
Godforsaken planet
has vanquished what
little appetite I have.
Warning! Warning!
Dr. Smith refuses
to do his astro chores.
Why, you clattering
clank of cogs and...
My dear lady, as you well know,
my back is a disaster area.
D'oh, the pain.
D'oh, the pain of it all!
Danger! Danger!
My hooks are flailing wildly!
Wait!
Daddy, wait, please!
Don't leave!
Take me with you!
Marge, are you aware
you just said.
"Please don't leave"
to your Daddy?
No, I didn't.
Yes, you did.
And you also infringed
on any number of copyrights.
Now, let's talk
about your father.
Sure, okay. I'll talk about Father...
Father Christmas.
That's what they call
Santa Claus in England.
They drive on the
wrong side of the road there.
Now that's crazy.
People are always saying
how small England is,
but you couldn't fit it all in here.
Not by a long shot.
You know what?
I'm cured.
Marge, get back here
and tell me about your father.
What did he
do for a living?
Mmm. Okay.
Okay, but you're going
to make a big deal out of this.
He was a pilot.
A pilot?!
This is a big deal.
You see?
Marge, this may not
be the best time to bring this up,
but your last check bounced.
Wait. I'm remembering
something.
Yes, Marge,
there's still the matter of...
I was a little girl.
Mmm. Good-bye, Margie.
Be a good girl now.
Why does Daddy
have to leave?
Because
he's a pilot.
He flies all
over the world.
I want to see Daddy fly.
Margie!
No, come back!
Daddy? Daddy,
where are you, Da...?
So who wants
a pre-flight cookie?
Fig Newtons? Hydrox?
Daddy?
Don't look at me!
My father was a stewardess.
Marge, there's nothing
to be ashamed of here.
Today, male
flight attendants,
or stewards,
are common.
They are?
Yes.
Thanks to trailblazers
like your father.
You might say
he was a pioneer.
Yeah. You might even say
he was an American hero.
Let's not go nuts.
The important thing
is that we've pinpointed
the precise moment
when you developed
your fear of flying.
Wait. Some other stuff's
coming back to me.
Open wide.
Here comes
the airplane.
This is what a cornfield
looks like, honey.
You think those things
could also have contributed
to my fear of flying?
Yes, yes,
it's all a rich tapestry.
Oh, well, thank you, Doctor.
You've changed my life.
You know Marge, we've really
just begun to scratch the surface.
There's still the far more
serious problem of your husband.
That's okay, you don't have to make
her into some kind of superwoman.
She can get on the plane.
That's plenty.
Thank you, Doctor.
Whenever the wind whistles
through the leaves,
I'll think
Lowenstein, Lowenstein.
My name is Zweig.
Lowenstein...
Don't worry about
a thing, honey.
I'm going to help
you through this.
Those are all
normal noises.
Luggage
compartment closing..
Cross-checking.
Just sit back and relax.
That's just
the engine powering up.
the engine struggling.
That's just a carp
swimming around your ankles.
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.