Mmm. When I die,
we should totally
get this sandwich place
for my memorial.
So good. Mmm. Can't wait.
Oh, all these people
loved Mr. Chase.
His students
are taking it so hard.
Yeah, nobody grieves
like theater kids.
This is my show!
Why are they singing
about computers?
- It was a musical about Y2
- K,
which was very scary back then.
Scarier than anything
we have now.
The whole show takes place
on New Year's Eve,
Mom, which one are you?
I was right over here.
In the wings,
calling all the shots...
as the stage manager.
Mrs. Chase,
I'm so sorry for your loss.
Oh, thank you, dear.
Say, look what I found
when I was cleaning out.
Franklin's office.
My prompt book.
This binder lists all the cues
for the entire production.
Oh, Franklin always said you
were the heart of the show...
That your stage managing
was so... zealous.
I definitely ran a tight ship.
But in a fun way
everyone loved, obviously.
- Oh, yeah, totally.
- Super fun.
Of course, I would have loved
to have been in the show,
except I'm not much of a singer.
But in my imagination, I've got
the voice of a Disney princess.
What a special time.
I'd give anything
to feel that magic again.
It's me!
The cast said yes!
We're putting on a musical!
Wow, you're the director?
No, more
important... the stage manager.
Five minutes, guys!
- Thank you, five.
- Five minutes.
I always used to love
saying that, before...
Good!
Wow, honey,
those dorks are so excited to be
in your show again.
And I will do everything
I can to support you...
while I'm at Moe's.
Mwah.
Sorry, Marge, but I got to
drop out of the show.
I broke my hip
while singing and dancing
about feeling young again.
Say, Dad, what if
you filled in for Lenny
and joined Mom's musical?
Yeah, then you'd be the most
supportive husband ever.
Great idea, kids.
I'm all in, babe!
One pair of super tight
dance pants, please!
From this day forward,
we are enemies.
Forever and ever.
Forever.
Okay,
back on stage... it's just like
we're teenagers again.
Now let's start the rehearsal.
Theater!
Wait, we can't start
without Sasha Reed.
- She was the star of the show.
- Mm-hmm.
She got into Julliard.
Sasha.
You never forget
your first diva.
I'd love to know
what she's been up to.
Well, as your dutiful
stage manager,
I did reach out repeatedly,
but never heard back.
I guess we'll never know
what happened
after Sasha
left little old Springfield
for New York City.
Never say never!
Hello, old friends!
Ah! It's Sasha!
Let me tell you all about it.
Oh, I can't believe
Sasha came back.
What a career!
I know a famous person
that knows what's his name,
who is she,
and never heard of him!
Okay, okay, everybody.
It's so exciting that
Sasha is a massive success,
but we really need
to walk through our blocking.
Let's make it precise, gang!
Blocking, so important.
That's what Hal always told me.
Hal Prince.
Boom! Named it!
But before we get into
the technical stuff,
we need to reconnect
as an ensemblé.
Let's all go to my lake house
and do trust falls.
But we have to carve out
some time to run lines.
Marge Bouvier,
you have not changed a bit.
Okay, Mom, we'll run lines,
but don't wait up for us.
Us? What do you mean?
This bonding session
is for the cast.
You understand, right?
Sure.
Of course.
Come on, friends!
I was wrong.
Theater kids are super cool.
Thanks for the hookup, honey.
Okay, the curtain-raiser
went a smidge long,
so stay on your marks next time.
- Take five!
- Thank you, five.
Anyway, I hope you all remember
the best part of rehearsal...
brownies!
Are those Margie's Brownies
with walnuts and M&Ms?
It's true, I do matter.
Look what else I'm included in.
It's all from our shows.
We were such
a tight-knit group.
Remember the tightness
of the knitting?
There's my old guitar pick.
Oh, I haven't played guitar
since I lost this!
Still works!
Oh, man, this takes me back...
Remember, guys?
Remind me who Billy was again?
You know... Billy.
Right. Uh-huh.
The diner.
Is that why you guys
always smelled
like burnt cinnamon?
- That was you guys?
- Yeah.
Okay, I might've missed
some of those specific moments,
but I'm sure I'll remember
all the other ones.
What else?
Wait, there was a party
at my house?
Where was I?
Guys, that's like,
pretty messed up.
You weren't even in the show.
Is that why I couldn't
go away to college?
Wait, I thought Jackie moved.
Which one?
How'd I miss all of this?
Except me.
I was unpopular and never knew!
All my best memories are ruined.
I wish I had never done
this stupid musical again.
As soon as Sasha showed up,
it was like I didn't exist.
I never liked that Sasha Reed.
Taking pop out of the fridge
without asking...
getting us sued...
Of course!
It's all Sasha's fault.
Someone ought to teach
that Broadway big shot a lesson.
Mom, do you
still have a computer?
Last night I made some
very interesting discoveries,
requiring the printing
of a revised playbill.
So you don't know the people
you said you knew
but who are they?
Marge Bouvier, you're...
mean!
Well, I'm sure you're all
as angry at Sasha as I am,
but now we can wipe
the slate clean
and really come together
as a theater family.
Without Sasha, there's no show.
You ruined everything,
you... techie!
But, w-w-wait.
She made it all up.
She's a liar!
I think this is
the kind of thing
that makes people not want
to invite you to stuff.
Stupid, ungrateful cast.
Did you sleep at all last night?
"We don't care
that Sasha's a liar."
"We still love her
more than you."
Mo-om!
Bart replaced my Kashi cereal
with woodchips
from the hamster cage!
So? You didn't notice
till I told you.
- What's wrong with Mom?
- Well, kids, your mother has
severely pissed off
all the theater weirdos...
Of which I am now one...
But she can't see
it's her fault.
So... are you gonna tell her?
Indeed I am, and there's
only one way to do it.
Marge, darling...
Leave me alone!
Marge, listen!
I'm being delicate!
Oh, are you?
Oh, you're right, Homie.
It's all my fault.
I did the one thing
a stage manager must never do:
I put myself before the show.
You see, kids?
I have to make things right.
You need to let me see
the cast-only text chain.
Yeah, I don't know.
It's really not cool
for me to share it.
Plus, you wouldn't get
any of the jokes.
You might want
to skip over the stuff
with your name in it.
Sasha hasn't left town.
There's still time.
Why would Marge do that to me?
I was never mean to her.
I never even talked to her!
Yeah, we don't care
that you only sell makeup
and that you're a huge liar.
I miss high school.
Remember the night
of the cast party?
You and me... in the hot tub?
That night really happened?
I thought I imagined it.
It was real.
And I've never had better.
Sasha!
Sasha, I'm so sorry.
Once my husband
sang and danced to me
about what I did,
I felt terrible.
I acted like
such a crazy teenager.
All I wanted to do was
recapture my glory days,
when I could've
become anything...
instead of what I really am,
a floor manager at Sephora.
Sales associate.
I guess we both wanted
to be stars again.
There she is.
Probably called us here
to expose the lies
the rest of us put
in our playbill bios.
What lies?
I am
"thrilled to reprise my role
- as Steve/
- Ensemble."
I was supposed
to manage the stage,
but instead I just managed
to screw everything up.
But there's still time
to put on the best show
of the latter part
of our lives.
What do you say?
Should we give it a try?
Oh, why should we?
What has trying
ever gotten anyone?
That's the saddest thing
I've ever heard.
Barney, nobody needs
to do this show more than you.
Yay!
It's a full house, so...
Marge, when I'm onstage
and it's not my turn to talk,
- can I look at my phone?
- No.
It's almost midnight.
What's going to happen?
Five, four...
Three, two, one!
So the show just ends?
What a cop-out!
At least at the endof Rent
you get to see
Mimi come back to life.
This is just lazy.
Marge, thanks for reminding me
how good it feels
to be a big fish
in a small pond.
I guess that's why
you never left.
Actually, I think
it was because my parents
couldn't afford college
after a lawsuit from a party
you threw at my house
but didn't invite me to.
Such timey times.
Oh, my God, it's really her.
It's Marge Bouvier.
Just ask her.
Um, would you please
sign my prompt bible?
You know me?
You're a stage-managing icon!
Would you go
to the diner with us?
We'd die to hear
some of your stories.
Invited to the diner.
I'm getting cheese fries!
Cast party at Marge's house!
All right!
Theater!