♪
[exclaims]
[school bell rings]
♪
[bicycle bell ringing]
[tires screech]
Okay, ladies, let's all
take out this month's book,
then open it, close it
and break out the wine.
[uncertain noises]
You're supposed to say "Woo."
[chuckles]
Luann, we're not
feeling very "woo."
What we're feeling is woo-ried.
-Mm-hmm.
-This is an intervention.
I don't have a problem
with drinking.
It's not the wine.
Luann, you have an addiction
to wine merch.
[sighs] And we say this
out of love,
it's super annoying.
[murmuring agreement]
But it's such a fun way of
telling the world I like wine.
"Mom Fuel,"
that "corks are for quitters."
"Wine is the answer,
what was the question?"
[laughs]
The question is do you want
to live your life like this?
Oh! And I suppose all your
throw pillows just say nothing.
Anyway, it's not like
it's hurting anyone.
Isn't it?
I'm the closing manager
at Mom Goods.
I was injured when you got into
a fight with another customer
over an apron that says
"This is my wine bib."
[ashamed groan]
Luann, we're here for you.
B-But being a funny wine mom
is my thing.
I have absolutely nothing else
in my life.
-[crying]
-[sighs]
You like coffee, right?
What if your new personality
was coffee?
Coffee merch
doesn't get me there.
Chocolate?
"It's chocolate o'clock
somewhere"?
That makes no sense, Bernice.
How about "proud slut"?
Hmm...
mm...
I love it!
And here is
your very first merch.
[cheering and laughing]
[whooping]
Goodbye, Malibu Stacy.
Good luck, Malibu Stacy.
Miss you already.
Goodbye, all you think piece-
inspiring Malibu Stacys.
I'm going to the real world
to find a little girl
who loves me the most.
♪ Closer I am to fine, yeah ♪
♪ Closer I am-- ♪
[birds singing]
-♪
-[children gasp, murmur]
[gasps] I knew
this day would co--
And you're not here for me.
Hi, Shauna!
Um, who are you, freak?
Besides a freaky freak,
you freak.
I'm Malibu Stacy,
your Malibu Stacy.
I came here
from Malibu Stacy Land
because a real girl who
plays with me needs my help.
And that's you, Shauna.
You still play with dolls?
[scoffs] No.
It's okay to be complicated.
As women, we can
encompass multitudes.
Encompass my fist!
[Stacy screams]
-[grunts]
-Yeah, get her!
Get out of here
and leave me alone, loser.
I'm so sorry.
Meet me at home after school.
We'll have a tea party.
I love you so much.
[grunts] You're not fighting me.
You're fighting your fears
of growing up.
-[grunts]
-[pops]
[screams]
[yawning]
All right, good night, Nelly.
Mama, could you tell me a story?
How about one from the Kingdom
of the Classy Ladies?
[chuckling] Another one?
Ah, please, I never get
tired of their adventures.
Well, once upon a time,
there was a beautiful princess
named Muntzeena.
Oh, and she loved to dance
with all of her friends
atop the glittery stage of...
[Nelson]
Lord Tracksuit's Manor!
[Mrs. Muntz]
One fine eve,
a party of knights
of the Order of the Bachelor
from the Valley of Silicon
were there,
tossing much gold.
Did they bring
a wizard with them
who could control the weather?
Oh, they sure did.
And boy, oh, boy,
did he make it rain.
But treachery was in the air.
As the evil Princess Rylee
with two Es
stepped onto the stage,
bidding the troubadour play
"Poureth Some Sugar Unto Me."
But that's Princess Muntzeena's
frolicking ditty.
-Rylee stole it!
-Indeed.
And filled with righteous fury,
Muntzeena removed
her magical Lucite heel
and chucked it at Rylee's
stupid face.
Oh, Princess Muntzeena
didn't get
docked two weeks' pay
again, did she?
No. Because the keeper
of the door,
Sir Gordo of the Latin Kings,
is fair and wise
and kind of into older broads.
So he banished Princess Rylee
to the shift of the morn,
when all the princes
are sleeping off
last night's potions.
[Nelson]
Then King Nelson came in,
stole all the ducats
and treated Muntzeena to lunch
at Krusty Burger.
Oh, my hero.
No, Mom, you're mine.
Ah, shut up.
[both grunt affectionately]
Fun fact about Jennifer Garner,
Marge:
She'll take a night at home
with the kids
over a Hollywood premiere
any day of the week.
I told you that!
Oh, I forgot the tampons.
Can you go grab a box?
Shh, the checkout stranger
can hear.
They don't care what you buy.
Just get the tampons.
We're in a hurry.
That's a happy graduation card.
Oh, it's not those things?
I guess I'm bad at shopping.
So you'll have to go get
those things.
[groans] Fine.
Stop right there, Marge.
Don't play dumb, Homer.
Do you even realize
all the embarrassing stuff
your wife buys for you?
♪ Incompetent husband,
you weak little punk ♪
♪ Your selfless wife
buys creams ♪
♪ To soothe the rash
on your junk ♪
♪ Incompetent husband,
just be a grown man ♪
♪ She didn't flinch when she
bought you an XL bedpan ♪
♪ You weren't even injured ♪
♪ You weren't even sick ♪
♪ Just too drunk
to make it to the can ♪
♪ To the can, to the can ♪
♪ To the can, can, can... ♪
Stop shaming me
in front of Hans Moleman.
Oh, we're just getting started.
♪ Your fungus has infections ♪
♪ Your infections
have the runs ♪
♪ Gassy nipples, crotch foot ♪
♪ Massive hemorrhoids
on your buns ♪
♪ You said they don't remember
or care what we buy ♪
♪ It's a little disconcerting ♪
♪ But I'm glad
they're on my side ♪
♪ She gets you meds
for blood pressure ♪
♪ Cholesterol and gout ♪
♪ I want to get the tampons,
but I can't figure it out ♪
♪ Yes, you can,
yes, you can ♪
♪ Yes, you can, can, can ♪
♪ She texted you
a photo of the brand ♪
♪ Incompetent husband,
we're so on to you ♪
♪ You're only bad at doing
things you don't want to do ♪
♪ You can't be this stupid ♪
♪ It's all just a ruse... ♪
Okay, okay, I'll do it!
I'll buy my wife tampons!
Just tell me where they are.
♪ Incompetent husband,
aisle two. ♪
Breaking news.
Smoke 'em if you got 'em.
A ship carrying America's
entire supply of cigarettes
has become lodged
in the Panama Canal.
R, D, R, D, R, D.
[horns blaring]
Do you think
the honking is helping?
'Cause I don't!
Experts say the cigarette
shortage could mean months
before are restocked
and lungs re-blackened.
Mm. I hope we have enough smokes
to last until this is over.
I'm sure we'll be okay
if we just pool
all our cigarettes.
You know, share.
Yeah. Share.
Share the cigarettes.
Thing is, I don't have any.
Yeah, me neither.
[Patty and Selma growl]
[both grunting]
Liar!
Busted!
Addict!
J'accuse!
J'accuse you!
-Aha!
[coughing, sputtering]
[coughing]
-[beeping]
-[coughing]
Oh, hey there, handsome.
What's your name?
Dr. Julius Hibbert.
No, it's not.
Ugh. Remember, tonight we're
roleplaying as strangers,
meeting for
a tawdry one-night stand
that my therapist says will
reinvigorate our marriage.
I'm a man of science,
not improv.
Mm. Hmph.
Okay, okay, I'll give it a try.
[clears throat]
Hello, stranger.
Got any sexually-transmitted
diseases I should know about?
Ugh. My name is Laverne McCray.
I'm a lingerie model.
Well, we have that in common.
You're a lingerie model?
No, um, my name is also
Laverne McCray.
I-I mean Maverne MacDoolittle?
-Uh, I'm a doc--
-[grumbles]
Documentarian.
Of motorcycles.
Which I race.
For, uh, pleasure.
Oh, Maverne, you're just
full of surprises.
Help! This man is choking!
Is anyone here a doctor?
Me, I'm a...
Uh, I'm a-hoping you find
a doctor before it's too late.
You want me to let a man die
to give our marriage a boost?
It would be a start.
Oh, my God, he's turning blue.
I can help.
I-I'm a French neurosurgeon.
No, he's not.
We're just roleplaying.
You said if I stayed
in character, we could have sex.
I took an oath, woman.
I deserve passion!
A sad scene.
Remember, if you're
going to role-play,
play it safe.
This has been a message from
the President's Council
on Marital Role-play,
which does not exist
because I'm only pretending
to be a spokesperson
to turn on the men in this bar.
Role-play, baby. I dig it.
Fireman Stu is hot for you.
I caught one.
We caught you, Luigi.
You've been smuggling diamonds
inside your four-cheese gnocchi.
Being caught with loaded
gnocchi is no "gn-jokey."
I want-a my mamma!
Eh, what you
should want is a lawyer.
How's about-a both?
♪ She was making antipasto
with a chop, chop, chop-a ♪
♪ When her baby boy was taken
by the cop, cop, cop-a ♪
♪ With-a-out her son, she knew
her heart would-a stop-a ♪
♪ Life had given her
a sock in the jaw ♪
♪ So she headed up to Harvard ♪
♪ Where they have
a law school-a ♪
♪ Her homespun wisdom made ♪
♪ The stuffed shirts drool-a ♪
♪ Well, she no speak-a so good ♪
♪ But she's nobody's fool-a ♪
♪ That's how she became ♪
♪ Mamma-at-law. ♪
It's-a not-a
looking a-good, Mamma.
They gonna
send-a me away forever.
Counselor Mamma,
your closing argument?
[clears throat]
Don't you dare
take-a my sweet, sweet, sweet
baby boy to jail.
You want to kill an old woman?
Uh, no?
Aw, thank you.
You too skinny. Have some ziti.
We find the defendant
not guilty.
[applause]
[Mamma] Next week,
on the Mamma-At-Law...
Civil forfeitures laws unfairly
discriminate against
low income communities.
You too skinny!
♪ Mamma-at-law. ♪
["Serenade No. 13 for strings
in G major" by Mozart playing]
[Dora]
I believe every great dish
is born of dreams.
I'll often awaken
with a new creation
fully formed in my head.
Every morning,
I go to the farmer's market
to get inspired.
Each ingredient
becomes a character
in the story of lunch.
Today's story is I have 14 bucks
and 500 kids to feed.
Salt.
Fat.
Acid.
Heat.
No, thanks.
I've eaten in restaurants
all over the world,
and Lunch Lady Dora's
doing things
I never thought
were possible... or legal.
Someone needs to stop her.
Maybe the government?
[Dora]
When I present my food,
I want it to evoke an emotion.
-Panic.
-Ah!
["The Four Seasons: Summer"
by Antonio Vivaldi]
[Dora]
If I wasn't a cook,
I'd probably be a painter
or a novelist.
Some other job where I could
drink vodka from a mug
and knock off by 2:00.
♪
Narnia.
All hail!
Our queen has returned!
Woodland friends,
it is good to see you.
How has the kingdom fared
in my absence?
The realm is troubled, milady,
and your wisdom
is much required.
By royal decree, we command
that the roads
of our kingdom be improved
so that all may benefit.
Whoa, who's gonna pay for that?
Oh... hmm.
Ooh, what about this?
For every spell cast,
we impose a tariff
of one gold piece.
You're aware that that
unfairly targets witches, right?
This is why so many of us
are moving to other kingdoms.
Well, you want
better roads, right?
And affordable housing?
So you can live closer to work?
Yes, give it to us now.
So, the money for all that
has to come from somewhere.
That's the kingdom's job.
What about
a property tax on moats?
Oh, yeah, soak the rich.
That's your answer
to everything.
Calm down, my good people.
You hear that?
She called us people!
That's racist!
Death to the tyrant!
Sorry, people!
I mean subjects!
I mean... citizens?
[screams]
Ugh. I can't even have fun
in my dreams anymore.
So, hi.
This is my first time
on one of these sites.
I'm not really sure
how this works,
but it's time to admit
that I'm lonely.
Janice passed away
six months ago,
and I'm finally ready
to open my heart
to a new enemy.
We were at war for 50 years.
Oh, God, what a nemesis she was.
The most loathsome,
sorry excuse for a human being
you ever met.
May she burn in Hell.
I know you're not supposed
to talk about your ex,
but that relationship
is a part of me.
Anyway, ever since
I spit on her ugly grave,
I've been alone.
I'm looking for someone
in my rage bracket.
I'm not young.
I don't have time to waste
exchanging
passive-aggressive emails,
or shooting hostile stares
across a supermarket.
I'm looking for
a real commitment.
If you think that could be you,
reach out.
I just want
to make someone miserable
for the rest of
their worthless life.
Hmph.
[chiming]
[playing over radio]
♪ Jesus hates your Prius ♪
♪ The Lord loves his V8 Ford ♪
[klaxon blares over radio]
[announcer]
We interrupt this program
for an emergency broadcast.
A massive tsunami
is headed for Springfield.
-You have ten minutes
left to live...
-[gasps]
...so if there's anything you
still need to do on this Earth,
now is the time.
Howdy, Helen.
-Thought you didn't see--
-[grunts]
Oh, hey, there, Mrs. Lovej--
Ooh!
[train whistle blows]
Helen, are you okay?
[panting]
Did I do someth--
[sighs] I can die now.
[klaxon blares over radio]
We have a clarification
to our previous warning.
A tsunami of savings
is approaching Springfield
at Costington's
Red Tag Clearance.
All is well, and on sale.
It's a great hobby.
Very, uh, manly?
I don't know...
Thanks. Yeah.
I enjoy it.
[children laughing, chattering]
Oh, Milhouse fell down.
I think he's okay,
but it looks like
the poor guy's about to...
[Milhouse wailing]
Yes, sweet music to my wallet.
Aw, I was so sure
it was gonna be Janey.
She's coming off
a two-sleepover weekend.
Doesn't betting on bad things
happening to children
feel just a bit wrong?
I feel nothing,
and I'm fine with that.
Someone just fell off
the monkey bars.
[all gasp]
Willie, we need
an ID on the faller.
[Willie]
It's Sheri.
[groaning]
Oh, yes! Yes!
[Willie]
Correction,
the faller is Teri.
Repeat, Teri.
-[groaning]
-Come to papa.
I-I can't be a part of this.
[Willie]
Oy,
shut up, you debt-ridden
chalk-sniffers.
We have a middle finger
on the playground.
Who flipped the bird?
Come on, weird
foreign exchange student.
I cannot believe
I'm saying this.
The bird-flipper
is Lisa Simpson.
[gasping]
Impossible. What were the odds?
500 to one.
I'm so disappointed in you guys.
Or should I say, for you guys.
Yoink.
Nice work.
Pleasure doing business
with you.
♪
[bicycle bell rings]
[rings]
♪
Captioning sponsored by
20th CENTURY FOX TELEVISION
and FOX BROADCASTING COMPANY
and TOYOTA.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
[narrator]
Every story needs a hero.
Every hero has a beginning.
Witness the rise of a legend.
You know, that
Jake from State Farm
kind of does it for me.
You want to go upstairs?
Yeah, all right.
♪
Shh!