What should we do now?
We've captured the cad.
We've captured the cad
who poisoned all those copper
barons, and it's barely 8:00.
Lucky thing I made
an 8:15 reservation right here.
Why, this is the restaurant
where you proposed.
Oh, you did remember
our anniversary.
Well, look who else remembered.
Aster.
And he's carrying
the Sapphire of Ceylon.
Oh, Mick,
you think of everything.
- Aster!
- Oh, let him go.
He can wear it with the diamond
brooch he buried last week.
- Well, I'll drink to that.
- Darling,
you drink to everything.
Oh, when I get married,
I hope I have the breezy
elegance of Mick and Moira.
Oh, I'm sure you'll have
what your father and I have.
Yep, ten years,
but we still got that magic.
Thanks, sweetie.
Mmm. Ooh, change the channel.
Love It or Lift It is on.
They're going to unwrap
Steven's new face tonight.
Ew, it's covered in Dad cheese.
I'm going to bed.
I'll leave you to your magic.
Bart, I'm worried
about Mom and Dad.
The mushroom spores
are replicating.
Torch the fungus.
Lis, I'm holding the ammo
for the whole team.
Bart, I need a reload.
Ow! Why do I feel that?
Mom and Dad have
completely given up.
Their relationship
has no spark or romance.
You got me out of my game
for girl words?
They're nothing like
the couples in movies
or prescription drug commercials.
They don't dance on beaches
or hang glide,
They just watch TV
and DustBust burp dust.
I don't know, this sounds
like another Lisa thing
- that's not actually a thing.
- Come with me.
What are our lovely parents
up to this fine Sunday?
Champagne brunch?
Historic walking tour?
Or is Mom crawling around
on homemade kneepads?
Good news. The only ants
I'm finding are already dead.
Leave the corpses.
It'll send a message
to the colony.
You might be wondering,
"Why does Dad
have a trash can
bungeed to his waist?"
Answer: To catch
his taco droppings.
Homer, if there's room
in your taco trough,
I've got a present from Maggie.
Hip hop.
Up top.
Nice throw.
Nice catch.
Okay, it's disturbing,
but that's why,
when it comes to parents,
my policy is:
- "Don't look, don't care."
- You should care.
You're gonna live with these two
well into your adult years.
Do you want your future dates
to be greeted
by Captain and Mrs. Underpants?
Hey, baby, you look great.
- We got to go.
- Bart,
introduce us.
We want to see her.
I hope you have
what we have someday.
Couch love. Couch love.
We got to do an intervention.
Mom, Dad, we need to talk.
Not during 21 Days in a Swamp.
They're about to reveal who
they found inside the alligator.
Cody, Cody, Cody, Cody.
First of all,
this is a safe space.
We love you.
But no child should have to see
their parent wear a waste basket.
- It's...
- All you loads do is sit on the couch and watch crappy TV.
We watch educational shows
that teach real-world skills,
like hauling crab
out of the Bering Sea.
Do you kids know
how to pull a gaff hook
out of a crabber's forearm?
They know nothing
of the sort, Marge.
You've gotten into a rut.
Look at this room.
Two people, and yet there's,
like, six throw blankets.
There's nine.
Each one serves a vital purpose.
And I think it's sweet
that we're so at ease
with one another.
There's so much
you're missing out on.
Entertaining, travel,
standing upright.
You won the school raffle
for a week at
The Saffron Togetherness Center.
But this voucher has sat
on the fridge for a year.
Ugh, that thing. We were hoping
to win the kettle corn kettle.
But this place sounds perfect.
A tranquil setting
that blissifies coupleosity
by removing the distractions
of technology and entertainment.
The Saffron Center
sounds so romantic.
It's at the top
of Honeymoon Mountain.
Unless you saggy-bottomed
couch monsters
have given up on romance.
What? I love romance.
Romance is like my oxygen.
But your mom doesn't want to go.
Oh. Do you want to go?
Of course I do.
Unless you're not into romance,
no judgment.
I love romance.
- So, we're going.
- Great.
- It is great.
- Yep.
So great.
Hmm, no phones or television
for the whole week,
and the menu is keto-based.
Are you trying to pronounce
"Cheeto-based"?
No.
Deep down, I knew
you probably weren't.
There's a group meditation
on Saturday with Sharice.
- What time's it start?
- Sunrise.
We won't be seeing Sharice.
There's silent sweat lodge yoga.
Oh, that's also at sunrise.
Hmm, "sunrise,"
"sunrise," "sunrise."
Ooh, there's a sunset hike.
Nope, that starts at sunrise.
- This place sucks.
- Sucks so hard.
I only wanted to go
because you did.
I never want to go anywhere!
Then turn around, baby.
- We're going home.
- Already turning.
Homer!
- Turn into the skid.
- I am!
Th-Then turn out of the skid.
What does the skid want?
Uh, are you okay?
Yes. Yes, I-I think so.
Rocks!
We have to jump now!
Homer!
Okay, I can pound that dent out.
I'll call AAA.
This seems like a good time
to join.
Okay, no phone, no car.
But we made it out of the water
and we're safe.
Homer, listen to me.
We are not safe.
We are in a dire situation.
We're soaking wet
and it's very cold.
We have to fix that now.
We have to make a fire.
On our survival shows,
they all use a bow drill.
- Find a sapling.
- Or we could do this.
That's amazing!
Where did you learn that?
Remember all those recall
letters that said our phone
- would swell up and explode?
- But you exchanged that phone.
Nope. I said I did.
Okay, fine, fine.
But we have a fire.
Now get those wet clothes off.
In front of the fauna?
Just do it!
Almost dry.
Okay, next step: Figure out
the way back to the road.
Help me up that tree.
No...
- No, Homer, no.
- I got you.
- Where'd you go?
- Not that way.
- Up or down?
- I'm not up!
- Can't breathe!
- Turn me around.
And watch my thingy!
Ooch. Ooh. Rough bark.
Homer, don't look up.
Dang, my thingy again.
Okay, if you see
more than one road,
we should walk to the one
with a sit-down restaurant,
because I could really go
for a booth.
Oh, no.
All I see are trees.
Nothing but trees.
So... we're lost?
Wait! I see something!
Something bright red!
And it's close by!
- What'd you see? What is it?
- I don't know.
But it looks man-made.
And right now,
it's our only hope.
Are the clothes dry?
Almost dry.
No, no, no!
This is worse than
Nude and Screwed season six
when Jerry got airlifted out
because howler monkeys bit
his pixilated area!
Homie, I know this looks bad.
We don't have clothes or fire
or shelter or food
or hope of rescue
- or...
- I know what we don't have!
But we have the red thing!
And it's all we have!
Now, run!
Maybe it's a fire truck.
Ow! Or a double-decker bus.
Owie! Or a Twizzler factory.
Ow! Ooh, that went in me.
A bathtub?
A sexy bathtub?
"Since 1943,
"Honeymoon Mountain has been
a mecca of matrimonial merriment
where newlyweds do that voodoo
you do after saying 'I do.'"
A cigarette machine!
Yes! A matchbook!
We have something
to jot phone numbers on!
- Oh... ah...
Oh, I can feel
my front stuff again.
We can turn these abandoned
snuggle shacks into shelter.
And warm clothes.
What the heck is that?
I think it's
a champagne glass Jacuzzi.
We might just be saved.
Bless you,
old-time honeymoon horndogs.
It might be
the melting fiberglass talking,
but I think we'll be okay
until they come and rescue us.
Oh, my God.
No one will know
we never made it
to the Saffron Center
because of their
stupid no-phone policy.
I hope their
rooftop tantric pavilion
falls into their
Zen meditation garden.
No one's looking for us.
They don't even know
we're missing.
Well,
on Helicopter Hiker Hunters,
they always say:
"If you're lost, stay put,
at least until the snow melts."
That could be tomorrow
or a month from now.
Oh, we've
just got to survive here
until they notice we're gone.
Luckily, we have
a warm shelter, water...
And love.
That's sweet.
No, that's the name
of this old massage oil.
Tomorrow we'll find food.
I'll throw another TV
on the fire.
Oh, no berries, no nuts,
our traps are all empty...
Oh, I thought I knew
what hunger was,
but now I know that was
just not being full.
Last week there was Cheerios
powder at the bottom of the bag,
and I just threw it out.
That powder sounds so good.
Tell me
about the powder again...
slowly.
Don't just complain...
Offer solutions!
Oh, great, now they're
talking to each other.
- This has to work.
- Yeah.
Fish are way stupider
than rabbits or nuts.
You stupid fish!
Why don't you bite
my bait-less hook?!
Oh, be careful.
You'll get your shag pants wet.
I didn't used to wear carpeting!
I used to wear pants!
Made out of pants! Oh!
Homer!
Homer! Homer,
get out of those wet clothes
and get to the fire.
Grab it! Grab it!
Don't let it get away!
Oh! I've got fishnet stockings.
Oh, no! They're crotchless!
Get him! Get him!
Get him! Oh! Oh, no!
Don't let it go!
We got it!
Oh, thank you!
Thank you, you beautiful fish,
thank you.
Group hug!
Oh, oh, this is the best meal
of my life.
Oh, God. This is what I want
to eat for every birthday now.
We're gonna be okay.
It's amazing how
the world seems brighter
with a little food
in your belly.
Yeah, you got that right.
- I miss the kids!
- Oh.
What if we never see them again?
Oh, honey, honey, honey,
honey, honey.
We're gonna get back home,
and you're gonna smother them
with so much love,
they'll never become
functioning adults.
You promise?
I promise.
Come on, dance with me.
What was that?
Probably just the wind.
Don't worry, don't worry.
The clamshell will hold.
I think there's a hungry
predator out there.
Oh. Good thing we're in here.
It's coming in.
- It's gone.
- What was that?
Wolverine!
Where is it?
Oh, my God, a wolverine!
Just like the one that killed...
- The Wolverine Whisperer.
- We need a weapon.
Wh-What are you doing?
I'm gonna lead it away.
You stay here.
Homer, no!
Hey, you!
Come and get the fat man!
Oh, Homie.
Ha! You've been outsmarted
by man:
King of Nature!
Destroyer of our planet!
Inventor of Earth Day!
Wait, what are you doing?
Hey, no fair. Cut that out.
Hey, you don't want to eat me.
I'm stringy.
Oh, who am I kidding?
I'm marbled.
I'm human Wagyu!
Leave him alone!
Uh... please?
Marge...!
Run! Run!
I can't hold him much longer!
Hip hop!
Up top!
Run, Marge, run!
Marge, run!
Marge, run! Marge...
Homer.
It's...
it's dead.
Marge!
Oh, oh, are you hurt?
I'm fine.
No, no. No, you're not.
Where's your shoe?
Oh, Marge.
Did I surprise you?
With that sexy wilderness musk,
you're not sneaking up
on anyone.
I'll go forage some more moss
for our love nest.
And later, I'll crotch milady
a fish for dinner.
Oh, sounds perfect.
Hey! Over here!
Come back!
Stop...!
Aw, damn it.
What happened? What is it?
Oh, I screwed up.
There was a park ranger
right there.
I should've yelled right away,
but I looked at you
and our little house, and...
and it... it was too late.
I'm so sorry.
I'm so stupid!
Homie, Homie, Homie, I get it.
But we've got
to get out of here.
Look... we can follow the tracks.
There has to be
a ranger station nearby.
Okay, we'll pack up some water,
wolverine jerky...
- And precious memories.
- Aw.
No, that's the name
of this love jelly
I've been using
as bug repellent.
Say goodbye to the love shack.
- You ready?
- Mm-hmm.
Bugs!
They're in my nose! Ugh!
We did it! There it is!
Homer, wait. Wait.
Just one more moment.
From now on, I'm gonna try
to be more romantic,
like the kids said.
Don't change anything, Homer.
Don't change anything.
I guess we could walk slowly.
We always do.
Captioning sponsored by
20th CENTURY FOX TELEVISION.
FOX BROADCASTING COMPANY
And FORD.
We go further, so you can.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org.
Sure you don't want to go inside
where it's warm?
No. It's time
for my favorite show.