The Simpsons.
This bus has seen
better days.
Well, at least it's
safer than the old bus.
Uh-oh. Time to move.
The hole's getting bigger.
Seymour, the children are
playing in the hole again.
Shouldn't you
get that fixed?
Edna, you know they just cut
the school's budget.
Besides, if I had the money,
I'd fix the exhaust leak
in the back.
Frankly, I think it's causing
some of our low test scores.
All right. The battlefield
is just a half mile ahead.
Begin braking procedure!
This civil war cannon
has been fully restored
and is in
ready-to-fire condition,
but it's good thing
we're not firing it.
Because it happens to be aimed
at the main support leg
of that lookout tower.
People don't realize
that cannons are
very sensitive,
and the slightest jolt
could set them off.
Of course,
for safety reasons,
we don't keep
the cannon loaded.
It's just common sense.
Otto, why don't you
get some more gas?
Here's the credit card.
And a mint
for afterwards.
Five dollars a child?!
Last year it was free.
Hmph. New ownership.
But we don't have
that kind of money.
In fact, no school
could afford the...
Here's the admission,
plus something for you.
See that they get a little
extra education, would you?
Yes, sir, Principal Valiant.
He thinks he's so hot ever since
he swept the Princi awards.
Those things are rigged.
On May 21, 1864,
the men of the
Ninth Bearded infantry
were sunning and fluffing
their beards in the sun.
Suddenly, enemy troops
crested that hill over there.
Fort Springfield,
we surrender unconditionally!
We're sick!
We need leeches!
And hacksaws to saw off
our gangrenous limbs!
But the Springfield brigade
was too brave to
accept the surrender.
Come on, boys.
Those white flags are
no match for our muskets!
Charge!
And the Springfielders
heroically slaughtered
their enemies
as they prayed for mercy.
It's hard to see
what's going on.
I can only make out
the fat soldiers.
All right, children,
switch.
Hey, they're trying
to learn for free!
Get them!
Use your phony guns as clubs!
Run, children!
Start the bus, Otto!
Start the bus!
Damn.
I shouldn't have eaten
the mint first.
Okay. Hop on.
Wait! Wait!
Well, Seymour, because of
your penny-pinching,
we're coming back
from a field trip
with the fewest
children yet.
God bless the man who
invented permission slips.
Uh, I think I
got your lunch.
Oh, yeah. I didn't think
this was for me.
Seymour, the teachers
are fed up.
You have to start putting
money back into the school.
You've cut back
on everything...
Salaries, supplies, the food.
I don't care what you say,
I can taste the newspaper.
Posh. Shredded newspapers
add much-needed roughage
and essential inks.
Besides, you didn't
notice the old gym mats.
There's very little meat
in these gym mats.
Our demands
are very reasonable.
By ignoring them,
you're selling out
these children's futures.
Oh, come on, Edna!
We both know these children
have no future.
Prove me wrong, kids.
Prove me wrong.
I've never seen them
fight like that, Bart.
I'm worried that all this posturing
and saber rattling
could lead to
a teachers' strike.
Strike, eh?
My bones are so brittle.
But I always drink plenty of...
"malk"?
How do you expect us
to teach with these supplies?
This pointer's so old,
it's worn down to a nub.
It still points,
doesn't it?
Stop that!
And look at this.
The only books we have
are ones that were banned
by other schools.
Well, the kids
have to learn
about "Tek War"
sooner or later.
Go away, Bart,
this is not a good time.
I saw you two fighting.
I'm worried
there could be a strike
and the school would shut down.
I'm sure you'd
really hate that.
There's not going
to be a strike, Bart.
Yeah. Skinner says
you wouldn't have
the won tons to go
through with it.
Skinner said that?
Well, I had to
clean it up a little.
But basically,
Krabappel said
you'd give the teachers
everything they want.
- She did?
- Yeah. She said
you'd fold faster than
Superman on laundry day.
We'll see about that.
Simpson,
I always thought you were
sneaky and manipulative.
But now I see
you're really a very
sensitive little boy.
Thank you, sir.
Seymour,
you're being totally unfair,
and the teachers
won't stand for it.
Teachers, you don't have
the guts to strike!
You don't have the guts
to take us all on!
- That's it!
- Stee-rike!
Attention.
This is
an emergency broadcast.
All is well in the school.
My authority as principal
is total...
Hey, give me that!
Attention, teachers.
We're on strike. Ha!
Oh, no. A strike?
Miss Hoover, are you on...
Go home, children!
Hello?
Mrs. Pommelhorst?
I'd like to get down now.
Hey, now that
Largo's gone,
we can play the
forbidden music.
I heard that!
Bart, Lisa, what are
you two doing home so early?
Great news, Mom!
Horrible news, Mom!
The school's on strike!
Maybe forever!
Oh! Overload!
Pleasure overload!
Luckily, I've prepared
for this,
so I'm not too worried.
Sit up straight.
Eyes forward.
No talking.
Is that gum?
Oh, yeah. Phew!
Bart,
leave that crowbar here.
You know I don't like you
prying and jimmying.
Mom! Dad! Great news!
The teachers...
We heard.
And we already
hired a tutor.
Well, looks like
we'll be staying late today
to make up for all this
dillydallying.
Awesome.
You, with the crane!
Spin around real fast!
Now you!
Dump three tons of sand
onto that Porta-Potty.
Hey! Can't you tell my voice
from a ten-year-old kid's?
Ay, caramba!
Hey, that little boy
is playing three games
at once.
- Checkmate.
- Dang.
Lousy teachers trying
to palm off our kids on us.
But, Dad, by striking,
they're trying to effect
a change in management
so they can be happier
and more productive.
Lisa! If you don't like
your job, you don't strike.
You just go in every day
and do it really half-assed.
That's the American way.
I've got some textbooks, but
without state-approved syllabi
and standardized testing,
my education can only go so far.
Honey, maybe you should
relax a little.
Relax?! I can't relax!
Nor can I yield, relent or...
only two synonyms?!
Oh, my God!
I'm losing my perspicacity!
Well, it's always
in the last place you look.
So, if we were
in school this week,
what do you think
we'd be learning?
Get away from me.
Good news, people!
I'm happy to announce
that another union has joined us
in a sympathy strike...
The Piano Tuners Local 412!
Now, for operation
strike-make-go-longer.
You know, I heard
Skinner say
the teachers will crack
any minute.
Skinner said
the teachers will crack
any minute purple
monkey dishwasher.
Well! We'll show him...
Especially for that
purple monkey dishwasher remark.
Seymour, you are
truly incompetent.
Well, I hardly think
it's fair to...
Dummy up, you! Listen to
those passing motorists
who support
the teachers.
15 minute recess,
Milhouse.
The recess assignment is
chapters three through seven.
Yay! Recess!
Milhouse, I found a hive
of killer bees.
You want to go
throw rocks at it?
Sorry, Bart. I'm deeply immersed
in the Teapot Dome scandal.
However,
it might be
feasible in a fortnight.
- Wha...
- I can play in two weeks.
Juh?
I just can't believe.
Stark would stoop to that,
and right in the middle
of Montana
and Dakota's wedding.
All this free time.
I never thought
I'd get sick of "Razor Fight II:
The Slashening."
I probably should stop.
My doctor says
I have the wrists
of an 80-year-old.
What do you mean,
the bank is out of money?!
Insolvent!
You only have enough cash
for the next three customers?!
W-Wait a minute!
J-J-Just a second here!
No, no.
I don't have your money here.
It's in Bill's house
a-a-and Fred's house.
What the hell you doing with
my money in your house, Fred?
Grade me!
Look at me!
Evaluate and rank me!
Oh! I'm good, good, good,
and oh, so smart!
Grade me!
I'm worried about
the kids, Homie.
Lisa's becoming
very obsessive.
This morning I caught her trying
to dissect her own raincoat.
I know.
And this
perpetual motion machine
she made today is a joke.
It just keeps going
faster and faster.
Bart isn't doing
very well either.
He needs boundaries
and structure.
There's something about
flying a kite at night
that's so unwholesome.
Hello, Mother dear.
Oh, that's it!
We have to get them
back to school.
I'm with you, Marge.
Lisa, get in here!
In this house, we obey
the laws of thermodynamics!
All right, I'd like
to call this meeting
of the P.T.A.
to or-diddly-order,
and let's see if we can't put an end
to this strike fuss, huh?
Mrs. Krabappel,
why don't you begin?
Oh, boo yourself.
Our demands are simple:
A small cost-of-living increase
and some better equipment
and supplies for your children!
- Oh, that's easy!
- Give it to 'em!
Yeah, in a dream world.
We have a very
tight budget.
To do what she's asking,
we'd have to raise taxes.
- Raise taxes?
- They're too high as they are!
- I've had enough!
- Taxes are bad!
It's your
children's future!
- Oh, yeah!
- Children! Yes!
I forgot.
It'll cost ya.
No to taxes!
They're gonna
raise taxes!
Come on!
All right.
That's a good point.
Oh, yeah.
That sounds...
- Oh, yeah! The taxes!
- That means money.
The finger thing
means the taxes.
Well, I guess this is
a case where we'll have
to agree to disagree.
- I don't agree to that.
- Neither do I.
Oh, ho-ho! This is
a dilly of a pickle.
Oh, my God!
The P.T.A. has disbanded!
No, no! The P.T.A.
has not disbanded.
We do have
an emergency plan
in case of
a prolonged strike right here.
Let's see.
"Replace teachers with
super-intelligent cyborgs.
"Or, if cyborgs
aren't invented yet,
use people from
the neighborhood."
Talkin' out of turn,
that's a paddlin'.
Lookin' out the window,
Starin' at my sandals,
that's a paddlin'.
Paddlin' the school canoe...
Oh, you better believe
that's a paddlin'.
All right.
So the compression and expansion
of the longitudinal waves
cause the erratic oscillation...
You can see it there...
Of the neighboring
particles.
- Yes, what is it? What?
- Can I play with it?
No, you can't play with it!
You won't enjoy it
on as many levels as I do.
The colors, children.
Okay. When I call your name,
you say "present" or "here."
No, say present.
"Anita Bath..."
All right. Settle down.
Anita Bath here?
All right. Fine, fine.
Uh, "Maya Buttreeks."
Hey, what are you
laughing at? What?
Oh, oh, I get it.
I get it.
It's my big ears,
isn't it, kids?
Isn't it?!
Well, children,
I can't help that!
Wow, Bart!
I'm impressed
the way you knocked off
all those substitutes.
In my weaker moments,
I almost pity them.
Then I just remind myself:
They're trying to teach.
Well, children,
I don't know what you did
to all those substitutes,
but it's going to stop now!
Leopold?
All right. You listen up,
you little freaks!
The fun stops here.
You're gonna shut
your stinking traps
and behave, damn it!
This is one substitute
you're not gonna screw with!
Marge Simpson.
Hello, class!
Hi, Bart! Over here, sweetie!
It's me, Mom!
Hi. Hey! Hello!
Well, I'm sure
some of you know me.
I'm Bart Simpson's mother.
Mom!
Hey, Bart, what about
the booby trap?
- May I?
- Thank you.
- Mama's boy.
- Teacher's pet.
Goody-goody.
I meant
the other booby trap.
Kids have been doing that one
since my day.
So, how was
everybody's day at school?
- Horrifying.
- Pointless.
Exhausting.
It took the children 40 minutes
to locate Canada on the map.
Marge, anyone can miss Canada
all tucked away down there.
Well, my teacher's
a nightmare.
Three kids got sick from
inhaling his ointment fumes,
he confiscated everything
made of tin,
and then he sent us
home early
because he got his beard caught
in the pencil sharpener.
Oh. Oh, um... okay.
Um, here.
Oh. Okay, uh...
let's see, um...
what if I did this?
You're on your own.
There's no way I'll get
into an ivy league school now.
At this rate I probably
won't even get into Vassar.
I've had just about enough
of your Vassar bashing,
young lady.
Look, Mom,
it feels really weird
having you on my turf.
How would you feel
if I started mopping the floor?
I'd be thrilled. You can start right now.
And I'm gonna keep
teaching your class...
Like it or lump it.
Well, then,
I guess I'll just have to get
into the crawl space again.
I hate it when he gets in there.
Psst. Over here.
Mom, I need a dollar.
Ever since you
started teaching here,
kids have been taking
my lunch money.
And I need that money
for candy.
Aw, here you go, precious.
Now go off
with your friends.
Here you go, precious.
Why isn't my
mom stopping this?
We've created
a diversion.
That's a very
nice jig, Kearney.
Now, isn't dancing
much more fun than bullying?
Yeah.
That's it. I can't
take this anymore, Milhouse.
I got to get the
real teachers back.
Bart, you'll never get Krabappel
and Skinner together again.
They're like two
positively charged ions.
Zuh?
Wait! That's it.
With your book smarts,
and my ability
to exploit people
with book smarts,
we can figure out a clever plan
to get them back together.
A surprise party for me
in Principal Skinner's office?
Well, I don't know,
but all right.
Me? Go to my office?
It's highly irregular,
but all right.
And you're not coming out
until you reach an agreement.
Let us out, Bart!
This is not funny, Bart!
Stop it, Bart.
Let us out right now!
Don't worry.
They'll start negotiating.
Let us out!
For the love of God,
let us out!
Man, this is like 'Nam!
Let us out!
Come on, or you will
be so sorry!
You're going to be
verrrrry, very sorry!
Well, Seymour, I guess
we could start talking.
What's the point?
There's no more money
unless you've got some
magic new source of revenue.
Well, we've got to figure
something out.
They've got us locked in
here like prisoners.
Prisoners in
our own school.
This is a great way
to make extra money.
Renting out our cloakrooms to
the overcrowded prison system.
Yo. I used to sit
right over there.
It's all right, children.
Just ignore the murderer.
As a bonus, some of our more
troublesome students
might be scared straight.
Psst, kid.
Help me break out of here.
I'll totally make it
worth your while.
I'm listening.
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.