(SINGING) The Simpsons
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
D'oh!
(EXCLAIMING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Ripped By mstoll
BART: Why does God
always need money?
HOMER;
It's a lot of little stuff.
God has to pay all the
elves in his workshop.
Plus, he's got all those
planets to support.
You see that ring
he gave Saturn?
(WHISTLING)
Who knew saints
had such fat heads?
Ah, it's all a big scam.
This booth?
No, religion in general.
LISA: Hmm.
(SCREAMING)
Not bad.
Here's your
candy apple, sir.
Excellent.
This fundraiser is close to
achieving the Lord's goal,
building a taller
steeple than the one
on that snooty Episcopal
church across the street.
Reverend, why do
we really need this?
To compensate for my
own sense of smallness.
And now for our main event,
the rubber duck race!
The first duck to cross the finish
line wins this home computer.
ALL: Ooh...
That's the new feMac, the
computer designed just for women.
The "you've got mail"
voice is Susan Sarandon.
SARANDON: You've got mail, unlike
the prisoners at Guantanamo Bay.
Get informed.
ALL: Ooh...
Don't worry, Marge.
Me and Terrible Two here are
gonna win that computer for you.
How can you be sure?
'Cause he wants it!
On your marks,
get set...
Wait. Someone's
not on their mark.
That's better! Go!
(HORN BLOWING)
(CHUCKLING)
Now to begin
Operation Slight Edge.
(LAUGHING)
Hee-hee!
I'm winning!
(SHRIEKING) He's headed for the old mill!
No, Cheatie! No!
(GRUNTING)
(SIGHING)
D'oh! D'oh! D'oh!
Too many paddles!
D'oh! (SPUTTERING)
(GROANING)
(CREAKING)
Protect the duck!
D'oh! Protect the duck.
D'oh!
Product the tact... D'oh!
(QUACKING)
Hey! This race
is for rubber ducks!
Not meat ducks!
(ANGRY QUACKING)
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
(QUACKING)
Woo-hoo! I won!
And the winner is...
Uh!
(GROANING)
A living duck?
I wished too hard
and he became real.
And the winner
is Ned Flanders!
This is my favorite
kind of surprise. Mild.
Oh.
There, there.
The fact that you tried
means everything.
Hey, that's the same
thing you said to Bart
after he choked
in that soccer game.
And we both know
he sucked.
And how.
But this is different.
Say, Marge, I don't
really want a computer.
You know, all those complete
strangers Googling each other
makes my flesh crawl!
Just put it in
the trunk and leave.
Ned, that's
so generous.
But there must be something
I could do in return.
Well, sir, we could do a little
quid pro for the Kaypro.
The left-handed
convention is in town,
and as the owner of Springfield's
largest southpaw shop,
I just gotta be there.
Could you, uh, nanny-goat
my kid-diddily-ids?
Uh, hmm...
Let see.
Just a second.
Oh, yeah, sure. I'd be happy
to babysit for Rod and Todd.
"Woo-hoo."
I'm so glad you're
watching the boys, Marge.
Our last babysitter let
'em watch Comedy Central!
Now, Rod makes me check the closet
every night for Rita Rudner.
(SHUDDERING)
"No Rudner."
Here are the numbers for the
police, fire, ambulance,
poison control,
burn clinic,
and people nearby with Rod
and Todd's blood type.
Ooh, Carl!
So you're gonna be
chillin' with me tonight.
Do you want
to play a game?
How about a sitting
still contest?
Hands folded.
Okay, game over.
It's a tie!
That means we both
come in second.
BOTH: We're number two!
We're number two!
What do you
think, Maggie?
Oh, wow.
It's the Big Unit himself, Randy Johnson!
(CHUCKLING)
You've fanned more
men than Salome!
Yeah, I get that a lot.
I'm here promoting my new line
of left-handed teddy bears.
Randy Johnson's Southpawz.
This one's a doctor. You can
give it to your doctor.
Huh? Huh?
You have one
for a mailman?
A bear can't be a mailman.
Now how many doctor
bears do you want?
They come in boxes
of a thousand.
Um...
(SIGHING)
One box?
You and me got a problem!
Here's my mask.
I'm a Star Wars.
Now let's see
who you've drawn.
I'm my brother, Todd.
I'm my brother, Rod.
Ahh! This is too scary.
Change back!
(BOTH WHIMPERING)
I'll help you.
I'm a chipmunk. I eat nuts
without saying grace.
I'm a permission slip.
Hmm.
And thank you, God, for letting Mrs.
Simpson come over.
It was the most fun we've
had since Mommy was here.
Aw...
And could you ask Mommy to
come to Daddy in a dream
and tell him how
to cut our sandwiches?
Aw...
And please tell Mrs. Simpson it's
rude to eavesdrop on our prayers.
Oh...
But we forgive her.
Aw...
Hiya, Marge. Rod and
Todd in the land of Nod?
Mmm-hmm.
We had a lot of fun.
They're terrific kids.
Hey, you're welcome to see
the dynamic duo anytime!
Hmm.
Well, then maybe I will
come by more often.
And Homer can spend
more time with our kids.
He's watching them now.
(SNORING)
Ready?
Ready.
And joust!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Ahh!
(GRUNTING AND YELLING)
Ah! That was awesome!
Let's do it again!
(MUMBLING) A canoe
made of country ham?
You know I'll eat it.
(SNORING)
Hmm, what's wrong
with your teeter-totter?
Daddy says up-and-down
seesaws are dangerous.
Chocks? Why don't
we try it freestyle?
(BOTH WHIMPERING NERVOUSLY)
(WHIMPERING CONTINUES)
(BEETHOVEN'S
SYMPHONY NO. 9 PLAYING)
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
(GRUNTING)
(SPUTTERING)
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
(DOORBELL RINGING)
I heard in study hall you
were babysitting tonight.
Homer, we're not
in high school.
So Marge,
in tomorrow's game,
I'm gonna recover
a fumble just for you.
Oh, maybe you'll run it
in for a touchdown.
Don't pressure me. I get
enough of that from my dad.
Well, maybe we can take
your mind off things
by studying
for the SATs.
Snuggles And Tickles.
(GIGGLING)
Oh!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(DOOR OPENING)
(SHRIEKING)
Old man Flanders!
Hey, Homer. Sneakin'
kisses from the missus?
Springfield High
football rules!
(THUDDING) HOMER: No one turn
on the sprinklers, okay?
Dad, Mom's over at the Flanders'
babysitting Nimrod and Nimtodd.
We wanna
do something.
Fine. As soon as I
finish watching my show.
I want to go to the Showbiz
Animal Retirement Home.
They take in animals
from the movies
and TV that
aren't cute anymore.
(BARKING NERVOUSLY)
(WHINING)
Old showbiz animals, eh?
You think any of the gremlins from
the Gremlins movie are there?
Um, sure.
(LAUGHING)
I'm gonna get them so wet.
Oh, this is much
sadder than I expected.
Sad?
You're crazy.
I feel like I'm at the
Oscars for the animals
I forgot existed.
(OINKING)
Aflac!
(COUGHING)
I'm not a real bear!
That was just the name
of my character.
Now let me out.
Hey, do you know
where the bathroom is?
Maybe I do
and maybe I don't.
You didn't hear it
from me,
but it's next
to the rhino cage.
Word on the street is cover
the toilet seat with tissue.
Sweet, sweet tissue.
(GULPING)
WOMAN:
This is Toot-Toot.
She played Tum-Tum in Teen
Tarzan's Eco-Adventures.
She looks like
she's crying.
(SOBBING)
Oh, she probably
misses her children.
They're all
in show business.
One of them played the
out-of-control judiciary
in a Republican
Party commercial.
Cheer up, Toot-Toot.
Have some of
my ice cream.
(CHIRPING)
(CHITTERING)
(YELPING)
(BART SHOUTING)
My son's been
ape-napped!
No, no,
it's still kidnapped!
The prefix applies
to the victim.
Help! She's grooming me.
(GRUNTING)
She's grooming me!
Aren't you gonna
do something?
I'm afraid there's
nothing we can do now.
A chimp that size could tear
your son's head right off!
But she'll leave
the rest of him alone?
Uh... Uh...
Would you like
to meet Flipper?
Oh, may I remind you they're
old when they come here.
Well, well, look at
my dull-eyed angels.
What's this?
(GASPING)
It's the ripcord from
a Band-Aid wrapper!
Call me Ned Zeppelin but is one
of my boys abrased and contused?
I cut myself on the knife
playing Christian Clue.
The secular humanist did it in the
schoolhouse with misinformation!
Well, I think it's about
time you boys get to bed.
BOTH: Yes, Daddy.
And so we don't
have another disaster,
you crawl up
those steps.
(BOTH GROANING)
Ned, I know
you like to worry,
but these boys are never
going to get self-confidence
unless you let them
try things for themselves.
I just can't.
They're all I've got
since that sad day
when Maude found
eternal happiness.
I thought they might enjoy
it if I took them here.
Everything's covered
in foam.
And it's owned by a corporation,
so you know it's safe.
Their mascot is a
knee-pad-wearing helmet.
Why not?
Where's Bart? I haven't seen
him since you came home.
Oh, you haven't seen
Bart for a few hours,
so you automatically assume I
let something terrible happen.
I didn't say that.
I know what you think.
"When stupid Homer
wasn't looking,
"Bart got kidnapped
by a monkey."
I could never think
something that horrible.
And now I'm using sarcasm
to confess the whole thing,
so later I can say
that I already told you.
Sorry I asked.
Dad, you can't keep
this up for long.
(SARCASTICALLY)
Oh, you're so right.
I guess I should be more
concerned with Bart's safety
than covering
my own butt.
And maybe
I'm talking like this
because I can't stop!
Help me, Lisa. I have
serious mental problems.
Look, it's been fun and all,
but I miss indoor plumbing.
(GIBBERING)
(GROANING)
Sorry, lady.
I've never eaten fresh fruit,
and I reckon I never will.
(EXASPERATED GIBBERING)
(GIBBERING)
Whoa!
This Oreo is rank!
(WHISPERING)
Bart! Bart!
When the monkey
falls asleep,
I'll sneak you out
in this trash bag.
Then I'll come back
and feed the monkey
a peach full of antifreeze.
(CHITTERING)
(WEAKLY) Wee...
Wee...
(SNORING)
(MUTTERING)
Oh, I fell asleep
before the monkey!
Uh-oh.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
Looking good, Rod!
Ned! Are you
checking up on me?
I'm not Ned.
I'm a friendly dog.
Oh, I'm not a good liar.
I did come here
to check on the...
Where's Rod?
He's up there, Daddy.
Daddy, look
how high I am!
(YELPING) What are you doing?
You're gonna get hurt!
l am?
(WHIMPERING)
(SCREAMING)
Ahh!
(CONTINUES SCREAMING)
He chipped a tooth.
How will he bite
Wheat Thins? How?
I'm sorry, Ned. I never
thought this would happen.
I don't want you watching
my boys ever again!
(ALL MURMURING)
MAN: She must be
an unfit mother.
l am not
an unfit mother!
KENT: We interrupt this skateboarding
footage for a breaking news story.
Local boy Bart Simpson
is being held hostage
by an angry chimpanzee,
who has improved both his
hygiene and posture.
His so-called real mother could
not be found for comment.
(GASPING)
Hey, monkey!
Eat tranquilizer dart!
(INHALING DART)
(CHOKING)
(SPUTTERING)
KENT: Mr. Simpson was later
revived by a police stun gun.
(ELECTRICITY SIZZLING)
(SIZZLING INTENSIFIES)
(SINGING) Welcome
to the jungle gym
I'll make it safe again
When playtime
is a safe time
Everybody wins
I'll lay down
some AstroTurf
So they don't
scrape their knees
Daddy, what are
we gonna do today?
Well, we're gonna do what every
kid your age likes to do.
Look at bread.
BOTH: No!
(GASPING) The "N" word?
We want Mrs. Simpson back!
She let us run barefoot
in the grass and play Uno!
Uno? That's a gateway
game to pinochle!
All diddily aside, boys. What is
it about her you miss so much?
She made us
feel happy.
And not church happy.
For-real happy.
(GASPING)
LISA: Maybe there's
another way to solve this.
Bart is clearly fulfilling an
emotional need for Toot-Tool.
Lisa, monkeys don't
have feelings.
If they did, then my experiments
could be called cruel.
Toot-Toot, look. I'm using
this rock as a tool.
(GRUNTING) Ow!
(DISTRESSED GIBBERING)
(GASPING)
She's kissing his boo-boo!
That's it! I'm going in!
(GIBBERING)
Excuse me,
Mrs. Toot.
I need to talk to you mother-to-mother.
(INQUISITIVE GIBBERING)
While you were living the
glamorous life of a TV chimp,
I was raising my son.
You have no right to take
him away from me now.
Please, please,
give me back my boy.
(GIBBERING)
(EXCITED GIBBERING)
Marge, Toot-Toot
and her son escaped!
(SIGHING)
The Hamburglar was survived by his
longtime companion, Mayor McCheese.
Now our latest update on
monkey boy Bart Simpson.
Toot-Toot has taken Bart to
the highest spot in town.
The new steeple atop the
First Church of Springfield.
(SOBBING)
Now, Marge, I know
things look bleak.
But it should
comfort you to know
we have this plaque
ready to go.
(MARGE GASPING)
(SOBBING)
Hey, I know how
we can save Bart!
HOMER: Mr. Teeny?
He also happens to
be Toot-Tom's son.
But Krusty said Mr. Teeny
was born in Funny Town.
Nelson, Funny Town
doesn't exist.
No! I was gonna live
at Cuckoo Corners!
Hmm.
Listen, we can trade
Mr. Teeny for Bart.
We just have to find
a way to get him up there.
I'm already doing it.
(SCREAMING)
Roddy, get down!
You're gonna fall!
(WHIMPERING)
Ned, Rod needs to know you believe
he can be okay on his own.
You'd be surprised what he could
do if you just gave him a chance.
Rod, you can do it, boy.
With God on your side,
you can't fail!
Toot-Toot, I have
something for you.
(GIBBERING)
(EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING)
Yeah, great.
New I need a new sidekick.
Get me a lemur
or a marmot.
Or Tom Green. He's not
doing anything these days.
And really stick it
to him on the money.
Hurry,
let's climb down.
Okay. But don't let our hands touch.
It's gay.
What's gay mean?
Um...
It means you used to be
afraid, but now you're not.
I'm gay, Daddy!
I'm gay!
(YELLING) Mrs.
Simpson made me gay!
(HYPERVENTILATING)
I believe he's saying,
"He's okay."
My little boy
is growing up.
Hey, I'll say.
I haven't seen
climbing like that
since Dudley Moore
married Susan Anton.
(LAUGHING)
Oh, Bob, why did I wait 100
years to get you up here?
You're telling me.
Now I can look down Dolly Parton's
dress whenever I want. (GROWLING)
Guys, I'm trying
to watch this.
Hey, I'm sorry.
What got into her?
Her kid's fruitier than
Carmen Miranda's hat rack.
Remember her?
(LAUGHING)
Ripped By mstoll