The Simpsons.
It's Channel Six Action News.
Ah, Action News,
the last place
an impressionable kid
can go for TV violence.
Now, here's
your action anchor.
Kent Brockman.
Hello. I'm Kent Brockman.
Our top stories tonight:
A tremendous explosion
in the price of lumber.
"President Reagan dyes...
his hair,"
says Garry Trudeau
in his new
musical comedy revue.
But first, let's check
the death count
from the killer storm
bearing down on us
like a shotgun full of snow.
Well, Kent, as of now,
the death count is zero
but it is ready
to shoot right up.
Oh, my God.
Damn you, snow!
All right, snow day!
No school tomorrow.
That doesn't mean you don't
have to do your book report.
What if the weatherman
is wrong?
Lisa, that man is a
professional meteorologist.
Kent,
I'd like to remind
everybody to come down
and watch me
at the Springfield
Laugh 'n' Brew
and Burgers 'n' Fries
this Saturday.
The forecast calls
for a 75% chance
of hilarity.
I like those odds.
Snowball fight!
You're going to eat
a blizzard of...
unseasonable warmth?
I made the snowball
from the frost in our freezer.
Nice P.J.s, Simpson.
Did your mommy buy them for you?
Of course she did.
Who else would have?
All right, Simpson,
you win this round.
Okay, it's book report time.
We'll do them alphabetically.
Today it's
"A" through "M."
I'm saved.
I love being a S-S-S-Simpson.
Let's see, we have no A's,
so let's go right to the B's.
Bart?
Mrs. Krabappel,
I... didn't...
Attention.
This is Principal Skinner,
your principal, with a message
from the principal's office.
All students please proceed
immediately to an assembly
in the Butthead
Memorial Auditorium.
Damn it, I wish we hadn't let
the students name that one.
Children, the times they are
a-becoming quite different.
Test scores are
at an all-time low,
so I've come up
with these academic alerts.
You will receive one as soon
as your grades start to slip
in any subject.
This way, your parents
won't have to wait
until report card time
to punish you.
How innovative.
I like it.
Hey, Dolph, take a memo
on your Newton.
"Beat up Martin."
All right,
first academic alert...
Wiggum, Ralph.
I won, I won!
No, no, Ralph.
This means you're
failing English.
Me, fail English?
That's unpossible.
Muntz, Nelson.
You're failing
History, Geography
and Math, but, uh...
you're doing quite well
in Home Ec.
Hey, keep it down, man.
Simpson.
Lisa.
Grades are all I have.
What could I be failing?
I'm smart and a teacher's pet.
Gym?
That's the stupidest thing
I ever heard.
Lisa, your father and I
are very concerned
about this warning.
I really hope
you try harder.
Whoo,
that's all of them.
And I'm so proud you
didn't try to forge my name.
How about
a present, son?
Well, I could use a new pair
of hockey skates.
Done and done.
That's not fair.
Why is Bart getting a present
and I'm getting chewed out?
Ah, the mysteries
of life.
Tell you what, Simpson.
I won't fail you
if you join one
of those peewee teams
outside the school.
You mean those leagues
where parents push their kids
into vicious competition
to compensate
for their own
failed dreams of glory?
Look, I don't need this.
I inhaled my favorite whistle
this morning.
D'oh, d'oh, d'oh, d'oh
d'oh, d'oh, d'oh.
Children, that was
our only ball.
There'll be no team
this year.
Aww...
Mom, this is really scary.
I'm going to get
my first "F" ever.
Cheer up!
So you're not good at sports.
It's a very small part of life.
Sports, sports,
sports, sports.
Marge, Bart rides up
in the front seat today
because he's a good
guy at sports.
I think Lisa needs to feel
a little special tonight.
How about letting her
ride up front too?
I tried.
Okay, son,
just remember
to have fun
out there today,
and if you lose,
I'll kill you!
Oh, Dad.
All right, Pigs,
beat those Gougers.
I could have been
equipment manager, but, no!
Our goalie
cannot stand up.
Tell you what.
Get some rope.
Defense, defense, come on.
You call that blowing?
Oh, yes!
We won, we won, we won.
Unfortunately,
since I bet
on the other team,
uh, we won't be going for pizza.
Well, boy, you won.
So I'm going to live up
to my side of the agreement.
Here's your turtle,
alive and well.
Aw, thanks, Dad.
How about some adulation
from my little sister?
Wow, Bart, I'm so impressed
you were able to give Milhouse
a concussion.
Oh, you're just jealous
because... you...
stink...
at... sports.
Cut it out, Bart!
What the...
You know, I wonder if her
skills would transfer over
to the game of hockey.
Well, only one way to be sure.
Heads up, little girl.
The goalie of my dreams.
Let's try a hard one
to make sure
it wasn't a fluke.
Oh, hey!
Way to knock
out my teeth.
That's it, Milhouse.
Keep up the chatter.
Lisa,
if the Bible has taught us
nothing else...
And it hasn't...
It's that girls should
stick to girls' sports
such as hot-oil
wrestling,
foxy boxing
and such and such.
I think women should be able
to play any sport men play,
but hockey is so violent
and dangerous.
Look at Milhouse's teeth.
Mom, will you stop
showing us those?
I have to join the team,
or I'll get an "F"
that will haunt me
for the rest of my life.
I now pronounce you
president of these United...
Stop the inauguration!
I just discovered
our president-elect
got an "F"
in second grade gym class.
In that case,
I sentence you
to a lifetime of horror
on Monster Island.
Don't worry.
It's just a name.
He said...
it was just a name.
What he meant is
that Monster Island
is actually a peninsula.
Do you have my teeth?
No.
Okay, hotshots,
now that my daughter
is on your team,
I want to make
a few things clear.
Please, Dad,
I'll be fine.
I don't want anyone
to give her a hard time
just because she's different.
No jokes, no taunting.
Look, that kid's got bosoms!
Who's got a wet towel?
Come here,
you butterball.
Don't make me run!
I'm full of chocolate.
Whoa!
I can't even watch.
I don't know how
you two can sit here
laughing at poor Lisa
while she's out there
probably scared to death.
We're laughing
with her, Marge.
There's a big difference.
Whoa!
With her.
You really think I did okay
out there, Mom?
Absolutely, honey.
By blocking the net, I really
think you helped your team.
Okay, little buddy, hop in.
Hup-ah!
I mean,
my little girl buddy.
That's very nice, Dad,
but it's wrong for you
to reward violent,
competitive behavior.
However, I will
sit up front with you
if it's a fatherly
gesture of love.
Okay, honey.
Sucker!
Competitive violence...
That's why you're here!
We are having
our best season ever.
I would like to say that
it is because of teamwork.
Gee,
who am I kidding, huh?
It's all because of Lisa.
Let's hear it for Lisa.
Hey, Bart,
if Lisa's better
than you at hockey,
does that mean you're gonna
become better than her at school?
Maybe I will, Milhouse.
Maybe I will.
Who can tell me
the capital of Spain?
Bart Simpson.
The square root of 36?
Who freed the slaves?
Bart Simpson.
Bart Simpson?
Bart Simpson,
will you stop raising your hand?
You haven't had
one right answer all day.
Sorry.
This is for wasting
teacher's valuable time.
Lay off, guys!
He's with me.
It's a lucky coincidence
you happen to be
your sister's brother.
Don't worry, Bart.
They won't
bother you anymore.
I hardly ever let Mother
fight for me anymore.
Sorry, Bart.
I'm gonna hang out
with Lisa for protection...
and to be seen.
Come watch TV
with me, Dad.
We missed the first
two episodes of "Cops."
But if we hurry,
we can catch the last three.
Sorry, Bart. Lisa and I
are going out for gelato.
We'd ask you to come, but...
you know...
Bart, I can spend
some time with you.
I don't know, Mom.
Don't have a
stereotypical view of me
just because
I'm your mother.
I know, how about
we play the basketball?
I'm no Harvey
Globetrotter, but...
Watch out for
the Shaq attack!
I told you
to watch out.
Hey, Milhouse, knock him
down if he's in your way!
Jimbo, Jimbo,
go for the face!
Look. Ralph Wiggum
lost his shin guard!
Hack the bone!
Wow! Eye of the tiger.
Mouth of a Teamster.
Just think of all the time
I wasted on you!
Yeah, well, not wasted.
Uh... I love you.
Let me give my special
little winner a big, big hug.
Ma, I think
I'm all hugged out.
Oh, one more.
Hello, Queen Lisa.
Bart, what are you
doing in my room?
Lisa, certain differences...
Rivalries if you will...
Have come up between us.
At first, I thought
we could talk it over
like civilized people,
but instead, I just ripped
the head off Mr. Honeybunny.
Bart, that was your
cherished childhood toy.
Ah, Mr. Honeybunny!
Quiet down, Bart!
Bart, just
get out of here.
Hey, it's a free country.
You get out.
That doesn't make sense.
I know you are,
but what am I?
Get out! Get out!
Okay!
But on my way,
I'm going to be doing this.
If you get hit,
it's your own fault.
Okay. Then I'm gonn start
kicking air like this.
And if any part of you
should fill that air,
it's your own fault.
Hmm, I'd better go
check that out.
Now, Homer,
don't you eat this pie.
Okay.
All right, pie,
I'm just gonna do this.
And if you get eaten,
it's your own fault.
Oh... my!
The hell with it.
Stop it!
Mom, that is
really annoying.
- Bart started it.
- Nuh-uh, Lisa started it.
I don't care who started it.
I don't ever want
to see you two
fighting like that
ever again.
We love you both.
You're not in competition
with each other.
Repeat: You are not
in competition with each other.
Hey, Apu just called.
This Friday, Lisa's team
is playing Bart's team.
You're in direct
competition!
And don't go easy
on each other
just because you're
brother and sister.
I want to see
you both fighting
for your parents' love!
Fight! Fight!
All right, I'm gonna make
a little deal with you mugs.
I'm gonna let you all out to see
my team play the hockey game
if you promise
to return to your cells.
Sorry, pig.
We can't make that promise.
All right. All right,
I'll sweeten the deal.
You can see the game,
you don't have to come back,
but you have to promise not
to commit any more crimes, okay?
- No.
- I'll take that as a yes.
All right!
We're free!
At 7:00 tonight,
the games begin.
Bart versus Lisa,
who will win?
Their father's fat,
and their mother's thin.
And Grandpa Simpson
reeks of gin.
Hey...
That's obsession for men.
Pass ketchup.
You'll have to do better
than that tonight, chump.
I asked for ketchup.
I'm eating salad here.
I won't have any aggressive
condiment passing in this house.
- Hello.
- Moe, what are you doing here?
What? What, a bartender
can't come by and say hi
to his best customer?
Hey, hey ya there, Midge.
Oh, gee, I like what you
done to your hair.
You caught me
at a real bad time, Moe.
I hope you understand
I'm too tense
to pretend I like you.
And how are
the little kids doing?
I mean, really
how are they doing?
Any disabling injuries?
Something, say,
that the gambling community
might not yet know about?
Come here,
let me see those knees.
Moe, I think
you should leave.
But, Blanche, you gotta
help me out here.
Please, I'm 64 grand
in the hole.
They're going to take my thumbs!
Charge!
Good luck tonight, sis.
I'll try not
to hurt you.
Don't worry. I'm wearing
my lucky rabbit's head.
Mr. Honeybunny!
You inhumane monster!
You want a piece of me?
Kids, stop it.
Conserve your precious
hatred for the game.
Now that we're all alone,
Marge, admit it.
- You like Lisa best.
- No.
Oh, so you're a Bart
woman, are you?
No.
Well, you can't possibly like
Maggie best.
What has she ever done?
Nothing for nobody.
Homer, we can't root for
one child over the other.
You wouldn't like it if the kids
played favorites with us.
Hey, Mom,
look at me, Mom.
Hi, Mom.
Over here.
Mom.
Hi, kids.
And now, to honor America,
here's Krusty the Clown.
O, say can you see
Da-da-da-da-da light.
What so proudly we...
Da-da...
I shouldn't have turned down
those cue cards.
I love Bart!
No, wait, I love Lisa!
Beer!
Oh, Marge, I love you.
He tripped my boy!
I demand vengeance!
I want vengeance!
Jimbo Jones
called for tripping.
The penalty shot will be
taken by Bart Simpson.
Oh, my God, Marge.
A penalty shot with
only four seconds left.
It's your child
versus mine.
The winner will be
showered with praise.
The loser will be
taunted and booed
until my throat is sore.
Kill her, boy!
Kill her!
Stop him dead, little girl.
Kill, Bart.
Kill, Bart. Kill, Bart...
Kill Bart. Kill Bart.
Kill Bart...
Great game, Lis.
Great game, Bart.
- Tie game?
- What the hell?
This is outrageous.
I've never been
so proud of them.
They're both losers.
Losers!
- Rip-off!
- We paid for blood.
Let's tear this place apart.
Good idea.
Those kids are, like, so sweet.
If only they had
had peewee hockey
when I was a lad.
Oh, well...
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.