(SINGING) The Simpsons
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
D'oh!
(EXCLAIMING)
Ripped By mstoll
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Where's Reverend Lovejoy?
He's never been late
for Christmas service.
Maybe he's cheating on us
with the Episcopalians.
Look at 'em with their bright, airy
narthex and light, flaky Eucharist.
I wouldn't mind dipping
my hand in their font.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Christ is born.
Who's on my horn?
Bad news, Ned.
There's been a horrible
train wreck.
So many little plastic
Christmases ruined.
(GASPS) You want me to deliver
the Christmas sermon?
Oh, I feel like
I'm born-again again!
(GRUNTS)
Don't be nervous, Ned.
You've practiced this so
many times in the shower.
(GROANS)
Paper cut!
(SWOONING)
Now there's no one
to deliver the sermon.
Did anyone order a hero?
(HUMMING)
(CLEARS THROAT)
Okay, Christmas,
Christmas...
You know how your paperboy always
sends you a Christmas card
with his home
address on it?
What's up with that?
BOY: I wanted you
to tip me!
No tip till they bring back
Hagar the Horrible!
BOY: That's not
my decision!
Oh, it's never
anybody's decision.
Anyhoo, I'd like to tell
you all a little story
I call "The First Christmas."
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
I for one am dying
to hear it!
A carpenter named Joseph
was about to get some
frankly preposterous news.
Uh, Joseph, you know
I have never lain with a man.
(SCOFFS)
Tell me about it.
And yet, lam with child.
A pregnant virgin?
That's every man's
worst nightmare!
Hail Mary,
full of grace.
That's not all
she's full of.
Quiet, you.
Mary, you carry in your
womb the Son of God
who will grow up to
become King of the Jews!
So, not a doctor.
Well, he will be able
to heal the sick.
But nothing to
hang on the wall?
(GROANS)
(DRUMS PLAYING)
King Herod,
we three wise men come
bearing gifts for
the King of the Jews.
We bring gold.
Frankincense.
And myrrh, which I am re-gifting,
'cause who needs myrrh?
Here's the tag.
Thank you.
Which one should
I open first?
BOTH: Hmm...
(LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
This is awkward.
(SNIFFLES)
Uh, the King of the Jews
we seek is a newborn child.
Find this pretender
to my throne
and bring him
to me!
Uh, now you wouldn't
hurt the little boychik?
Of course not.
Kings don't hurt babies.
Giant pointy swords
hurt babies!
Oh, Hoyven
good King Herod,
except you don't really
have the "good,"
so what do you
have really then?
Don't you worry. I got
plenty of rooms in my inn,
all with brand new
carpeting.
I think my water
just broke!
You can have the barn.
Ah, now feel free to come by
the main house for breakfast,
there won't be any.
(MARGE BREATHING HEAVILY)
(MOOING)
Just keep pushing, sweetie.
The doctor will
be here any second.
Shalom, everybody!
(MOOING AND BLEATING)
I've got some
very good news.
Caesar just invented
the caesarian!
Get him outta here!
I knew I'd like him, but I
never dreamed I'd adore him.
I've got the Messiah's nose!
Give it back! Give it back!
He'll kill us all!
(CHUCKLES)
He looks just like his dad.
Not you!
Oh, I'm not the father. I'm not a wise man.
I'm nothing!
This is the worst
Christmas ever!
Hmm? Maybe a little toot off the
old wineskin will cheer me up.
Uh!
My wine
turned into water!
Who could've performed
such a cruel miracle?
(CHUCKLES)
Why you little...
(THUNDER CRASHING)
Joseph, no!
He has to stay alive
till he's 33,
when he'll be renounced by
his friends and crucified!
Huh?
Sorry, kid.
(WAILING)
(SIGHS) Anytime anyone suffers in
the world, he starts crying again.
Can you do something?
Me? But I'm watching
the orange bowl.
Now!
(WAILING)
Oh!
(LAUGHING)
(BLEATING)
D'oh!
(LAUGHING)
Hmm, you like
physical comedy, eh?
Nyuck, nyuck, nyuck.
Ah, wise man. eh?
Pick two.
(GROANING)
(CHUCKLES)
Why I ought to...
Mmm, mmm, mmm...
Now hold still.
Gnah, gnah, gnah.
(CHUCKLES)
(YAWNS)
(COOING)
Ohh...
I think this non-traditional
household just might make it.
Mmm...
Jesus, Mary, and Joseph,
we got a great family.
Now let's get some sleep.
Herod is coming
for the child!
Manger danger!
(ALL GRUNTING)
The kid you're looking
for is in there!
The other tenants
have been complaining
about the incessant swaddling,
all hours, day and night.
Gee, Chief, l feel pretty bad
trying to take out a baby.
Ah, don't worry, boys.
No one will ever speak
or write of this again.
What a boffo beginning
for my book!
(ALL GRUNTING)
There they go!
I see his head-dealie!
Follow that glow!
(ALL SHOUTING)
(QUACKS)
They put his halo on a duck.
The oldest trick
in the book.
What the hell
are you doing?
Well, he does have a halo.
Hail, Quackie!
(QUACKS)
(TREMBLING)
That ought to
spruce things up.
(ALL SCREAMING)
(QUACKING)
(BOTH GASP)
What a beautiful
Hanukkah bush!
I say we call it
a Christmas tree.
ALL: Aww!
A Christmas tree,
what a great name.
Makes you feel
all warm and fuzzy.
(GROANING)
And did you know
that little baby Jesus
grew up to be Jesus?
(ALL GASP)
I know! It's weird,
isn't it?
(CAROL PLAYING ON TV)
ANNOUNCER: Coming up next, The
Energizer Bunny Christmas Special.
Oh, I don't know why
I'm so run down.
I must be low
on Christmas spirit.
It's because you're
using regular batteries.
You forgot about
Energizer Ultra.
Now let me crawl
inside you.
(GASPS) Cold! So cold!
(CLATTER)
(GASPS) It's Santa!
(GRUNTS) Ooh!
Grampa?
What are you doing
in the chimney?
Trying to kill Santa.
What's it to ya?
What do you have
against Santa?
He screwed me
over back in WWII.
I was a Navy pilot
in the Pacific.
Oh, Bart, Why'd you ask him
a follow-up question?
(WHISPERS)
lt just slipped out!
Yup. I was a Navy pilot
in the Pacific
along with
my big brother, Cyrus.
Cyrus? You never
mentioned him before.
And I'll never
mention him again.
But I loved him
all the same.
Okay, Abe,
let's win this war quick
so we can go home and slowly
give black folks more rights.
(SIREN BLARING)
Kamikazes at two o'clock!
Well, I don't usually
drink after lunch but...
Oh, my God!
The sky is full of that kind of
plane that crashes into the boat!
Cyrus, you be
careful up there.
No, I'm not worried. Not as long
as I have my good luck charm.
(AMERICAN PATROL PLAYING)
Good thing I stole two of
these off dead soldiers.
Lieutenant, radio my brother and
tell him to watch his tail.
Quiet, you.
I'm talking to my best gal.
I miss you, too, Bernadette.
You hang up first.
No, you hang up first.
(LAUGHING) No.
You hang up first.
(GROANS)
Cyrus!
(WHIRRING)
You'll pay for that,
you haiku-spouting savages!
(ABE GRUNTING)
I wish I tried reefer!
Mmm.
(GRUNTS)
(STRAINED GRUNTING)
Mmm.
Quit lollygagging
and build a fire.
I don't have
to listen to you.
On this island,
military rank means nothing.
We're in a state of nature where the
strong of will control the weak.
(GURGLING)
(SPITS)
How dare you drown the king
of New Burns Island?
(GURGLING)
(SPITS)
How'd you like to be the
Archduke in charge of coconuts?
(GURGLING)
I give up. I give up.
ABE: Days turned to weeks.
Weeks turned to months.
Months turned back to days.
Even Burns was starting
to look good to me.
Hey, sailor.
My eyes are up here.
ABE: By Christmas Eve, our
hopes of rescue were fading.
You know, Simpson,
we've had our dust-ups.
So I've made you
a little peace offering.
ABE: A shaving kit?
Is this pomade?
Oh, it's nothing really. Just
seagull brains and snail goo.
Thanks, Lieutenant.
Merry Christmas.
Incoming!
Is it one of ours?
Who cares? lt's Christmas.
I want to shoot something.
(EXPLOSION)
What in the name of the
Tennessee Valley Authority?
Donder! Blitzen!
He's German!
That's good eatin'!
You useless waste of socks!
That ain't no Kraut!
We just shot down
Santie Claus!
Oh! Thank you, boys.
I guess I must've run
into a sudden storm.
Yes, yes.
Everything happens to you.
My sleigh!
It's ruined!
Well, we'll get you
up and running
or my name ain't
Young Grampa Simpson!
(PEPPY MUSIC PLAYING)
Boys, I'm almost ready.
I'm just missing Prancer.
And Rudolph.
(HISSING)
And now to bring joy to boys
and girls around the world!
Ho-ho...
(GROANS) Ow!
Damn it!
Sorry, Chuckles.
Change of plan.
This sleigh is my ticket
off this hellhole.
And I'm keeping
all the toys for myself,
because at heart, I'm just a very
wicked child. (BELLS JINGLING)
(URGES REINDEER)
You backstabber!
And I let you spoon me!
Let's go, you flying hat rack!
(GRUNTS)
Hmm?
(WHIRRING)
Come on, baby.
(STRAINED GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
(SQUEAKING)
Somebody should've beat you
with a tricycle years ago!
(GRUNTS)
Thanks for
everything, Abe.
And now I'm off.
I'll be back in a few days
to take you ho-ho-home!
Well, that's the craziest
thing I'll ever see.
Gah! Except for that!
I waited and waited.
But Santa never came back.
If I hadn't invented a jet ski
made of coconuts,
I'd have never
gotten home.
And then when I did,
the war was over
and the nurses
were all kissed out.
That's quite a tale, Grampa.
(STAMMERING)
You little...
It's true, I tells ya!
(BELLS JINGLING)
(THUD)
It's Santa!
I got an old
score to settle!
Doggone it!
I missed him again!
(AMERICAN PATROL PLAYING)
My brother's lucky watch!
Santa must've left it!
Cyrus, I miss you every day.
SANTA CLAUS:
He misses you, too.
(STUTTERING)
He... What... Who?
Your brother didn't
die in the war, Abe.
He crashed into Tahiti. And he
liked it so much, he never left.
And now, if you like,
I'll take you to him.
Will we be back for the
Tournament of Roses Parade?
Probably not.
Good. I hate that crap.
SANTA CLAUS:
Yeah. Me, too.
Santa, one thing's
still buggin' me.
Why didn't you ever
come back to pick me up?
I kept putting it off. And then
l was just too embarrassed.
Sorry I never called, Abe.
I was too busy
with my 15 native wives.
(WIVES GIGGLING)
Fifteen! Whoo!
That sounds like a lot of sex.
I said wives,
not girlfriends.
(WIVES GIGGLING)
WIVES:
No poko-miku for Cyrus!
(MUSIC PLAYING)
Oh, my God!
It's over. We're free!
It's not over!
It's just intermission!
I said we're free!
We're still doing Act Two!
I'll be in the audience.
Boo! This is terrible!
Ugh, I hope I never hear that
God-awful Nutcracker music again.
I don't know, Dad. This time
of year, everybody does it
because you don't have to
pay for the music rights.
Really?
I've still gotta bake
my Christmas pie
We gotta get Dad
a lousy tie
Christmas crowds
is what I hate
No time left
to procrastinate
So move your ass
And let me pass
Because Christmas
Eve is here!
BOTH: Ow!
Eh, why is this Santa suit
so snug?
Grr. Why should I care?
it's all humbug
We jacked my prices
up so high
But there's no junk
these saps won't buy
Last year's eggnog,
a green hot dog
Because Christmas Eve
is here
These holiday cookies
swell my fat
(BABBLING)
Cat
Even though
we're not Gentile
We'll get together
for a while
To shoot the breeze
And eat Chinese
Because Christmas
Eve is here! Oye!
Christmas is a family day
I told Grampa we'd be away
He's at the door
Let's hit the floor
(WHISPERING) Because
Christmas Eve is here
Fine! I'll spend Christmas Eve
with the raccoons.
(GRUNTING)
(CHITTERING)
You got me a gift?
Rancid lard?
Aw, you shouldn't have.
Every year at this time, I show what's
probably my most-requested clip!
Roll it, Freddy.
(SINGING) It's the most
wonderful time of the year
(GROANING)
Ow! Ow! Oh...
“Give the audience snowballs,“
they said.
"It'll be cute," they said.
Oh...
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(CHUCKLES)
Okay. Time for my annual holiday
tradition, attempting to kill myself.
(SOBBING)
(GRUNTS)
MAN: Hey, watch it!
(HORN HONKS)
(SIGHS)
What's it say?
Hey, Barn, as a special gift to
me this year, will you kill me?
But I already
got you a wool hat!
Maybe next year, huh?
Merry Christmas, Homie.
I think you're really
gonna like this.
(CHUCKLING)
Oh, that's great.
Now, I'll just get
my present for you.
Which is right
outside the door.
Oh, my God! I forgot to
get Marge a present!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(SINGING) I need a present for my
wife or I'll have no sex for life
Diamond ring, a vase by Ming some
kind of useful kitchen thing
I need a store I can break
into or a place run by a Hindu
(BELL DINGS)
The Christmas rush
has cleaned me out
I just have jerky
made of trout
Uh!
I knew you'd forget.
So, my gift to you is a
gift for you to give me.
Oh, it's just what
I wanted!
Here, Marge.
This is for you.
Aw...
(MOANING)
(HORN HONKING)
MOE: Oh! Eighteen wheels
and they all missed me!
Ripped By mstoll