(SINGING) The Simpsons
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
D'oh!
(EXCLAIMING)
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
ALL: Surprise!
(SCREAMING)
Ripped By mstoll
(INAUDIBLE)
Dad, taking the family
to opening night
is the nicest thing
you've ever done for us.
Or will ever do.
I can't wait to see
this re-imagining
of Itchy and Scratchy
by avant-garde director
Juliana Krellner.
Hey, it says here the book
was written by Tom Stoppard.
This isn't a book,
it's a play.
(LAUGHING)
BOOK.
(TRIBAL CHANTS)
All hail the king
of the cats.
(CHANTING CONTINUES)
(GASPS) They're coming
down the aisles.
What if they want
to interact with me?
Looking through my purse,
looking through my purse...
Keep walking, monkey.
Don't worry, Mom,
they all passed by.
(SIGHS)
(GIBBERING)
(CHUCKLING)
(SINGING) Itchy, Scratchy,
Itchy, Itchy, Scratchy
Itchy, Scratchy,
From the day you
are born in the alley
To the day
you are hit by a car
Itchy, Scratchy,
Itchy, Itchy, Scratchy
There's cream to drink
And mice to eat
And great big balls of yam
Itchy, Scratchy,
Itchy, Itchy, Scratchy
It's the circle...
The circle of...
Knife!
(LAUGHING)
(GROANING)
I love the use of
streamers as blood.
It robs the violence
of its power.
Whoo-hoo!
I'm drenched in blood!
(MUSIC PLAYING)
I don't know why I trust him
I guess some cats
just never learn
I feel so good
When I have crushed him
(SOBBING)
Or left him mangled,
maimed and burned
BOTH:
I suppose it's symbiotic
And perhaps a bit erotic
'Cause pain is
my narcotic
You really liked it?
Yes, I loved it.
And that's why
we're always...
Fighting and biting
And dynamite igniting
(EXPLOSION)
Check it out!
I'm Scratcher
or something!
(SINGING) It's the circle...
The circle of knife
Yes, the circle...
The circle of knives
(APPLAUSE)
MAN: Bravo!
WOMAN: Genius!
Necessary!
I insist on seeing
the director.
Thank you,
thank you.
It's such a thrill
for me to be back
in my hometown,
Springfield.
She also graduated from
Springfield Elementary.
(GASPS)
Principal Skinner!
(CHUCKLES)
You know, Juliana,
it's no surprise you
became such a success.
You always got
straight A's in school.
Well, I remember getting
a "B" or two in math.
(CHUCKLES)
Well, of course
you did.
You are a girl.
(ALL GASP)
No. All... All I meant
was, from what I've seen,
boys are better
at math, science.
The real subjects.
There, that should
put the matter behind us.
(ALL GASP)
Calm down,
calm down.
I'm sure principal Skinner didn't
mean girls are inherently inferior.
No, of course not. I don't
know why girls are worse.
Uh, one thing we can
all agree on, though,
this little lady sure
looks pretty tonight.
Am I right?
(CROWD JEERING)
(GRUNTING)
(CROWD BOOING)
(CHANTING)
Two, four, six, eight
Step the man
from teaching hate
Eight, six, four, two
We do math as good as you
One, two...
Skinner! You've got to
deal with these kooks.
Don't worry,
I have a plan.
Pretend I agree
with them.
Well, you'd better hurry. Look
what they've done to your car.
No, that's how
it always looks.
Oh, how sad.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Today, we celebrate
the first of many,
many, many,
many diversity forums.
Why is it that women “appear“
to be worse at math than men?
What is the source
of this “illusion?
Or as I call it,
the biggest lie ever told?
You're a worse
version of Hitler!
Please believe me,
I...
I understand the
problems of women.
See?
(ALL GASP)
Ha-ha! The principal's
a tranny.
Am I wearing
women's clothes?
I didn't notice.
When I look in my closet, I don't
see male clothes or female clothes.
They're all the same.
Are you saying that men
and women are identical?
Oh, no, of course not! Women
are unique in every way.
Now he's saying women
and men aren't equal.
No, no, no.
It's the differences,
of which there are none,
that make the
sameness exceptional.
Just tell me what to say.
(HYPERVENTILATING)
Oh, dear.
Um, attention, students.
Due to nervous exhaustion and
diarrhea of the mouth...
(ALL LAUGHING)
Yes, yes, yes,
I said "diarrhea."
Principal Skinner
is going to be replaced
by women's educational
expert, Melanie Upfoot.
Children, meet your
new principal.
(ALL GASP)
For too long,
there's been an
anti-woman bias in math.
Boys are aggressive,
obnoxious,
and never let us
be heard.
From now on, I am splitting
the school in two,
separating the boys
and the girls forever.
(ALL GASP)
You heard
your principal.
Girls on the left,
boys on the right.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
This rocks!
No more stupid girl classes,
like ballroom dancing.
Oh, no, that's still
mandatory for everybody.
Willie?
(MUSIC PLAYING)
Now, this is why
I got into education.
They're going to divide
the school in two?
Yeah, one for boys
and one for girls.
It is going
to be awesome!
Now I can walk down the hall with Bart Jr.
hanging out.
Isn't that right,
Bart Jr.?
(CROAKING)
All this hoo-haw about
girls and math is silly.
Women are as smart
as men.
Why, a woman invented
Liquid Paper.
Well, do you know
what a man invented?
Actual paper.
Well, a woman also invented
the windshield wiper.
Which goes great with another
male invention, the car.
Um...
(STAMMERING) I think a woman
came up with nylon stockings.
I mean, probably.
We certainly use them.
Let's see, men also
have rocket ships,
suspension bridges,
constitutional government,
snow shoes,
brass knuckles...
(GROWLING)
...pinball machines,
the Renaissance...
Oh, why did women invent
sleeping on the couch?
(BRAKES SCREECH)
Girls' entrance.
Have an empowering day, my
pony-loving leaders of tomorrow.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
All right, I'm going to open
this cage, but no biting!
You're not the boss
of my teeth!
(GASPS)
It's so beautiful!
Ooh! Paintings
by female artists!
(GASPS) Frida Kahlo,
Georgia O'Keefe...
(GASPS)
Cathy Guisewite!
Now that the boys and their
atmosphere of intimidation are gone,
we can finally breathe.
Breathe, ladies.
(ALL BREATHE DEEPLY)
Now, let's buckle down
and do some math.
Yes!
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
How do numbers
make you feel?
What does a plus
sign smell like?
Is the number seven odd,
or just different?
Are we going to do any
actual math problems?
"Problems"?
(SCOFFS)
That's how men
see math,
something to be attacked,
to be "figured out."
But, isn't it?
I mean, confidence building
cant replace real learning.
Uh-oh, Lisa.
Sounds like you're trying to
derail our self-esteem engine.
Let's sing it
back on the tracks!
(SINGING) The best thing
I can ever be
ls to be okay with me
ALL: Me!
(QUACKING)
Okay, boys' school,
I need a challenge.
(GROWLING)
A mental challenge.
(LOW GROWL)
Ugh!
Now, boys,
who can tell me
the volume of this snowman?
Anyone?
Just add the volume
of the spheres.
We know the radii.
He forgot the volume
of the carrot nose,
one-third base
times height.
Oh, math,
I have missed you!
SEYMOUR:
No girls allowed!
Principal Skinner?
It's Groundskeeper
Skinner now.
Assistant Groundskeeper,
you puke!
Assistant
Groundskeeper Skinner,
don't you think
it's wrong
that I can't get the best math
education because I'm a girl?
(SIGHS) I don't have
any opinions anymore.
All I know is that no one
is better than anyone else,
and everyone is
the best at everything.
Not you.
You're the worst!
Now get poisoning
those squirrels.
(CHEEPING)
(EXCLAIMING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Please, be reasonable.
(STAMMERING)
I'm sure we can...
(GAGGING)
Mom, the girls' school
is a joke,
and I'm not allowed
to take the boys' math.
When I was in school,
I loved math. until...
Hey, Professor
Von Hubba-hubba!
Want to hop in my dune bug
and erode some beach?
Oh, I'd love to, but I've got
my Calculus final tomorrow.
Come on, baby.
The only math you need is
you plus me equals forever.
Oh, Homie!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Since then, I haven't been
able lo do any of the calculus
I've encountered
in my daily life,
but that's not going
to happen to you.
Well, what can I do? They won't
let me in the boys' school.
Yes, unless...
There. You're the
perfect little he-she.
Mom, I don't think
this will fool anybody.
Hey, who's the rude dude
with the attitude?
He's one of Bart's friends.
Mmm-hmm.
You seem cool.
Want to catch a movie?
You never take our kids
to the movies.
Let's not fight in front
of my cool new friend.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Ow!
What are you playing?
Punch for a punch.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
BOTH: Ow!
So, what's your name,
newbie?
I'm, uh... Jake.
That's your Christian name.
What's your surname?
Uh... Boy-man...
Boyman.
Jake Boyman.
You have toilet paper
on your shoe.
(CHUCKLES EMBARRASSEDLY)
Yeah, I guess I do.
I'm going to
call you Toilet.
My name isn't Toilet.
It's Jake.
Hey, a talking toilet!
(LAUGHING)
ALL: (CHANTING)
Toilet! Toilet!
Class, settle down. We
have a new student today.
His name
is Jake Boyman.
He likes the Hardy Boys,
boy scouts,
boy bands, Chef Boyardee,
and he is a boy.
What are you drawing?
A robot with guns
for arms shooting
a plane made out of guns
that fires guns.
LISA: Mmm.
MISTER PEIRCE: Everyone take
out your math books, come on.
Now, how many different
numbers can Y be?
That's easy, just one.
The number five.
Wrong.
(GASPS) There are two
possible solutions,
five and negative five.
LISA: Oh, my God,
I was wrong!
And by being corrected,
I learned!
And no one cared about my feelings!
(CHUCKLES)
Psst! I drew a picture of
you being shot by a gun.
Ha-ha!
Mmm.
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
Hey, Toilet.
(LAUGHING)
Just kidding, bro.
They used to razz me
when I was new here.
It'll pass.
Hey, Mildew. Do you
like tongue twisters?
Boy, do I!
(GROANS)
I'm sorry.
Do you want
a jawbreaker?
Boy, do I!
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
So do you miss having
the girls around?
No.
Girls never really got me.
Did you know
Lisa Simpson?
I heard
she was pretty cool.
Lisa?
Oh, yeah,
we totally had a thing,
but I had
to break it off.
What the hell are
you talking about?
She got too clingy.
Milhouse doesn't do clingy.
I have to go.
That was my eating food!
(WHIMPERS)
ALL: (CHANTING)
Fight! Fight! Fight!
LISA: Okay, I can talk
my way out of this.
Nelson, you're not
really angry at me.
You're full of rage 'cause
your father abandoned you.
(GRUNTING) And
because you're poor,
so you don't feel like
you're good enough.
You just want somebody
to say, "I love you."
I love you.
I love you, too, Nelson.
I love you, Jimbo.
Hey, every joke has
a kernel of truth!
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
Eep!
(LAUGHING)
Hey, Lis, you missed it.
While you were
at girls' school,
Nelson totally whaled
on this dork.
(LAUGHING)
(LISA SOBBING)
Oh, my God.
That's right.
I'm Toilet.
(LAUGHING)
Toilet.
So, did you tell Mom
you got beat up?
Not yet.
If I do, she'll never let me go
to the boys' math class again.
Hey, no one with a choice
should ever have to be a girl.
I'll teach you
how to be a boy.
You'd do that for me?
That is so sweet.
You're a boy,
nothing is sweet.
Ow!
That hurt.
Sweet.
BART: Now,
when you eat like a boy,
only two french fries in five
should make it into your mouth.
(CHOMPING)
lf they fall on the floor,
you want 'em more.
Because then they come
with extra toppings.
(GAGS)
I'm gonna be sick.
Awesome!
Do it in that guy's bag
while he's not looking.
I am looking,
and don't start a puke war
that you cannot finish.
Good night.
So, do you want to
Wang Chung tonight?
I don't know.
I'm still frowny
with you.
Do you really think women
are mentally inferior?
Well, uh, honey, you're
just as smart as a man.
Sometimes when
I'm with you,
I feel like I'm doing it
with a dude.
(growls)
Oh.
Well, I won't be lonely.
I can always cuddle
with the dog.
Mmm.
At least everyone knows
I'm smarter than you.
Oh, how did this happen?
Ah, now I've been every
ball on the playground!
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
(ALL LAUGHING)
Now, for your final test.
To fully become a man,
you must pick a fight
with someone
weaker than you.
LISA: A fight?
That would mean rejecting the
last part of me that's aim a girl.
Do it, Lisa!
You'll be greater than
or equal to boys.
Even though
you're only eight,
your possibilities
are infinite.
Twenty-seven!
LISA: Okay, I'll do it.
But whom should I beat up?
These dots are itchy.
(SIGHS) Fine,
I'll beat up Ralph.
Uh, give me
your lunch money.
Okay!
Um... Uh...
I guess I'm gonna have
to get this party started.
(GRUNTING)
Fight! Fight! Fight!
Forgive me for this.
Okay!
(GRUNTS)
(SOBBING)
You just beat up the most
harmless kid in school.
Well done!
(INDISTINCT PRAISE)
Hey, Toilet, want to play guns?
Sure!
(IMITATING FIRING)
Pyew! Pyew!
(SINGING) I know
what boys like
I know what guys want
I know what boys like
I know what's on their minds
Sucker
And the award for
outstanding achievement
in the field of
mathematics goes to...
Jake Boyman!
ALL: (CHANTING)
Toilet! Toilet! Toilet!
Toilet! Toilet!
Thank you. Or should
I say thank you!
(ALL GASP)
Toilet is Lisa?
We've been Yentl'd!
That's right,
everyone.
The best math student
in the whole school is a girl!
Wait a minute!
Do you know why
you did good at math?
"Did well."
Give it a rest, Melanie.
Calling me by my first
name is harassment.
Well, in for a penny,
in for a pound.
(MOANING)
Oh, Superintendent!
The only reason Lisa won is because
she learned to think like a boy!
I turned her into a burping,
farting, bullying, math machine!
That's a lie!
Ow!
I got hit by boy Lisa
and girl Lisa!
Mmm...
(GASPS)
What have I become?
I always thought
that boys had it easier.
But now I see their world
is more cruel
and sadistic than
lever imagined.
(BOYS CHEERING)
Chair fight!
(ALL GRUNTING)
And I did get
better at math,
but it was only by abandoning
everything I believed in.
I guess the real reason we don't see
many women in math and science is...
Would you
hurry it up, please?
You're cutting into the
award for best flutist!
Well, whatever
the answer is,
I'm glad I'm a girl, and
I'm glad I'm good at math.
Now enjoy
your stupid flutist.
(PLAYING FLUTE)
(SINGING) And the sandcastle
virtues Are all swept away
In the tidal destruction
the moral melee
(GROANS)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
The elastic retreat
rings the close of play
As the last wave uncovers
the newfangled way
But your new shoes
are worn at the heels
And your suntan
does rapidly peel
And your wise men
don't know how it feels
To be thick as a brick
Ripped By mstoll