(SINGING) The Simpsons
(TIRES SCREECHING)
D'oh!
(EXCLAMING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Ripped By mstoll
(DINGS)
Ha-ha!
And now let us bow our
heads in silent prayer.
Maggie! That's not what
you do with a hymnal.
Homer!
What? I forgot to
floss this morning.
Oh, somethings wrong
with Maggie.
We should get her
to Dr. Hibbert.
But I don't see
him anywhere.
The Hibberts now attend a more boisterous
house of worship. (CLEARS THROAT)
(LIVELY GOSPEL MUSIC PLAYING)
(SINGING) Let the light
ALL: Shine on!
From the lighthouse
Shine on me
ALL: Shine on
In the morning
This is awesome.
Black God rules.
Shine on
Oh, let it shine on
(CHUCKLES)
Um, Dr. Hibbert?
Mmm-hmm?
I hate to interrupt while you're
rejoicing but Maggie is terribly itchy.
Mmm-hmm!
Oh, this looks to be the
initial stages of chicken pox.
Say amen!
Amen!
Coat Maggie with this calamine
lotion and the scabbing will heal.
The scabbing will heal!
ALL: The scabbing will heal!
Heal my scabs, Lord.
Praise the Lord!
I can walk again!
Hmm...
What? My foot
fell asleep.
(SCOFFS) Sweetie,
I know it itches.
But you've got to
stop scratching.
No!
(GASPS) No!
Here. Here,
play with your teddy bear.
(GROANS) Sugar booger.
Aww, poor Maggie.
(GASPS) Homer, don't touch her.
You've never had chicken pox.
I know. And you did.
And you're great.
Oh, I'm just saying it's very
dangerous if you get it as an adult.
It can leave you sterile.
Down there.
(SCOFFS) You always gotta
work blue, don't you, Marge?
You're better than that.
Can't even go in
my own kitchen.
Bet Bart's in there right now
licking frosting off my eggbeaters!
Mmm. Don't worry, Dad.
I'm saving one for you.
(LAUGHS) I'll just leave it
here in the dog's mouth.
No!
Bart!
That's a really
bad storage area.
Hey, Homer.
Why the sour puss?
Did you chug-a-lug
a skunky Snapple?
I don't know. Maybe.
Plus, my wife
won't let me inside
because the baby's
got chicken pox.
Really?
Do you mind if I
bring my boys over
so she can
infect Rod and Todd?
Then there'll be
a pox on both our houses.
Why would you do that?
Are you a bad parent?
Au contraire,
man with no hair.
You see, Rod and Todd could
only get the chicken pox once,
and childhood's
the safest time.
So you want Maggie
to infect your kids?
You betcha!
In fact, some parents have been
known to hold "pox parties"
so other kids in
the neighborhood
can get the disease
when they please.
And would they pay handsomely
for the privilege?
They might.
You'd have to be
awfully money-grubbing
to charge your
friends and neighbors.
$15 to infect your kids!
Now featuring the pox box!
Pox box not recommended
for pregnant or nursing women.
As with any disease box,
results may vary.
Pox box!
Welcome to our pox party.
Save room for punch.
Maggie's bathing in the bowl.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
Hi.
Luann'll pick up Milhouse
when the party's over.
I'll just read in
the car till then.
Oh, Kirk. Come join
the parents in the kitchen.
We're having alcohol drinks and dishing
on the parents who aren't here.
Ordinarily, I'm not the one to
laugh at a man's urinary blockage
but you should've seen...
Oh! There he is.
Ladies and gentlemen,
presenting the sister with the
blisters, the tot with all the spots,
Maggie!
(COUGHING)
I feel like
a chicken already.
I just made
an egg in my pants.
Hey, Marge.
Hit me with a little hit
more of that silly slush.
Chief, don't you
think you've had enough?
I'm fine. Watch, I can even
touch my gun to my nose.
(BOTH GASPING)
Don't worry.
I'm the "pief of cholice."
I mean,
I'm the beef with no cheese.
(SOBS) Why doesn't
Lou like me? Why?
Knock-knock.
Luann? What are
you doing here?
I thought you were just
dropping Milhouse off.
I could get some
coffee and come back.
No, no, no. You stay.
I'll just drive home.
Uh, who's gonna
let me siphon?
Why don't you both stay and
have one of my Marge-aritas?
All right!
I never drank one of these
without a cigarette in it.
Now kids, in lieu of one of those
inflatable jumping things,
please welcome
Mr. Krusty the Clown!
(ALL CHEERING)
Hey, hey, kids!
(LAUGHS)
This putz only paid for 20
seconds so listen fast.
Moishe caught
the chicken pox,
he scratched
all night and day.
He asked the rabbi what to
do and he said... (BEEPS)
Time! I'm outta here!
(LAUGHS)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Kirk, you look good.
Have you been working out?
Well, dogs have
been chasing me.
No one's been
chasing me lately.
What happened to
your last boyfriend?
The one who would always go to
the gym after visiting you,
then have lunch at
that place downtown?
You know,
his taillight's broken?
I'm not seeing
him anymore.
Does that mean that there
might be a chance for me?
Almost anyone's
got a chance now.
(ALL COUGHING)
Goodbye.
Thanks for coming.
If my party made you sick,
tell your friends.
(MOANING)
Sweet Lizzie McGuire!
You think that's traumatic?
Mr. Stomach, are you hungry?
"I'm always hungry, now make
with the pizza, fatso."
(LAUGHS)
You're the stomach.
I have to do this for work.
So Milhouse walks
into the bedroom
and there's his morn and dad going...
(MIMICKING MOANS)
(IN HIGH PITCHED VOICE) "Oh, Mr. Van
Houten, I love when you kiss me."
(IN LOW VOICE) "Yeah, yeah,
kissing ladies is the best."
(IN HIGH PITCHED VOICE)
"Oh, baby, kiss my mouth."
(IN LOW VOICE) "Kiss me
like we're in a fancy hotel."
All right, we get ii.
(WHIMPERING)
Marge, what's happening to me?
Oh, Homie, you got chicken pox.
But how?
I don't know. I kept away
from Maggie all day.
Uh!
I'm so itchy!
(CHOKING)
Oh! Oh, yeah.
Son, we want
to talk to you
about what you saw in
the Simpsons' house.
Well, I didn't see anything to get my
hopes up, if that's what you mean.
Well, maybe you should
get your hopes up a little.
They're already up!
They're sky high!
Your father and I
are going through
what's called
a trial un-separation.
And son, l want to
make one thing clear.
Unlike the breakup,
this is not your fault.
I can't believe it! Our family
might get back together again!
(SINGING) Our house is a very,
very, very fine house
With two cats in the yard
Life used to be so hard
Now everything
is easy 'cause of you
And our la, la, la
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(SIGHS)
I haven't daydreamed
in color in so long.
Thank God. We were
afraid we lost you, son.
You sit in this
oatmeal awhile
and it'll send
your itchies packin'.
Homer!
Mmm!
Homer oats.
Stop eating the oatmeal. That's
the third tub you've eaten.
(PHONE RINGING)
Y'ello? No. I'm not coming in to work.
I have chicken pox.
I know I said that last
month, but I was lying.
Jeez.
Right. Right.
Right. Right! Okay.
Right. I love you. Bye.
I just got fired.
Better check the want ads.
Ooh! Truck driver
needed in Iraq.
Trucks are like big cars.
(GROANS)
Okay, Luann,
for honesty's sake,
we should
probably talk about
everyone we dated
while we were separated.
Well, the Sea Captain
and I...
Yeah, okay.
I don't want to know.
So what are we gonna do
as a family today?
Mini golf, pedal boats,
indoor rock wall?
Um, Milly...
Botanical garden,
build a bear workshop,
arena football with
the Springfield Stun?
Not today, big guy.
Your dad and I need more
time to get reacquainted.
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
Why are you laughing?
Tell me!
Private jokes are rude.
Uh, son, here's 10 bucks.
Why don't you go to the bowling
alley and throw some solo balls?
But it's league night.
(G ROANS) This trial
un-separation stinks!
My parents used to compete for my
love and I'd cash in every time.
And I always
got the spillover.
Drive-in movies, two
Christmases, soda with dinner.
(SIGHS)
We lived like kings.
Remember when you told
my dad to go to bed
and he did?
That was some New Year's.
Now listen. I think
we should consider
breaking your
parents up again.
I don't know, Bart. I've wanted
them back together for so long.
Look, you know they're
gonna separate again.
Why don't we just
speed up the process?
You know, Bart.
My imaginary friend never made me
do things I thought were wrong.
That's why he had
to go away forever.
I thought you were gonna
let him come back!
I'm afraid he has to spend another
year searching for his brain.
(GROANS)
(STRAINING)
Luann! I'm moving
my stuff back in!
Uh...
Dad, Mom says
you're stinky and gross!
Your mother said that?
This is so great.
I mean, she used to keep her
criticisms all bottled up
until they destroyed
our marriage.
And I guess I am
a little funky.
Well, this is what
cologne samples are for.
(HUMMING)
(SIGHS)
Mom, I don't want to
get Dad in trouble,
but he just let me
drink a beer!
Hmm, looks like we
have a problem here.
The problem being that
you are addicted to fibbing.
lam drunk! I'll prove it! Watch
me kiss this picture of Nana!
I can't do it!
She's so mean to me!
She wouldn't let me
eat Froot Loops!
Maybe my mom and dad are
meant to be together, Bart.
You'd better hope not, 'cause
you know what comes next?
Your worst nightmare.
A baby sister.
Hi, Bart.
I baked you some cookies.
Skanks for nothing,
Lame-orella.
If you two don't mind,
I'd like to watch
that cool Fox show
about teenagers
in Orange County.
(HIP HOP MUSIC PLAYING)
Austin, I was
looking for my belly ring
in your recording
studio and I found this!
Does this or does this not
belong to Feather?
Sorry, Jade. That's how
we light it up in the OC.
You cheated on me! Our
mixed-race fling is so over!
Whatever.
Let's score some jam
at Knott's Berry Farm.
For sure, dawg.
We'll be kickin' it
old-school at Bigfoot Rapids.
Gonna get my
flume on, log-style!
(SINGING) We've been on the
run Driving in the sun
Looking out for number one
California here we come
Right back
where we started from
Hustlers grab your guns
Your shadow weighs a ton
Driving down the 101
California here we come
Right back
where we started from
California!
I bet that bra was planted by
Sterling to break them up.
That's a brilliant idea!
Those TV writers are geniuses!
Whatever they' re paid,
it's not enough.
This bra is really
gonna lift and separate.
Lift your mother's suspicions
and separate your parents.
LUANN: Milhouse, I need slender
fingers to get me a pickle.
This isn't mine.
(BOTH GIGGLING)
I have a message
for your wife.
"Stop sleeping
with my husband."
Okay-doke!
And you are? The wife
of your wife's lover.
Does she know what
this is regarding?
(SCOFFS) You moron! Marge is
having an affair with Kirk!
(LAUGHS) That's ridiculous.
No woman would want to
have sex with that loser.
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
And, uh, congratulations on
snagging him back. Good stuff.
Just answer me
one question.
How did your wife's bra end up
in my husband's bed? (GRUNTS)
(GASPS)
This is Marge's bra.
I bought it for her boobs.
Of all the people for Marge to cheat
on, why did it have to be me?
Oh, boy, am I beat.
If you want to return a
melon to the grocery store,
clear your day.
Well, that answers the mystery
of the missing melon.
But I have one
more question.
Did you sleep
with Kirk Van Houten?
(GASPS) How could
you ask me that?
I repeat. Did you
sleep with Kirk?
Homer, you're crazy.
You're not saying "no".
Fine. No.
I'm still not
hearing "no."
No, no, no!
Well, methinks the lady
doth protest too much.
You don't trust me?
After I salved every chicken
pock on your ungrateful body?
How dare you?
I'm still
waiting for that "no."
Get out of this house!
Gladly!
(GRUNTS)
We tried to break up your
parents and we broke up mine!
Wanna call my therapist
to tell her how you feel?
Hello, Dr. Wexler?
DR. WEXLER: Stop calling me!
I'm on my honeymoon!
Yeah, it's that
weird kid again.
Dad?
(GASPS)
I thought Mom kicked
you out of the house!
I came to get my mail.
"Resident." "Occupant."
I can't open these.
Ooh! A traffic ticket!
I'd do anything to get your
mother and that donut back.
Okay, look, you and
Mom can fix this.
What exactly happened
between the two of you?
Lisa, we don't need
to know how.
It's a natural
thing that happens,
like a hurricane
or going to war.
Hmm...
Well, I'd better go.
Where are you staying?
You know the Four Seasons?
Well, I'm experiencing
them firsthand
because I'm
living in the park.
Bart, I think you're
behind this whole thing.
Yeah, I can see
how you'd think that.
But on the other hand...
(GRUNTS)
Ha! I can read you
like a book.
Ha-ha. You read books.
If you don't tell Mom
what you did, I will.
AW, come on.
Wouldn't it be easier
if our parents divorced
and you compensated
by marrying much older men?
And meanwhile, I'll be one
of those weird guys who's 35
and shows up at high
school basketball games.
(SIGHS)
(GROANS)
Why did I marry
that selfish jerk?
I've asked him to flip the
mattress a thousand times
and he never does.
(GRUNTING)
Uh, Mom?
Hi, sweetie.
Uh, you know that bra
that broke up our family?
Uh-huh.
Well, I looked into it, and it
turns out I was responsible.
Really?
Well, just for that,
I'm gonna erase all the saved
games on your PlayStation.
What? How do you know
about things like that?
I learned about it in here.
Ha!
But Dad can come home, right?
No!
But he's innocent.
Innocent?
After all I do for your father,
he still doesn't trust me.
I'm finished with him!
Does this mean you and Dad
might get a D-A-V-U-R-S?
Young man, you go
work on your spelling
or I'll delete all the custom
ring tones from your cell phone.
No!
(SIGHS) Our reverse Parent Trap
just made everything worse.
Maybe we should use a
different movie as our guide.
Like Oklahoma!
(SINGING) Oh, the farmer and
the cowman should be friends
Oh, the farmer and the cowman
should be friends
One man likes to push a plow
The other likes to chase a cow
But that's no reason
why they can't be friends
What do you think, Bart? A hoedown
could solve all our problems.
I just need your chap size. lt's
two more than your pant size.
How many times do I have to tell
you no Rodgers & Hammerstein?
Rodgers and Hart?
No!
Well, what will trick your parents
into getting back together?
LISA: Enough
with the tricks!
Stupid movie schemes
do not work in real life!
Mom and Dad have a
marriage on the rocks.
And they need to work
through it in therapy
to make sure it
doesn't shatter.
Rocks. Shatter.
Jagged cliff!
Lise, you've just
given me an idea for
the most insane, harebrained,
foolproof scheme ever!
(SIGHS)
Okay, when my mom and dad see
this dummy fall in the river,
they'll think it's me.
And they'll realize what really matters.
Each other.
Do you like
the dummy, Bart?
I even made it
smell like you.
Now make sure
Homer and Marge
are in proper
viewing position.
So I got your note saying you
wanted to meet here to apologize.
Well, I got
your note saying
you were gonna bring me
a bucket of potato salad.
Where's my apology?
Where's my bucket?
Now I'll get Mom
and Dad's attention
and you shove
the dummy in the water.
Any questions?
Yeah.
What are you going
as for Halloween?
Pile of dog doo.
Let's roll.
Mom! Dad! I'm playing
on a dangerous cliff
because you're too busy arguing
to pay attention to me!
(GASPS)
Bart! We're all disappointed
there's no potato salad!
But for God's sake,
don’t jump!
Now!
I can't tell
which is which.
Oh, no! I'm already running!
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
Whoa!
I did it, Bart!
Bart?
(SCREAMING)
I'm a-comin', boy!
(BOTH SCREAMING)
(HUMMING)
(WHIMPERING)
This is all my fault.
I planted Mom's bra
on Milhouse's parents' bed.
Why, you little...
(CHOKING)
Homer, I can save you both.
Just let go of the rock.
Just do it! Trust me!
Okay.
(ALL BREATHING HEAVILY)
Mom, Dad, I'd give
a kajillion dollars
for you to
get back together!
Make it two kajillion. Homer!
We'll lose the first
kajillion to taxes.
Well, I guess you showed
you do trust me after all.
Of course I do.
The only thing I can't believe
is that a woman as great as
you would be married to me.
Aw, Homie...
MILHOUSE: I don't want to
live in a world without Bart!
(GAS PS)
Can he swim?
What do you think?
(SINGING) California!
California!
Here we come!
Ripped By mstoll