The Simpsons.
When Krusty wants to,
he can still blow them away.
Yes, he can take a simple,
everyday thing
like eating a bicycle
and make it funny.
See you tomorrow, kids.
But before I go,
I'd just like to say...
Ah, there's nothing better
than a cigarette,
unless it's a cigarette
lit with a hundred-dollar bill.
Put 5,000 bucks on the Lakers.
Hire Kenny G. To play
for me in the elevator.
My house is dirty,
buy me a clean one.
Krusty, as your accountant,
I must warn you...
Did you send those 1,000 roses
to Bea Arthur's grave?
Yes, but she's still...
I don't want to hear
the end of any sentences.
George Carlin on three.
Yeah? Lawsuit?
Oh, come on.
My "Seven words you can't
say on TV" bit
was entirely different
from your "Seven words you can't
say on TV" bit.
So I'm a thief, am I?
Well, excuse me!
Give him ten grand.
Steve Martin on four.
Ten grand.
Krusty, in regards
to the large wager you made
on yesterday's horse race.
Oh, come on, how about letting
me go double or nothing
on the big opera tonight.
- Who do you like?
- The tenor.
Okay,
but we're only
letting the bet ride
because you crack us
so consistently up.
You've got to stop blowing
your money like this, Krusty.
No can do.
And those ridiculous
bets you make.
Gambling is the finest thing
a person can do
if he's good at it.
But you haven't won anything
in months.
So I'll just make
some more money.
Crank out some
cheesy merchandise.
But you've already
merchandized everything.
Krusty's Monopoly game.
The Krusty crowd control
barrier.
Nothing is selling anymore.
Not even your new
Lady Krusty line.
But our infomercials
are running 24 hours a day.
So what do you think
of the Lady Krusty moustache
removal system now, Angelique?
It's Krusteriffic,
Johnny Unitas.
But is my upper lip
supposed to bleed like this?
Probably.
At this rate,
you'll be broke in a month.
The only thing left to do
is to open a clown college
and train some
regional Krusties.
You mean like that bozo,
Bonko the Clown?
- Exactly.
- Forget it.
I'll just cut back
on the condor egg omelets.
Mmm, a couple of those
would be tasty right now.
I'll found
the college tomorrow.
It must be
the first of the month.
New billboard day!
Finders keepers.
"This year, give her
English muffins."
Whatever you say,
Mr. Billboard.
"Best in the West."
That rhymes.
Clown college?
You can't eat that.
Well, I got everything
I was supposed to get.
I'm not going to enroll
in that clown college, though.
That advertisement
had no effect on me whatsoever.
Hey, Homer, the section
you're supposed
to be monitoring is on fire.
Clowns are funny.
Mom?
I think I'll have
some wine.
Marge...
Yes, Homey?
That's it.
You people have stood
in my way long enough.
I'm going to clown college.
I don't think any of us
expected him to say that.
Hurry up.
It's my first day
of clown college.
Hold still, Homer.
Don't squirm.
I am holding still.
I am squirming.
Dad, you can't just go around
pretending to be Krusty.
It's sacrilege.
He's a one and only.
I mean, he invented
the pie fight,
the pratfall,
and the seltzer bottle.
As far as I know.
Yeah, Dad, it was
bad enough
when you tried to pass
yourself off as Tom Bosley.
But Krusty?
You weren't complaining
when I got you this close
to Chachi.
What's a Chachi?
All right. There can only be
one Krusty in each territory,
so I hope this works out.
Tell me where you're from.
- Georgia.
- Texas.
Uh, Brooklyn.
Russia.
New Hampshire.
Homer.
Okay, we'll start
off with the baggy...
What?
Those are supposed
to be baggy pants.
Baggy!
Ooh, I've never had
a pair of pants
that fit this well
in my life.
Okay, memorize these
funny place names.
Stop it, you're killing me!
Seattle!
And now, everybody's favorite:
The Spin Cycle
Fantastique trick.
It's a great piece of buffoonery
if you pull it off.
But if you blow it,
you'll look like a fool.
Steady...
Steady.
Now, when the wealthy
dowager comes in,
the party's over, right?
Wrong!
Kill wealthy dowager.
Uh, burn that seat.
These Krusty brand balloons
are three bucks each.
But get a cheap one
and what happens?
Goes off, takes out the eyeballs
of every kid in the room.
What's that gonna cost you?
Hey, Bill, what did
that cost us?
Wow! I'm sorry I doubted
you before, Dad.
If there has to be
a bastardized version of Krusty,
I'm glad it's you.
Thanks, honey. Bank shot.
Wow!
That's good aim, Dad.
Well, it was my major.
Welcome to the noble family
of skilled Krustaceans.
You will now go back
to your hometowns
and do kids' parties,
swap meets,
and all the other piddling crap
I wouldn't touch
with a ten-foot clown pole.
Now come and get
your cat skins...
Uh, I mean sheep skins.
This is the happiest
day of my life...
Got it.
No shock for me.
Oh, yeah?
And now to help introduce
our fantastic new burger,
the one with ketchup,
here he is,
coming in by parachute,
Krusty the Clown!
"To audience.
"I now proclaim
this new burger...
For sale!"
Lord, save me.
It's the Krusty burglar.
Oh, my God.
He's stealing all the burgers!
Why, you little!
I've got you!
Oh, Homer!
It's... It's...
It's all just an act.
Stop!
He's already dead!
Let go!
Get him!
Uh, Krusty the Clown, everybody!
Please look at my MedicAlert bracelet.
Oh. Hey. Hey.
And then, take that
and put that in there,
and you...
There's your giraffe,
little girl.
I'm a boy.
That's the spirit.
Never give up.
I guess you're pretty impressed,
huh, Bart?
My dad got
Krusty the Clown
to personally appear
at my party.
I have a feeling I could get him
to appear at my house.
I don't know, Bart.
My dad's a pretty big wheel
down at the cracker factory.
Uh, it's not
5:30 yet.
- Hey, nice threads.
- I'm beat.
And after work,
I got to dedicate a new Jiffy Lube
and cohost
the Ace awards.
Wow! Jiffy Lube!
Boy, you're really
running yourself ragged.
Oh, yeah. When I started
this clown thing,
I thought it would be
nothing but glory.
You know, the glory
of being a clown?
But I tell you,
it's hard, tiring work.
But when I see the smiles
on their little faces,
I just know they're getting
ready to jab me with something.
My time's almost up here,
so I'd just like to say
I know Woody Allen.
And now the winner
for the most promising
new series on cable...
Old "Starsky and Hutches."
Accepting the award
is the son of the guy
who played Huggy Bear.
Let's walk and talk.
I have some
wonderful stories
about other famous people
that include me in some way.
Can't. I gotta go distract
bulls at a rodeo.
Hey, me, too.
We can go together.
Uh... No, I'm going
a different way
than you, Dick.
Your churlish
attitude reminds me
of a time I was having
dinner with Groucho...
Look, you're gonna be having
dinner with Groucho tonight
if you don't beat it.
Ah, being a clown sucks.
You get kicked by kids,
bit by dogs,
and admired by the elderly.
Who am I clowning?
I have no business
being a clown.
I'm leaving
the clowning business
to all the other clowns
in the clowning business.
Ah, no.
Well, well, well,
velocity boy.
I'm gonna give you the
biggest ticket you...
Hey! Krusty!
I'm not Krusty.
To think I was going
to give you a ticket!
Krusty the Clown!
I am not Krusty!
Hey, Krusty, Krusty,
you remember that time
we got loaded
and set those
beavers loose
in that pine
furniture store?
Ah, memories.
All right, you take
it easy, Krusty.
Hey, he didn't give me a ticket.
This is
an intriguing development.
You mean I get five percent off
on everything in the store
just because I look like...
I mean, just because
I am Krusty the Clown?
How could I charge full price
to the man whose lust
for filthy magazines
kept me in business during
that first shaky year?
By the way, here is your new issue
of "Gigantic Asses".
I'm telling you, Marge,
this will work.
They'll think I'm Krusty
and give us free stuff.
I've been getting
free stuff all day.
Look at this swell bucket
of house paint.
Look at it.
I'm not saying
it won't work.
I'm just saying
it's dishonest.
Well. If we agree,
then why are we arguing?
Hey, Krusty!
Hey, ooh, beautiful
date tonight, huh?
And such lovely
children you have.
I'm more striking
than lovely.
You come a-with me.
Come with Luigi.
You don't want to sit
with the rest of this a-scum.
I only consider you scum
compared to Krusty.
- Well, all right.
- Well, okay.
Yeah, you see
how you scum.
Let me get this straight.
You took all the money you made
franchising your name
and bet it against
the Harlem Globetrotters?
Oh, I thought
the Generals were due.
He's spinning the ball
on his finger!
Just take it!
Take the ball!
That game was fixed.
They were using a freakin' ladder
for God sakes.
I am afraid the time has come
for you to pay us.
Look, I'm cleaned out.
Just take the clown college.
We have already taken it.
Kids have a lot
of money these days
so after you finish
your performance,
you might consider robbing them.
Look, what can I tell you?
You can't get blood
from a turnip.
You want to kill me,
go ahead and kill me.
Oh, hey, hey, all right,
okay already!
Look, we can talk this over.
No more talk.
It is time for us
to take you for a ride.
Oh, no!
Mind if I go
to the bathroom first?
I see no harm in that.
When he's done in there,
I got to go.
Okay, wherever Krusty's gone,
we'll find him.
Legs, you check out
the east side.
Louie, Rome and Budapest.
Tell the boys I want
a total world search.
- Right, boss.
I want a free car
because I'm Krusty.
Krusty the Clown!
Get it?
Krusty.
Cancel the world search.
I want everything that's
coming to Krusty the Clown,
which is me, Krusty.
Hey, it's Krusty, all right.
Should I shoot him
gangland style
or execution style?
Listen to your heart.
Well, I can't give
you the car, Krusty.
But I can let you have
this little number
for practically nothing...
Only 38,000.
Hey, what are all these holes?
These are speed holes.
They make the car go faster.
Oh, yeah. Speed holes.
You want my advice?
I think you should
buy this car.
We need more ammo.
Let's go to Big 5.
Krusty, your plastic surgery
is complete.
When I remove the bandages
don't be alarmed by
the total stranger
staring back at you.
I look exactly the same,
you moron!
Nonsense, Krusty.
You look at least ten years younger,
plus, I did your breasts.
Does anyone hear me complaining
about the breasts?
Oh, what's the use in hiding?
I got to go back to Springfield
and face the music.
Can you loan me
bus fare?
Hey, hey, hey!
What you
diddley-doing, neighbor?
Putting speed holes
in my car.
Makes it go faster.
Is that so?
Gee, maybe the old
Flanders-mobile could use...
Wow! Lucky I always keep
a bible close to my heart.
Lucky I was wearing
an extra-large piece
of the true cross today.
I think I'll go inside.
What keeps doing that?
I told you we should have bought
more than three bullets.
Let's just grab him.
But wait, you can't kill me
for being Krusty.
I'm not him.
I'm Homer Simpson.
The same Homer Simpson
who crashed his car
through the wall
of our club?
Uh, actually,
my name is Barney.
Yeah, Barney Gumble.
The same Barney Gumble
who keeps taking pictures
of my sister?
Actually, my real name is, uh...
Think, Krusty, think...
Joe Valachi.
The same Joe Valachi who squealed
to the senate committee
about organized crime?
Benedict Arnold.
The same Benedict Arnold
who plotted
to surrender West Point
to the hated British?
I am so glad I had
a chance to meet you
before we did this, Krusty,
because I am a great fan.
Don Vittorio DiMaggio.
Krusty the Clown.
Sorry I have to do this, Krusty.
I cannot do it.
To murder a funny man
of such genius
would be a crime.
Tell you what, Krusty.
Do for me my
favorite trick,
where you ride the little bike
through the loop
and I will let you live.
But I've never been
able to do the...
Hey, how about if I just squirt you
in the face with my boutonniere?
Okay.
I'll never be able
to do this trick.
- Never.
- Go! Go!
Oh, oh, oh! Hey!
I'm doing it.
I'm doing it!
I'm the greatest clown
in the world!
Ta-da!
The fact that you did not
do the trick well
is the biggest insult of all.
Hey, guys, I came to, uh...
Oh, you've got a deadly game
of cat and mouse going.
I'll come back.
I'm seeing double here.
Four Krusties.
Krusty!
Oh, thanks! Thanks a lot!
You came here to save me!
Yeah, that's what I did.
My apologies to you.
I almost made
a grievous error.
Good-bye, Krusty.
Wait! He can't kill anybody
if he doesn't know
which one's the real Krusty.
Oh, whoa!
Hup, ha ha!
I am confused.
Good one, Krusty.
Oh, crap.
Because of that
disrespectful display,
I shall now kill
both of you.
Unless...
you both go through the loop
together.
I can't see, you idiot!
Take your hands off my eyes.
- Hey!
Not bad.
Without the loop,
it is nothing.
Whoa!
Ta-da!
Yay, Krusties!
Hey, hey.
Grazie, grazie.
You have brought great joy
to this old Italian stereotype.
No, no, Don Vittorio,
you're not...
Yes, I am.
I know it, I am.
Anyway, thank you, Krusty.
You're welcome.
So we're even now, huh?
No, we just
won't kill you.
But you still
owe us the money.
Forty-eight dollars.
Here's 50.
And two your change.
And we thank you.
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.