(SINGING) The Simpsons
Ripped by jasonnguyenn2606
(SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
(HORN BELLOWING)
(PLAYING DIFFERENT TUNE)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(HONKING)
D'oh!
(SCREAMS)
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
(BUZZING)
Oh!
(BEEPING)
COMMENTATOR: We got a real nail-biter
here at Mile High Stadium.
The Broncos down by one, and
30 seconds left on the clock.
Come on, Broncos,
you can do it.
And I'm joined in
the broadcast booth
by the stars of
ABC's latest reality show
Billionaire versus Bear.
Let's review the easy-to-follow
rules of your show.
Each of you thought
you were in a race
to plant the Taco Bell flag
at the North Pole.
What you didn't know is,
the race was a chase
spiced up by the presence
of the betrayer.
(GROANING)
Well, now, the bear
has a surprise for you.
He's not really a bear,
he's a tiger!
Oh, lookie there! Denver
just won the ballgame!
Oh, the Broncos won?
Why didn't I bet on them like
Professor Pigskin told me to?
Who's Professor Pigskin?
He's a pig who can predict
football winners in advance!
How is that possible?
Because he's got something
no gambler's ever had!
A system!
I've gotten the pamphlet four
weeks in a row and every time,
the pick-of-the-week
has been right on the money.
Oh!
I get it.
Every week, they send
out two pamphlets,
Half picking one team and
half picking the other.
Eventually, there's
a small group of people
who only receive
the correct predictions
and think Professor
Pigskin is always right.
That's when they
ask for your money.
(GASPS) I have money!
Dad, it's a scam!
A scam?
Not according to Eddie F.
from Tucson,
or Football Millionaire
in Beloit, Michigan.
Look, all I'm saying is, you really
should think twice before...
Expiration date,
06/08.
Oh, Professor Pigskin told me to bet
on the Raiders, but they look awful!
And with 37 starting players out
with the flu, the Oakland Raiders
have turned to drunks
conscripted from local bars.
Spare some change,
football dude?
(GROANS)
Now, you have
a good day.
Dad, how much
money did you bet?
Hey, I didn't bet
any of our money.
I just borrowed
some from him.
Don't worry.
We can hammer
out a payment plan.
Ow! (SOBBING)
It's not my fault
the Raiders lost!
It's Professor Pigskin's!
If he mentions that pig
again, use two hammers.
But the pig...
(SCREAMS) Ow! Ow!
Now, I do have a way
we could settle this debt.
We would like to use your
home to shoot an adult film.
Yeah, it's called Lemony Lick-it:
A Series of Horny Events.
(GASPS) Marge
would kill me!
Please! There's got to be
something else I can do.
Like mow your lawn
every week for two weeks.
I can't do it next week.
Ow! All right!
You can shoot your gay
adult film at my house.
I didn't say
anything about gay.
I thought you guys
were the gay mafia. Ow!
Oh, they're shooting an adult
film at my house tomorrow.
How am I gonna get rid
of Marge and the kids?
Well, I got these free
tickets to Santa's Village.
I know a guy
who turns the dead
sleigh horses into jerky
and sells it to bars.
Ugh!
Thanks, Moe!
Why would we want to
go to Santa's Village?
It's August.
I want to see Santa. He can
explain why he gave me
a Playstation box with nothing
inside but a coloring book.
It got your hopes up, didn't it?
Homer, before
I take the kids
I want you to swear you're
not up to something.
I swear.
And I'd also like to know why
your hand is in that cast.
Because you look
even more beautiful
now than the day
I married you.
Aw!
(FLIES BUZZING)
Welcome to Santa's Village,
where it's Christmas every day.
Closed on Christmas.
Those reindeer look
really uncomfortable.
That's because they don't
thrive in this environment!
Watcha reading,
Santa?
Torn Clancy's Op-center.
You don't seem
very jolly.
Well, Santa got
some bad medical news.
Okay...
And, action!
We've been on this spaceship
for a hundred years.
When will we ever get
to Planet Satisfaction?
Hey, Homer,
we... Wow!
Angela Dare!
Sultry Stevens!
Yeah, what is this, a reunion
of Fahrenheit 9-on-1?
Guys! Get out of here!
Homer, how'd you ever get
Marge to go along with this?
Look, if you promise never to tell
her, I'll let you be in the movie.
We just came over to borrow
a board game, but okay.
I've always dreamed of
working in an adult film.
I'll run
the sound board!
And I'll perform
in the sex scenes!
Merry Christmas!
I'm your old pal
Frosty the Snowman!
In your dreams.
Frosty!
Where's your magic top hat?
Oh, God, please don't tell Mr.
Roselli I lost my hat again!
(WHISTLING)
My Christmas present
to myself this year
was leaving
that place early.
Mom, I got a rash where
the reindeer licked me.
Huh?
When they put Santa in the ambulance,
Why'd they pull the blanket
all the way up
over his head?
Look, I know this wasn't
the greatest outing
but your father
meant well,
so don't let him know that we didn't...
(EXCLAIMS)
Are you guys
almost done?
Listen, I got a tattoo of Foghorn
Leghorn on my right thigh.
Are we gonna get
into any trademark
or copyright
issues here?
'Cause we could
put a Band-Aid on it
and say my character just
got stabbed.
Relax, three guys'll put
their hands on it, okay?
Now, everybody is
very much in love.
And, action!
Homer! Is this
a snuggle film?
Er...
You're in
the wrong house, lady!
How could you
allow this?
In the room where
we do puzzles!
(GRUNTS)
Oh, uh-uh.
Honey, please, just listen
to what I have to say.
All right.
Lowed the mafia money.
Oh!
Where are you going?
Away from you.
When will you be back?
I don't know.
Who's going to watch the kids?
You are.
Me? But I'm
the father!
(ENGINE REVVING)
Boy, Homer, I've never
seen Mom this mad.
Honey, come back!
You didn't say bye to the kids!
MARGE: Bye, Bart.
I love you, Lisa.
Sleep tight, Maggie.
Today's the last day you can
eat the yogurt in the fridge.
Well, we better
go eat that yogurt.
Kids, I'm sure, your
mother will be back soon.
She should be back now.
It's dinnertime.
Look, we've been
down this road before.
I do something stupid, your
mom leaves, we eat waffles.
We're out of waffles.
All we got is ketchup.
You mean Homer's
famous marinara sauce?
No, I mean ketchup.
Where's your sense
of magic and wonder?
Come on, Marge. When
are you going to call?
(RINGING)
Let it ring, play hard to get.
That's hard enough!
Oh, my darling, I love you!
Please forgive me!
MOE: Hey, Homer.
Moe, what are you calling me for?
You told me to call.
You wanted to see
if your phone
was working.
But what if Marge tries to
call while I'm talking to you?
Ain't you got
call waiting?
Of course, I have
call waiting, you idiot!
I just never
learned how to use it!
Uh-oh, I might have broken the phone.
I better call Moe.
(DIALING)
Oh, hey, Homer. Moe, will
you get off the line?
(GROANS)
I guess I better tell them
I'm coming home.
(RINGS)
(STAMMERS)
Oh, Marge, what
a pleasant surprise.
I'm at a rest stop
south of Springfield.
I know.
You're sorry now.
Then you'll buy me some
Kwik-E-Mart flowers
maybe a box of candy,
where half the pieces
mysteriously
have testing bites,
and a week
later you'll be back
to your old
thoughtless self.
No, no, it's not going
to be like that, I swear.
Ew! Lemon cream.
You're going in the Marge pile.
I mean,
I love you so much.
Yeah, I love you, too.
(POUNDING AT DOOR)
Hold on. I'll be
off in a minute.
(POUNDING CONTINUES)
Listen, buster, I had to buy
a club soda I didn't want
to get change
for this phone.
An oogly-boogly!
(ROARING)
Be still. Don't
give it the phone.
Settle down,
sugar plum.
Look what daddy's
got in his pocket.
Yummy, yummy kelp-
Good girl,
yes, yes.
This animal
means you no harm.
She's a sweet old
Florida manatee,
also known as
a sea cow or dugong.
HOMER: Hello, Marge, where do we keep
the socks that don't smell like feet?
I'll call you back.
I'm Dr. Caleb Thorn
and I would do anything
to protect a manatee
except harm
another manatee.
What if by harming
a manatee
you could save
two manatees?
But before you answer,
consider this.
The manatee you'd have
to harm is pregnant.
Those are the questions
that keep me up at night.
(GROANS)
I see a manatee
the needs a hug.
Ooh!
HOMER: Hello, Marge?
Does the pizza
guy take a check?
If so, where do we
keep the checks?
And lastly,
how do you write a check?
I think the worst
part was when I realized
that Homer lied to me.
From what you've told
me, it sounds like
what your husband did
was nothing new.
Exactly.
I have a saying
which goes,
"You can't teach
a manatee any tricks."
Maybe you could just put a hat
on him and say it's a trick.
My point is Homer is the
exact same man you married
and if there's
a problem here,
it's that you keep
expecting him to change.
Huh!
MARGE: He cares so much
about those doggone dugongs.
I wish I felt
that kind of passion.
Maybe I should join
him on his mission.
Hey, lady blue,
while you're sitting there
staring at the ceiling
your boyfriend's
in the parking lot
with his hands
in a walrus.
Yeah, that'll be
good for business.
Got to find your mom.
BART: Dad, I promise
I'll be good.
Can I get out of
the dog carrier?
It was hard enough getting you in there.
I'm not letting you out.
Yeah, she came
through here.
I believe she
was looking
to rekindle
her passion for life.
Ain't that right, Victor? Yes.
Señora left for the coast with a rugged,
yet sensitive man of science.
Rugged? Is that the
same as handsome?
Oh, no, no.
"Handsome" means he look at
himself in the mirror all day.
"Rugged" means
you look at him.
(SOBBING)
Oh!
Okay, water monsters, be friendly...
But not too friendly.
What do I do?
Talk to it!
Let it know
you're not a threat.
Okay. You know, up close,
you're kinda cute.
(RETCH ES)
Aw, you're a good thing.
I know it.
Let me clean out your ears.
I've bonded with him!
(GIGGLING)
Where is he taking me?
To his underwater palace.
Just kidding.
It's a lagoon full of bugs.
(MARGE YELLING)
Dad, I don't think
we're gonna find Mom today.
And I'm sick of eating
at restaurant chains
I never even heard of like
Skobo's and Dim Willie's.
LISA: Ugh!
Okay, kids, we'll
stop for the day.
I have cousins near here.
We'll stay with them.
Country cousins?
Are they rubes?
'Cause I don't
cotton to rubes.
Oh! The rubiest.
Oh, look, a new restaurant chain.
Whoo-hoo!
Can we say it's my birthday
and get free stuff?
We'll say it's
all our birthdays.
(MUMBLING)
(BANJO PLAYING)
Cousin Homer,
how are you?
And this must
be Bart and Lisa.
Well, aren't you
nice-looking kids.
Hey, do you folks
want to see a quilt
that's been
in our family
for five generations?
I warned you
he was an idiot.
Well, all I need
is some moonshine
and someone
playing the harmonicky
and I'm as happy
as a pig in plop
We're having
lasagna and Caesar salad.
Don't laugh. They're
doing the best they can.
So, Homer,
how are you?
Just great. Things
couldn't be better.
And how is
our lovely Marge?
She, uh, was killed by a
falling air conditioner.
Oh! Why, that's terrible!
Ooh, er,
it wasn't all bad.
As part of
the settlement,
her funeral was
air conditioned.
Now if you'll excuse me, I have
to use the outhouse again.
Well, we don't have
an outhouse.
My recording studio!
So how are
we related again?
Our dogs
are brothers.
BART: Oh, yeah.
(GASPS) I see Mom!
(GIGGLING)
I've got
my groove back!
We've got to tell Dad!
Where is he?
Oh!
You lost that first
game to hustle me!
(CLUCKING)
I can't believe how many
manatees we saved today.
And the ones we can't save,
we put to good use.
Hmmm.
What am I supposed to do,
bury them at Arlington?
Marge?
Homer?
These are for you.
Ooh!
Listen, I thought
about what I did.
And it was really,
really wrong.
I'm sorry.
Homie, I accept
your apology.
I love you, Marge.
But I'm not
coming back yet.
(EXCLAIMS IN DISBELIEF)
I've found a place
where I'm needed.
You're needed at home!
And treated
like I deserve.
You're needed at home!
I'm sorry, Home.
I just can't find it in my
heart to come back right now.
Well, that's
very reasonable.
You stole my wife!
I'll kill you!
Homer, I have no interest
in stealing your wife
but Marge is getting something
from her work with me.
Something a strong, passionate
woman like her needs.
A Purpose.
WOW!
I can see why
she loves you.
She doesn't love me. She's
just trying to find herself.
(EXHALES)
You know everything.
I don't know everything.
I'm just a man.
And what a man!
Okay, the key to this
thing is the manatees.
Is Marge saving them or killing them?
Saving!
Okay. To save the manatees,
I guess I could donate
my time and money
and help them build a...
Screw that!
Dad!
Those jet skiers are headed
right for a herd of manatees!
Check out those gentle,
exotic sea creatures.
Let's whomp 'em!
(MOTORS REVVING)
(ALL LAUGHING)
Man, I just wish we
could see their tears.
(PANTING)
Why don't you pick
on someone your own size?
They are roughly our size.
In fact,
they're bigger than us.
Look, if it were up to me I'd
be harassing them with you.
If anything, I'd be the
guy who took it too far.
But I love my wife
and I want to win her back!
You're a brave man.
And we respect two things,
bravery and tattoos that look
like barbed wire. Let's go.
(LAUGHS)
Rubes!
What did you
call us?
Catch me if you can!
Manatees! Defend!
(MOTOR REVVING)
(YELLING)
(GASPS)
(HOMER GROANING)
Attention jet skiers.
I have a court order here requiring
you to vacate these waters.
No court order's gonna
tell me what to do.
Oh, man!
It's notarized!
Let's boogie!
Homer, are you okay?
How many fingers
am I holding up?
Poor dumb country mouse.
Can't even count.
(MOANS)
My sweet, sweet Homie!
You sacrificed
yourself for the manatees.
Oh!
Rubes.
So many rubes...
Pounding me with their jet skis.
Rubes...
Please, no, rubes.
(GROANING)
(RETCHING)
I'm gonna take you
home and fix you up,
'cause you're
the real endangered species,
a devoted husband.
Marge, I'm always
amazed you chose me.
And I always will.
Whoo-hoo!
(SIGHS)
I'm starting to think
I should find a woman.
(BLEATING)
Yeah, Miranda was nice, but I'm
not driving to Corpus Christi
every time she needs
a light bulb changed.
(BLEATS)
Amen.
Hey, since we got the kids
with us, why don't we all take
a few days of much
needed R&R?
Don't you have to
be back at work?
Yes. But I've got a friend
who owes me a solid.
Smithers, who is this
barrel-chested go-getter?
I believe it's a manatee
posing as Homer Simpson, sir.
That's cute.
(PANTING)
I think this is the beginning
of a beautiful friendship.
Actually, sir, I believe he's
about to die of dehydration.
Good heavens!
Grab a sponge, man!
(WOMAN SINGING) Ooh
You might not
ever get rich
But let me tell you it's
better than digging a ditch
There ain't no telling
who you might meet
A movie star or maybe
even an Indian chief
Working at the car wash
Working at
the car wash, yeah!
Come on and sing it
with me, car wash
Sing it with the feeling
now, car wash, yeah
Come some of the work
get's kind of hard
This ain't no
place to be
If you planned
on being a star
Let me tell you
it's always cool
And the boss don't mind
sometimes if you act a fool
At the car wash
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa
Talking about
the car wash, yeah!
Come on y'all
and sing it for me
Car wash, whoo-hoo!
Car wash, yeah!
Ripped by jasonnguyen2606