(SINGING) The Simpsons
(TIRES SCREECHING)
D'oh!
(SCREAMS)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Ripped By mstoll
(SINGING)
Tis the season to be jolly
Mid-June?
(CHILDREN LAUGHING)
Kids, this is the holiest night of
the year. Tomorrow is Father's Day.
And that makes tonight
Father's Day Eve.
(SINGING) Joy to the world
A father's born
Let me receive great gifts
Dad, there's no such thing
as Father's Day Eve.
No Father's Day Eve?
Does this mean there's no
such thing as Daddy Claus?
(WHIMPERS)
Fine. There's a Daddy Claus.
Is there a Super Bowl
Bunny?
Sure. Why not?
(GIGGLING)
Bart, Lisa, we've gotta get
to the mall before it closes.
Oh, can I come with you?
I know I can't!
(GIGGLING)
Hey, Mom. Can I have some
money to buy Dad a present?
If I give you money, how is
the gift really from you?
Where do you get your money?
Here's a 10.
Make your own card.
(GIGGLING)
Now, Ralphie, let me
explain it to you again.
I give you $5
and you buy Daddy a present.
Okey-doke. (GULPS)
(SIGHS)
Hey, give me that! Oh!
Whoa! This is a 50!
(CHUCKLES)
This kid's finally
paying off.
All right, Ralphie. Let's see
what you can do with a hundred.
(GULPS)
Come on, Ralphie. Big money!
Big money, Ralphie!
Big money...
Cool.
That's what I'm getting.
How about you?
I'm afraid the best thing
I could find is this.
BART: Ay, caramba! You know,
this mass-produced junk
doesn't express how I feel about Dad.
(HUFFS)
lam making him a present
that comes from the heart.
Hello. I'm looking for
something in a pipe cleaner.
Extra bendy
with medium fuzz.
Mmm-hmm. This just
came in from Zanzibar.
Oh...
Mmm-hmm.
HOMER;
What a great Father's Day!
Here you go, Dad.
I hope you like it.
I've forgotten what it is.
(GASPS)
A Leather Buddy!
There's no limit to
what I can do with this.
Fear not, m'lady.
Captain Dash Superstud
is here with his small tool!
(PIRATES YELLING)
(GRUNTS)
(ALL GROANING)
(SWORDS CLATTERING)
Arr.
This is the worst
Father's Day ever!
(BONE CRACKS)
(GROANS)
Oh, Captain,
you're so handy.
Bart, this is the greatest
present I ever received.
To open another gift now
would be like following
the London Philharmonic
with Jessica Simpson.
What you got, Lisa?
What the hell is this?
(GROANS)
The unicorns
are you and me, Dad.
I drew it myself!
What do you think,
huh? Huh?
Pretty heartfelt, huh?
Huh?
Oh, it's heartfelt.
There's no escaping that.
(CHUCKLES) Thanks, honey.
You didn't like it,
did you?
No, no, no. It's great.
I'm done with it now.
(SOBBING)
Lisa, sweetie,
I think your father
would like to put your
book up on the fridge
where everyone can see
how nice it is.
Aw, isn't that cute?
Oh, Dad,
how could you?
It's not my fault!
Lousy magnet!
(SOBBING)
NO, no...
What the...
(READING) D'oh!
Ohh...
I still don't understand how
her feelings can be hurt.
It's my day!
She's not going to get over this quickly.
I know women.
Yeah. But I know
how to win women back.
I even won you back after I lost
our wedding album in a bar bet!
You what?
I mean, I will win you back!
(SINGING) Here comes the Moe
With a pretty girl
'Cause these are things
that happened In real life
(GRUNTS)
Mmm-hmm.
Hey, Moe.
Can we get a drink?
Ah, shut up and hand me
more Moe heads.
(GROANS)
(HUMMING)
Hmm?
Cool, I'm a street.
Hey, Simpson. Are you
gonna steal the sign?
Yeah. If a sign's got your
name on it, you can take it
and the cops can't do
nothing about it.
It's like the Sixth Amendment
or something.
Well, that sign would look
good hidden under my bed.
Whoa! Can we dish out the peer
pressure or what? (GRUNTS)
Hey, Milhouse!
Cool kids ride bikes
with their eyes closed!
MILHOUSE: I'm cool!
(TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWS)
(CRASHES)
I'm outta here.
I got Hebrew school.
(SPEAKING HEBREW)
I'm sorry I made you
feel bad, honey.
But I'm gonna show you just how
much I care about your feelings.
One adult
and one baby, please.
I'm not a baby.
A baby is zero to two.
Her first words.
Play along!
It's 50 cents
less for babies!
I'd rather not go than lie.
How you doing?
So, is that your jacket
on the back of that chair?
Check it out.
I stole the sign.
We stole The Scream.
Put that away.
It creeps me out.
(GRUMBLING)
...stupid dad doesn't care
about my feelings.
Oh, Lisa, may I borrow
one of your colored pencils?
Sure! That's all you men do
is take and take and take
without regard to feelings or unicorns!
(GRUNTS)
Here, take my lunch, too!
Just take my whole backpack!
(GRUNTS)
Which of you boys hurled Lisa
Simpson's backpack through my window?
Oh, it had to be
a boy, did it?
You think a girl can't flip out?
Well, you're wrong!
(GRUNTING)
My flexi-cast!
(GRUNTS)
(SHATTERS)
(NEIGHS)
Lisa, I hold in my hand a sticker
with a frownie face on it.
Don't make me
affix it to your file.
(MOCKS) "Don't make me
affix it to your file."
I'm peeling off the back.
Don't make me do this.
(SIGHS) May God forgive me.
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
Willie, we've got rats chewing
through the wiring again.
Leave me alone!
I'm making me ramen noodles!
Mr. and Mrs. Simpson, I'm afraid
we have a real problem with Lisa.
(GLASS SHATTERS)
Your daughter broke a window,
upended an ash can,
and hurled a Thermos
brand thermos onto the street!
Does it still keep hot drinks
hot and cold drinks cold?
I'm afraid it doesn't keep any
drinks anything. (GASPS)
I've asked the school
psychologist to shed some light
on your daughter's sudden
burst of inappropriateness.
I'm afraid Lisa's rage stems from
extraordinary disillusionment
with a parental figure.
In this case, her father.
Oh, sure. It's easy
to point out my faults.
It's a little harder
to shut up!
Looking at your daughter's
essays, this isn't a new trend.
"Daddy's Face-Down
Thanksgiving,"
"Left at the Grand Canyon,"
"The Day a Policeman
Came to My Soccer Game."
Mr. Simpson, Lisa
is at a crucial juncture.
If she doesn't see her father
as a positive role model,
she could hate men
for the rest of her life.
Oh, I know!
But how can I undo
eight years of jerkiness
in two easy sessions
at no cost to me?
If I may make a suggestion.
The school is looking
for a new Safety Salamander.
When Lisa sees you teaching children
to avoid downed power lines,
it could restore her faith
in you and the male gender.
Oh, I don't know.
What happened to the last
Safety Salamander?
Uh, he fell asleep
in the suit and suffocated.
I can do that!
HOMER: Okay, Lisa.
Time for Daddy's big surprise.
(GROWLS)
(LISA SCREAMS)
(LAUGHS)
Sometimes it's scary when your
dreams come true, isn't it, sweetie?
I guess.
Yeah.
Now I'm off to bring safety
to Springfield Elementary
and win back your love!
Whoa!
(GROANS) What's that, honey?
I can't hear you very well?
(SPUTTERING)
Salamander away!
(CAT YOWLS)
Sorry, Bart!
HOMER: The first rule
of bus safety
is always wear
your seatbelts.
School buses
don't have seatbelts.
Then what protects you
if we crash?
A metal bar at tooth level.
Stop this bus!
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
(CHILDREN GROANING)
BOY: My teeth!
Look, Lisa.
I made safety happen.
(GROANS) Oh.
Safety tip 99,
always double bolt
your easel.
(SNAPS)
Ouch! Son of a...
(DEEP BREATHING)
Questions? Comments?
Are you a girl?
Because I don't see
a sala-wiener.
(CHILDREN LAUGHING)
Did I hear,
"Where are the fireworks?"
Because here they are!
(CHEERFUL TUNE PLAYING)
CHILDREN: Ooh!
(ALL SCREAMING)
(SHRIEKS)
Every man for himself!
Trample if you must!
(WAILING)
(FIRE ALARM RINGING)
(GRUNTS) on!
(WHIMPERS)
Safety! Safety!
Time for safety!
(GROANS)
So, sweetie,
am I your hero again?
Jamie's father just takes her
to the zoo once a month.
Couldn't you be
that kind of dad?
Now, honey, you know Daddy's not
allowed in the zoo anymore.
Oh, yeah.
But I'll never stop trying
to redeem myself in your eyes.
How did you do that?
I don't know.
I said turn left
on Bart Boulevard.
I'm telling you there
t'ain't no Bart Boulevard.
Forget it.
Baby's already out.
Just get out your hunting knife
and cut the umbrelical cord.
Yes'm.
(BRAKES SCREECH)
Hey!
Watch it!
Ahh!
This is Kent Brockman live at
the scene of the worst accident
in Springfield history.
But not to worry. The city's
emergency services are on the way.
(POLICE SIREN BLARING)
(AMBULANCE SIREN WAILING)
(FIRE TRUCK WAILING)
(SCREAMING)
Can we all agree not to get
our insurance involved?
Come on, people. Be cool.
Springfield needs a hero
and it needs one now.
This looks like a job
for a dad trying
to win back
his daughter's love.
I'm forever indebted to you,
and my many creditors.
We were carpooling!
And that's it!
My mother's
still in the car!
No, she's not.
Ha-ha!
Three cheers
for our new hero!
Only three?
Okay, six.
That's more like it.
Hip hip hooray!
Oh, please.
You're embarrassing me.
I hereby award you
Springfield's
highest honor,
the key card to the city!
Now any new business?
Mister Mayor,
your administration
has been one fiasco
after another!
Who the hell are you?
Your press secretary.
I knew I should've hired
my nephew.
lam your nephew.
Okay, so I stink.
Tough Toblerone.
Read the charter, people.
I cannot be removed
from office
except by a simple
recall election.
And... Uh...
Disregard that last part.
CROWD: (CHANTING)
Recall! Recall! Recall!
BIRDS: (SQUAWKING)
Recall, recall, recall.
Mayor Diamond Joe Quimby has
survived 12 re-election campaigns,
countless accusations of
infidelity, bribery, extortion,
and his bizarre attempt
to hijack a 747.
Take this plane anywhere
girls are going wild.
But the mayor may
have a tougher time
getting past next month 's
special recall election.
Over 200 candidates
have filed,
including yours truly,
Kent Brockman.
In other news, a common
household fabric can kill you.
Find out which one when you
vote for Kent Brockman.
Dear God. Every whacko, nut case,
and Disco Stu in this town
is gonna run against me.
Just imagine me the mayor!
Then nobody would laugh
at my singing.
(SINGING)
I'm proud to be an American
I am so screwed.
Vote Luigi. I make the good
government just the way you like.
Vote for me,
a steroid-abusing,
pot-smoking, women-groping,
son of a Nazi,
washed up
has-been movie star!
(CROWD CHEERING)
Oh, also, I believe we
should keep an open mind
toward stem cell research.
(CROWD BOOING)
This election
is out of control.
Someone terrible could win.
If you're lame enough
to vote, vote for me.
MAN: Jimbo, tough on nerds.
Tougher on dorks.
Dad, we gotta
do something.
What can I do?
I'm only one man.
Lincoln was only one man.
Are you sure there wasn't
a midget in his hat?
I read an e-mail
that said there was.
Look, as the Safety Salamander,
you are beloved by all.
And if you were the mayor,
we could make sure that only good
people, like me, tell you what to do.
Hmm.
I will run for mayor.
And I will be your
campaign manager!
And I'll find out
what a mayor does!
Expand my brain,
learning juice.
Oh, I hate
press conferences.
Homie, you might
score more points
if you didn't wear
that salamander suit.
You look like the mascot for
some horrible southern college.
Marge, without this outfit, I'm
just Homer Simpson, multiple felon.
With it, I'm a costumed hero like
George Washington or Dame Edna.
(CROWD CHEERING)
Today marks a new
dawn for Springfield.
This salamander is sitting on eggs
labeled elder care, flextime,
and downtown
pedestrian mall!
And those eggs
are ready to hatch!
(CHEERING)
Now I will take
your questions.
Uh, what special powers would a
salamander bring to the office of mayor?
Well, there's my
x-ray vision, my fire breath,
and I can get big laughs
with tennis balls.
Bloop, bloop, bloop.
(CROWD LAUGHING)
Oh, I didn't know salamanders
could do all those things.
And to think, for all these
years I've been a gecko man.
Take a hike, jerk.
(SQUEAKS)
Mister Simpson,
what about those photos
of you strangling
your child?
Why should we let
this election be influenced
by a photo
taken hours ago?
(CHEERING)
Now restaurant matchbooks
for everyone!
CROWD: (CHANTING)
Salamander! Salamander!
Homer, you're doing great.
You're way ahead in the polls.
Even those negative campaign
ads aren't hurting you.
Simpson barely even comes
in to work anymore.
He pays a homeless man
to do it for him.
I, um... I don't
feel so good, Blue.
(CHUCKLES) Hey, people may
not love Homer Simpson
but they love this suit.
Just like they love
their stupid American flag.
(HOMER GULPING)
Oh, what's that smell?
It's the smell of impending victory.
(RETCHES)
Did you just vomit
in that suit?
A little.
Oh.
Have you cleaned that suit
once since you got it?
No. But I swam in it.
Ugh. I better
wash that thing.
It's hard to know where the
suit ends and you begin.
Yeah.
But aren't you gonna
have fun finding out?
No!
(CLUCKING)
That's weird...
Started off as an egg.
KENT: Our next question
goes to Eleanor Abernathy.
Also known as
the Crazy Cat Lady.
Uh, Cat Lady,
how would you boost
the city's commercial
tax base?
(BABBLING)
Small business incentives,
(YELLING INCOHERENTLY)
corporate accountability.-.
Cats in everyone's pants!
All right. Thank you, Cat Lady.
See you in the spin room.
Okay. Okey-dokey.
(YELLS) Yeah.
Our next question
is for the Safety Salamander.
(CROWD CHEERING)
Sir, how would you restore our
city's crumbling infrastructure?
That's an excellent question, Kent.
First of all...
What the... Must have shrunk
when my wife washed it.
Why, without his costume,
he's naught but a man!
Hey, screw this. I'm not gonna let
any human tell me what to do.
That's right. lam a man.
The man who dressed
like a salamander
to win back
his daughter's love.
Let's meet her now!
Uh, well, my son is here, too.
Let's meet him now.
BART: Here's Bart!
What's up?
Boring!
We're sick of you
and your hatchlings!
(CROWD BOOING)
Please stop throwing fruit!
(SCREAMS)
(GROANS)
KENT: Our exit polls
show no candidate
attained the 5%
necessary to win.
And Mayor Joe Quimby will keep his
job, which I didn't want anyway.
Your loss, jackasses.
(SIGHING)
Well, Dad, you tried to
make this town a better place.
And no matter what,
that makes you my hero.
Aw, thanks. Now how about
a dance with your daddy?
I can't believe
I lost after Ben Affleck
campaigned
day and night for me.
LISA: Yeah, I warned you
about that.
Whoops!
Be careful of my tail!
You don't have a tail anymore.
You know, I...
I still feel it.
It's so itchy.
(GRUNTING)
Ripped By mstoll