The Simpsons.
Hello. I'm Kent Brockman,
and this is Eye on Springfield.
Tonight, we'll visit
Springfield's answer
to the Benedictine monks...
the Rapping Rabbis.
Don't eat pork.
Not even vit' a fork.
Can't touch this!
Marge, are we Jewish?
- No, Homer.
- Whoo-hoo!
- But first, we all stink.
- We all... hey!
That's according
to a national survey
ranking Springfield as the
least popular city in America.
In science, dead last.
I'm telling you people
the Earth revolves
around the sun.
Burn him!
What a story!
You've stolen my soul!
In culture, dead last.
Eleanor, we've got
to do something
about this depression,
so I propo...
Oh! That's right,
I'm crippled.
This is terrible.
People will start
to avoid Springfield.
But what can I do?
I'm just... one... one man.
I think we should call
a town meeting.
If we don't do something soon,
we won't get any tourists at all.
No tourists?
I'll be ruined.
Maps to movie stars' homes!
Mapas por las casas
de la cineastas.
Top-u stah noh cheezu map-u.
Excuse me.
Are you Drew Barrymore?
What? Get out of here.
I'm hung over.
- Sorry, Miss Barrymore.
- What?
Are there
any suggestions for how
to attract more tourism?
The easiest way to be popular
is to leech off
the popularity of others.
So we propose changing
our name from "Springfield"
to "Seinfeld."
I may be just a boy,
but I have an idea.
If I may, I'd like
to show you a few slides.
Here's Springfield
as it appears from space.
Somewhere in this windy valley
is the Lost Dutchman's Mine.
Young man, that appears
to be a picture
of your rear end.
So long, suckers!
Whoa!
Aw! This is the last time
I use an escape plan
devised by Milhouse.
Uh, sorry, Bart.
I'm Marge Simpson,
and I have an idea.
Marge is going
to say something.
Now I know you haven't liked
some of my past suggestions
like switching
to the metric system...
The metric system
is the tool of the devil!
My car gets 40 rods
to the hogshead,
and that's the way I likes it.
The old person's remarks will be
stricken from the record.
Who said that?
But my new idea is different.
I think we should hold
a film festival
and give out prizes.
Could we make our own movies
and enter them?
- Yes.
- At last, an excuse to wear makeup!
All in favor of Marge Simpson's
film festival idea...
Film festival!
You like my idea?
Actually,
I have several others...
Don't push your luck!
And... action!
Hello. I'm Bart Simpson.
In the past, I've brought you
such classic films
as Homer in the Shower
and Homer on the Toilet.
And now I give you
The Eternal Struggle.
"Relaxed fit," my Aunt Fanny.
Stupid Dockers.
Oh, the belt is buckled.
Now Maude, in our movie,
you lay baby Moses in the basket
then put it among the reeds.
Okay? Lights! Camera!
A-diddily-doddily-
doodilly-action, Jackson!
Help me-e-e-e-e-e!
Flanders to God,
Flanders to God.
Get off your cloud
and save my Todd!
Yay!
Thanks, God.
Okely-dokely.
What are you doing, Ma?
I'm looking for a film critic
to help judge our festival.
Did you know there are over
600 critics on TV,
and Leonard Maltin's
the best-looking of them all?
Welcome to Coming Attractions.
I'm your host, Jay Sherman.
Thank you.
Tonight, we review
an aging Charles Bronson
in Death Wish Nine.
I wish I was dead. Oy!
But first,
we have a special guest.
Rainer Wolfcastle...
Star of the reprehensible
McBain movies.
Jay, my new film
is a mix
of action und comedy.
It's called
McBain: Let's Get Silly.
Did you ever notice
how men always leave
the toilet seat up?
That's the joke.
You suck, McBain!
And now,
my Woody Allen impression.
"I'm a neurotic nerd
who likes to sleep
with little girls."
Hey, that really sucked!
The film is just me
in front of a brick wall
for an hour and a half.
It cost $80 million.
How do you sleep at night?
On top of a pile of money
with many beautiful ladies.
Just asking. Eesh!
I like him.
He's smart, he's sensitive,
he's clearly not obsessed
with his physical appearance.
My ears are burning.
Uh, I wasn't talking
about you, Dad.
Well, my ears
are really burning.
I wanted to see inside,
so I lit a Q-tip.
Dear Mr. Sherman,
on behalf of the people
of Springfield,
I would like to invite you
to judge our film festival.
You can stay with us
and enjoy the sights and sounds
of the country.
Marge, is this
a pimple or a boil?
Just a minute, Homer.
Oh! Look what
you made me write.
Anyway, we think you'll really
enjoy our quiet little town.
Sincerely, Marge Simpson.
Hmm... do I really
want to leave Manhattan?
Sherman, I just realized,
you insulted me.
Now you will die.
Uh, hey, Nudnick,
your shoe's untied.
From here,
they appear to be tied,
but I will go in
for a closer look.
Taxi!
To the airport!
On closer inspection,
these are loafers.
Attention. The flight
from New York has arrived.
Hey, I'm landing here!
It's supposed to say
Jay's name, not yours.
Oh, you're right.
There you...
Just a second.
- That's it... D'oh!
- Hello.
I'm Marge Simpson,
and this is my husband, Homer.
Oh, nice to meet you, Marge.
I saw your hair
from the plane.
And you must be
the man who didn't know
if he had a pimple or a boil.
It was a Gummi Bear.
Coming up next... The Flintstones
Meet The Jetsons.
Uh-oh. I smell another
cheap cartoon crossover.
Bart Simpson, meet
Jay Sherman, the critic.
Hello.
Hey, man,
I really love your show.
I think all kids
should watch it.
Ew... I suddenly feel so dirty.
I don't know
what's happening.
It seems our profits
have dropped 37%.
I'm afraid we have
a bad image, sir.
Market research shows people
see you as something of an ogre.
I ought to club them
and eat their bones.
Heh-heh. Well, maybe this
film festival could help us.
A film biography might let them
get to know the real you...
Virtuous, heroic, nubile...
You left out pleasant!
But I like
that film biography idea...
A slick Hollywood picture
to gloss over
my evil rise to power
like Bugsy or Working Girl.
- Get me Steven Spielberg.
- He's unavailable.
Then get me his non-union
Mexican equivalent.
Listen Señor Spielbergo,
I want you to do for me
what Spielberg did
for Oskar Schindler.
Schindler es bueno.
Señor Burns es el diablo.
Listen Spielbergo, Schindler
and I are like peas in a pod.
We're both factory owners.
We both made shells
for the Nazis,
but mine worked, damn it.
Now go out there
and win me that festival.
Homer, the guest should get
the last pork chop.
But I'm still hungry.
Mr. Sherman,
I understand you have
two Pulitzer Prizes.
Well, it's not like
I carry them around with me.
Ooh, it's so hot in here.
Oh, look, here's
my People's Choice award.
Five Golden Globes.
Where's my Emmy?
Thank you.
Yeah, well, I won
the belching contest at work.
Very nice, Homer.
Wow, how many
Pulitzer Prize winners
can do that?
Just me and Eudora Welty.
Oh, I invited my sisters over.
Ooh, sisters.
Allow me.
So then I said to Woody Allen,
"Well, Camus can do,
but Sartre is smartre."
So original.
How droll.
Yeah, well,
"Scooby-doo can doo-doo,
but Jimmy Carter is smarter."
Okay, Sherman,
you're a movie expert.
So tell us, who's gay?
Oh, I don't know.
Harvey Fierstein.
- No!
- Who else?
Oh, MacGyver's gay.
You badmouthed MacGyver,
didn't you?
What you doing, Marge?
Making out the jury list
for the film festival.
Mayor Quimby, Krusty, Jay...
Marge, do you respect
my intelligence?
Yes.
Okay. Wait a minute.
Why did it take you
so long to say yes?
No reason.
Okay.
Wait a minute.
Are you humoring me?
Yes.
Okay.
Wait a minute.
That's bad.
Look, I know I'm not witty
like that critic guy,
but does he know all the words
to the Oscar Mayer song?
Oh, I wish I were
an Oscar Mayer wiener.
That is what
I'd truly like to be.
'Cause if I were
an Oscar Mayer wiener.
Everyone would be
in love with me...
That's it, Marge.
He knows
the whole hot dog song.
Go ahead. Sleep with him.
I'll just take
a lock of your hair
to remember you by.
It's just you and me now,
lock of hair.
You don't have
to do this.
Yeah? Well you think
I'm stupid.
I don't think
you're stupid.
Prove it... put me on that
film jury festival thing.
Fine, you're on the jury.
Sir, the actors are here
to audition
for the part of you.
Excellent.
- Next.
- Exc-ell-ent.
- Exactly... D'oh!
- Next.
- Excellente.
Es muy bueno.
Oh, it's hopeless.
I'll have to play myself.
Oh, I thought they were playing
the Rocky Horror Picture Show
tonight.
Our first film
is by Indian director.
Apu Nahassapemapetilan.
Bright Lights, Beef Jerky.
Help! Help! Police!
I got problems
of my own right now.
Oh, boy. This is going to get worse
before it gets better.
Next, we have Moe the Bartender
in Moe Better Booze.
Money gets you.
One more round,
drink it down.
You stupid clown.
Money gets you
one more round.
Then you're out on your ass.
Whoa!
Ah, my back!
This contest is over.
Give that man the $10,000.
This isn't
America's Funniest Home Videos.
But the ball... his groin.
It works on so many levels.
Roll it again.
Next, they're going
to show my movie.
You made a movie?
I made a movie?
No wonder I was on the cover
of Entertainment Weekly.
My name is Barney Gumble.
I'm 40...
I am single...
and I drink.
There's a line in Othello
about a drinker.
"Now a sensible man
"by and by a fool
and presently a beast!"
That pretty well covers it.
It's brilliant.
Savagely honest, tender...
he has the soul of a poet.
You're very kind.
Excuse me. Did something
crawl down your throat and die?
It didn't die.
My name is Barney,
and I'm an alcoholic.
Mr. Gumble,
this is a Girl Scout meeting.
Is it, or is it that you girls
can't admit you have a problem?
Don't cry for me.
I'm already dead.
I think we have
a winner.
What'd I miss?
Homer! Please pay
attention.
There's just
one more movie.
Simple villagers,
I promise you.
I will close plants in America
and bring work here.
Viva, Señor Burns.
Viva! Viva!
Whoa!!
We did 20 takes,
and that was the best one.
Remember, Elliott.
I'll be right here.
- Pure egotism.
- Self-indulgent tripe.
I don't care
what they say.
I'm going to win
this festival.
Drink up, Judah Ben-hur.
You truly are the king of kings.
Excellent.
Smithers,
are they booing me?
Uh, no, they're saying,
"buu-urns, buu-urns."
Are you saying
"boo" or "buu-urns?"
I was saying, "buu-urns."
Alright it's time
to vote for the grand prize.
I vote for Barney Gumble's
sensitive, yet unfortunately
titled film Puke-a-hantas.
- Second.
- Well I vote for Burns's movie.
Me, too.
Now let's get going.
I got a date
with Eudora Welty.
Coming, Eudora.
Excellent.
Bribing those two judges
has paid off
just as it did during
the Miss Teen America pageant.
How can you vote
for Burns's movie?
Let's just say
it moved me...
to a bigger house!
Oops! I said the quiet part loud
and the loud part quiet.
Oh, dear.
Two to two.
Well, Homer,
it all comes down to you.
Football in the groin!
Well, we're not going to resolve
this deadlock any time soon.
Why don't we all take
a five-minute break?
It'll clear our heads.
Good idea, Marge.
My mind is going
a mile a minute.
I knew this
would happen.
I put you on the jury
and you vote
for the stupidest film.
I have every right
to be on that jury
even though I got there
by sleeping with
the head of the festival.
How many times have
I heard Rex Reed say that?
Aw great, now you're going
to make fun of me.
No, Homer, I won't make fun,
but I will suggest that there
may be better things in life
than seeing a man get hit
in the groin with a football.
- Well, Homer?
- Marge...
I've got some
serious thinking to do.
Hmm... Barney's movie
had heart,
but football in the groin
had a football in the groin.
Don't cry for me.
I'm already dead.
Wow. I'll never drink
another beer.
- Beer here!
- I'll take ten.
And now to announce
the winners.
The award for Outstanding
Animated Short goes to:
Itchy and Scratchy
for their film.
Four Funerals and a Wedding.
And now, the winner
of the grand prize.
Barney Gumble.
Homie, you voted
for the right movie.
I'm glad you
were on the jury.
Aw... you know
something, Marge?
It's not that tough
being a film cricket.
I've learned I have a gift
to share with the world.
From now on, there'll be
a new Barnard Gumble...
Hard-working, clean and sober.
Congratulations, Barney,
and enjoy your grand prize...
A lifetime supply
of Duff beer.
Just hook it to my veins!
Good-bye, Mr. Sherman.
If I ever play
Carnegie Hall,
I'll give you a call.
And if you ever want
to visit my show...
Nah, we're not going
to be doing that.
Well, Jay, I hope you tell
your New York friends
that people in small towns
arent quite as dumb as they think.
Marge, look.
This has spring snakes inside,
but the suckers will
think it's beer nuts.
Mmm, beer nuts.
Well, it was a lovely festival.
The best movie won,
and Mr. Burns found
there are some awards
that can't be bought.
And the Oscar goes to...
I've got to win this one.
I bribed everyone in Hollywood.
George C. Scott in
Man Getting Hit by Football.
Arr! My groin!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.