The Simpsons.
Welcome to the 6:00 news
in our brand-new studio.
Looking good, Springfield.
In today's news,
a two-ton rhino
escaped from
the Springfield Zoo,
but zoo officials
were quick to act,
and Petunia, as she is known,
is safely back in captivity.
In other news,
a three-ton rhino
that escaped
from the zoo last week
is still at large.
All right, who broke my vase?
Who took my test papers
off the refrigerator
and tore them up?
Who spread garbage
all over Flanders' yard
before I got
a chance to?
Oh, please. This is
senseless destruction
with none of my usual
social commentary.
If it wasn't you,
then who was it?
Well, I'm sure these things
didn't destroy themselves,
now, did they?
Did they?
Hmm, I guess
Bart's not to blame.
He's lucky, too,
because it's spanking season
and I got a hankering
for some spankering.
I don't know why you're
so energetic today, boy,
but prepare
to be worn out.
What's wrong, boy?
Getting tired?
I think there's
really something wrong
with Santa's
Little Helper.
He was up barking
all night
and dug up the back yard
worse than ever.
My bongo drums!
My strobe light!
My best of Ray Stevens
featuring "The Streak" Album.
So it was the dog
that buried all our stuff.
Yes. The dog.
Oh, my God!
He's got the precious cable TV
cable!
Always use fresh macaroni.
If the box rattles,
throw it away.
Your cable TV
is experiencing difficulties.
Please do not panic.
Resist the temptation
to read or talk to loved ones.
Do not attempt
sexual relations,
as years of TV radiation
have left your genitals
withered and useless.
Well, I'll be damned.
Excuse me. We're having
a problem with our dog.
Lady, I'll tell you what
I'm telling everyone else:
I'm sorry if
your dog went blind
but your gripe is with Hartz Mountain,
not with me.
No! No, our dog
is out of control.
He's wild, destructive
and has little or no respect
for authority.
Hmm. Let me try
a canine-human mind meld.
It's an incredibly rare
psychic power
possessed only by me
and three other clerks
at this store.
Okay.
I'm bored.
I'm restless.
Need change in life.
Like imported leather leash...
Blue contact lenses...
200-volt shock training collar.
Well, problem solved.
Homer, hold on to the wheel!
You've got it.
Hey!
Don't worry. We'll catch him
or run him over trying.
Look, he's headed back
to the greyhound racing track
- where we found him.
- Don't worry,
As soon as they find out
he doesn't have any money,
they'll throw him out.
Believe me, I know.
Ooh, this place is so big.
Do you think
we should split up
and look for him, Homie?
Homie?
Two bucks to win
on number eight.
And have you seen
my beloved dog?
Give me the ticket.
We can't lose!
Look at the name
of the dog I bet on.
"She's The Fastest."
Homer, I don't think
that means necessarily...
And they're off!
She's The Fastest jumps out
to an insurmountable lead.
You're lucky
you got looks, Marge.
As they round the far turn,
it's She's The Fastest
followed by Always Comes in Second
and I'm Number Three.
Yes! Come on, you little horse.
And they're
in the home stretch.
It's... Wait!
Another dog is on the track!
It's Santa's Little Helper!
The mystery dog is gaining
fast on the outside.
Of course,
he could never win this race...
Or could he?
What's Santa's Little Helper
doing to that dog?
Looks like he's trying
to jump over her
but he can't
quite make it.
C'mon boy,
you can do it!
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is the end...
This is the end of dog racing.
I think they're in love.
Aww!
Aw! So that's what's been wrong
with the little fella.
He misses casual sex.
Can we keep
Santa's girlfriend, Mom?
Please?
But she's not our dog.
She's yours now.
Once they fall in love,
they lose their racing spirit.
Won't you miss her loyalty
and companionship?
Lady, you're all right.
Okay, you can go
out and play
but no more you-know-what in
front of the house, all right?
Hey! What did I just say?
Take it.
It fell on the floor.
Hey, boy, you want
to play fetch?
Oh! Me and Santa's Little
Helper used to be a team,
but he never wants
to play anymore
since his bitch moved in.
Bart, don't ever say
that word again!
Well, that's what she is!
I looked it up.
Well, I'm going to write
the dictionary people
and have that checked.
It feels like
a mistake to me.
Hey, look!
A really small dog
just fell out
of Santa's girlfriend!
Oh, my God!
She's having babies!
Oh, I'm sorry, girl.
I thought you were
just getting fat.
- Look! It's twins!
- No, it's two sets of twins.
Two sets of twins
and a triplet.
Homer! Homer, find a place
for all these little miracles.
Oh, my!
I've never seen
anything like this.
How many more can there be?
Twenty-two...
Twenty-three...
Twenty-four...
Twenty-five!
Wow! 25 puppies!
An army of dogs!
No bully will ever
touch me again.
Hey, jerkface.
You have the face
of a jerk.
All right Simpson,
- you asked for it.
- Get him, boys.
Say, Jimbo,
hope I wasn't out of line
with that
"jerkface" crack.
Oh, Homie,
aren't they adorable?
Yes.
We've waited many years,
but the good Lord
has finally blessed us
with a real family.
Look at Branford II.
Isn't that cute?
He thinks he's one
of the Models, Inc.
Get that cat out of the way!
Ah! My socks!
Mom, why do I have
to wear a flea collar?
It's just easier
this way.
This time...
Yeesh.
This house stinks.
You're not just putting
the new newspapers
over the old ones, are you?
Do you have
a better idea?
Now, I know
we love the puppies
very much,
but I think they're getting
to be a problem.
Yeah, they ate all my socks.
I have to wear Lisa's
to school today.
How do you explain
the culottes, boy?
Well, I have to coordinate,
don't I?
Your mother and I
have been thinking
about giving the puppies away.
- No!
- Mainly your mother.
Is that what we do
in this family?
When someone becomes
an inconvenience,
we just get rid of them?
Hello?
Is anybody there?
All right, we'll give
the dogs one more chance.
As long as the puppies
don't do anything else wrong,
they stay.
On a completely unrelated topic
I'm having a very, very
important dinner party tonight.
Splendid. Who's coming?
Reverend Lovejoy,
your old Army drill sergeant,
and the regional director
of the I.R.S.
Oh, just lovely, Marge.
The whole town will hear
what a perfect evening this was.
How nothing at all
went wrong.
Simpson, this evening
has gone so flawlessly,
I'm gonna forget that
you were mistakenly let
out of the army a month early.
I'm so impressed
by this problem-free evening
that there's no need
for that audit.
A toast to the Simpsons.
And to the delectable turkey...
That's walking
around the table?!
Dear Lord, it's a demon bird!
Simpson, see you at reveille
0500 tomorrow.
See you at the I.R.S.
See you in hell.
From heaven.
Well, we sure could use
a pooch to guard the flock
at the Flanderosa.
It would be nice
to have some companionship
when Mother goes out
on dates.
We could use a new pet
over at the home,
seeing how we accidently
killed that smart-mouthed bird.
They don't like
being broken up.
We've got to be
realistic, kids.
Who's going to have
a big enough heart
to take care of 25 puppies?
And I know the little
fellows will love romping around
my many acres,
chasing my many cars,
drinking from
my many toilets.
Who wouldn't?
Mom, don't give
the puppies to him.
He'll be mean to them.
She's right, Homer.
There's something about
his face I don't trust.
Uh... I'm sorry, Mr. Burns,
but you can't have these dogs.
Am I fired?
Hmm? Oh, of course not.
They're your pets.
You can do as you wish.
Good day, everyone.
My, he certainly
took that well.
A little too well,
if you ask me.
I'm sure he's plotting
some brilliant scheme
to get those puppies.
There you go.
You, too.
Honestly, sir,
you just don't put the effort
into your schemes
that you used to.
Er, uh, don't worry, folks.
We'll find your wallet.
Dogs!
Chief, you're
getting powdered sugar
all over my floor.
No, I'm not.
I'm, uh...
dusting for prints.
We don't have to wait
for the cops.
Who can track
the puppies better
than their own mom and dad?
Let's go find your babies.
Dinner's on, dogs!
I'm sorry, kids.
I don't think we're ever going
to find your greyhounds.
Maybe Mr. Burns will sell you
one of the 25 he got last night.
Who knows what horrible things
he's doing
to those innocent
little puppies?
Oh, there.
Now, wasn't that heavenly?
Don't you feel better too?
He's giving them a bath.
There you are.
There you go, little fella.
And you.
Smithers, look.
He's standing up.
I've never seen
anything so adorable.
You know who it
reminds me of?
- Benji?
- No.
- Lassie?
- No, no, no.
A person.
You know who I mean.
Snoop Doggy Dog?
Bob Barker?
David Brenner?
No. No. The person who's
always standing and walking.
Rory Calhoun?
That's it.
You stay with me.
You're the pick of the litter.
Maybe we were wrong
about Burns on this one.
Are you sure you want
to go through with this, sir?
You do have a very full
wardrobe as it is.
Yes... but not completely full.
For you see...
Some men hunt for sport.
Others hunt for food.
The only thing
I'm hunting for.
Is an outfit
that looks good.
See my... vest.
See my vest
made from real.
Gorilla chest.
Feel this sweater.
There's no better
than authentic Irish Setter.
See this hat,
t'was my cat.
My evening wear,
vampire bat.
These white slippers.
Are albino
African endangered rhino.
Grizzly bear underwear.
Turtles' necks,
I've got my share.
Beret of poodle,
on my noodle, it shall rest.
Try my red robin suit.
It comes one breast or two.
See my vest.
Like my...
Loafers, former gophers.
It was that or skin
my chauffeurs.
But a greyhound fur tuxedo
would be best.
So let's prepare
these dogs...
Kill two
for matching clogs.
See my vest.
Oh, please,
won't you see my vest
- I really like the vest.
- I gathered. Yeah.
He's going to make
a tuxedo out of our puppies.
Bart!
Sorry. You got
to admit, it's catchy.
Come on, Smithers.
Let's go finish
the little flea circuses off
except for "Little Monty,"
of course.
We got to get
the dogs out of there.
Hush, puppies!
We got to get
you out of here.
I know. The window.
No, Bart!
What are you doing?
Dogs always land
on their feet.
That's cats.
No. It's dogs.
I'll prove it.
Best two out of three.
Bart, look.
A laundry chute.
Okay, guys.
Let's move.
Come on. Come on.
I got an idea.
Sorry, Monty
but you're too big
for this ride.
- Quick!
- Let's get the...
Going somewhere?
That's impossible.
How did you get here first?
Oh, there'll be plenty of time
for explanations later.
Right now, I'll be taking
my puppies back.
But they're ours.
You stole them from us.
Here's a phone.
Call somebody who cares.
Now, if you'll excuse us,
children,
the pups have a date
with a fashion knife.
There. Now you don't know
which one's little Monty.
I guess if you don't want
him to be part of your tuxedo,
you have to let
the other dogs go, too.
Nice try.
Come on, Little Monty.
Stand up.
Come on. Stand up.
Do your trick.
- No. Don't.
- No.
- Stay down, Little Monty.
- Stay down.
- Don't get up.
- Stay down, boy.
Excellent.
Now, it's...
...simply a matter
of bending down
and picking up the one
and only...
This can't be happening.
They're all standing.
I can't tell them apart.
Well, all right, you win.
- I'll have to kill them all.
- No!
But they're
so wretchedly adorable.
25 little Rory Calhouns.
I can't do it...
But I can kill you.
No. I can't kill you either.
Look at you.
Standing there
on your hind legs
like a couple
of Rory Calhouns.
Well, Mr. Burns, I hope
you've realized the folly
of killing innocent
animals for fashion.
Oh, I have, I have!
I swear I'll never wear
any clothing
made from an animal...
...that can do an amusing trick.
Another victory for Montgomery
Burns's champion greyhound.
25 dogs, 25 world champions,
which, so far,
have earned their owner
over ten million dollars.
I'll bet whoever gave him those dogs
is kicking themselves now.
Homer!
For the love of God, no!
Marge, you know
that batting this light bulb
is the only thing
that cheers me up
after giving away those
million-dollar greyhounds.
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.