In case you were wondering
why I'm so tired...
- I wasn't.
- I was up late
watching French films
in French.
And then, last night,
my dreams were in French!
My dream is you keep moving.
Lisa Simpson,
a bright girl in a dull school.
She likes the sound
a Sharpie makes
when she does well
on a test.
She adores the woody sweetness
of a fresh baritone reed.
But she hates,
more than anything,
finding a place
to eat at lunch.
What was this?
You will soon see.
Frankly, I am redundant.
J. Beardsley.
Jasper!
Suddenly, in the middle
of this crap school,
a mystery!
Meanwhile, for the first time
in his life,
Homer would be disappointed
in a kitchen.
Oh, my God. Leftovers!
Air, nothing,
more air, space, air,
not spaghetti, not meatloaf,
missing chili,
absence of mac and cheese!
There must be some food here.
The devil's trees.
No!
- Homie, relax.
- Okay.
I've decided to be
a Tubberware salesperson.
Tubberware?
Isn't that the thing
where you find people
to host parties
where you then sell everyone
plastic food boxes?
Well, you do
your Kickstarters.
Hey, if people pay
to send me on my tour
of rocking chairs in the
Midwest, that helps everyone.
We really could use the money.
They're still garnishing
your wages
after that garnish war
you waged.
Please, Homie.
I want to open
a checking account
so the family
finally has one.
Marge, no wife of mine
will ever have to work.
Is what men used to say
for some insane reason.
You have my blessing.
Where's Jasper?
He's late again.
Maybe we should feed the birds
without him.
Don't tell me
you fed the birds without me?
You were in a coma!
Mein Gott,
what else happened?
You won't like
who's president.
It's not Bernie?
Lisa returned
Jasper's childhood,
and all she wanted
was her own secret giggle.
Jasper.
Oh, my God.
What do you got there?
A bento box?
Somebody's ashes?
Apple TV?
One more guess,
and I'm gonna need a nap.
When I was six years old,
I brought my treasure box
for show-and-tell.
Another kid took it,
never gave it back.
And now, somehow, it's here.
I've been angry my whole life,
but suddenly,
the world seems magical.
For the first time ever,
Lisa experienced a feeling
that could only be described
as magnifique.
I don't mean to overstate this,
but the sun is shining
a little bit brighter,
because of me!
Tubberware?
I'd love to buy some.
No, you don't buy it now.
You have a party, and then
I sell it to your friends.
No!
You have the party
at your house...
Then, when your friends
fill out the order forms, we...
If you host a Tubberware party,
you get an exclusive gift,
a lemonade pitcher!
Ma'am, if the good Lord wanted
us to store juice in plastic,
he wouldn't have made
a possum's bladder watertight.
Okay, Marge, you're like
a black hole of sadness
and split ends.
What is wrong with you?
I haven't booked
a single Tubberware party.
I don't know why
I thought I could do this.
I don't have that... What's the
Jewish word for chutzpah?
You mean you have
no confidence?
I don't.
I always take the bad pancake.
I spend so much time putting
sunscreen on everyone else,
I get sunburned.
Just like with a doormat,
the key is underneath.
You know what?
I will throw
a Tubberware party for you.
But it's gonna take me
a while to plan.
- How about tonight?
- You're on!
What the heck are you doing?
That's a punchbowl, and
that's for leftover lasagna.
What?! Whoever heard
of leftover lasagna?
Maybe you should
just go to Moe's.
Fine, but I'm not
gonna get drunk.
Oh, okay, sweetie,
I'll get drunk.
I just can't stay sober
at you.
I can't do this.
I can't do this!
Can't? Can't?
Marge, I never want
to hear you use the
C-A-Next-Tuesday word again.
You need to tap
into your female warrior side.
I don't have one of those.
Then we're gonna have
to create one!
Makeover time!
Okay, think pretty thoughts!
Now, get rid of those things
on your feet and put these on.
It changes my whole body.
And what is going on
back there?
Behold, your rump has become
a booty, baby!
Now go out there
and sell some thingies!
Julio,
what is this?
I don't want to sit
through some kind
of sales pitch.
I just want a simple evening
of appetizers,
cocktails and nitrous oxide.
Hello, boys.
I see you're checking out
the merchandise.
Let me assure you,
the lids match the tubs.
You should have told us this
was a drag Tubberware party.
He's the most convincing woman
I've ever seen.
Oh, oh, yes, yes.
He is quite the impersonator.
He calls himself Marge.
Perfect! Marge.
If she were any more camp,
she'd be a Coleman lantern.
All right, boys,
let's put tops on bottoms.
And you wanted to go dancing.
And voilà, a Marge-tini!
But don't worry.
That's not the only surprise
I've got tucked away.
- She's funny.
- Bea Arthur funny?
No one's that funny.
And that night,
Marge sold more Tubberware
than she ever imagined.
And I, drawn by
the farcical premise,
began narrating her story too.
Look at all these orders!
I'm really good at this.
Yeah, well, you see...
Marge is good at this.
Yeah, Marge. Me. I'm Marge.
Okay, so here's
what happened, okay?
This is so important,
I'm gonna drop the accent.
Everyone thought
you were a drag queen.
I felt so pretty,
but the whole time,
people thought
I was a man.
A man who looked like
a fabulous woman!
Drag queens can be very
beautiful. Exhibit, me.
I call myself
Penelope Cruising.
I was Mr. Burns's date
for the Kennedy Center Honors.
See? Look how cute I am.
All his dates have
to give him transfusions.
Now I know why he said
I was his type.
You get it?
Well, the next time,
I'm just going to be myself.
But that was you,
you with confidence.
Oh, you're just being nice.
It was ju! It was ju!
It was ju!
And besides,
the top Tubberware sellers...
they're all drag queens.
What? That can't be true.
So, what do you say, Marge?
Are you in it to win it?
Go for it, Marge!
Who cares if what's outside
doesn't match what's inside?
I'm labeled Lunch Snacks,
but people use me to store pot.
And I'm for storing bread.
All the bread you're gonna make
selling Tubberware.
Did you just high-five
that bowl?
Be cool, Marge. Be cool.
Homer, order anything you like.
It's on me.
Anything.
Okay. I'm gonna need two menus
and four tables.
And get rid
of all this silverware.
- It just slows me down.
- I got it. I got it.
We need help. Someone get Mama
back from bingo.
I am on my way.
But all you need is a G.
You should be like the G
in gnocchi...
Silent!
Oh, Marge, thank you.
Thank you. I'm so happy!
And there it is.
Leftover lasagna.
D'oh!
Lisa still felt
sort of magnifique,
but the magical feeling from
her good deed started to fade.
So she thought...
why not secretly bring magic
into others' lives?
Yes.
Her first project,
restore the lost love
between the identical-looking
Kirk and Luann.
Looks like dying my nose hair's
really paying off!
Next, Lisa helped Gil,
Springfield's Pepé Le Pew,
minus the charm.
Sir, would ya like one?
No, huh? Well, I guess not.
Ma'am? Maybe next time.
Come on! I only get paid
if they're all gone.
And they check the trash,
believe me.
Oh, my God.
People are taking them!
I'm turning the heat on
in my car tonight.
Bart. Wake up.
Bart! I need your help again.
But Lisa's greatest challenge
was to make Mrs. Skinner
believe in her son again.
So Lisa created an imaginary
journal for Seymour,
one that would mend all fences.
I have to get this fake diary
into Skinner's house.
Here's the key.
Here's a floor plan
of the house.
Oh, and here's some tuna.
I'm making his cat really fat.
So Lisa hid the diary
where she knew Mrs. Skinner
would find it...
anywhere a grown man
would expect privacy.
Mother is a great woman.
Seymour loves me!
Oh, my God!
How does a mother apologize
for 50 years
of ridiculing her son?
A gift card now,
and an apology on my deathbed.
Meanwhile, to help perfect
her art and increase business,
Julio took Marge
to Springfield's
hottest drag club,
with its most confusing
bathroom signage.
Marge, this is Queen Chanté,
Barbra Streisman,
the Mysterious Waylon,
and Fiona Adams Apple.
Hello, squirrel-friend.
You're the tallest thing
I ever...
And you're still getting up.
Honey, I spend half my day
getting up
and the other half
getting down.
- Oh-kurr?!
- This is the kind of confidence
that you need.
The secret is to imagine
the fiercest version
of yourself, then realize...
you are that version!
Mel, is that you?
Yes! I've taped my bone
between my legs.
Your Majesty,
can Marge lip-synch with us?
Honey, I'll tell you
what I told Eddie Murphy.
Sure, why not?
So, tell me about
this Marge character.
What is she like?
Well, she's long-suffering,
kind of a single mom...
and that's it.
She's a damn hero,
is what she is, sis.
You've got all eyes on you
A nasty housewife lady
Come out of your mom shell
And become a bombshell
You've got this, Margie
You're stronger
than you know
Get up and dance
Get up, get up and
Sashay with Chanté
Work that blue bouffanté
Do it, do it
All the boys say
Women can have it all.
Even penises!
She's so chic
Such savoir faire
Serving housewife realness
Selling Tubberware
She's a female phenomenon
And much more than a mom
So sexy, so snuggable
Her cocoa is so chuggable
Our blue duck
has become a swan
She's a Glamazon
Sashay with Chanté
Work that blue bouffanté...
Oh, hi, Helen.
Hi, Marge.
I heard you're selling
Tubberware.
Money troubles at home?
Why are you so bitter, Helen?
Is it because your husband would
rather play with his toy train
than with you?
All aboard!
Not Helen!
You better beware, Bart.
Mom just grew a backbone.
You mean it, Mother?
You'll finally let me take
karate lessons?
I'll even buy you a gi.
Oh, I won't have
to wear pajamas?
Only at bedtime,
which I'm moving to
after The Big Bang Theory.
Bazinga!
All seemed well,
but like Young Sheldon,
it would not last forever.
Oh, hello, Mother. Karate
is so much better than I ever...
Seymour! I knew
this journal was a lie!
How would you know that?
Seymour never uses semicolons.
He says they make him queasy.
I don't even keep a journal.
I have no inner thoughts.
I planted that journal.
I'm sorry.
I did it so you'd
be nicer to your son.
Nicer?! I spoiled
the little loser!
But not anymore.
I'm so sorry.
Oh, my God, that poor girl.
Go to her, Seymour.
Give her an A.
The teachers' union forbids me
from giving out
anything more encouraging
than a pumpkin sticker.
You're a disgrace
to that yellow belt!
Look at me, boys!
I'm living off my wife
like Mr. Meryl Streep!
Don Gummer.
Homer, do you know exactly
what Marge is up to?
Because, we know, and
we've told everybody except you.
Like true friends.
What's going on?
If you want to know the truth,
- go to this address.
- That's the address of this bar.
That's right.
Get really drunk,
then go to this address.
Hello. Are you on the list?
I have to be on the list
for a Tubberware party?
Well, you do for this one.
Marge is like if Donna Reed
and Donna Summer combined
to solve all your
food storage problems.
And rumor has it, out of drag,
Marge is hot, hunky and all man.
My wife is none of those things!
She leaves the room to burp!
Marge! You didn't tell me
you're tricking all these people
into thinking you're a drag queen,
when you're really
a regular housewife in need
of empowerment, and now...
that I say it out loud,
it doesn't seem so bad.
She's not a female impersonator.
- She's just a personator.
- Women co-opt everything.
Good to see
another couple in trouble.
- Let's go, Dewey.
- I'm not leaving
till I find my butter tub.
Look in the mirror.
Kids,
please give us a moment.
You're cool.
Marjorie,
I'm not a perfect man,
but I like to think
I've evolved.
I've accepted
the several different actors
who played Batman.
I now believe cats
should earn as much as dogs.
I don't want to hear
your stupid speech.
I had a moment of confidence,
and now it's destroyed.
I'm going out.
You can watch the kids
and wonder where I am.
No. I don't want anything
to do with him.
Lisa, are you okay?
I tried to play God,
and like the real God,
it went horribly wrong.
Life was a struggle
for the Simpson women.
Even Maggie.
But where there is life,
there is hope.
That was the beginning
of a new day, a wonderful day,
a day that would soon change
the Simpson women forever.
Read the tots.
Go to the roof?
Enjoy.
Next!
Aw, man!
Lisa, would you
join us for lunch?
We decided to bring some magic
into your life.
Ah, you deserve it, sweetie.
You're the only person
in this town who thinks about
someone other than herself.
The only person who would listen
to old Gil when he...
She had finally found
her place to eat lunch.
But what is this? Has Homer
lost his will to drink?
Homer, we're sorry
we razzed ya.
We were just trying
to hurt your feelings.
I am so sorry.
I don't know what I can do.
Nothing you can do.
Change your name,
glue on a wig and find
yourself a new woman.
That's it!
Moe, you're a genius!
Wish me luck.
Why do people always stride out
without paying their tab?
I have no idea.
But as God is my witness,
I will find out!
You two stay right there.
Everyone, I have
two enormously sad things
I feel a need
to tell all of you.
Number one,
I've deceived you.
I'm not a drag queen.
Girl, you didn't deceive nobody.
We all knew.
I didn't know,
but I'm super self-involved.
Now number two.
And, as always
happens in such matters,
number two is the kicker.
My husband and I have had
more than the usual
number of scrapes,
but we've always
gotten back to our love.
But this time,
you all made me feel
understood and supported,
and therefore made me realize
how selfish Homer is.
Oh, honey.
And what hurts the most
is that I can't imagine
there's anything he can say
or do to make me come back.
Well, then I went through
a lot of work for nothing.
- Homie.
- Honey, I understand it now.
The feeling of power,
the mystery,
wondering...
is she or isn't she?
Hey, believe me,
nobody is wondering, baby.
If you don't go to him,
Marge, I will.
And he will never leave
my kitchen.
My pulled pork banh mi
keeps baby in the cradle.
Oh, Homie, I love you!
When we're out there
dancing...
Having a man dressed
like a woman
to win back his woman
who pretended to be
a man dressed like a woman
is the most romantic thing
I've ever seen.
And so all was well.
Au revoir
jusqu'à la prochaine fois,
or in English...
Bye!
So, are you a...
you're a drag queen now?
I don't know. I guess these days
it's okay for everyone
- to be everything.
- So, miss, are you alone?
It's me, Homer!
All the good ones
are either married or Homer.