CHORUS [SINGS]:
The Simpsons
Brake My Wife, Please
D'oh! Ah!
Okay, kids, stay together.
I appreciate you helping us out
with this field trip.
Oh, a mom's work is never done.
Hmm, I thought I was being kicked
exceptionally hard lately.
If I could be any type of shark,
I'd be a tiger shark.
- How about you, Milhouse?
- I guess a nurse shark.
I mean... Oh! Ow, ow!
[ROARS]
Well, looks like Mr. Walrus
and his family...
...are enjoying their Sunday brunch.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Shut up. What am I,
some sort of joke to you people?
Now, over here is our newest exhibit,
Wonders of the Gulf Coast.
ALL:
Ooh!
Shut up. It's not that exciting.
The gulf is home to a breathtaking array
of sea life.
But oil spills
are threatening its delicate ecosystem.
[ALL GASPING]
Hey, without oil, you wouldn't have
your fancy four-wheel drives.
You want to go back
to two-wheel drive?
Well, do you?
[CHUCKLES]
I didn't mean to steal focus.
MAN [ON MONITOR]: Antarctic
life is a constant struggle.
These sea lions survive
by eating the leftovers...
...of the various film crews
that plague the continent.
[GROANS]
Hmm...
[BLEATING]
[GASPS]
This tank is for our Pacific Habitat,
which is currently being remodeled.
Where do you keep the fish
till it's done?
Oh, they're well taken care of
in our storage facility.
In this tank...
...we see some of the most
exotic species of the coral reef.
Look, that giant clam
appears to be opening.
This could be
a wonderful journal entry.
[CHILDREN GASPING]
Look at the size
of those flawless pearls.
[HUMMING]
[CHILDREN LAUGHING]
Oh, I might have known. But I didn't.
Bart, get out of there.
[BART GRUNTING]
- My boy. Will he be all right?
- This kind of injury is routine.
[HIBBERT CHUCKLING]
Bart will be up and underachieving
in no time.
All I need is your insurance card.
Hmm, my husband has our card.
No problem.
Now, you stay shackled to that radiator
until you come up with some insurance.
[CHUCKLES]
Well, it's 11 a.m. on a workday,
so he must be at that stupid bar.
[PHONE DIALING]
Is my husband there?
I don't think he's here.
Uh, hang on. Let me check.
[GRUNTS]
Nope.
What you wearing?
[LINE DISCONNECTS]
[SIGHS]
Okay, five more minutes
and I'm chewing my hand off.
- Bart, are you okay?
- Oh, Homie, where have you been?
- I've been calling all over for you.
- Hey, take it easy.
I went to the video store
to rent a movie for the family.
[HOMER HUMMING]
MAN [ON TV]: He's got a nose for news...
HOMER: Hmm.
...and a diaper full of headlines.
- Hey, chief.
MAN: He's editor-in-chimp.
[LAUGHING]
That monkey's wearing a hat.
WOMAN[ON TV]: Lifetime Films
presents Buttercups of Autumn.
I fear I have become
a buttercup of winter.
Hush up, Nana. That's fool talk.
[SOBBING]
[MONKEY GIBBERING]
[LAUGHING]
[SOBBING]
Nana, she's so wise...
...but no one's gonna benefit
from her wisdom.
[MONKEY GIBBERS
AND HOMER LAUGHS]
Look, he's misspelling words.
WOMAN: Nana.
- [SOBBING] Oh, she's so...
Well, from now on, you need to get
a cell phone so I can reach you.
You just can't get a cell phone.
Lindsay Naegle, Veriqual Cellular.
And I can offer you a whole range
of cellular solutions.
Can I get a phone
that plays the Mexican hat dance?
I insist on it.
[MEXICAN RINGTONE PLAYING
OVER PHONE]
[SINGING]
I dance, I dance, I dance
Around the Mexican hat
And that's the end of that
Or is it? I guess I'll keep singing
My cell phone appears to be ringing
[CAR HORN HONKS]
MAN:
Hey!
Barney, you ever notice how hard it is
to drive with your knees?
Why don't get
one of those hands-free phones?
It's the next best thing
to paying attention to the road.
Hands-free, eh?
Then I could give the brothers
the black-power salute.
Black power, black power.
Was that Al Roker?
His exuberance is perplexing.
We have headsets,
but you'd be mad to stop there.
Tell me, what is currently plugged
into your car's cigarette lighter?
- Uh, a lighter.
- I weep for you.
These days, everything from
fax machines to coffeemakers...
- ...can be plugged into your dash hole.
- I'll take them.
DVD player, check.
Snow-cone machine, check.
Lite-Brite, check.
Fog machine...
Even I think this is crazy.
[SCRATCHES]
[RAPPING]
Chaka Khan, let me rock you
Let me rock you
Chaka Khan, Chaka Khan
Whisk the egg whites
into the batter mixture...
...while scraping the edges
with a very stiff rubber spatula.
Now let's look in
on our hush puppies.
[HOMER HUMMING]
Ah.
[GRUNTING]
[GASPS]
Oh, my God. I gotta do something.
[BEEPING]
Come on, transmit.
Transmit.
Save me, Chaka Khan, Chaka Khan!
[SPUTTERS THEN COUGHS]
Oh, I'll never mock
the Coast Guard again.
You Navy rejects are all right.
Mr. Simpson, give me your license.
[GROANS]
[DOGS GROWLING]
Burn their poop.
I am so screwed.
I can't drive to work.
I can't drive to the store.
And I certainly can't drive
to the store at work.
[SIGHS]
I guess I'll have to do
all your driving chores.
That's what a good wife does,
picks up the slack.
That reminds me. We gotta pick up my
slacks at that dry cleaner in Shelbyville.
Why can't you use
the local dry cleaner?
Uh, I didn't want him to know my size.
[GROANS]
Thanks for picking my friends up
from the strip club, Marge.
- Can we stop for ice cream?
- Homer always stops for ice cream.
- We'll see.
- That always means no.
[GROANS]
Where's your mother?
I gotta get to Moe's.
Dad, Mom's been driving
everyone everywhere.
Why don't you take
public transportation?
Public transportation
is for jerks and lesbians.
Oh, I guess I'll walk.
Stupid walking.
Thighs chafing horribly.
No drink holder.
I miss my car so much.
Everyone's driving but me.
I can't drive 55
because it only goes 38.
- I let go of the parking brake.
- [PANTING] Ralphie, if you stop...
...I'll let you play with my gun.
[HUMMING]
I did it.
I walked all the way to Moe's
from my house.
BART:
Way to go, Dad.
You know, I feel pretty good.
Maybe I should just keep walking
instead of going into a dark, dreary bar.
Get in here, boozy.
You're late for your drunkening.
No. From now on, walking is my beer
and feeling good is my hangover.
Hmph.
Huh. Hey, maybe this is a sign.
Maybe it's time
to get out of the alcohol business...
...give barber college another try.
And this time, I won't join a frat.
Who the hell am I talking to?
You know,
all this walking is paying off.
Look how healthy I am.
You see? I'm finally thin enough
to wrap this thing around my arm.
Good for you, Dad.
Could you get me some syrup?
Mm, mm.
You see? Before I probably
would've driven to the syrup.
Kids, hurry up and eat. We have to leave
for the dentist five minutes ago.
[BART GRUNTING]
We don't have time for choking.
Calm down, Stresserella.
Unh, I'm stressed because now
that you've lost your license...
...I'm a full-time family chauffeur.
Now, now, honey,
we all appreciate what you do.
But real chauffeurs
have uniforms and licenses.
You could get in a lot of trouble
with the Livery Commission.
To hell with the Livery Commission.
You don't know what you're saying.
What a day for a stroll.
MAN: Come on!
WOMAN: What are you doing...?
[CHATTERING]
Seymour, the two of us
could make good use of this time.
Indeed. You take this
teacher-evaluation test.
I'll proctor. Read the directions silently
as I read them aloud to you.
Look at those suckers
in their metal coffins.
I can go to work any way I want.
[WHISTLES]
Psst. Bishop to queen four.
We're playing dominoes.
I said bishop to queen four.
All right, all right, you.
[WHISTLING]
[GRUNTS]
Simpson, you're a menace.
Oh, George, leave the boy be.
Martha, I want a divorce.
Oh, George,
you've made me so happy.
[HOMER HUMS]
You're the first one here. Please accept
this free ticket to the 1939 World's Fair.
Thanks, Mr. Burns.
I owe it all to walking.
Walking, eh? Let me give it a try.
[GRUNTS]
- Whoa!
- Huh!
Well, I'd better drag myself
to the hospital.
[GRUNTING]
Oh, dear.
Smithers, scoop me up.
How could you both miss the bus
to school?
We touched hands.
Then we had to wash the cooties off.
[GROANS]
[RUSTLES]
What's all that rustling?
My show-and-tell project.
A Peruvian fighting frog.
Hey, I brought
a Peruvian fighting frog.
[BOTH CROAKING]
[GRUNTING]
When will they stop?
Come nightfall.
How about we take a family walk
around the block?
- Yay! I wanna amble.
- I wanna saunter.
- Amble.
- Saunter.
Stop saying things.
Honey, you seem frazzled.
Why don't you come with us?
Hey, I'd like that.
Oh, I can't.
I have to go pick up Grampa.
He proposed to another hooker
at the bus station.
[CHUCKLES]
You sure love driving.
Mm-hm.
[HUMMING]
Morning, Homer. Looking good.
Walking has made
a new man out of you.
It sure has.
You see this bulge back here?
Now it actually is a fanny pack.
Unh, no, wait. It's still my ass.
But your point is well taken.
You see...
[SINGING]
I like to walk down the avenue
Bust a move with Disco Stu
You shake me from my booty
To my 'fro
Yes, I strut down the boulevard
Burning off my excess lard
I rarely feel the
need to utter "d'oh"
- Top of the morning, ladies.
- Bite us.
I can walk from
Springfield to Alaska
Then hobnob with the stars in Malibu
Hi, Homer. I'm actor Steve Buscemi.
The guy who got fed
into the wood chipper in Fargo?
- And when I hear...
BOTH: You can't walk to Turkmenistan
I say, of course, I can
Screw you
Hey, would you guys like tickets
to the Independent Film Awards?
[IN UNISON]
Would we?
Oh, I love to perambulate
It's standing still I really hate
So let me please
reiterate, I love to...
[TIRES SQUEAL
THEN HOMER SCREAMS]
[GASPS]
Oh, my feet are inside me.
I am so sorry, Homie.
How is your crushed pelvis?
Pretty good. Thanks for asking.
I don't know what happened.
I saw you and I went for the brake...
...but I hit the accelerator.
It's okay, Marge.
It would've been worse if I hadn't
been carrying this Bible in my crotch.
Marge, while Homer recuperates...
...I'm afraid you'll have to do everything
for him.
That's okay.
I can handle it.
Homie, why don't you just relax
and have a little soup?
- Aah! Too hot. Too hot.
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Aah! Hot. Hot. Hot.
Warm. Tepid. Cool.
Cold. Cold. So cold.
Oh, you're really coming along,
Homie.
Yeah. The doctor says
that soon my pelvis...
...will actually be stronger
and more beautiful than ever.
Gee, everything always works out
for you.
[HOMER GRUNTS]
Aah! Oh, my God. Let me help you up.
Marge, you're trying to hurt me.
What? That's crazy.
No, it's true. The car, the soup.
It's like you hate me,
your own husband.
That's ridiculous. I don't like you.
I mean hate you, hate you, hate you.
I hate you!
I've heard that from coworkers,
strangers on the street...
...even my own children.
But I never thought
I'd hear it from you.
Maybe we should see a counselor.
Who's we?
Got a mouse in your purse?
Manjula, I'm so glad you have finally
forgiven me for having an affair.
[GRUNTS]
She used to elbow me in the face.
[CHUCKLES]
Next, please.
I've been married to my husband
for 10 years...
...and part of me wants to kill him.
Perhaps you feel that your husband
sees you as less of a partner...
...and more of a doormat?
Nothing could be further from the...
You could be onto something there.
[HOMER DROOLING]
What? Oh, sorry,
I got a lot on my mind.
That's okay. Take your time.
All right, before you came in,
I asked you each...
...to make a list of the people
that are most important to you.
- Homer, you first.
- There's Homer...
...Homer J. Simpson,
and Commander Cool, a.k.a. me.
That's us in a nutshell.
I care so much about you, Homer.
But I'm not even on your list.
Excuse me.
We gotta help her.
If Marge isn't happy, I'm not happy.
And if I'm not happy,
Moe is very happy.
But for once, this isn't about Moe.
What should I do, Dr. Hotdog?
All right, I have an answer.
You must perform for her
one completely unselfish gesture.
You mean, like give her full custody
of the kids?
Yeah, full custody.
That's exactly what I...
- You're an idiot.
- Unh.
You gotta knock her off her feet
with something utterly romantic.
Something that says,
"I care about you."
I see. Do you have any suggestions?
- I do. But the hour's over.
- Here's a dollar.
- Romantic dinner.
- Gotta go.
You know what Mom really loves?
Julienne potatoes.
And for dessert, peach crumble.
You wanna know how to make a peach
crumble? Kick it in the groin. Ha!
Anyway, what's going on?
I'm gonna treat Marge
to a romantic dinner...
...to make up for all my shortcomings.
Hey, Homer, if you're having a banquet
for Marge, I'd like to help.
Hey, me too.
I can whip up my famous...
...poulet au vin avec champignons
à la Carl. Mwah.
You can bring a bag of ice.
Lousy Homer. I'll show him.
Tonight, his beloved mock apple pie
will have real apples.
Wha...?
[GASPS]
Oh, my God. It's so beautiful.
Hey, look, everybody, Marge is here.
[ALL CHEERING]
Oh, Homie.
You got everyone in Springfield
here for me.
Honey, I couldn't keep them away
if I tried, except for Flanders.
He was mysteriously
called out of town.
[CHUCKLES]
I got your letter.
I'm coming as fast as I can.
Tonight, we're here to serve you.
Sit back and enjoy the finest foods
Springfield has to offer.
I brought you me finest catch
of the day.
We lost a dozen good men.
But it's worth it just to see ye smile.
Wow!
That's it, eh?
Twelve men.
Well, I've got some families to inform.
- Unbelievable...
- What?
Nothing.
Just a curse on your very soul.
Marge, I bring you the main course.
Elektra recording artist-
slash-political activist...
...Jackson Browne.
Oh, the Pretender.
When Homer told me about this special
night, I just had to be a part of it.
I'm here to serenade you with a song.
ALL:
Yay!
From my latest album.
SKINNER: Oh, no.
ALL: Oh.
Just kidding.
Here's one of my many classics.
That I fixed with new words.
[PLAYING PIANO]
[SINGING]
You hooked up in high school
Now you've come so far
Then you started to hate him
And hit him with your car
So I threw you a fancy banquet
And now you can't stay mad
How about a make-up snuggle?
It would be so rad
Oh, I'm really touched
by how much you care.
I love you too.
So, uh, you don't wanna kill me
anymore?
- Only with kisses.
- Oh.
Oh, don't be a wuss.
JACKSON [SINGING]:
When you turn out the light
I've got to hand it to me
It looks like it's me and you
again tonight Marjorie
[CROWD CHATTERING]
[BAND PLAYING
SOFT INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC]
[HOMER CLEARS THROAT]
Now I'd like to propose a toast to
a woman who's done so much for us...
- ...without getting anything in return.
- Except a place to live and free food.
Why, you little...
[BOTH GRUNT]
Now let's all raise our wine boxes...
...to Marge.
ALL:
Hear, hear! To Marge!
Unh, I'm so full,
my control-top panel is in shards.
[SIGHS]
I wanna thank you all so much.
You're welcome.
And now, Marge, we cooked, you clean.
- What?
- Ha, ha, only teasing.
We've flown in the finest busboys
from France... Uh, I mean, America.
[ALL SPEAKING IN FRENCH
THEN LAUGHING]
And now to all my dear friends,
I say, get the hell out of my yard.
[CROWD GRUNTING
AND CHATTERING]
WOMAN:
Shh.
[English - US -SDH]