♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
(glass shattering)
-(chortling)
-(applause)
Please, Krusty,
this is very demeaning.
Shut up and conduct!
(chittering)
("Blue Danube waltz")
(chitters)
-(screaming)
-(all monkeys screeching)
-(gnawing)
-(groaning)
(laughing)
Maggie, can you point
to the monkey?
(blows raspberry)
What do babies know?
Maggie, can you point
to the credenza?
-D'oh!
-MARGE: Homer, you didn't do
a very good job frosting
Maggie's birthday cake.
What? It's not
"Magaggie's" birthday?
Oh.
(chewing loudly)
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Stop it!
I made a special cake
for you to ruin.
-It's over there.
-Ooh.
-(chews loudly)
-(doorbell rings)
Hello, everyone,
except Homer.
Happy birthday,
granddaughter.
Marge, I think that's your
father-in-law across the street.
Happy birthday!
Everybody get ready.
Here comes
the birthday girl
in her very first
dress.
ALL: Aww!
She's a little angel.
Yeah. I wanna put a hook in her
and hang her from our Christmas tree.
What smells?
Uh-oh.
Shouldn't we wait for the other babies
before we open the presents?
We didn't invite
the other babies.
Maggie doesn't seem to get
along with the other babies.
MARGE: Maggie, we have
a surprise for you!
(whimpering)
(shutters clicking)
(whimpers)
Ooh, put some Lister's Carbolic Unguent
on a wad of cotton.
Put the cotton
in her ear.
That'll stop them shakes.
No, no. What she needs
is a Balsam Specific.
Balsam Specific!
Oof-- While we're
burning money,
why don't we give her a curative
galvanic belt too?
(raspy voice) Don't forget
to give her Smeckler's powder.
BOTH:
Don't make fun.
I remember Lisa's
third birthday.
She and Bart did this adorable
little song and dance routine.
Oh! (laughs)
That was a real
horn-honker!
-Let's see it.
-(Bart groans)
Now! Do it!
(both groaning)
Do it!
♪ Hot dogs,
Armour hot dogs ♪
Sing it like you mean it!
♪ What kinds of kids
eat Armour hot dogs ♪
-♪ Fat kids ♪
-♪ Skinny kids ♪
♪ Kids who climb
on rocks ♪
-♪ Tough kids ♪
-♪ Sissy kids ♪
♪ Even kids
with chicken pox ♪
ALL: ♪ Love hot dogs ♪
♪ Armour hot dogs ♪
♪ The dogs kids
love to ♪
(off-key)
♪ Bite ♪
Doesn't this family
know any songs
that aren't
commercials?
ALL: ♪ I feel like
chicken tonight ♪
♪ Like chicken tonight,
like chicken tonight ♪
(sighs)
It's been great spending time
with my family again.
I guess the next time I see you
won't be until Thanksgiving.
Or if not then,
Christmas.
I suppose I'll
be getting home too.
At least I got
Matlock to keep me company.
D'oh! He's on
in five minutes!
He is? Step on it!
(tires screech)
OLD MAN: Hurry up! Hurry!
Each Matlock
could be our last.
Homie, you know
it's funny,
both my mother and your father
seem pretty lonely.
(giggles)
That is funny.
Yeah. Anyway, maybe they could
go to a matinee together,
or shopping,
or to that room in the library
that's always full
of old people--
Periodicals, that's it!
Marge, please, old people
don't need companionship.
They need to be
isolated and studied,
so it can be determined
what nutrients they have
that might be extracted
for our personal use.
Homer, would you please stop
reading that Ross Perot pamphlet?
Oh!
Say, I've got
a neat idea.
Why don't you go in
and pick up my mother,
and we'll go out to dinner?
I'll be back
in a jiffy!
That's not my mother.
I'll be back
in a jiffy!
Can I come too?
Oh.
(electrical buzzing)
You know, Mom, you and Abe
have a lot in common.
Um-- Hmm.
You both got swindled
by that telemarketing scam.
Oh, it's not a swindle.
What you do is, see,
you give them all
your credit card numbers,
and if one of them is lucky,
they'll send you a prize.
I was just happy to talk
to someone on the phone.
Aw, feelin' blue, eh?
I got somethin'
that'll cheer you up.
(grunts)
(humming)
-(wheezy laugh)
-(humming continues)
Hmm?
Sir, I represent the estate
of Charles Chaplin.
I have a court order
demanding an immediate halt
to this unauthorized
imitation.
-Boys!
-(both grunting)
And here's a picture
of me getting arrested
for indecent exposure.
It was the most embarrassing day
of my life.
(Grampa whistles)
Lift those gams!
You were one
nifty number.
The boys all paid attention
to me
and it drove
my friends crazy.
Oh, who were
your friends?
Oh, Zelda Fitzgerald,
Frances Farmer,
and little Sylvia Plath.
You know, you remind me of
a poem I can't remember
and a song that may
never have existed
and a place I'm not sure
I've ever been to.
You're so sweet.
Ooh, I feel all funny.
(gasps)
I'm in love!
No, wait,
it's a stroke.
-(sirens blaring)
-GRAMPA: No, wait, it is love!
I'm in lo-o-o-o-ve!
(car horns honking)
-(applause)
-Hello, I'm Troy McClure.
You might remember me
from such films as
"The Boatjacking
of Supership 79"
and "Hydro: The Man
with the Hydraulic Arms".
Coming up this hour on
the Impulse Buying Network,
your chance to own
a piece of Itchy and Scratchy,
the toontown twosome
beloved by everyone--
Even cynical members
of Generation X.
(scoffs)
Yeah, "groovy."
Troy, I'm proud to offer
your viewers
these hand-drawn
Itchy & Scratchy animation cels.
Each one is absolutely,
positively, 100% guaranteed
to increase in value.
ANNOUNCER:
Not a guarantee.
Whoo!
-(grunts)
Pardon me, sir.
Forgive my clumsiness.
Not at all.
-(chuckling)
Uh, yes, my name
is Homer Simpson.
And I'd like to order
an Itchy & Scratchy cel.
My credit card?
Uh, do you accept the
"Federal Breast Inspector's" card?
"License to Ogle"?
"Vyza"?
Oh, yes, of course.
That's what I meant, "Visa."
It's these new dentures.
(all chomping food loudly)
Well, I think it's wonderful
that your father
has fallen in
love with my mother.
Well, I'm opposed
to the whole thing--
Damn opposed!
He's damn opposed.
Damn, damn, damn opposed.
Bart!
Homer, what possible
reason could you have
against Grampa
being in love?
If he marries your mother, Marge,
we'll be brother and sister!
And then our kids,
they'll be horrible freaks
with pink skin, no overbites
and five fingers on each hand!
(screams)
-(line ringing)
-Hello, Mom?
Fine. You know Abe had
a very nice time with you last Sunday.
Tell her I love her!
Grampa, shh!
I know my mother.
If you come on too strong,
she's going to get scared away.
-I love ya.
-What?
Uh, I love ya, mom.
-I love ya. I love ya.
I love ya, mom.
Gotta go.
(doorbell rings)
Yeah, hi. I got a special
delivery for Homer Simpson.
That's me!
(groans)
Don't write no more
letters to Mr. Sinatra.
(doorbell rings)
I've got a special delivery
for Homer Simpson.
Uh, that's me.
(groans)
Stop stealing golf balls
from the driving range.
-(doorbell rings)
-(moans)
MAN: Homer Simpson,
I've got a, uh,
special delivery
for you.
Go away.
If you do not open
the door, Mr. Simpson,
I cannot give you your...
special delivery.
(sighs)
Here's your
special delivery.
-Thanks. (groans)
-That's for keepin' me waiting.
Hey, Lis, guess
who's got a genuine
Itchy & Scratchy
animation cel?
Oh! That is so cool!
That is so exciting!
That is so--
Crappy.
It looks like part
of Scratchy's arm.
Oh, no. I used Dad's
credit card to buy this?
-Yeesh! How much was it?
-$350.
- Ooh.
-Ha-ha!
-(weakly) Ha, ha, ha.
-Oh, my God.
This boy is having
an out-of-body experience.
This is very...
bad for business.
Hot diggity!
I'm gonna smooch her like
a mule eating an apple!
(licking, kissing noises)
I even bought me some
special novelty dentures.
See?
Dad, that will never work.
If you wanna make your move,
you gotta play it cool.
(jazzy singsong)
Now, what you gotta do,
if you wanna get a kiss,
is act real smooth
and make your move like this.
-(yawns)
-Oh, I see.
So, if I take
your advice
and make your
patented move,
then my chances for love
will slightly improve.
(yawns)
(giggles)
Now what's that rule?
Play it cool.
(doorbell rings)
(screams)
(big band music plays)
Is this cel
worth anything?
(sighs) Let me
show you something.
This-- This is a Snagglepuss
drawn by Hic Heisler.
It is worth something.
This-- This is an arm
drawn by nobody.
It is worth nothing.
Can't you give me
anything for it?
I can give you this telephone.
It is shaped like Mary Worth.
-(groans)
-No groaning in my store.
("Moonlight Serenade" plays)
Oh, my favorite song.
This is so nice.
I can't remember
when I felt this young.
Oh! I really can't.
-Oh.
-MR. BURNS: Say, sport.
Mind if I have
the next dance?
Wha-- D'oh! What the--
Don't sneak up
on a-- Oh, you!
No need for the blown
gasket, Charlie.
I'll have her back
in one piece.
("Sing, Sing, Sing")
Hey!
(growls) That big ape thinks
he can muscle in
on my girl, does he?
I'll show him.
I'm gonna give him
the frowning of a lifetime.
(grunts)
(Mr. Burns laughing)
-(wheezing)
-(laughs)
I swear, Monty.
You are the devil himself.
I-- Who told you?
Oh, yes, yes, well.
I'd say you were
an angel, but
angels don't
dance like that.
-Oh!
-(laughs)
(grumbles)
(groans)
Good night, Mrs. Bouvier,
wherever you are.
(groans)
Mr. Simpson, I represent
the estate of Jimmy Durante.
I have a court order demanding
an immediate halt
to this unauthorized
imitation. Boys!
(growling)
Well, would it be
all right with you
if I just laid down
in the street and died?
(papers rustling)
MAN: Yes, that
would be acceptable.
Smithers, guess what
happened to me last night?
I don't know, sir.
You had sex with that
old woman?
She said "no" to me.
Do you know how many
women have said "no" to me?
130-- But only one since
I've become a billionaire.
And she's the one
for me. I'm in love!
-Whoop-dee-do, sir.
-Yes, whoop-dee-do.
Whoop-dee-do to the world!
Whoop-dee-do, Mr. Florist.
Whoop-dee-do,
Mr. Physical trainer.
Whoop-dee-do, Mr. President.
I'm happy you've
finally found love.
Whoop-dee-do,
tarantula town.
Whoop-dee-do, employees.
BURNS: Everyone who's found
true love may leave early today.
(cheering)
HOMER:
All right!
(sniffles, sobs)
"Memorandum to Mrs. Bouvier.
Re: Delineation of romantic intentions."
(scoffs)
Too sappy.
Smithers, come over here
and help me write
a mash note to my girlfriend.
Fine.
Darling one: Read my words
and hear my heart
speak of a love,
soft and undying.
A love that will
be with you always.
Sincerely,
yada-yada-yada.
That's marvelous.
How did you think
of that so fast?
I... sent it to you
on your birthday.
(sniffles) Excuse me.
I have something in my eye.
Hmm.
Mom's almost ready
for her date.
She sure seems taken
by this new beau.
I feel so bad
for Grampa.
Dad says this new guy is a repulsive,
obnoxious old billionaire.
So, let's all
be extra nice to him.
(doorbell rings)
-(screaming)
-Hello.
Why, it's--
It's, uh--
Oh, it's, uh--
(whispers)
-Ah.
-(snickers)
Why it's Fred Flintstone
and his lovely wife, Wilma.
Oh, and this must be
little Pebbles.
Mind if I come in?
I brought chocolates.
Yabba dabba do!
He's an awful, awful,
awful man.
I guess if he makes Mom happy,
that's all that really matters.
That's right, "money."
Your "money's" happiness
is all that "moneys."
-(exhales)
-Hmm.
Hi. You know, Grandma
really likes it
when her boyfriends
are nice to me.
She especially likes it
when they give me money.
Run along, peewee.
Baby gets nothing.
Very well, you leave me
no choice.
This gun
is filled with ketchup.
This one with mustard.
Now give me $350 bucks
or you're gonna be a mess
for your date.
You don't have
the guts.
(growls)
(yells) Here.
Take your money. Take it.
Ooh! Now, the tables
have turned, haven't they?
GRANDMA:
Monty, I'm ready.
-Hmm?
-Ooh.
Oh, why'd she
have to leave me?
Hi, Abe.
We heard you was in need
of some cheering up.
So we got you
a special cake.
(woman coughing)
Uh-oh. Better call
the nurse.
Bravissimo, Luigi.
Bring us your
finest bottle of vino.
Hey, you trust Luigi.
He knows what for to make-a
really nice the amore.
Monty, I've never been to a more
romantic restaurant.
LUIGI: Hey, Salvatore,
break out the cheap hooch
for Mr. No tip and the dried-up
zombie he's-a captured.
Dad, I'm really sorry,
but I charged $350 on your credit card.
-What?
-Don't worry. Here's the cash.
Whoo-hoo! $350.
Now, I can buy
70 transcripts of Nightline.
-But, Dad--
-(laughs)
Oh, well,
he's happy.
I'm gonna keep this
Mary Worth phone right here.
Her stern, but sensible face will remind
me never to do anything so stupid again.
(ringing)
MILHOUSE: Hey, Bart,
you wanna go play
with that x-ray machine
in the abandoned hospital?
Sure.
Now, my dear. If you
look in your champagne,
I think you'll find
a little surprise.
(slurps, gags)
(laughs nervously)
Not to worry.
I believe there's another one
around here somewhere.
(yells)
Ooh! Yes.
(joints cracking)
My darling,
since my kneecaps are filling
with fluid as we speak,
I'll be brief--
Will you marry me?
Oh! Mom, you can't marry
Mr. Burns. He's an evil man.
Evil, schmevil, Marge.
Monty can provide for me.
Besides, he's
a great kisser.
Ew! Yuck!
Mm, what about
Abe Simpson?
Don't you have
any feelings for him?
Oh, he's a dear,
but he's too much
of an old fusspot.
We're all aware
of Grampa's problems,
but compared to Mr. Burns,
he's Judge freaking Reinhold.
I don't know
who that is.
Oh! Who needs her?
Now I'll have more time
to read things
I find on the ground.
"la-tex con-do."
Boy, I'd like
to live in one of those!
(groans)
(chatter)
Hey, Barney, why don't you
fill out the groom's side?
-Hey! Down in front!
-Nein!
(organ plays "Wedding March")
Where's Grampa?
Wasn't he invited?
Yeah, but his
reply envelope
just had a check
to the gas company in it.
(both groaning)
(camera shutters clicking)
And, so, when Eliphaz came down
from Mount Hebron bearing figs,
he offered them
to Moham,
who you will remember
is the father of Shecham,
and to Hazar, on the occasion
of their matrimony,
much in the same--
We've heard enough about Bliz-Blaz
and Him-Ham already.
Get to the bloody point!
(mutters)
Do you, Charles
Montgomery Burns,
take this woman to be
your lawfully wedded wife?
-I do.
-Oops.
The ring, you little imbecile,
before I really lose my temper.
-(growls)
-(grunts)
Hmm? Hmm?
I know. I know.
Ow, ow, ow!
Do you,
Jacqueline Bouvier,
take this man to be your
lawfully wedded husband?
(organ plays
"Moonlight Serenade")
Oh, Monty!
My favorite song.
How did--
I specifically requested
no romantic music!
Wha--
Mrs. Bouvier!
(screams)
(grunts)
Mrs. Bouvier!
Honey, are you sure you wanna be
Mrs. Montgomery Burns?
Wouldn't you rather be
Mrs. Abraham J. Simpson?
-No.
-(gulps)
I don't wanna be either.
Hot diggity damn!
That's good enough for me!
(chatter)
(organ plays "Wedding March")
(cheering)
(sighs)
(soft rock plays)
Hmm? Turn off
that racket!
Yeah, fat chance, pops.
♪ Hello, Grampa,
my old friend ♪
♪ Your busy day
is at an end ♪
♪ Your exploits have been
sad and boring ♪
♪ They tell a tale
that's worth ignoring ♪
♪ When you're alone
the words of your story ♪
♪ Will echo down
the rest home hall ♪
♪ 'Cause no one at all ♪
♪ Can stand the sound
of Grampa ♪
GRAMPA:
I first took a fancy to Mrs. Bouvier
because her raspy voice
reminded me of
my old Victrola.
Oh, it was a fine machine,
with a vulcanized rubber
listening tube
which you crammed
in your ear.
The tube would go in easier
with some sort of lubricant
like Linseed oil
or Dr. Shumway's--
-Shh!
-I'm sorry.
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.