Spin-off!
Is there any word more thrilling
to the human soul?
Hi. I'm Troy McClure.
You may remember me
from such TV spin-offs
as "Son of Sanford and Son"
and "After Mannix."
I'm here at the Museum
of TV and Television
with a real treat
for Simpsons fans, if any,
because, tonight,
we present the...
♪♪ (theme plays)
Not long ago,
the Fox Network approached
the producers of "The Simpsons"
with a simple request:
35 new shows
to fill a few holes
in their programming lineup.
That's a pretty daunting task,
and the producers
weren't up to it.
Instead, they churned out
three Simpsons spin-offs,
transplanting
already popular characters
into new locales
and situations.
First up,
a gritty crime drama
starring Springfield's
beloved police chief Wiggum.
Keep at least one eye open,
'cause his best friends,
The Simpsons,
just might pop in
to wish him luck.
Let's us wish him luck, too.
Good luck, Wiggum.
♪♪
Ah, New Orleans.
The Big Easy.
Sweet Lady Gumbo.
Old Swampy.
I still don't understand,
Clancy.
Why give up your job
as a small-town police chief
to set up a detective shop
in New Orleans?
Oh, lots of reasons,
I suppose.
Got kicked off the force
for one thing.
For massive corruption.
-For massive corr-- Exactly.
-Yeah.
As for me,
I was born and bred here
in the mean streets
of "N'awlins."
Oh, sure, I left briefly
to take that principal's job
in Springfield,
but in my heart,
I've always been
a small-time hustler.
I know. That's precisely
why I hired you
as my leg man,
Skinny Boy.
I want you to put the word out.
Chief Wiggum is here
to clean up this crime dump.
Bleh.
Hmm? Looks like you've already
got an enemy, Chief.
You know, folks around here don't
much care for law-and-order types.
Is that right? Well, maybe they'll
change their minds
once I arrest them for throwing skulls
all over my floor.
Hmm.
Aw, man, what a day.
It's no cakewalk
being a single parent
juggling a career and a family
like so many juggling balls.
Two, I suppose.
Daddy, these rubber pants
are hot.
You wear them
until you learn, son.
Mwah.
-I gar-ohn-tee...
-Will you stop saying that?
So, Skinner, who do you figure threw
that skull through my window?
What's the word on the street?
Well, to be honest, Chief,
I haven't lived in
New Orleans for 42 years.
Although...
according to an article
I read in "Parade" magazine,
a criminal by the name
of "Big Daddy" runs this town.
Big Daddy, eh?
Well, he won't feel so big
if he messes
with Chief Wiggum, P.I. again,
which I sincerely doubt
he will.
(snoring)
(laughing)
Hey.
Oh, God!
Lucky for you,
this was just a warning gator.
The next one won't be corked.
Listen up, Big Daddy!
You don't scare me.
I'm three steps ahead of you.
Oh, Chief?
Your boy has been kidnapped.
Oh, God!
Big Daddy's trademark
calling card.
See, it's right here
inside the skull.
Looks like we've got our first case ever,
Skinny Boy,
and this time it's personal.
MALE ANNOUNCER: Chief Wiggum, P.I.
will return right now.
(ringing)
Who is this?
It's me, Chief.
I'm on the other extension.
Now, you listen up,
mon ami,
and you listen good, heah?
The name's Daddy,
Charles Daddy.
Big Daddy! What have you done
with my boy, Daddy?
Ah, the boy is fine, so far.
I taught him
to play the spoons.
If you ever want to see
that boy again,
I suggest you
leave town today, heah?
(dial tone)
Huh. Sounded like
some sort of party
going on in the background.
Are there any parties today,
Skinner?
Nah. It's not really
a party town,
though if I remember correctly,
they occasionally hold
a function called
Mardi... something.
-(music blaring)
-(crowd clamoring)
Ahh.
(evil laughter)
-(giggling)
-Huh?
If it isn't my old
friends from Springfield,
the Simpsons.
What brings you folks
to New Orleans?
Mardi Gras, man.
When the Big Easy calls,
you got to accept the charges.
Chief Wiggum,
I can't wait to hear
about the exciting,
sexy adventures
you're sure to have
against this colorful backdrop.
Golly, I'd love to chat,
but my son's been kidnapped.
You haven't seen him,
have you?
Caucasian male between the ages
of six and ten,
thinning hair.
Over there.
Look, Big Daddy,
it's Regular Daddy.
The Chief!
Ooh, I suppose I best to run.
Lord have mercy,
I wish I weren't so fat.
Police business.
Hang on, son,
I'm coming to-- Ow, ow!
Hey, my tongue.
Hee-ya!
(screaming)
Ha! Ha!
Nah! Nah!
(whistles) What do you suppose
the rent is on a hideout like that?
It's not rented, Chief.
It's stolen.
That's the Louisiana
Governor's Mansion.
It's been missing
for eight months.
(gasps)
You!
Welcome to my maison, Chief.
I've been expecting you.
Is that so, Big Daddy?
Well, expect this--
the arrest of you by me.
Mais, cher,
New Orleans is my town.
Won't nobody going to mess
with me.
I got interests, and I ain't talking
about stamp collecting,
though I do find that
extremely interesting.
Oh, yeah?
Well, that makes two of us.
You know, boys
there's an old saying
down on the bayou that...
(cries out)
He's gradually
getting away, Chief.
Ah, let him go.
I have a feeling
we'll meet again
each and every week,
always in more sexy
and exciting ways.
Daddy, when I grow up,
I want to be just like you.
Better start eating, kid.
Start eating?
(all laughing)
I didn't mean it that way.
♪♪
Oh, hi.
Welcome back to our
spin-off showcase.
Could "The Simpsons" ever
have maintained its popularity
without Moe the Bartender?
Let's hope so, because Moe's
leaving to do his own sitcom.
But don't panic. He's taking
a familiar sidekick with him.
And his best friend Homer might
just pop in to wish him luck.
Let's take a peek.
Well, I'd better go.
I got a date with that lady
in front of the drug store
who's always yelling things.
She told me she was washing
her hair tonight.
Oh, I'm so desperately lonely.
(audience laughing)
GRAMPA: Aw, quit your bellyaching,
you big loser.
Who...? Who said that?
I did. It's me, Abe Simpson.
But you're d-d-dead.
I was, but I've come back...
as your love testing machine.
I'm the Love-Matic Grampa.
(screaming)
(bouncy melody playing)
♪ While shopping
for some cans ♪
♪ An old man passed away ♪
♪ He floated up toward heaven ♪
♪ But got lost
along the way... ♪
♪ Now he's
the Love-Matic Grampa ♪
♪ The wise, Socratic grampa ♪
♪ And he'll fill
our hearts with love ♪
Don't be afraid, Moe.
I'm here to help you
with your romantic problems.
Hey, I don't need no advice
from no pinball machine.
I'll have you know,
I wrote the book on love.
Yeah. All quiet
on the Western front.
AUDIENCE: Ooh...
Aw, kiss my dishrag.
(audience laughing)
See, that's your problem.
You're a crab.
Ladies like sweet-talkers.
Hey, I'm sweet.
I'm sweeter than Jewish wine.
Then prove it. I want you to charm
the next pretty young thing
that walks through
that door.
Mm, greetings.
(audience laughing)
(applause)
Son, it's me.
I floated up toward heaven,
but got lost along the way.
(gasping)
Dad, is that really you?
Darn tootin',
you lousy fink.
You buried me naked
and sold my suit to buy
a ping-pong table.
-What kind of a son--
-(electricity zaps)
Call me when you get
a karaoke machine.
(audience laughing)
That's the second time
he pulled the plug on me.
(footsteps approaching)
I was just in a car accident.
Can I use your phone?
Using the phone's
a four-drink minimum.
(buzzing)
What's the matter?
I'm making as nice as I can.
Test-lady. Test-lady.
Go ahead, give it a try.
It goes by how clammy
your hands are.
Well, I suppose I could use
a laugh after that accident.
(bell dinging)
Lovelorn. You need man.
Moe near now.
Go near Moe.
-What?
-Go near Moe.
I'd say that's
a pretty strong endorsement.
So how about you and me
go out sometime?
You know, out back.
-(buzzing)
-I mean, out to dinner...
at a fancy
French restaurant?
-Bing!
-Sounds great.
And if this love tester
is as accurate as it looks,
maybe we'll be having
breakfast, too.
AUDIENCE: Wooo!
You did it, Grampa.
You really are a love expert.
Dang right.
Fact is, I invented kissing.
It was during World War I,
and they were looking
for a new way
to spread germs.
(canned laughter)
Sorry, Grampa, but I got
to stash you in the bathroom,
so Betty won't get wise to us.
This is not the evening
I envisioned.
Oh, jeez, she just got here.
Give me some advice, quick!
You know, just be sweet,
pour on the honey, you know...
Yeah, yeah, yeah, romantic.
Ain't sunshine pretty,
ain't flowers stupid, I got you.
(sighs)
I've suffered so long,
why can't I die?
You know what's great
about you, Betty
is you're letting
your looks go gracefully.
You're not all hung-up
on looking attractive
and desirable.
It's just so rare
and refreshing.
So, Moe, tell me
a little about yourself.
Myself... uh... uh, jeez.
Um, I got to go
to the can again.
-Huh?
-I got the runs.
(grunting)
Hey! Get away from that!
Leave him alone!
-It said I was gay.
-(canned laughter)
You all right, Grampa?
Oh... Daisy, Daisy...
give me your answer true...
will you quit your clowning?
I need help here.
Whoa, tell her her rump's
as big as the queen's
and twice as fragrant.
Okay.
You are absolutely,
positively the dumbest
haunted love tester
that I have ever met.
(gasps)
What is going on in here?
Um, uh... Oh, gah...
I might as well
come clean with you.
I ain't too good
at talking to women,
and I really wanted
to do you,
so I brought along
the love tester to help me.
As you may have guessed,
it's inhabited by the ghost
of my friend's dead father.
Why, you conniving, devious,
monstrous, despicable...
sweet, little angel.
Look, Betty, if you just
give me a chance-- What?
I can't believe you went
to all that trouble for me.
-(audience cheers)
-Mmm!
Ding, ding, ding, ding.
BOTH: Thanks, Grampa.
Yeah, yeah,
now how's about introducing me
to that cute little
pay phone out front?
(audience laughing)
He's horny.
♪ He's the Love-Matic Grampa ♪
♪ And he filled
our hearts with love ♪
Welcome back.
I'm talking with the curator
of the Museum of TV
and Television,
Mr. John Winslow.
In our final spin-off tonight
the Simpson family
finally gets the chance
to show off
the full range of their talents.
Unfortunately, one family member
didn't want that chance
and refused to participate
but thanks
to some creative casting,
you won't even notice.
Show us what you got, TV.
Live from Radio City Music Room
in downtown Springfield,
it's The Simpson Family
Smile-Time Variety Hour,
featuring
the Waylon Smithers Dancers
and the Springfield
Baggy Pants Players.
And now... a family
that doesn't know the meaning
of the word "canceled,"
-the Simpsons!
-(cheering)
♪ Come on along
and bring the family ♪
♪ Come along
and join the fun ♪
and join the family ♪
♪ Join the family Simpson ♪
♪ Roll call ♪
Remember me?
My name is Marge,
the TV mom
whose hair is large.
Step back, mom,
it's Bart's turn now.
Eat my shorts,
don't have a cow.
I'm Lisa, peppy,
blonde and stunning,
sophomore prom queen
five years running.
Go... Lisa!
Wait a minute.
Whoa, whoa.
(whistling)
Stop the music.
Where's Dad?
-Here he is!
-I'm hiding from
the-the-the ghost!
-Ghost? What ghost?
-Before the show,
you said we were having
a special ghost tonight.
I said we were having
a special guest tonight.
Mr. Tim Conway.
(applause)
What's a Tim Conway?
Uh, 'bout 120 pounds.
(audience laughing)
♪ It's the Simpson Family ♪
♪ Smile-Time Variety Hour! ♪
You know, Homer,
we've all been busy as beavers
preparing for
our very own show.
Marge, have you ever imagined
what it would be like
if we really were beavers?
Yes, and it might look
something like this.
Honey I'm home.
(audience applauding
and cheering)
Hello, dear.
How was work at the plant?
It's not a plant, Marge.
It's a tree, and I've
nearly chewed through it.
Now, remember, my new boss
is coming home
for dinner tonight.
I know,
and I made your favorite:
-Stakes!
-(audience groaning)
-(applause)
-Hey, would you two close the dam door?
Bart!
-But that's where we live-- a dam!
-(laughter)
Look, everybody!
Maggie got her first tooth!
(laughter)
ALL:
Aw!
Okay, now,
before my boss comes,
there's something important
you should know.
(doorbell ringing)
In a minute, Homie.
I have to get the door.
-But, Marge!
-(gasping)
Uh, was it something I said?
Yarr! Someone should be
keelhauled for that one.
(boat whistle blowing)
I move that the last sketch
be stricken from the record.
Now, bring in the next offender.
Inflation, trade deficit,
horrible war atrocities--
How are we supposed to do
our big musical number
with so many problems
in the world?
Well, I know
one thing in this world
that's still pure and good.
Christian love?
No. Candy!
Sweet, sweet candy!
(Bo Diddley-style riff)
♪ I want candy ♪
But don't you want
to end world famine?
♪ I want candy ♪
Or save the endangered
Alaskan salmon.
♪ I want candy ♪
Well, if you won't think
of society's ills...
♪ I want candy ♪
At least think
of our dentist bills.
(twist-style riff)
♪ Got a new dance,
and it goes like this ♪
♪ And the name of the dance
is the Peppermint Twist ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Lollipop, lollipop ♪
♪ Oh, lolli, lollipop ♪
♪ Lollipop ♪
-(popping noise)
-Ow.
♪ Crack that whip ♪
♪ Licorice whip ♪
♪ I said whip it ♪
(grumbles)
(Bo Diddley riff)
♪ We want candy ♪
♪ Candy ♪
(applause and cheering)
A poem, by Hans Moleman.
I think that
I shall never see,
my cataracts
are blinding me.
And they thought I stunk.
(steam whistles)
MARGE: Well, it's time
to say good night.
I wish our special guest
Tim Conway
didn't have
to leave so soon.
I'm still here.
Fox wouldn't spring
for a decent hotel room.
(audience
and performers laughing)
He's just kidding.
We'd like to thank Fox
and the good people
at Budget Lodge.
Well, that's all
the time we have
so, this is the Simpson family
saying, "As you walk down
that road of life..."
Hitchhike!
It's faster.
-ALL: Bart!
-(laughs)
We're like this all the time.
ALL:
Good night, everybody!
(cheering and applause)
That's it
for our spin-off showcase.
But what about the show
that started it all?
How do you keep "The Simpsons"
fresh and funny
after eight long years?
Well, here's what's on tap
for season nine:
Magic powers!
Wedding after wedding
after wedding.
And did someone say
long-lost triplets?
So, join America's favorite
TV family
and a tiny, green space alien
named Ozmodiar
that only homer can see
on Fox this fall.
It'll be out of this world,
right, Ozmodiar?
Damn straight,
Troy, my man.
TROY, OZMODIAR:
Good night, America!
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.