♪ The Simpsons ♪
(chalk screeches)
(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(tires screeching)
(horn honks)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
I don't need your crummy job,
Mister Employer.
I won the lottery!
Well, who needs employees?
I won the lottery too!
We both won the lottery!
ALL: Why don't you
win the lottery too?
MAN: Where everybody wins!
Actual odds of winning:
one in 380 million.
The lottery--
exploiter of the poor
and ignorant.
You know, I heard the jackpot's
up to $130 million.
(sputtering)
$130 million?
Did you say $130 million?
-Yeah.
-Wow!
(clamoring)
Yes, yes. Here's
your lottery ticket.
Thank you for knocking
over my inventory.
Please, come again.
Bart, I need
some lucky numbers fast.
How old are you?
Uh-huh, and
what's your birthday?
No kidding.
And what's Lisa's birthday?
What? You don't know
your sister's birthday?
What kind of brother are you?
Strap on your
bulletproof vest, Sanjay.
It's time
for another bank run.
Alright, but if
I don't make it
promise you won't
sleep with my wife.
I promise nothing.
You'll never guess
what happened, Marge.
Are you ready?
I have a feeling
that we may win...
the lottery!
But we never, ever...
I know you're excited,
but calm down and listen
to me carefully.
Go get all your money...
I buy one lottery ticket a week
with the girls
at the hair salon.
We each play our birthday,
and that's enough
excitement for me.
You don't understand, Marge.
The lottery is the
one ray of hope
in my otherwise
unbearable life!
Uh, the lottery and you.
Homer, we're on a
tight budget, here.
Promise me you won't
get carried away.
Yes, money-- I mean honey.
Ooh! Here comes the news
report about the lottery.
Hey, down in front.
The whole state is suddenly
in the grip of lottery fever
and Springfield is
no exception.
In fact, every copy
of Shirley Jackson's "The Lottery"
has been checked out
from the Springfield Public Library.
Of course, the book does
not contain any hints
on how to win the lottery.
It is rather a chilling tale
of conformity gone mad.
Ohh....
But there's already
one big winner--
our state school system
which gets fully half the profits
from the lottery.
Just think what we can buy
with that money:
History books that know how
the Korean War came out.
Math books that don't have
that Base-6 crap in them.
And a state-of-the-art
detention hall
where children are held
in place with magnets.
Magnets,
always with the magnets.
HOMER: I've never been
so sure of anything in my life.
I am going to win this lottery.
Homer, the odds
are 380 million to one.
Correction:
380 million to 50!
So, what are you gonna do
with your share of the money, kids?
Put it in the bank.
Give it to the poor.
Pfft. What do kids know
about spending money?
What are you
gonna do, Homer?
Hmm...
Hey Homer, what did you do,
get a haircut or something?
(booming voice)
Look closer, Lenny.
Oh, I know what it is.
You're the biggest man
in the world now
and you're covered
in gold.
14-karat gold.
Take a hike, boss.
I'm running things now.
All hail King Homer.
(triumphant laughter)
(chuckling)
We now take you
to the drawing live.
I hope you've got
your tickets. I've got mine.
-(phone rings)
-They're about to start, Chief.
No, you got
the wrong number.
This is 91... 2.
We'll be with you
in a minute, kids.
This could be our ticket
out of here, Mel.
I will now draw
the first winning number.
(groaning)
I've got so many tickets
I can't lose.
The first number is 17.
D'oh!
You can still
win some money
if you have
five out of six.
Woo-hoo!
And the second number
is... three.
D'oh!
Yeah, I knew
we wouldn't win.
Well, why didn't you
tell the rest of us?
Why did you
keep it a secret!?
If you were 17,
we'd be rich.
But no,
you had to be ten.
And the final number
is... 49.
38... 49!
Oh, my God...
I won. I won!
(screaming)
(crazed laughter)
(clearing throat)
Recapping our day's
top story:
the winner of today's
state lottery is...
me, Kent Brockman.
Can we get a shot of me?
There you go.
In other news, uh...
A tragic mix-up
today in Cleveland.
Many people killed. Uh...
Good-bye!
Oh, well,
we lost the money
but at least we've
still got each other.
Hey, the dog's dead.
(gasping)
BART: Grampa, he's not dead.
HOMER: Dad, you shouldn't say
the dog's dead when he's not.
It's not fair to toy with
people's emotions like that.
He is dead.
I'll get a shovel.
Well, he's not dead,
but he is awfully sick.
Oh, sure, the old man's
off his rocker.
If Grampa says he's dead,
he must be alive.
He is alive.
He's wagging his tail.
That don't mean nothin'!
Dogs wag their tails
for hours after they die.
I'm tired
of this conversation.
Let's talk
about something else.
I'm going home.
Clear.
Doctor, he's gone.
Ugh! This is the part
of the job I hate.
Hey, you did the best
you could.
I love animals.
I spend my life saving them,
and they can't thank me.
Well, the parrots can,
but anyway,
let's see what's wrong
with this little fellow.
(dog whimpering)
Hmm...
I'm afraid that your dog
has a twisted stomach.
He needs an operation
to correct it
-or he'll die.
-♪♪ (dramatic)
How much will it cost?
$750.
Oh, dear.
This is never an easy decision.
It's an awful lot of money.
Well, I guess
we'll have to talk it over.
Talk what over?
What's there to talk about?
What are we gonna talk over?
Mr. Teeny needs a refill
of his nicotine gum.
I can't help but notice
we're leaving the hospital.
When's the dog going
to get his operation?
Uh... later.
First I want to tell you
about the most
wonderful place
in the world--
Doggie Heaven.
In Doggie Heaven,
there's mountains of bones
and you can't turn around
without sniffing
another dog's butt.
And all the best dogs
are there--
Old Yeller and about
eight Lassies, and--
Is there a doggie hell?
Well, of course,
there couldn't be
a heaven if there
weren't a hell.
-Who's in there?
-Oh... Hitler's dog,
and that dog Nixon had,
what's his name? Chester?
Checkers.
Yeah, and one of the Lassies
is in there too.
The mean one--
the one that mauled Timmy.
Hey, wait a minute,
does this have anything to do
with Santa's Little Helper?
Oh, honey,
$750 is a lot of money.
We really can't afford
this operation.
You're gonna just let him die?
I know you're upset.
Darn right I'm upset!
Bart, watch your language.
Oh... you did. Sorry.
We're not going to let
our dog die, and that's it!
Lousy, dog-killing
son-of-a--
(sighing)
Well, it will be okay.
We'll get him
a new dog--
one with
an untwistable stomach.
(whimpering)
Oh, come on.
I'm sorry but we just
can't afford it.
Marge, make him stop.
Oh!
All right, all right,
we'll find a way.
Lousy, manipulative dog.
Uh, Mr. Burns
I need to borrow some money.
Please, do go on.
HOMER: I know you're
a good man
and I have a dog
that's very sick.
Oh, please, continue.
I thought maybe you...
Oh.
Well, thanks
for your time.
What makes a man
endanger his job
and, yes, even his life
by asking me for money?
People like dogs,
Mr. Burns.
Nonsense. Dogs are idiots.
Think about it, Smithers,
If I came into your house
and started sniffing
at your crotch
and slobbering
all over your face
what would you say?
If you did it, sir?
Exactly. You'd be fit
to be tied. Dogs!
Hmm...
-No!
-What?
You are not going to perform
that operation yourself.
But Marge, it looks so easy.
Just like carving a turkey.
ALL: Oh! Oh!
Eww!
(grunting)
Maybe you're right, Marge.
I found a way we can pay
for the operation.
-BOTH: All right!
-Hear that, boy?
-What do you got, Marge, insurance scam?
-No.
I'm afraid we're
just going
to have to make
a few sacrifices.
Homer, you're going to have
to give up beer for a while.
Bart, from now on,
you'll have to get
your hair cut for free
at Springfield
Barber College.
No problemo.
I'm going to give up buying
my weekly lottery ticket
and I found a way to stretch
the food budget.
Fried chicken night will now
be organ meat night.
Ham night will be Spam night,
and pork chop night--
-(sobbing)
-Will be chub night.
Chub? I don't even know
what that is.
Lisa, I'm afraid
we'll have to stop getting you
those volumes of
Encyclopedia Generica
from the grocery store.
But Mom, next week is
volume four--
Copernicus
through Elephantiasis.
We all have
to make sacrifices, dear.
Maggie's baby clothes will have
to last for a little longer.
Marge, I've figured out
an alternative
to giving up my beer.
Basically, we become a family
of traveling acrobats.
I don't think
you've thought this through.
-(gasping)
-Good news, Mr. Danielson.
We saved your gamecock,
but I'm afraid
he'll never fight again.
That's what you think.
He'll fight and he'll win.
Clamp.
(beeping)
Wipe.
(flat tone)
No!
MAN'S VOICE:
Come to the light, boy.
Come into the light.
Come on now.
There's a good boy.
Come on. Come on.
(rhythmic breathing)
(monitor beeping)
-Um, Simpson?
-(gasping)
(barking)
Oh, Santa's Little Helper,
you're alive!
Oh, you're all better now!
It's times like this
I'm glad
I flunked out
of dental school.
HOMER:
Lousy chub night.
Hey, how come he gets
meat and we don't?
You wouldn't want
what he's eating.
It's mostly just
snouts and entrails.
Mmm... snouts.
Yes, I'm back.
Kent Brockman
is not the kind of man
who would leave
a $500,000-a-year job
just because
he won a lottery.
Hey, I'm a journalist.
Well, he's got all the money
in the world
but there's one thing
he can't buy.
-What's that?
-A dinosaur.
Of course,
I'm not the only one
who benefitted from
last week's big payoff.
Our state schools got
their share too.
Here, lottery officials present
Springfield Elementary
with a brand-new eraser.
One eraser?
I'm used to my government
betraying me.
I was in 'Nam.
I served for 3--
And speaking of lotteries
here are the winning numbers
for this week's
$40,000 'jackpot'.
3-6-17-18-22 and 29.
Oh, no!
Those are my numbers.
If it wasn't for that dog,
I would have won.
Class, for tomorrow, I want
you to write a report
on Copernicus.
D'oh!
MAN:
Come on, booze hound.
You want the 25 cents,
don't you?
Keep singing!
♪ Buffalo gals, won't you
come out tonight? ♪
♪ Come out tonight? ♪
Who's that old rummy?
Before his dog got sick
that old rummy used
to be my best customer.
♪ ...of the moon ♪
(all cheering)
Sing it, baby!
Go get it, pal!
My quarter! Aagh!
Okay, I'll just even
this out and--
(buzzing)
Mr. Laswell...
I've done it again.
(panting)
I know you can't understand me
but you're a lousy dog
and I hate you.
Not now.
Can't you see I'm reading
a third-rate biography
of Copernicus I found
at the bus station?
Dumb dog.
(whimpering)
Homie, did you
close the gate?
Yes.
(gate banging)
Oh, you mean tonight.
The dog will get out.
Bart, close the gate!
Oh, Lisa, close the gate!
Close the gate, Maggie!
(whimpering)
MARGE: Here, boy!
(whistles)
Here, Santa's Little Helper!
Oh...
it's all my fault.
I called him a dumb dog.
Oh, he's gone and he's never
coming back.
Wait! There he is!
No, that's a horse.
(growling)
(both growling)
(meowing, barking)
(cat screeches)
(barking)
Have you found a picture yet?
Not one that
I want the public to see.
Mmm...
Oh.
Oh, dear.
FLANDERS: So, recycling
is our way of giving
Mother Earth a great big hug.
Yes, well,
it does sound like fun.
I can't wait to start pawing
through my garbage
like some
starving raccoon.
Release the hounds.
Well, neighbor
I see you've got
your running shoes on.
That's a good thing.
(growling)
(screaming)
(tired panting and growling)
What's wrong
with Crippler?
He's getting on, sir.
He's been here
since the late '60s.
Ah, yes,
I'll never forget the day
he bagged his first hippie.
That young man didn't think
it was too groovy.
(chuckling)
I'm looking for something
in an attack dog--
one who likes the sweet,
gamey tang of human flesh.
Why, here's the fellow.
Wiry, fast, firm,
proud buttocks.
Reminds me of me.
Ah, the last one.
D'oh!
Now, as an attack dog
you'll be expected
to neutralize intruders.
Want to buy some cookies?
(barking and whining)
(groans)
If that were
a real girl scout
I'd have been bothered
by now.
I know how you feel.
I lost my dog too.
He's in here somewhere.
(muffled whining)
BURNS:
Now here's a film
that will turn you into
a vicious, soulless killer.
Enjoy.
♪♪ (Beethoven's "Ode to Joy")
Poor Santa's Little Helper.
I'm starting to think
we'll never see him again.
That was his dish
and that was his leash
and that's where he took
a whiz on the rug.
(sobbing)
Homer, get a hold
of yourself.
Even if he has passed on,
there's no reason to cry.
Remember, Doggie Heaven?
Oh, Marge!
There is no such place.
(Marge clears throat)
Or...
to put it another way...
there is.
I'm not giving up.
I don't care if I have to
knock on every door
in this two-bit town,
I'm gonna find my dog.
And I'll be right here
watching TV.
Poka, poka, poka.
(snarling)
Poka, poka, poka...
(screams)
(growling)
Excellent.
(doorbell rings)
Hello, I'm Kent Brockman.
Excuse me, sir.
I lost my dog.
Mm-hm. And I suppose you want me
to buy you a new one, hmm?
You know, ever since
I won the lottery
everybody wants a piece
of Kent Brockman--
homeless this and hungry that.
Gee, I'm sorry, mister.
Sir, your llama
just bit Ted Kennedy.
Good!
(doorbell rings)
I hate to interrupt your
longevity treatment, sir,
but there's a sweet
little boy at the door.
Release the hounds.
(growling and barking)
Santa's Little Helper!
It's you!
(screams)
(gasps)
What's the matter, boy?
Don't you know me?
I'm your buddy.
(growls)
I love you, boy.
(echoing)
(whining)
(growling)
(dogs whining)
(laughing)
HOMER:
Let me pet him again.
You already petted him
for ten minutes.
I know, I want to
pet him again.
You can pet the cat.
The cat?
What's the point?
Good boy,
Santa's Little Helper.
Oh, good boy.
This will never,
ever happen again.
BART: You can have
anything you want.
You can sleep on my bed,
you can chew on slippers.
HOMER: Yeah,
he's a good doggie.
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.