Aw, water soup again?
Now it's crow soup.
Ooh, I call an eye!
- Me, two!
- Me, three!
And Maggie gets the beak.
Your hovel got
in the way of my horse.
Kiss his hooves
in apology.
Oh, please,
forgive us, noble steed.
Our nostrils are not
worthy of your mighty stench.
Are those new
horseshoes?
Oh, they look good on you!
Lousy nobles!
We serfs are starving,
while they're feasting
and jousting
and posing for tapestries
where they're friends
with a unicorn.
As if any unicorn
would like them.
Unicorns like nice people,
I'm a nice person.
Young lady, that kind of
talk is anti-feudalist,
and I won't have it!
Without feudalism, we
wouldn't have this hovel,
our bountiful filth,
or my awesome buboes.
I'll lance you later.
Bart! They just stuck
new severed heads up
on the city walls!
Can we go, Ma?
Can we? Can we?
That's a lovely idea.
And we can bring my mom.
I hope she's doing okay
in her new nursing home.
Which one is your mom's web?
Son, is that you?
No.
Ah, you ruined my nap!
Just like you ruined
my daughter's life.
That's her.
They didn't skimp
on the tar.
That's the secret
to long-lasting heads.
Oh, there's Ned Flanders!
It's always nice when
you know someone.
Those are the kind of sideburns
I was saying you should grow.
Pretty sharp.
Pretty, pretty sharp.
See how the heads
of rich people
get the tallest pikes
with the best view?
It's so unfair.
I told you
to lay off feudalism.
It's the only system we know.
We have no choice about it,
and therefore it's the best.
The system is designed
to keep us down.
That's not true.
In a great country
like ours,
a poor girl can grow up
to be anything she wants...
a wife or a harlot
and... that's it.
I wanted to be a harlot,
but it's all who you know.
It's never too late.
Everyone is somebody's
weird fetish.
Mom. What's wrong
with your skin?
It's blue,
and ice-cold.
This could be a
serious disease.
Homer, she needs
medical attention.
Pretty, pretty sharp.
It's never easy to say this.
You've got...
Genital Snerfs.
La, la, la-la, la-la
We love our new home
Doc, is there any way to
control occasional flare-ups?
Nope.
Yeah! Yay! Yippee!
Now, what have we here?
Progressive
frozen-mortification!
This can only be the bite
of an Ice Walker!
An Ice Walker?
Mom, how did
this happen?
I dated a ravenous wight who
abhors the warmth of the living.
- And?
- He got fresh.
I'm sorry, baby.
I know I screwed up.
But you got to give me
another chance.
I love you.
She's 900 years younger
than you, you pervert.
I like 'em young,
that ain't no crime.
Is my mom
gonna be okay?
I'm sorry,
but a week from now,
your mother
will be frozen solid.
No! No, that can't be.
She's barely into
her hag years.
All you can do is give her
leeches for the pain.
Here's an organizer.
So... So there's nothing
we can do to save her?
Well,
there's one treatment.
All we have to do
is buy this amulet.
My mom is saved!
Yeah...
but a hundred GP?
I mean, that's more than a
tenth-level fighter makes
in an entire campaign.
Don't worry, we'll
figure it out.
Hey, sweet young thang.
What time they cuttin'
you down?
Ooh, baby!
Okay, we just need to come up
with a hundred gold pieces.
How much do we have
in our savings?
Hmm, let me think.
There's that thing...
What are savings?
Well, then we can sell
our possessions.
The pig. The spoon.
The gelatinous cube has
to be worth something.
Is this because of
what happened to the cat?
I told him not to nap on me.
So... that's on him.
Look, honey,
I love your mom.
As crones go, she's tops.
But does it make sense...
I mean total sense
to spend all that money
so a really old lady
can get a little bit older?
This is my mom's life!
This family will do whatever
it takes to keep her alive!
Is that understood?
Of course. Of course.
- Good.
Good.
All I'm saying is...
Homer Serfson,
you are the most selfish jerk
in the entire Tri-Kingdom Area!
I should have listened
to that witch
and married
my twin brother, Markery.
Always here
if you need me, sis.
Get lost, freak!
She chose me!
You get that money
to save my mom,
or never set foot
in this hovel again!
Good things come
to those who wait.
Is Marge still sore
at you, Homer?
Yeah. It's not like
I want to kill her mother.
I just want to let
her die from neglect.
If I don't get
the money for that amulet,
I'll be sleeping
on the iron couch.
Now, let's see here.
An urgent message
for Milady Gwendolyn Partz.
Milady Partz?
Hey, has anyone seen
Ah, come on,
somebody grab Milady Partz!
That depends... how
big is your dowry?
You little craven, if
I ever get my hands on you,
I'm gonna slice you open and
drain all of your humors...
blood, black bile,
yellow bile...
And phlegm.
Okay, break's over.
Lord Montgomery?
I've had some unforeseen
family medical expenses,
and I was wondering, could
I get an advance on my salary?
But first,
can I have a salary?
Peasants.
Serfson, you've pushed
that wheel around and around
for 20 years...
did you ever wonder why?
Mostly I just push it.
Have you ever noticed
that the wheel
isn't hooked up
to anything?
The rumors were true!
But your work does produce
something very special...
human misery...
which, when collected,
ground into a powder
and snorted, gives rich people
tiny wings that do nothing.
So if you help me,
it reduces my suffering,
which means less wing powder
for my betters.
I'm glad we
had this talk.
- But I really need the money...
- Flit-flit.
Thank you
for your time.
Hi, Azzlan.
Marge, my child.
I've come to offer solace
in this difficult time.
You mean convert me
to your religion
when I'm at my
most vulnerable?
Oh, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no.
I'm just here to ask you
an important question.
Have you heard the news?
Yes, yes.
I will be saved.
Thanks so much
for stopping by.
I'm just going to leave you with
this literature, praise God...
I can't go home
and face your mom
without the money
for that amulet.
In here.
Do you have your
lucky lead nugget?
Always.
A lead-lick a day
keeps the doctor a-blah...
Gold.
Sweet, sweet gold!
Why didn't you ever tell us
you could do magic?
Because if the king finds
out, he'll take me away
and force me to be one
of his evil wizards!
You necromancing nitwits!
I wanted an all-seeing eye,
not this!
No daughter of mine is gonna
end up in the hex trade.
Now, let's go
buy that amulet.
And don't worry,
mum's the word.
Did you say The Word?
- Hi, Azzlan.
12-nothing.
My serve.
You know, eventually,
you're gonna run out of us.
I said, my serve.
Mom, I've got
a surprise for you.
Thanks to who?
I said it when I was 11,
and I'll say it now.
You're the greatest husband
in the world.
Where'd a dirt-poor
loser like you
get all the gold
for that?
Oh, well...
let's just say...
I strangled a leprechaun.
I'm not wearing that.
But without it,
you'll die.
- Fine by me.
- What?!
I want to die.
Oh, typical!
I want to live,
I want to die.
Just make up your mind...
they're both terrible.
Oh, I've lived a full life.
I saw a drawing of an ocean,
I watched my daughter
marry an ogre.
I am not an ogre.
My father married an ogre
after my mother was eaten
by a different ogre.
You're my mom.
I can't bear the thought
of saying good-bye.
You want me to live, I'll live.
Let's celebrate!
I'll roast a hobbit for dinner.
Bet you a packet
of South Farthing pipe weed
she picks me, Gaffer.
Hush now, lad.
The big folk will choose
who's tastiest and no mistake.
Hey! How do you know
you got them from me?
We miss you!
We miss you too!
Love you!
Love you more!
Is it really so bad
for Grandma if she dies?
Won't she spend eternity
in the Fields of Bliss?
Yeah. We're all going
to the Fields of Bliss...
where the days are passed
in frolic most joyous.
Just frolicking? That's it?
Sometimes, you wave
ribbons through the air.
But mainly, frolicking.
Doesn't that get old?
Did I mention the ribbons?
'Cause there's ribbons.
Fields of Bliss? Nonsense.
The afterlife is an
eternity of slaughtering
and being slaughtered
by your enemies.
Oh, yeah.
You're both wrong.
After death,
you spend all day counting
Goblin Jesus's money.
And it
better all be there.
71 mermaids.
Some where the fish
is the top part.
Top.
Mushrooms.
Everywhere, mushrooms.
Frolicking and ribbons!
Yeah, but what if
after we die, that's it?
We're just gone?
So just poof?
Really? Poof, and then
just super nothing?
Well, it's clean.
I'll give you that.
Oh, yeah.
This is way better
than death.
Come on, Mom.
There's so many things
we can say to each other now.
Oh, really?
Okay, then, say them.
I'm waiting.
Well...
What about you guys?
What do you want
to ask your grandma?
I got nothing.
I'm gonna take a stroll
and enjoy the golden age
of cleavage.
Lisa?
Oh! Well, Grandma,
tell us of your
most ardent swain.
I dated a shape-shifter once.
I thought I could
keep him from changing.
I was wrong.
Love is a fairy tale!
Every moment with her
is a precious gift.
Yes. Yes, it is.
All that matters
is that we're a family
and we're together.
Sorcerer-intendent
Chalmers.
Your daughter has been detected
using witchcraft.
Under the Magic
The Gathering Act,
she is hereby
property of the crown.
What? My daughter
isn't a magician.
Oh, I'm terribly sorry,
but she is.
Yes, the moment that
she transmuted lead into gold,
our palantirs...
they just went bananas.
I've never seen palantirs
go so bananas.
It was the only way.
I just didn't want you
to be sad about Grandma.
Oh, no.
This is all my fault.
Don't blame
yourself, honey.
We're all at fault
for doing whatever it takes
to make you happy.
Help!
You can't nap my kid!
That's kidnapping!
Toenail Imprisonum!
D'oh!
Lisa's magic?
Maybe I'm magic too!
Abra-carumba!
Yeah, just grab a stick
and say a funny word.
Yeah, that's not
insulting to us at all.
Please don't
take my daughter.
She was only trying
to save her grandmother.
She sounds like
a wonderful kid.
Now please say good-bye
to her forever.
Take a peasant,
leave a peasant.
She's gone.
Lisa's gone.
Clip me out of here, Marge.
I'm gonna rescue Lisa
if I have to kill every
noble in that castle.
But Dad, serfs can't
rise up against nobles.
You'd be attacking
the system itself.
And nobody loves feudalism
more than you.
Son, feudalism
is a beautiful vision.
The Bill of No Rights.
One person, no vote.
But I'm willing
to betray all that
to get my daughter back.
Hey, you mind if
I dissolve those?
Just checking.
Better to ask.
Peasants, peons,
and distinguished beggars!
Aren't you tired of the nobles
taking the wheat we sow,
the yarn we spin,
and the wine we steal
from travelers
we murder on the road?
They even take our children.
And not just
the worthless Barts,
but the magical Lisas.
If we can put a
moon-spangled hat on a man,
why can't we kill a bunch of
rich jerks and take their stuff?!
How are we going to
get over these walls?
Walls...
cannot stop us.
The trees will fight with you.
We will never
forget your sacrifice.
Sacrifice?
We could have torn down
the castle walls
in five minutes.
Trees can't talk, silly.
Mom!
Dad! Help!
Milhouses,
save your girlfriend!
Lisa! Lisa! Lisa!
Okay, no...
I'm just a friend
who is a girl.
It's something to build on.
You peasants are a drag-on
the economy.
Oh! I get it.
Because he's riding a dragon!
My love for wordplay
is undiminished!
Oh, no!
We're losing.
We need to talk.
- Now?
- Yes, now.
It's time for me to go.
Life is about moving forward.
Girls want to be women,
women want to be mothers,
mothers want to be grandmas,
and grandmas
want to know what comes next.
But what if
I'm not ready?
I wouldn't leave you if I didn't
know you'll be all right.
Okay, Mom.
I understand.
Maybe I was born a peasant,
but I'm going out
an ice queen.
Now we won!
My mom gave her life
to save ours.
Take comfort, Marge.
Now she's in
the Fields of Bliss.
No, she's in
Goblin Money Heaven.
The afterlife is snakes
chewing your eyes,
but it feels good.
This is our heaven!
Or, as long as Grandma
lives on in our hearts,
then she's
never truly gone.
Until we die.
Then it's like
she never existed.
And, someday,
no one will remember you.
Or anybody.
All is well...
the nobles are defeated,
the dragon is dead,
and I've got a daughter
who can turn lead into gold!
Ooh. Actually,
I can't anymore.
Dragon fire is the
source of all magic.
And Grandma killed
the last one.
Everything wondrous and
extraordinary about our world
is going to fade.
But maybe now we can use science
to improve our world.
With new technologies,
we can put an end
to poverty and disease.
Sure, it'll be hard work,
but far more rewarding
than waving your hand
over a rock
to change it into gold.
I mean...
Please come back, magic!
Live, damn you, live.
I am risen!
But what about science?
Oh, sweetie, who would
want to live in a world
without magic?
It would be so boring.
People would have to make up
fantasy stories...
Most of them poorly
written pretenses
for explicit sex
and violence.
Just to escape
the tedious real world.
That does sound awful.
Look! The dragon is
burning our village.
I love our life.
Dry your tears
A journey's end
The saga's done
We part as friends
We must away
We cannot tarry
The minstrel's burden
Is ours to carry
All other stories
Will ever pale
For we have sung
The perfect tale