(clearing throat)
Hello, everyone.
Before last year's
Halloween show
I warned you not to let
your children watch,
but you did anyway.
Well, this year's episode
is even worse.
It's scarier, more violent,
and I think they snuck in
some bad language too.
So please, tuck in
your children and--
(groans)
Well, if you didn't
listen to me last time
you're not going to now.
Enjoy the show.
(thunder crashes)
♪♪
(wolf howl)
(evil laughter)
(ghostly shriek)
NEWSCASTER: And to conclude
this Halloween newscast
on a scary note:
Remember,
the presidential primaries
are only a few months away.
Hey, if you don't like it,
go to Russia.
(doorbell)
BOTH: Trick or treat, man.
Hey, aren't you
a little old for this?
You're not even
wearing costumes.
Hand over the candy,
old dude
or we egg your house
back to the Stone Age.
Here you go, kids.
Heh-heh, heh.
Lousy punks.
(splatter)
D'oh!
(kids laughing)
We're home.
Aah... whoo!
Get a good haul
this year?
Jackpot!
I'm very, very proud
of you kids.
We would have gotten more
if Lisa could walk faster.
I didn't select this
costume for mobility.
I wore it to salute
the noble native Americans
of the Pacific Northwest.
Yaahh!
(laughing)
Now, children, you can have
one piece of candy tonight,
and save the rest for--
(groans)
If you eat too much,
you'll have nightmares.
Oh, yeah,
everybody in this family
is gonna have
a bad nightmare tonight.
Oh, yeah,
three bad nightmares.
I'd like to see that.
Heh-heh-heh.
(thunderclap)
Ooh.
(speaking Arabic)
What a dump!
Why would Princess Grace
live in a place like this?
-Dad, that's Monaco.
-D'oh!
I can do that,
but I don't want to.
Ugh! What is this thing?
It is a monkey's paw, dating
back to Al-al Ben Abdallah.
It has the power to
grant wishes to its owner.
Oh, yeah? How much?
Sir, I must strongly advise you,
do not purchase this.
Behind every wish
lurks grave misfortune.
I myself was once
president of Algeria.
Come on, pal,
I don't want to hear
your life story. Paw me.
Eww, Homer. Where did you get
that ugly thing?
Why, at that little shop
right over... there.
(gasps)
Oh, no, wait,
it was over there.
You'll be sorry.
MAN (on PA): Flight #7,
Marrakech to Springfield,
now boarding.
Just a moment.
(yelling in Arabic)
Don't shoot!
They're souvenirs.
You must pay a fine
of two American dollars.
Okay.
Let's wish for x-ray specs
that really work.
No, Bart-- peace on earth.
-X-ray specs.
-Peace on earth.
Forget it, you two.
As the pants-wearer
of this house,
I get the first wish.
Homer, there's something
I don't like
about that severed hand.
Marge, don't flake out
on me.
That monkey's paw is gonna
make our dreams come true.
Oh, no!
Maggie made a wish.
(horn honks)
Oh, my land!
Ooh! A luxury car.
Good baby.
Good Maggie.
MARGE: Ohh, a new pacifier.
D'oh!
Okay, no more foolin' around.
Paw, this is Bart.
I wish for the Simpsons
to be rich and famous.
Now you're talking.
BOTH: Yay!
Woohoo!
Look, everybody.
My purse exploded!
Come on, everybody.
We're going to the fanciest
restaurant in town.
MAITRE 'D:
I'm terribly sorry.
I have absolutely nothing
until June.
Ah, the Simpsons!
Right this way,
please.
Homer, maybe fame and fortune
aren't as bad as they say.
If I hear one more thing
about the Simpsons,
I swear
I'm going to scream.
At first they were
cute and funny,
but now
they're just annoying.
18 bucks for this?
What a rip-off.
♪ Man smart,
the woman is smarter ♪
The woman is smarter ♪
Man, this thing's
really getting out of hand.
Is there anything they won't do?
Oh, Homer,
this is awful.
Come to think of it,
the guy that sold me this thing
did say the wishes
would bring grave misfortune.
I thought he was
just being colorful.
I wish for world peace.
Lisa, that was
very selfish of you!
Sorry about the Falklands,
old boy.
Oh, forget it.
We kind of knew
they were yours.
Well, won't be needing
these anymore.
♪ Come on, people now,
smile on your brother ♪
♪ Everybody get together ♪
♪ Try to love one another
right now ♪
Foolish humans.
Oh, yes, Kodos.
Earth is now ripe
for the plucking.
(menacing laughter)
(menacing laughter continues)
People of Earth,
we come to you in the spirit
of hostility and menace.
Now, let's be reasonable.
We can resolve our
differences peacefully.
Uh... ow!
Your superior intellect
is no match
for our puny weapons.
Gordon, you've got
to do something.
What do you
want me to do?
I'm a baker now.
They conquered us
with a club.
Wish we'd saved an A-bomb
or two.
Move along humans.
(groaning)
This is all
the Simpsons' fault.
Before I was just
bored with their antics
and their merchandise.
Now I wish they were dead.
Geez, now we're slaves.
This paw sucks.
Okay, okay, I'll make
a wish that can't backfire.
I wish for a turkey sandwich
on rye bread
with lettuce and mustard
and-- and I don't want
any zombie turkeys.
I don't want to turn
into a turkey myself
and I don't want any other
weird surprises, you got it?
Hey!
Hmm... mmm!
Mmm... not bad.
Nice hot mustard...
good bread...
turkey's a little dry...
The turkey's a little dry?!
Oh, foul the cursed thing!
What demon
from the depths of hell
created thee?
Hey, fellow slave.
Is that one of
those monkey paw dealies
that lets you
wish for things?
Yeah, but I got
to warn you
that this thing is--
Yeah, that's what it is.
You want to try it?
Okely-dokely.
Ooh, would you
look at that.
Aahh!
Kneel before my slingshot,
puny earthling!
Well, I guess
my first wish
is to get rid
of those awful aliens.
Aahh! He's got a board
with a nail in it!
Enslave humanity, will ya?!
Run, Kodos!
Ha-ha-ha!
Well, Kang, it seems
the earthlings won.
Did they?
That board with the nail in it
may have defeated us,
but the humans won't stop there.
They'll make bigger boards
and bigger nails.
Soon they will make
a board with a nail so big
it will destroy them all!
(menacing laughter)
(cheering)
Hey, Homer,
this little thingumajig
really works great.
Now that I've saved the earth,
maybe I ought to spruce up
the old homestead.
I wish I had a monkey's paw.
LISA: Bart?
Bart?
Huh? What's the matter?
I had a bad dream.
Could I sleep in your bed?
No.
I'll give you a candy necklace.
Climb aboard.
Thanks, Bart.
Less talk, more sleep.
NARRATOR: Presented for
your consideration:
Springfield--
an average little town
with a not-so-average
monster.
VOICES: Happy thoughts.
Happy, happy, happy...
NARRATOR:
The people of Springfield
have to make sure
they think happy thoughts
and say happy things
because
this particular monster
can read minds,
and if displeased
can turn people into
grotesque walking terrors.
Happy thoughts.
Boy, I'm getting
mighty sick of this.
Huh?
Ruff, ruff, ruff. Bow-wow.
NARRATOR:
And did I mention
that the monster
is a ten-year-old boy?
Quite a twist, huh?
Betcha didn't see
that one coming.
Good morning.
(spitting)
-Morning.
-Good morning, dear.
Hiya, Bart.
How's my boy?
(nervous laughing)
-(meowing, purring)
-Every day, same old cat.
I'll make him more interesting.
(screaming)
Ah, there. That's better.
Much better.
Oh, good,
the curtains are on fire.
It's good that you made
that awful thing, Bart.
It's real good.
Hadn't you better
get ready for school?
Okay.
He gets it from your side
of the family, you know.
No monsters on my side.
-Hi, guys.
-Aahh!
Hi, Otto.
Move over, I'm driving.
No can do,
little buddy.
See, there's a rule--
Oh, wait.
You're the little dude
with all the gnarly powers.
(kids screaming)
Quit riding the brake, Otto.
Give it some gas, man.
Hey, this is fun, isn't it?
We're going to die, aren't we?
BOTH: Hiya, Bart!
TEACHER:
Well, class,
the history of our country
has been changed again
to correspond
with Bart's answers
on yesterday's test.
(all groaning)
America was now discovered
in 1942 by...
"some guy"
and our country
isn't called America anymore.
It's Bonerland.
Your attention, please.
This is Principal Skinner.
Bart, this one's for you.
(pitch pipe)
♪ Hello, my baby ♪
♪ Hello, my honey ♪
♪ Hello, my ragtime gal ♪
♪ Send me your kiss... ♪
Phone.
ALL (mumbling):
Happy thoughts,
happy thoughts...
Moe's Tavern.
Hold on. I'll check.
Uh, hey, everybody.
I'm a stupid moron
with an ugly face
and a big butt
and my butt smells and
I like to kiss my own butt.
(laughing)
BARNEY:
That's a new one!
Wait a minute.
(laughing)
(fake laughing)
SKINNER:
One more time.
(pitch pipe)
♪ Hello, my baby ♪
♪ Hello, my honey,
hello, my ragtime gal ♪
Double time now.
I love school.
(yelps)
Come on, come on.
Make it, make it, make it.
Please, please, please.
I want to watch Krusty.
Shut up, boy.
If they make
this field goal,
I win 50 bucks.
ANNOUNCER:
The kick is up.
It's looking good.
The ball is turning into
a fat, bald guy.
Aahh!... oof!
ANNOUNCER: And it's no good,
and you know what we say
every time
something strange happens--
it's good that
Bart did that.
It's very good.
(weary laugh)
Well, we're still on.
346 consecutive hours
and all because of
one little boy who--
who won't let me stop!
Anyway, now let's go over
and see if Sideshow Mel
has any more of those legal
over-the-counter
wake-up drugs of his.
(kids cheering)
(thinking)
Slowly, slowly.
Don't make a sound.
Don't even think
because he can
hear your thoughts.
Then, when he's least
expecting it
bash his head in
with a chair.
End of monster.
(chuckles)
(Homer shrieks)
(gasps)
Bart!
Lisa did it.
That's it, young man.
You're coming with me.
Please?
You like attention
don't you, Bart?
Do I ever.
Well, we all do.
The problem is that
you don't care
whether you get
good attention for, say,
getting high marks in school
or bad attention
for, say,
turning your father into
a Jack-in-the-box.
Homer, I see you agree
with my theory.
I'm not nodding.
It's the air conditioning.
Well, that's too bad because
the attention the boy craves
should be coming from you.
I want you to spend some
quality time with him.
Get to know him.
Maybe even love him.
(cheering)
D'oh!
Whoa-oh-oh.
(all screaming)
Eeyii!
(grunting)
(yawning)
Good night, son.
Good night, Dad.
You know, these last few days
have been really swell.
I wish there was something
I could do to repay you.
Well, if you wanted to,
you could give me my body back.
You got it.
Oh! Hey, hey.
Oh, oh...
Thanks, boy.
I love you, Dad.
I love you, son.
Aaaaaaaaahhh!
BOTH: Mom! Dad!
My goodness!
What's wrong?
We both had nightmares.
Can we sleep with you?
You both toilet trained?
-BOTH: Yes!
-Well, okay, then.
4:00?
(yawns)
Couple hours, I have
to get up and go to work.
Got to go to work.
Go to work...
(snoring)
MR. BURNS:
Ooh, look at them, Smithers--
goldbrickers,
lay abouts,
slugabeds.
Little do they realize
their days of suckling
at my teat are numbered.
Oh, in the meantime, sir,
may I suggest a random firing,
just to throw
the fear of God into them?
Very well.
Eeny, meeny, miny--
Ugh! Him!
SMITHERS (on PA):
Attention, Homer Simpson.
Wake up, Homer.
What? Huh? What?
-SMITHERS: You're fired.
-For what?
SMITHERS:
For sleeping on the job.
How did you know
I was sleeping?
SMITHER:
We've been watching you
on the surveillance camera.
Camera?
D-ohhh!
Smithers.
To the laboratory.
(thunderclap)
You know, Smithers
I've always despised
the laziness
of the common worker.
Then I realized
his spirit was willing
but the flesh was weak.
So I replaced the flesh,
which is weak,
with steel,
which is strong.
Behold!
The greatest breakthrough
in labor relations
since
the cat o' nine tails!
How long till it's
up and running, sir?
Keep your pants on,
Smithers.
First we need...
a human brain.
Hey, here's
a good job, Dad.
Oh, wait. You have to know
how to operate
an ultrasonic
lithontriptor.
How hard can it be?
Hey, Dad, here's one.
$28 an hour,
plenty of fresh air
and you get to meet
lots of interesting people.
Ooh, what job is that?
Gravedigger.
(diabolical laugh)
(grunting)
Deeper, wider, faster.
I wouldn't bury my turtle
in that mud puddle.
What's the use?
Sheesh!
What a slave driver.
(yawning)
(snoring)
(howling)
What corpse
should we unearth, sir?
I don't know.
I feel like a kid
in a candy store.
Hello!
An open grave.
Smithers,
get him out quickly.
The stench is overpowering.
Wait a minute, sir.
That's Homer Simpson.
He wasn't exactly
a model employee.
Well, who is a model...
employee?
(shuddering)
Simpson will do just fine, sir.
(grunting)
Did you hear that, sir?
No, I didn't.
Who is it,
Frankenstein?
The Boogerman?
It's the man in the bag, sir.
I think he's alive.
Oh.
Bad corpse. Bad corpse.
(muffled scream)
Stop scaring Smithers.
Satisfied?
Thank you, sir.
(whirring)
Excellent.
Smithers, hand me
that ice cream scoop.
Ice cream scoop?
Damn it, Smithers!
This isn't rocket science,
it's brain surgery!
All right.
♪♪ (humming
"If I Only Had a Brain")
Hello...
look at me--
I'm Davy Crockett!
(giggling)
Look, Smithers--
a twitch.
It's moving!
It's alive!
Oh, that fellow at Radio Shack
said I was mad.
Well, who's mad now?
(maniacal laugh)
Hi, there.
I'm your daddy.
HOMER'S VOICE:
Mmm!
Mmm! Sprin-kles.
JOHNNY CARSON:
Geraldo Rivera,
Madonna,
and a diseased yak.
LISA:
Mom, what's wrong?
It's your father--
he's missing.
Dad's missing?
Get out of here.
He's been gone for two days.
What do you know?
She's right.
It wasn't supposed
to be this way.
It was supposed to be
a thing of beauty,
not this abomination.
(snoring)
Oh, Smithers,
I was wrong to play God.
Life is precious,
not a thing
to be toyed with.
Now take out that brain
and flush it down the toilet.
Sir, his family
might appreciate it
if you returned the brain
to his body.
Oh, come on. It's 11:45!
Oh, Smithers
when you look at me
with those puppy dog eyes...
All right.
Ow... ow...
ow... ow...
Oh, will you
quit your complaining.
Sir, do you know
what this means?
He is alive.
Ooh, you're right,
Smithers.
I guess
I owe you a Coke.
And as for you
you clinking, clattering
cacophony
of collagenous cogs
and camshafts--
take... that!
Aahh!
Run, sir.
(panting)
Every bone... shattered,
organs...
leaking vital fluids,
a slight headache,
loss of appetite.
Smithers, I'm going to die.
Sir, is there nothing I can do?
Well, perhaps.
Smithers,
go to my office.
In the third drawer
of my desk are...
surgical tools...
and some ether.
Aaaaaaaaaaaahhh!
Did you have
a nightmare, Homie?
No, Bart bit me.
Hey, man,
you were crushing me.
I tried to scream,
but my mouth was full of flab.
Got to go shake the dew
off the lily.
Aahh!
Perhaps you're wondering
why you have two heads.
Well, my body was crushed,
so I had my head grafted onto
your, shall we say,
ample frame.
I can wake up.
It's all a dream.
It's just a dream.
Oh, that's right.
It's all a dream...
or is it?
(diabolical laughter)
Next week on
"The Simpsons"...
Don't forget, Dad.
Tonight my class is having
an all-you-can-eat
spaghetti dinner.
Mmm... spaghetti.
But Homer, tonight's
our reception
for Queen Beatrix
of the Netherlands.
Oh, I hate
having two heads.
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.