-CHOIR: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
-Whoa!
(sneezes)
HOMER: Hmm?
Our first anniversary.
And we're more in love than ever.
In your face, people who said
it wouldn't last a year!
I stand by my wedding toast.
Let's just enjoy our happiness, Homie.
Accidental motherhood
is the greatest thing
that can happen to a woman.
And I think Bart's finally
outgrown his misbehavior.
(Homer shrieks)
(shrieks)
(grunting)
(pop)
Oops, better clean that off.
(humming)
You have a great day, ma'am.
(sighs)
Wish I could get a little
of that attention.
D'oh!
Hey, Simpsons.
Don't mean to be a pesto,
but I'll be happy to watch
your scampi shrimp.
Aw, thanks, Flanders.
Got to warn you, he doesn't talk much.
Daddy.
(groans) He's not your daddy.
Nice daddy.
Moustache daddy.
Good daddy no yell.
-(grunts)
-Fat daddy smell like beer.
I'll teach you to speak
in complete sentences.
But first, m'lady,
let me escort you to Heaven.
The fancy Swiss chocolate store
on level three.
Oh...
Oh, Homer, you're
the anchor store of my heart.
Just call me Borders Books,
'cause I'll always be here.
(theme from Love Story playing)
Haw haw!
His first word.
Oh, Homie, what a wonderful anniversary.
Yep, we've got something money can't buy.
Love on a train.
And I promise each anniversary
will be better and better.
Oh.
They have to get off and get back on.
Sometimes you have
to say to hell with rules.
(grunting)
But somehow our anniversaries
didn't get better
than that first one on the train.
Wait, you named me after a train?
Yeah, just like we did with Bart.
Anyway, this year, I'm gonna re-create
our magical first anniversary,
ending with a romantic ride
on that... (gasps)
Why are you taking away the train?
I'm afraid no one rides it anymore
despite millions in government subsidies.
So we're replacing it
with something that makes money
and sends people to the food court.
Step right up. Medical marijuana.
You got nausea, my friend?
Everyone's got nausea.
And what is your malady, my son?
Uh, I had one, but I forgot it.
Memory loss!
Could be a brain tumor.
Take this and go see Fantasia.
(Homer moaning sadly)
Kids, I've only had three great ideas--
marrying your mother,
using a hot dog as a straw
and this romantic train ride anniversary.
Sir, I need this train.
Eh, take it home. It's yours.
Are you sure Mom is really gonna want
a rusted-out kiddie train?
She won't see it like this.
I'll make this train look as beautiful
as it did when this mall was young.
Aw, Dad, I just got
a little twinge in my heart.
-Try this.
-You stay away from my kids
unless you're driving them to school!
So, I'm not babysitting tomorrow night?
Oh, we're still on for tomorrow night.
Dad, do we have to ride like this?
Hey, what could be cooler than
a choo-choo with lollipops on it?
Hey, babies-- where you
going in your baby train?
Babytown?
Shake it off, kids-- they're just jealous.
Hey, lardo, where you
going in your lardo car?
Lardville?
There's no such place!
(laughing)
Okay. I've entered my billing address,
expiration date... and charged.
We're back from "Baby Beethovens."
(playing Mozart's
"Eine Kleine Nachtmusik")
That's Mozart, dummy.
Well, thanks for watching Maggie.
I just ordered Homer's anniversary gift.
Must be tough.
Yeah, what size cuff links
do you get an elephant?
Well, in the first place,
the elephant's cuff links
would be the same size.
It's the cuffs that would be bigger.
As for Homer, I'm getting him a case
of his favorite snack cakes,
Dolly Madison.
Marge, this isn't Dolly Madison.
It's Sassy Madison.
Trust me, Homer doesn't care
where the cupcakes come from.
Sassy Madison is a dating site
for married people
who are tired of the same old dessert.
(gasps)
Check out their webvertisement.
♪ Kelly was at the end of her wits ♪
♪ Her husband was truly the pits ♪
♪ Her relationship spousal ♪
♪ Had zero arousal ♪
♪ Then she watched this commercial ♪
♪ And found herself Herschel ♪
♪ Thanks to Sassy Madison.com ♪
ANNOUNCER: Sassy Madison.com.
It's not cheating if you
don't know the person well.
I just put all my personal
information on their Web site.
So now you're gonna get hit on
by every loser in town.
And this town's got losers like
Mexico has headless corpses.
So many unhappy men.
How sad.
You've got a lot of fish
wriggling in that net.
Maybe I should get married
so I can date these guys.
Selma, cheating is a sin.
As much a sin as not replying
to an instant message.
So, if you'll excuse me,
I've got a lot of sleazy
gentlemen to let down gently.
(Sassy Madison commercial jingle playing)
Are you watching the commercial again?
I'm a fan of animation.
LOVEJOY: Oh, Lord,
may thy couplings stay forever locked,
and may thy dead man switch
never be used.
ALL: Amen.
All right, guys, let's get this train
fixed up for Homer's anniversary.
But first, start your power tools.
(laughs)
(sighs)
One more to go, and I'm done.
"Dear Horny in Haverbrook:
Sorry. I'm not interested
in cheating on my wonderful husband,
who is described in the attached PDF.
Say hello to my trash folder.
Marge Simpson."
Hi, Homie!
A crazy thing happened when I was
ordering your anniversary gift.
HOMER: Don't blow the surprise.
Pretend you forgot.
Uh, anniversary? That coming up?
Yes, and it's a big one.
Remember?
Marge,
I am focused on this like a laser.
(laughs) "Laser."
That's a funny word.
It's just "loser" with an "A."
And speaking of losers,
I lost my train of thought.
Oh, and speaking of trains,
wait till you see...
(shrieks)
The surprise is safe.
The expression on her face
will be priceless.
(groans)
He forgot our anniversary again?
He remembers the exact number
of pork chops in the freezer.
Currently-- zero.
(humming happily)
-(computer chimes)
-(groans)
One of those cyber smoochers
wrote me back.
MAN: Thanks for your note.
You seem way too nice for this site.
-Why are you here?
-Good question.
"I thought I was buying snack cakes."
That's so cute. Really, really cute.
You... you are over 18, right?
"I am, and you seem more interested
in my day than my husband."
I know what it's like
not to be listened to.
Please ignore every
sensible instinct you have
and continue this conversation.
And by the way, this is my real voice.
(phone rings)
HOMER: Don't worry, Moe.
When Marge is asleep,
I'll sneak back.
Oh, good, the strippers are here.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah!
That is all coming off.
(groans)
"Tell me more."
Homie, I bet you're wondering
why I stayed on
the computer until 4:00 a.m.
Hey, those Yelp reviews
don't write themselves.
Did you know a well-placed
one star can destroy
a mom-and-pop hardware in nothing flat?
Listen, I want us
to be honest with each other.
HOMER:
Uh-oh. If you're honest,
you'll have to tell her about the train.
Huh? What train?
How stupid are you?
Hey, thinking is your department, jerk.
That's what I pay you in beer for.
Just for that, I'm not gonna help you.
What? Where are you going,
you...? (grumbles)
Oh!
Um, Marge, I have to go.
What? Now? Why?
(shrieks)
(door slams)
(phone dings)
He's writing me again.
Better put a stop to this.
(phone dings nearby)
Is that him getting the text?
He's in the market.
We might have squeezed
the same tomatoes.
Are you Marge?
Ooh, I'm going to hell.
I'm sorry. I didn't even
know you were here.
What a crazy coincidence
that you buy food, too.
Gee, I thought you'd be
some kind of creep.
But you're actually
a perfectly normal-looking...
Whoa! "A" is for "apple," right?
Okay. I'll-I'll just be going.
Wait, wait, wait!
Let me get the stain out.
But not here.
I know a place where no one
in town will see us.
(wind whistling)
(grunts) There you go.
Good as new.
Now, let me at least buy you a coffee,
or dare I say a Danish?
-No Danishes!
-Sorry. I go to pastry way too fast.
I want to be very clear.
I'm a happily married woman.
Going on ten years.
The aluminum anniversary.
Nothing turns leftovers
into swans like aluminum.
MARGE:
What the heck am I saying?
Homer's probably at that bar
right now, getting hammered.
(yells)
All worth it for Marge.
Marge, you are terrific.
I am so glad I reset my distance
filter from 15 to 25 miles.
-Mmm...
-Your Homer is the luckiest man on earth.
Well, he keeps falling
down a cliff and living,
so I guess that's true.
The only time my wife and I talk
is when I apologize.
(posh English accent)
"Life's an infernal muddle,"
as Mr. Drake says on Upton Rectory.
Ooh, I love that show.
Isn't it great?
Finally, a reason to watch TV on Sundays.
Such great characters,
like Buxton, the scheming larder-keep.
Why can't Lady Cavendish see
he's pilfering the aspic?
(shudders)
Uh, does... does Homer watch?
He says shows set during
World War I are too sad.
Particularly how everyone's
always climbing stairs.
You are watching the season
finale this week, right?
Yeah. Alone, I'm sure.
Well, we could, uh... live blog it.
Save that sugar for your coffee, bub.
♪ I've been working on the railroad... ♪
Why are you singing that?
Because it's in the public domain.
-(phone rings)
-Hello!
It's Moe from Moe's Tavern.
Oh, uh, I'd better take this.
You see,
Moe's been depressed and needs
to hear a friendly voice.
(chuckles)
Why the hell are you calling me
at home, you moron?!
Lovejoy went to get a hamburger,
and the whole thing fell apart!
I'm getting cooked like a cabbage.
Then keep quiet like a cabbage!
All right, all right, I'll be right there.
(humming "I've Been Working
on the Railroad")
(groans)
Is it me, or did this house
just get classy?
(laughing and grunting)
Mom, Lisa made me break a lamp.
Mom, Bart's twisting facts
in an Orwellian fashion.
Can I have one hour of grown-up time
where you two aren't
tattling on each other
or using obscure references?
Orwell, obscure?
The author of Animal Farm?
Grampa says he was a Commie.
No tattling!
ANNOUNCER: Upton Rectory is made
possible by a sizeable endowment
from Hooters Restaurants,
and a generous grant from a man
named Generous Grant.
(phone rings)
Are you watching it?
No, I can't.
My wife's watching a reality show
about a man
who repossesses zoo animals.
Come on, Taser that flamingo!
(electrical buzzing, flamingo shrieking)
Can't believe I'm missing the finale.
Hmm... Maybe I can help.
Bless it all, Polly, I love you!
And we shall be wed
by Boxing Day Eve, aka Christmas.
But Lord Upton has forbidden it,
on the grounds
that he once saw me exchange pleasantries
with the Egyptian riding master.
Can you follow everything okay?
I guess sometimes you just don't end up
with the person you're supposed to.
Marge, can I use
your free Amazon shipping?
Not a good time!
I know your password!
Drake, Polly, perhaps I was too hasty.
(gasping)
Love should flower,
even an ill-advised alliance
between a coarse Irish maid
and a man who once served me
soup from the wrong side.
He hasn't been the same
since the war, Lord Upton.
Hush, Polly.
Whom you marry is none of your concern.
I have something to say.
The dowager grandmum!
I'm afraid you cannot marry...
without a proper ring.
Take mine-- the Star of Bombay.
Once again, India is denuded
of her treasure
by the imperialist devils.
Why do we watch this show?
Because I like the costumes!
(elegant classical music plays)
(both sigh)
I've never felt so flushed
after watching public television.
Maybe sometime we could...
watch it in the same room.
-Chat room?
-Room room.
Show's over!
(sighs)
That turned ultra-steamy in a jiff.
I can still hear you.
(screams)
-(grunts)
-(door opens)
-Happy anniversary, Mom!
Our gift is us!
Three kids with no money,
but plenty of love!
-(noisemaker blares)
-(gasps) That's great.
I wonder what surprise
your father has in store.
(Homer yelling and groaning)
HOMER: Boy, oh, boy!
Oh, Marge, I threw my back out!
Can you please refill this
prescription right away?
(sighs) Where's it from?
It's in Drugtown... not the nice part.
That'll take hours! On our anniversary!
And what better way
to spend it than commemorating
the glorious words
you spoke ten years ago:
"for worse." Oh!
-Oh!
-Ow!
(groans)
Ooh!
(moaning)
-(groans)
-(chuckles)
Hmm.
(chuckling)
It's working.
She's gone.
All right, everyone, magically appear.
Wow, Moe, great shrub costume.
Yeah. I sell 'em on the Internet
for like-minded people.
Now, let's lay some track.
You guys are the best.
I just want you to know
when I'm holding Marge
in my arms tonight,
I'll be thinking of all of you.
(all cheer, then groan)
(dog howling)
When does it get better?
When he's 800 pounds and has to be
cut out of the house to go to a movie?
I lost my cleaning stick in my belly fat.
But I found a kitten.
(meows)
That is so sweet.
There I go again, settling.
Marge, run off with me. Bring your kid.
I have three kids.
Whoa, you really went all in
with this guy, didn't you?
Get out of my head.
I guess this is good-bye, then.
♪ Someday ♪
♪ When I'm awfully low ♪
♪ When the world is cold... ♪
-I said no!
-Fine. Sorry.
♪ Just thinking of you, Marge ♪
♪ And the way you look tonight ♪
The Nelson Riddle Orchestra!
Leave me alone!
Fine.
Sorry, guys, you're dead again.
I'm gonna do what I've done
at every key point of my life:
suck it in and smile.
(grunts)
There goes a woman
who's unhappy with her partner.
Yeah, I know how she feels.
Yeah. What was that?
(chuckles)
(train whistle blows)
What the...?
Happy anniversary!
(gasps) Oh, my God.
Our train.
Homie, you do care.
You care a lot.
What a wonderful anniversary.
Do you think we'll last 25 years?
Nothing should.
Trains... they can fix every marriage.
(phone dings)
What the...?
Ugh. Happy moment derailed
by the Bipolar Express.
(chuckles)
None of you heard that.
ALL: Happy anniversary!
Where is she?
Where the hell is Marge Simpson?
Ramona, please! When you asked me
who she was and where she lived,
I never dreamed you'd go confront her!
Mmm, I'm Marge Simpson.
So... you're the kind of man-eater
Hall and Oates warned us all about.
Hall and Oates? What's going on here?
Your wife and my husband
have been watching British TV together!
Costume drama or naughty comedy?
Drama! Drama!
You just dodged a bullet,
Mr. Sugarpants.
Ben, Ramona,
I want to tell you something
I've learned over ten years of marriage.
The secret is: no secrets,
except good secrets like this train.
(indistinct chatter)
My only secrets are:
my marathon time isn't 4:26; it's never,
I often go online to see how Lindsay
Wagner's looking now-- fabulous--
and I once pushed a kid off a swing
and he broke his wrist or something.
But it's no secret
how much I love my Margie.
-Mmm...
Look at them, coochie-cooing
like that time
our connecting flight
was delayed and we got drunk
and friendly in the Admiral's Club.
That was you?
I mean, it-it was wonderful.
And you're fighting for me.
Maybe that means you still care.
Of course I do.
Now, let's go home
and spend a romantic night
looking through your computer's
browsing history.
That exists? Oh, boy.
Honey, just what was going on
with you and that guy?
Well... (clears throat) I was
trying to buy you snack cakes...
Oh, baby, that's all I needed to hear.
(moaning)
(classical music playing)
How did we get here?
WOMAN: ♪ Marge was feeling
lonely and bored ♪
♪ Every night she was ignored ♪
HOMER:
♪ But when Marge went boo-hoo ♪
♪ I was building a choo-choo ♪
HOMER and MARGE:
♪ And love conquered all ♪
♪ With a train from the mall ♪
(train whistle blows)
WOMAN:
♪ So that very same night ♪
♪ Ben went back on the site ♪
♪ And he lined up a date
with Selma_B_88 ♪
♪ She said that she's smokin' ♪
♪ And I wasn't jokin' ♪
(screams)
♪ Find love on the net ♪
♪ You deserve what you get ♪
♪ Three awesome kids
and a life of regret ♪
(groans)
And now it's time for Grampa's song!
♪ Down by the old ♪
♪ Not the new, but the old, mill stream ♪
♪ Not the river, but the stream ♪
♪ Where I first--
not the second or the... ♪
Shh!
Subtitled by A. Vandelay