♪ The Simpsons ♪
(chalk screeches)
(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(tires screeching)
(horn honks)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
Would you turn off
that rock n' rock music?
Hey, don't have
a stegosaurus, man.
(laughing)
These talking dinosaurs
are more real
than most
real families on TV.
Ooh! Ooh! Ooh!
Hee hee hee. Look, Maggie,
they have a baby too.
It's like they saw our lives
and put it right up on screen.
Now kids, I know
you're all excited
about meeting Aunt Selma's
new boyfriend tonight.
-(raspberry)
-But I think that before he gets here
I should tell you
something about him.
Something disturbing.
Ooh!
Eyugh!
You see, Aunt Selma has
this crazy obsession
about not dying alone.
So in desperation,
she joined this prison
pen pal program.
Her new sweetie
is a jailbird.
Cool, he can teach us
how to kill a man
with a lunch tray.
Now, now, he's
an ex-convict.
He's paid his debt
to society.
Then how come
you're not using
the good silverware?
I'm just not.
-(doorbell rings)
-That's them.
Remember, everyone,
be understanding
and forgiving
for the sake
of family unity.
Everyone,
I'd like you to meet...
BOTH:
Aah! Sideshow Bob!
SELMA:
What the--
Selma, dear, I'm afraid
the children's reaction
is quite understandable.
You see, Bart here is
the shamus in short pants
who sent me
to prison.
That's right, Aunt Selma.
Your new boyfriend here
framed Krusty the Clown
for armed robbery.
(gasps)
Gee, if some snot-nosed
little kid sent me to prison,
the first thing out,
I'd find out where he lives
and tear him
a new belly-button.
(grunts)
Lousy snitch.
Yaah!
(nervous laughter)
(chuckles)
Ah, Mr. Simpson, you're forgetting
the first two noble truths
of the Buddha.
-I am not.
-Yes, you are.
One:
Existence is suffering.
Two: The cause
of suffering is desire.
In this case, my desire
to do high-quality
children's programming.
When prison put
an end to that dream,
I became a seething cauldron
of rage and recrimination.
(growls)
(monkey hooting)
(Krusty chuckling)
When I was nominated
for best supporting performer
in a children's program
at the daytime Emmy awards,
my bitterness ruined
what should have been
the greatest night of my life.
And the nominees are:
Droopy drawers,
Colonel Coward,
Pepito, the biggest cat
in the whole wide world,
Sideshow Bob,
and Suckup the Vacuum.
And the Emmy goes to...
Oh, I don't believe this...
Sideshow Bob.
(applause)
This is one more Emmy
than you'll ever win,
you bantering jack-in-the-box!
Just don't drop that thing
in the shower, Bob.
-No-talent, shill!
-Second banana!
-Panderer!
-Bore!
Stop it! I can--
Release me!
Uh, now for the highlight
of the evening,
best film-to-video transfer.
Do you know
what prison is like
for a life-long,
conservative Republican?
In our overcrowded cell
we became little more
than beasts.
Who used my chap stick?
Oh, I did.
Here you go.
I don't want it.
My only joy came with plotting
a horrible revenge
against the boy
who put me there.
Ay, caramba!
Bart, if I
wanted to kill you,
I'd have choked you
like a chicken
as soon as I walked in
that door.
(all gasp)
But then what kind
of a guest
would I have been?
(laughing)
Now, where was I?
Ah, yes. My lowest ebb.
You can't take
my Emmy.
Hey, you know the rules.
Awards for excellence
in entertainment are contraband.
No Emmys, no Oscars,
not even
a Golden Globe.
But kismet can be kind,
as well as cruel.
I received an answer
to my letter
from the prison
pen pal program.
SELMA:
"Dear #24601...
"I need a man
and I cannot find one
"among the law abiding.
"I have a steady job
and a lucrative hobby:
"filing nuisance lawsuits.
"I share an apartment
with my twin sister.
"Enclosed is a photo of us
"on a tandem bike.
I forget which one I am."
BOB:
"Dear Selma...
"your latest letter
set off a riot
in the maximum-security wing
of my heart."
Ohhh...
(pffft)
Like the lone crocus
that pokes through the prison yard,
our love bloomed
despite all obstacles.
Selma, may I?
Uh, uh, uh.
On the cheek.
(kissing)
Inspired by the love
of a good woman,
I resolved to be
the best darned inmate
#24601 I could be.
I bade farewell
to my cellmates,
and left with
the woman I loved.
Cutter.
Icepick.
Snake.
I'm going to miss you
most of all.
ALL:
Aww!
What a beautiful story,
sideshow Bob.
You're living proof
that our revolving-door
prison system works.
Selma, I've never
seen you so happy.
Giggling like a schoolgirl.
(hoarse giggles)
I've got to admit it,
Selma,
he's a once-in-a-lifetime
catch.
Yes, I hope the police
are saying that as well.
(laughing)
I can't believe you guys.
This man framed
Krusty the Clown.
-Bart!
-Indeed, I did
and I'd like to thank you
for catching me, Bart.
You seized the wheel
of my slow boat to hell,
and pointed it
straight towards
the sunny shores of Selma.
Hear, hear.
Selma, would you mind
if I did something
bold and shocking
in front of your family?
All right,
but no tongues.
Although kissing you
would be like kissing
some divine ashtray,
that's not what
I had in mind.
Selma, will you marry me?
(gasps)
Don't be a fool,
Aunt Selma.
That man is scum.
Then call me "Mrs. Scum."
SIDESHOW BOB:
♪ I know I stand in line ♪
♪ Until I think
you have the time ♪
♪ To spend
an evening with me ♪
♪ And if we go
someplace to dance ♪
♪ I know that
there's a chance ♪
♪ You won't be leaving
with me ♪
SIDESHOW BOB:
♪ And afterwards, we drop into ♪
♪ A quiet little place ♪
♪ And have a drink or two ♪
BOB AND SELMA:
♪ And then I go and spoil it all ♪
♪ By saying
something stupid ♪
♪ Like "I love you" ♪
(pleasurable moaning)
Could you... pumice
my corns for me?
Avec plaisir.
HANS MOLEMAN:
"A"... "G"...
"Q"... Seven...
Close enough.
May you drive safely
and find true love.
ANNOUNCER:
We now return to the 27th annual
Krusty the Clown telethon
for motion sickness.
Tympani.
(drum roll)
Whoo-hoo! I love you people!
I love my kids!
Poor little guys.
So tragic.
So nauseous.
You should see the bus
they came to the studio in.
(crying)
What's next?
Oh, yeah.
And now, a man who needs
no introduction,
"The Chairman
of the Company"--
You know who
I'm talking about.
Get out here, you gumba!
Krustelah, there's
an old friend backstage
-who wants to say hello.
-Huh? What?
-I can't believe it!
-Oh, they've been feuding for years.
Come here, you.
Oh, you old clown, you.
I missed you.
This guy is
a national treasure.
That jerk I got
to replace you,
he isn't fit to hold
your slide whistle.
All I can be is myself.
Krusty, can you ever
forgive me for framing you
and putting you in jail?
Hey, if they ever open
the books on this telethon,
I'm right back in there.
That sideshow Bob
is a no-good
show biz phony.
Come on, Bart.
If Krusty can find it
in his heart to forgive him,
surely you can, too.
Oh, Krusty,
I can't tell you
how much I missed this.
Ha-ha!
Now, about your
wedding dress...
Mmm. I'm not sure
how to put this...
-White!
-White.
And what would you like
for appetizers?
Ooh, appetizers.
Well, Homer, you seem
to be a trencherman.
What should we serve?
Well, you can't go wrong
with cocktail weenies.
They taste as good
as they look,
and they come in this
delicious red sauce.
It looks like ketchup,
it tastes like ketchup,
but, brother,
it ain't ketchup!
Well, Selma,
he makes a good case.
Eh, get whatever you want.
It all tastes
like Styrofoam to me.
Selma, dear, I'm confused.
Well, when I was a kid,
we were playing
with bottle rockets,
and one shot
straight up my nose.
I permanently lost my sense
of taste and smell.
Okay, we've got cocktail weenies
and Swedish meatballs.
Selma, this wedding is
spinning out of control.
Can we really afford it?
I've already run through
eight of the ten dollars
they gave me
when I left prison.
Hey, relax.
I told you I got money.
I bought stock
in a mace company
just before
society crumbled.
Selma, that's wonderful!
I just hope people
don't think
I'm marrying you
for your money,
instead of your...
less tangible qualities.
(slurps)
Tomorrow we'll be
Mr. and Mrs. Bob Terwilliger.
Isn't it grand?
Hey, Bob, give some
of that honey this way.
Mmm...
Holy frijoles!
We've got ten minutes
till "MacGyver".
Driver, here's a fin.
Get me home,
and don't spare the whip.
Whatever you say, mum.
(belches)
(door slams)
What did I miss?
MacGyver was wearing
a tank top.
Dang.
Why, Selma, I thought I was
the only man in your life.
Sit down and shut up!
MAN:
Thank you, Señor MacGyver,
you saved our village.
MACGYVER:
Don't thank me.
Thank the moon's
gravitational pull.
That MacGyver's
a genius.
First of all,
he's not a genius.
He's an actor.
And second, he's
not much of an actor.
You're lying.
You're lying!
No, Selma, this is lying:
That was a well-plotted piece
of non-claptrap
that never made me
want to retch.
No!
(crying)
(Selma sobbing)
He was so cruel.
The things he said--
They're just not true.
There, there.
Oh, well, I guess
the wedding's off.
Fiddle-dee-dee.
Tomorrow's another day.
-Bart, stop that!
-No, he's right.
We're a package.
Love me, love "MacGyver".
I guess the wedding's off.
Selma, I don't know
what to say.
Just tell me
you like "MacGyver".
Very well. I...
I...
I can't do it!
Even that car chase
seemed tacked on.
(sobbing)
Oh, would you
two knock it off?
I hate all the programs
Marge likes,
but it's no big deal.
You know why?
-No.
-Go on.
Whenever Marge puts on
one of her nonviolent programs,
I take a walk.
I go to a bar, I pound a few,
then I stumble home
in the mood for love.
Very well, Selma.
Whenever you
watch "MacGyver,"
I'll take
a vigorous constitutional,
and return more in love
with you than ever.
Oh, Bob.
Bart no like.
Bad medicine.
(organ playing
"The Wedding March")
I could have been
the flower girl,
and I wouldn't keep
falling down either.
Hey, they chose Maggie,
okay?
Yeah, well, if you want
to go for cutesyness
instead of competence, fine.
Do you, Bob, take Selma,
to have and to hold,
in sickness and in health,
till death
do you part?
(gruesome-voiced)
I do.
(gasps)
(playing generic lounge music)
Mmm.
Oh.
Hey, wiener boy.
Where do you think
you're going?
(munching and gobbling)
I'm the only single girl
left in the family.
Well, I guess
it could be worse.
Oh, there's
Krusty the Clown.
Krusty! Krusty, say
something funny.
Oh, gee, a joke, huh?
Um... Uh... Funny...
Okay, this guy
walks into a bar
and takes out a tiny piano
and a 12-inch pianist...
Oh, no, wait.
I can't tell that one. Oh-ho!
Dear friends, 41 years ago,
God took 168 pounds of clay,
and he made me a woman,
and for this,
I thank him.
I just wanted to say,
on the advice
of my new husband,
I've decided
to give up smoking...
(cheering)
...except for after meals
and after "MacGyver".
Why, Selma, dear, you'll bury us all.
(chuckles)
Chief Wiggum,
you've been around.
You don't trust
sideshow Bob, do you?
Ah. Lighten up, son.
If he was going
to commit a crime,
would he have invited
the number-one cop in town?
Now, where did I put my gun?
Oh, yeah.
I set it down when I got
a piece of cake.
(cheering)
I don't know what to say.
Just tell me what you
know I want to hear.
I'm dying of jealousy.
Thank you.
(shouting farewells)
That's right, dear.
Enjoy your rest.
The wedding was
very tough on you,
and the honeymoon
is going to be...
murder.
(menacing laughter)
Welcome to our
video honeymoon.
We're using the video camera
Cousin Doug gave us,
and the video cassette
Homer gave us.
Hey, and after we watch this,
we can tape over it. (laughs)
There's Shelbyville Falls,
rolling rock,
and here's another
breathtaking sight.
My brand-new hubby.
I wanted a room
with a fireplace,
you brainless
luggage monkey!
Like the one
in your brochure!
Oh, Selma, dear.
I was just chatting with
my good friend... Dennis.
Now, smile for the camera,
that's a good lad.
(metallic squeaking)
Ah, fire.
Scourge of Prometheus,
toaster of marshmallows,
eradicator of dead wood.
Oh, Selma, dear,
you and your little camera.
What do you say we
shut it off for a while?
And make love?
I suppose so.
MARGE:
Oh, that's sweet.
Why would Sideshow Bob
go so nuts over a fireplace?
Because he wants
his honeymoon
to be romantic.
Romantic? With Aunt Selma?
I guess you're just
too young to understand.
Hmm.
(Selma moaning)
Bob, one of my fillings
fell out.
Even murder
has its ugly side.
Bob, would you mind
rubbing my feet?
(shuddering groan)
Darling, you make it
sound like a chore.
Ooh... Oh...
Good... Mmm...
Soon I will kill you.
Huh?
Son pieds sentit beau--
French for
"Her foot smells lovely."
Oh.
Prepare to be murdered.
-Huh?
-(speaking Sanskrit)
That's... Sanskrit for
"Your toes are like perfume."
(laughs)
-Voy a matar a usted.
-Wha..?
That's Spanish for
"I am going to kill you."
Say what?
Why, dear,
I do believe it's time
for your beloved "MacGyver".
-(alarm beeps)
-Oh, hey, you're right.
(metallic squeaking)
-Well, time for my walk.
-Mm.
Don't forget to die.
Ding-dong.
I was feeling kind of
lonely without Selma.
Mind if I watch TV with you?
Oh, go ahead, Patty.
Tonight, on "MacGyver"...
"MacGyver,"
"MacGyver," "MacGyver."
Aunt Selma
has one hour to live.
HOMER:
Hey, down in front.
Goodbye.
(explosion)
(screaming)
Front desk, there's been
a terrible accident in my room!
(glass crunching)
Poor Selma.
You were having such a lovely evening
♪ And then I went
and spoiled it all ♪
♪ By doing something stupid
like explode you ♪
Sideshow Bob,
I'm afraid
the only victims here
are the good people
at Best Western hotels.
Bart!
Selma!
Oh!
You tried to kill me.
I want a separation.
My best-laid plans
have gang agley.
Chief Wiggum, think you
have room in your jail
for a two-time loser?
Well, no, frankly, but that never
stopped us before. Ha!
Bart, I must know,
how did you untangle my web?
Yeah, Bart, clue us in.
Well, I'd hate to tell
the number-one cop in town
how to do his job.
No, no, please, it's
the only way I'll learn.
All right.
Sideshow Bob seemed
so desperate
to get that fireplace,
but why?
Then it hit me.
The gas!
Surely anyone would have
noticed a gas leak
except Aunt Selma.
SELMA: I permanently lost
my sense of taste and smell.
BART:
She happily watched her "MacGyver,"
unaware that her room
was silently filling
with natural gas.
All it needed to explode
was a single spark,
say, from a cigarette.
SELMA:
I've decided to give up smoking
except for after meals
and after "MacGyver".
BART:
Her only hope was a plucky young boy
and his slow-witted father.
Dad, when Aunt Selma
lights up her cigarette
at the end of "MacGyver,"
she'll be blown
to kingdom come.
Come again?
After trying four times
to explain it to Homer,
I explained it to Mom,
and we were on our way!
To the Simpson-mobile!
(tires squealing)
No!
But wait, if you saved Selma,
why did the room explode?
Oh, I'll field that one.
Me and the boys were
all celebrating a job well done,
when I threw my match
in the vicinity
of the crime scene.
Oh, right!
The gas.
I'll be back.
You can't keep
the Democrats out of
the White House forever,
and when they get in,
I'm back on the streets
with all my criminal buddies!
(maniacal laughter)
I feel like such a fool.
Well, he fooled
almost everyone,
but there was one little boy
who never lost his mistrust.
Thanks, Mom.
Now, let's get out
of this gas-filled hallway
before we all suffocate.
(all laughing)
♪♪
Shh.
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.