CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screeching)
D’oh!
(shrieks)
(tires screeching)
(music playing)
(music stops)
(Homer groans)
("Take Me Out to the Ball Game"
plays)
Homer,
what took you so long?
The game’s almost over.
I got hung up
at the snack stand
watching those hot dogs
rolling and turning,
not a care
in the world.
No more lazy Saturdays
for you.
(chomping)
(grunts)
Strike two!
By my calculations, we’re only
one strike away from victory.
Numbers are fun.
This is it, boys.
One more out and we go
to the championship game.
Let’s do it
for Groundskeeper Willie,
who made me this beautiful
black bicep warmer!
It keeps me naughty hands busy.
(grunts)
I got it! I got it!
(groans)
I hogged it!
(trumpets playing)
(crowd cheering)
My son caught the ball!
This makes up
for everything
that’s gone wrong
in my life
or ever will!
I’m also pleased!
After years of failure
in everything we’ve attempted,
we are one victory away
from a championship, people.
And our newfound glory is all
due to these wonderful boys.
(cheering)
Behold
my naked butt!
Each cheek
is a god to you!
FLANDERS:
Now Bart,
stay humble.
Your baseball cap won’t fit
over a swelled head.
Flanders, these boys
have earned the right
to behave like
arrogant oafs.
Can we egg the crowd?
In this modern-day
Deadwood
you can do
anything.
BOYS:
All right.
(laughing and cheering)
Smithers,
I’m missing the fun!
Upsy-daisy, sir.
Ah, what glorious goo!
I need a dress to wear
for my son’s big game.
He’s the star, I’m his mom,
and he’s my son.
Mm-hmm, you’ve
mentioned his name
and batting average
several times.
Well, he’s done very well
for someone
who came out blue
and backwards.
Listen, do you mind
if I hum while you talk?
Not at all!
-(humming)
-He single-handedly
got the team
-to the championship,
first time ever.
-(humming)
My son caught the ball
-that won the game.
-(continues humming)
(sighs)
I hate shopping!
I’m bored; my feet hurt; I’m
too big for the choo-choo train.
Hmm...
where’s the "husband chair?"
Unless you’re serving me
a cold beer,
you keep moving.
(moaning):
Oh!
There must be another chair.
-(cocks gun)
-Eh-eh.
My wife’s lookin’
for a bathing suit
that doesn’t make
her look "horsey."
So, I’m gonna
be here a while.
Mm-hmm.
(moaning)
I guess I could just sit
on a bed.
Wow, this is soft.
Sure feels weird lying on top
of the covers.
Sure feels weird lying in bed
with my pants on.
(sighs)
(snoring)
What in the name of...?
Hey, you!
Whoa! How many?
Are you sleeping in the middle
of my department store?
Well...
who wouldn’t
with an incredible mattress
like this?
It works with my body’s
natural curves
and supports
my back-boobs.
That’s the best
endorsement I’ve heard
since Mickey Mantle
for Maypo!
I’ll take
five mattresses.
I don’t work here.
You do now, son!
(jowly):
You’re hired!
Woo-hoo!
(cheering)
All this fuss
for a baseball game?
Why don’t thousands come to
watch a teacher inspire a child?
But it did happen.
Just yesterday,
in Crazytown!
BASEBALL ANNOUNCER:
So, in the amber gloaming
of this September afternoon,
Shelbyville has
the bases loaded,
but the Isotots
only need one out
to win the championship and get
that pizza party at Luigi’s!
Luigi’s, they deliver on flavor,
but not to your house!
Damas y caballeros,
if the Isotots win, please do
not fire your guns in the air.
The bullets will come down!
And kill my sister.
A lazy pop fly
to star shortstop Bart Simpson.
And this should do it!
Now for the defining moment
of my life.
Huh?
(crowd gasps)
(clamoring)
Simpson drops the ball!
And he kicks it!
And he kicks it again!
And again!
Oh, it’s horrible, but you can’t
take your eyes away!
It’s like watching a monkey
swallow a hand grenade.
The Isotots lose the pennant!
(crowd booing)
(booing continues)
Bart, you choked!
I put on fresh
makeup for this?
(booing)
Knock it off!
He’s just a kid!
Aw, hey that’s the guy
what created him!
If Homer had used
some protection,
we’d all be poopin’
roses on easy street!
Hey, get off my case!
He’s the choke artist!
(crowd booing)
Quick, Bart,
Bart, get in!
(sighs)
Thanks, Chief.
Don’t mention it, son.
He’s back!
Go nuts, everyone!
(crowd booing)
Bart’s coming down!
Hide the sports section!
D’oh!
Good morning, sweetie.
There’s nothing you can say.
After that game,
my life is over.
Was there even a
baseball game yesterday?
I don’t remember...
Marge, we were just talking
about it a few seconds ago.
Don’t you have to get to your
job as a mattress salesman?
Oh, yeah. Let’s see
where that goes.
Let me tell you
about a land
where it rains beer
and hails pretzels
and you can play swim-up
blackjack with Abraham Lincoln.
It’s the land of sleep.
And your passport:
a simple mattress.
Heh-heh-heh-heh-heh-heh-heh.
Yes, I need to be able to sleep
through my wife’s nagging
and my eight
horrible babies
and the anguished howls
of my ancestors.
A common problem.
Try this.
Oh. Ooh.
Oh, I feel like I’m floating
on a river of corpses.
(clearing throat)
Homer,
we have a friend--
actually a friend
of a friend...
Sex problem, eh?!
Homer, please.
They can hear you
in Fine China.
Relax. I’m a licensed
mattress professional,
if there were
such a thing,
and I’ve got the answer
to your problems:
The Snugulux by Matrimonium.
Ooh, sold.
And remember: your
most intimate secrets
are safe with me.
(louder):
Okay, who else
is dead in bed?
BILL:
You’re listening to KBBL,
your official
"Bart Simpson sucks" station.
Oh-ho, and here comes
another "Bash Bart Block,"
starting with this
entry from Jimbo,
Dolph, and Kearney.
JIMBO/DOLPH/KEARNEY (on tape):
♪ Bart stinks ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
-♪ Bart stinks... ♪
-(clicks radio off)
Oh, my favorite
song ruined!
Bart, come with me.
I’ll take you to someone
who will make you feel better.
Is it my rabbit
Cottontail?
The one who went
to live upstate?
He died, Bart.
Dad buried him
in the backyard.
But not in that order.
(gasps)
Bart,
meet Joe LaBoot.
LaBoot, LaBoot.
Sounds familiar.
You probably remember me
from 1943 World Series.
With the score
tied in game seven,
Tommy Heinrich of the
Yankees hit a ball
in my direction.
Jugglin’ Joe LaBoot
they called me.
When I finally
picked up the ball,
I threw it into the stands,
hitting Eleanor Roosevelt,
who up till then
had been a great beauty.
We lost the game
and the series.
(chuckles):
But I bounced back.
Got my own car
dealership.
I have 17 grandchildren
and a big home in Idaho.
It’s a great life!
Yeah, in Idaho.
And at these card shows,
the fans let me know
that I’ve put my gaffe
behind me.
You stink, LaBoot!
No, I don’t!
Google my stats!
Take it from me, kid,
you’ll be just fine.
Feel better now,
Bart?
"Bart?!"
Are you Bart Simpson?
The kid who dropped
that easy fly ball?!
You stink like
a Dutchman’s throw-up.
Talking to you was the
biggest error of my life!
(crowd booing)
Boo. Boo, indeed.
The Lovejoys?!
If this is about me
drinking that holy water,
let me tell you,
I had had like
a million Doritos.
You know, the ones
with the flame on the bag?
Oh-ho, that bag
ain’t lyin’!
We’re here about
the mattress.
What’s wrong with it?
We tried raising Cain,
but we weren’t able.
Oh, I think I know
what you’re doing wrong.
Have you tried...
(loud whispering)
I know the mechanics
of lovemaking, Homer!
You owe us a refund!
I’ll write you a check.
"Pay to the order
of Stupid Reverend.
Memo: Bite my ass."
(moaning)
Wha...?!
Homer, I’m not a man
who believes in miracles,
but this bed of yours
could resurrect our sex life.
If you let us
have your mattress,
we’ll give you ours.
On one condition:
you do the shlepping.
Well, I’ll have
to check with my wife.
♪♪
HOMER:
Move over just a...
MARGE:
Ow, well,
maybe if you go...
No, wrong,
wrong, wrong!
I’m sorry, Homie.
I want to snuggle, but
I’m just not feeling it.
Yeah, something has changed,
but I can’t figure out what.
(gasps):
Our mattress!
I traded it to the Lovejoys!
You traded
our mattress?
I had my secret
cash in it.
Oh, that’s long gone, baby.
Long gone.
It was made for Elvis,
but he found it tacky.
But I can’t believe
a mattress
could make
that much difference.
♪ This little light of mine ♪
-♪ I’m gonna let it shine ♪
-♪ Oh, glory ♪
♪ This little light of mine ♪
♪ I’m gonna let it shine ♪
♪ Every day, every day ♪
♪ Every day ♪
♪ Yay, yay, yay! ♪
(Mrs. Lovejoy giggles)
(mumbling):
Lousy Reverend,
he’s having my sex
while I’m at home
with Marge
not doing anything
sensual or erotic.
(birds singing)
(splatters)
(gasps loudly)
(muttering):
A damp sponge will take care
of this weak, water-based...
It’s oil-based!
Oil-based!
Daddy?
Fetch Daddy’s
thinner, boy.
But it’s
in the "stay away" closet.
You just fetch it!
Who would do
this to Bart?
The person who hates Bart
more than anyone else. Look!
Oh, yeah,
that’s really something.
Mom, put your
glasses on.
But they make me
look dowdy.
(gasping)
My baby!
(whimpers)
See? I hate me, too.
Now we can be friends again.
(crazy laugh)
Bart, stop!
No one’s mad
at you anymore, right?
-(crowd murmuring)
-Mm.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
-You know.
-CHIEF WIGGUM: Jump!
Who-Who said that?
I hate Bart Simpson!
I got him! I got him!
You stink,
LaBoot!
Damn it!
He’ll be all right.
Right now he just
needs peace and quiet.
CROWD (chanting):
Bart sucks! Bart sucks!
Bart sucks!
You should all be ashamed!
Passing judgment on a child
for a sports boo-boo!
What have you people ever done?
Well, I wrote a best-selling
series of mystery novels.
Stephen King called it,
"Scary, good fun."
Besides that.
Now, thanks to you,
my special little guy
will be haunted
by this for the rest
of his life.
I always thought
that was just a slogan
to attract
small businesses.
But now I know
it’s the truth.
(crowd murmuring)
Okay, Midge.
You made us feel bad
about what we done to your boy,
but what can
we do about it now?
It’s not like we can play
the game over again.
Can’t we?
Like I just said, we can’t.
Are you sure?
Open your freakin’
ears. No!
I think maybe we...
♪ Could. ♪
And I say,
I have difficulty
♪ Envisioning it. ♪
Let me get this straight.
You want our boys
to play a fake rematch
against Springfield so your son
can make the catch he missed
and feel better about himself.
Exactly.
I guess I could, uh,
if you pretend
to be my fiancée
when my mother comes to visit.
Okay. If you pretend
to be our chauffeur
at my high
school reunion.
Fine, fine, if you pretend
to be a ghost
at an old amusement park
I’m trying to buy.
-We should
stop now.
-Yeah.
You want me to reannounce
a game I’ve already called?
Oh, sister, I got
too much integrity.
The same integrity Farmer Dan
puts into every link sausage.
Then I guess
you wouldn’t mind eating one.
(sloshing)
Of course I wouldn’t.
It’s not like they’re made
of skunk tails
and horse nipples.
(sighs)
I’ll do whatever you say!
Just get that death wiener
away from me!
I’m starting to feel funny
about doing this.
Look, we’re just going
to take our mattress,
do a quick sweep of
the medicine chest,
then we’re
out of here.
(Homer hissing
like drummer’s high hat)
Homer, stop that.
Sorry.
There it is--
Old Bounce an’ Giggle.
(chuckles)
(engine revving,
tires squeal)
You put on
the Michael Bolton CD.
I’ll put on
my edible vestments.
(footsteps running)
HELEN LOVEJOY (gasps):
Oh, my God!
How dare you break
into our house,
defile our bed,
and smash our family photos
with your foot.
Well, excuse me
for being a powerful
yet careless lover.
Reverend Lovejoy, our
marriage needs this bed.
Our marriage
needs it more!
Well,
I am reminded
of the story
of wise King Solomon.
(scoffs)
You would be.
(dings)
I wish he hadn’t
cut it that way.
It looks like a
grilled-cheese sandwich.
Or a chicken club.
Or a-a Reuben.
Or a Monte Cristo, or...
Pull over behind
that billboard!
(engine revving,
tires squealing)
(moaning)
-Oh!
-Oh, yeah!
Oh! You really want
to make love
on half a mattress
behind a billboard?
It’s like our honeymoon
all over again.
Oh!
We even have the same bum
looking at us.
I knew you kids would make it.
Man, you
got fat.
MALE ANNOUNCER:
So, it’s déjà vu all over again
as Springfield needs
just one out to win the game
and the championship.
Who’d have thunk it?
Probably everyone
who was here the last time.
I still can’t
believe it.
They dusted the plate
with a non-regulation brush,
so we have to play
the last inning over again.
I think this time
it’ll have a happier ending.
Why do you think that?
Uh... uh...
Oh! They warned me not
to talk to you.
Who warned you?
Nobody!
(panting)
Oh!
(crowd cheering)
(grunts)
Hello, redemption.
Bart gets another try!
Uh, the batter hit it
by accident, not by design.
(sighs)
Play ball!
(grunts)
(all groaning)
Er, uh, that is also a do-over
’cause, um, er, uh...
There’s a naked idiot
on the field.
(grunts)
(crowd groaning and gasping)
(laughs)
(humming)
(sighs)
(instrumental version of "Take
Me Out to the Ballgame" plays)
(squawks)
Woo-hoo!
D’oh!
(lights click on and hum)
(sighs)
Play ball.
(wind whipping)
I did it!
I did it! I did it!
(weak cheering and applause)
-Oh. Yay.
-All right.
(Homer blows raspberry)
ANNOUNCER:
And the 78th time is the charm!
Now, over the left field wall,
the real show’s about to begin:
the glorious sunrise,
brought to you by God,
the invisible giant you turn to
when you’re about to die.
(spaceships whirring
and humming)
BART:
Hey, Milhouse,
did I ever tell you
about the catch I made
when I was ten?
Greatest moment
of my life.
It was a fake,
you idiot!
We did it
to make you feel better.
A fake?
Then I did suck.
I-I... I do suck!
(sobbing)
No, that was a fake
just now.
You did make the catch.
I knew it!
I rule!
And you drool!
(laughs)
Boy, our son can be
a real jerk.
Hey, do you want
to have ghost sex?
I keep telling you,
ghost sex is nothing.
It’s worse
than nothing.
Then why were you moaning
last time?
Because
I’m a ghost!
(moaning)
(shrieks)
A ghost!
(wind whipping)
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Shh!
Enhanced by Fotokem