♪ The Simpsons 25x20 ♪
Brick Like Me
Original Air Date on May 4, 2014
(snoring)
MARGE: Homie! Homie, wake up!
You're having a nightmare.
HOMER: It's not selling out.
It's co-branding.
- Co-branding!
- MARGE: Wake up!
(Homer grunting)
Oh, honey, the best part of every day
is waking up to your smiling face.
Oh...
Just like the best day
of my life was when you
gave me your hand
in marriage. (pop)
- Ooh.
- (chuckles)
I'd like it back, please.
(barks)
Hey! Drop it,
you stupid dog!
That's one of my
wife's pieces!
She needs it to
reciprocate high fives!
(Homer grunting)
That's okay, Homie.
I'll just grab another.
Mmm...
Oh... I haven't worn this
one since New Year's.
(sizzling)
Hmm. Is it just me, or
does something seem...
weird today?
You're right... something is
different about the Simpsons today.
Your father's
wearing a tie.
Oh, that's what's
different!
- That's the one and only thing.
- Maggie! Stop that!
No more playing
with your food.
Aw, they're so cute
when they're Duplo.
Uh, yes, is this
a toy store?
Uh-huh. I'm supposed to get my
daughter a birthday present...
hmm, what's it called?
Here it is. Perky
Patty's Princess Shop.
- (grunts)
- (groans)
Oh! I'm so sorry... but I
have an awesome excuse:
I was distracted driving.
Oh, don't worry about it.
(chuckles): Good thing
we don't feel pain.
Hey! These are
the monkey's legs!
(whimpers)
(panicked chattering)
Come back! I'm a clown! I can't
afford to look ridiculous!
(school bell ringing)
Hey, Bart, check out what
I brought for share day.
BART:
Whoa! A skunk!
Who should we stink first?
It can't spray...
it's been de-sacked.
Ew! The gypsy
skunk-seller lied!
(panicked yelling)
He went in there!
Stop it! If you pull out those bricks,
the whole school could collapse!
But there's a
skunk in there.
(gasps)
Scottish steak!
(students groaning)
(both gasp)
You are going to rebuild
every brick of this school.
This says: Ages 12 and up.
Age guidelines are conservative,
and everyone knows it.
And to motivate you, some words
of support from the school chum.
Haw-haw!
SKINNER:
Thank you, Nelson.
(Homer humming)
One Perky Patty's
Princess Shop, please.
Ah. Always good to
meet a fellow AMFOP.
- Huh?
- Adult Male Fan of Princesses.
It's for my daughter.
Yes, yes, it's always
for the daughter.
Well, that's weird. I feel like
I've seen this toy before.
(rumbling)
- Do you like it, honey?
- I love it, Dad! Thank you.
Well, have fun
putting it together.
Wait, wha... Dad, don't you
want to build it with me?
Well, there's no dad on the box.
I don't want to get in trouble.
(laughs):
Of course I do!
Mm-hmm.
Well, what do you know?
I enjoyed playing with you.
Me, too, Dad.
No, no, no.
Listen to me.
We played... and
it wasn't boring.
We've played
lots of times.
Of course we have!
Because you're my
girl and I love you.
But I'm letting you
in on a secret.
When parents play with their
kids, they don't like it.
- And I'm no different.
- Oh.
Suddenly I can't breathe.
Every fiber of my being
screams out for a nap.
And if someone handed me an
issue of The New Yorker,
(chuckles): I would
read the fiction.
I swear to God I would.
Wow. But there are millions
of parents in the world.
- Surely some of them like playing with...
- Nope, not even one.
Just look at the things you kids
like: Tea parties with pretend food;
Hide-and-seek with
flagrant peeking;
And the most inhumane torture
ever devised by man...
(shudders)
Candy Land.
- Oh.
- But this...
this is tolerable!
(gasping breaths)
What a crazy vision.
I was in a world where nothing is
made of bricks, except for toys!
Hey, read the sign.
Thank you.
(whimpering)
Marge, I'm telling you,
it was so weird.
My body was squishy, and my hands
looked like snakes made of meat!
It was horrible!
Oh, Homie, it was probably
just a mini-stroke.
You're just saying that
to make me feel better.
Whatever you saw,
it wasn't real.
That's how the
world works.
Everything fits with everything
else, and nobody ever gets hurt.
I know.
Oh, maybe you just
need someone to...
you know, take
your mind off it?
Hm?
I always need that.
I only don't ask because
being rejected...
(breathily):
gets old.
(Homer and Marge sigh)
Oh, baby, I feel so
close to you right now.
(whistling a tune)
(clinking)
(shrieks)
Hmm? Hmm?
Marge? Did you replace
our regular mirror
with a magical mirror
from a mystical salesman
at a weird store that if
we went back to find it,
it wouldn't be
there anymore?
- No.
- (screams)
Okay, Homer, get a grip.
I'm sure lots of people,
every time they look in the mirror,
see a hideous flesh monster.
Just a one-time thing.
(gasps)
Oh, brick me!
Leave me alone! Why don't you
go back where you came from!
I have as much right
to be here as you!
I, sir, am in the
Advent calendar!
- Hmm?
- APU: December 18,
final week! Huh?
Moe, I'm going crazy... I need to kill off
as many of my brain cells as possible.
Well, I'm here to help.
(clinking)
(sputters)
What the...?
This isn't beer.
Beer is plastic circles.
How can I drink...
(shudders) this?
(mug shatters)
Did you guys see... that?
Oh, it's getting worse!
(shrieks)
(grumbling)
Ugh! Rebuilding the
same boring old school.
I could make this place so much
cooler if they just gave me a chance.
(yawns)
(snoring)
(sneaky chuckling)
(gasps)
What have you done
to my school?
I put in a rock-climbing wall, all
the classrooms are skate parks,
we got zip-line stairwells,
Terminator gym teachers,
your office is now a haunted forest... extra
ghosts... and, if you can believe it,
two tetherball poles.
How will children learn if they don't
feel like they're in kid jail?
Relax. I used all
the same bricks.
- Plus Ralph.
- Yo soy language lab.
(groans)
But I don't want to go to church...
I'm too busy going crazy.
Come on, Homie.
When I'm troubled,
I always find solace in the
airtight logic of religion.
"Before the world began,
there was only table.
"Then the Great Constructor
scissored open bag one
"and dumped out the universe.
"Then came the time
of the Great Sorting:
"Color to color, shape to shape, and
a pile of just windows and doors.
"And everything was made
of eternal, unchanging
acrylonitrile
butadiene styrene,"
or in the common
tongue, "plastic."
But, Reverend, what if everything
isn't made of plastic?
I think there's
more to this world.
You mean like decals? Well,
the Orthodox don't use them,
but we're a Reform
congregation.
No. I mean a place where
nothing snaps together
and you just can't toss your kids
in a dishwasher to clean 'em.
(chuckles): Oh, Homer,
a place like that
could only exist in some
kind of magic rock song.
Look around... we live
in a perfect world
where everything fits together
and no one gets hurt.
Mustache is right.
(others agreeing)
But I'm having all
these hallucinations.
Like right now my hands look like
they're these weird wiggly things.
I think they have a name, but
I can't put my finger on it.
(congregation gasps)
Don't look, boys!
(pop)
Wait! You guys see them, too?
He's a freak!
Take him apart and lose the
pieces under the couch!
Well, I don't find
him disgusting.
Oh, boy, that's mushy!
Come on, Marge. We
need real answers,
and there's only one
place we can get them!
Let's see, "fingers."
Come on, show me
something about fingers.
(sighs)
Bad news, people.
Our religion is not true.
Sorry about that.
Really sorry.
If I'm right, when
I touch this box,
it'll trigger another memory
from some alternate me's life.
If I don't come back from that other
place, tell my wife I loved her.
I'm right here.
Promise me!
(rumbling)
I can't believe all the time
I wasted playing with Bart
when I could have
been playing with you.
Aw...
Our little Springfield is
really turning out great.
City Hall, the weird-smelling
bank, Rehab World...
Krustyburger,
Krustyburger Express,
the Krustyburger where
the governor got stabbed...
Oh, you two.
Hey, look what I found in
the "Arts-Weekend-Obituary"
section
of the paper.
LISA (gasps):
A builders competition!
We got to enter
our mini-Springfield.
We're a great team!
We're there.
I'll clear my calendar.
Hey, Lenny, remember those two
surfers we were gonna fight?
Well, you're on your own.
But you're the one who
sat on their fish tacos.
Great talking
to you, buddy.
(chuckles)
Lisa, Lisa, I spent
all day at work
making a Duff brewery
for our mini-Springfield.
I don't want to brag, but...
it really brews.
Huh? Where is she?
Okay, I got us tickets for the
7:30 show of Survival Games.
I've never been to a
PG-13 movie before.
I wonder what the one
swear word will be.
What if it's...
- (whispering)
- (gasps)
Oh, I've never
heard that one.
My grampa said it
at Thanksgiving.
We usually don't hang out
with second graders,
but we saw your Survival
Games book report
hanging in the hallway, and
we were very impressed.
You really understood that the
theme of the book was love.
Hey, older girls,
I'm Homer Simpson.
That's right. Lisa's
playtime partner and BFF.
(girls groaning)
I assume Lisa told you about
the pretend tiny town
she's building with her
overweight father.
Oh, yeah, it's gonna
be mucho fresh.
Come on, honey. It's time
to click some bricks.
I don't know what
he's doing up here.
He usually stays
in the basement.
It's okay, Lisa.
We have dads, too.
I have three dads.
See you Friday.
Friday? But that's
when Brick-Stock is.
Um, actually, Friday is the opening
night of the new Survival Games movie,
and they invited me.
But this was our thing.
I know. I'm sorry,
but cool older girls have never
wanted to hang out with me before.
One of them wears
deodorant.
I don't know which one.
Oh.
All right.
Thanks for
understanding, Dad.
What just happened?
It's not you.
Lisa's growing up.
It's a really complicated time in a
girl's life from age eight to...
actually, all the
rest of the way.
Oh! I finally found something I like doing
with my daughter, and now I've lost it.
I don't fit
into her world.
This is for the tacos!
Ow!
Tacos, brah! Ow!
- What did you build?
- Mmm...
Oh, that's the teenage crossbow ace
who stole my daughter from me.
Keendah Wildwill is a
modern feminist hero...
strong, independent
and resourceful.
She's a little... bustier
than I remember.
My work on that front
is never done.
I wish I lived in
little Springfield.
Everything fits together,
and no one ever gets hurt.
- (yells)
- (groans)
COMIC BOOK GUY:
Okay...
Apparently, our whole world
is a fantasy in the mind
of an emotionally-devastated
Homer Simpson.
One of the main questions
I have about that is, why?
The real Homer fears losing
his daughter's love,
so he invented this toy world
where nothing will ever change.
How can you be sure?
I have devoted my life to
second-rate science fiction.
Trust me, that is what
we are dealing with here.
So if I don't find
my way out of here,
I could be trapped
in a fantasy forever?
I'm afraid so.
(whooping)
I'm trapped in a
fantasy forever!
Kiss my flat plastic
butt, reality.
(giggling)
Ooh.
Daddy-daughter time
will never end!
Inventing this toy world to
live in is the smartest thing
my brain-damaged
brain ever did.
Nothing bad can
ever happen here.
Great throw, Homer.
Put it in Tupperware, boys.
We'll rebuild it tomorrow.
Homie, ask yourself...
can you really live in a paradise
if you know it's just pretend?
Marge, who would give up eating steak
in the Matrix to go slurp goo in Zion?
We don't have
that movie here.
Now Lisa can never ditch me, and
I can play with her forever.
(sighs)
There, I finished.
All 12 of them.
I'll never build
what I want again.
Then you've learned
your lesson.
Too bad I got these
for my birthday.
They always give
me the school.
(groans)
Sparkle Unicorn, would
like some more tea?
Oh, yeah, hook me up with some
more of that imaginary nectar.
I've never seen you throw yourself
into a tea party like this.
Before, it always seemed like
you were kind of phoning it in.
Not anymore, Lisa.
I've created a perfect world with no
PG-13 movies to take you away from me.
(sips loudly)
Ah!
'Cause in a toy town, everything
stays shiny and wonderful,
just the way I want it.
You'll always be
my little girl.
Maggie will always
be my giant baby.
Bart will never move
out of the house.
I'll work for Mr.
Burns forever.
Marge and I will never grow old together
and live like fat cats on Social Security.
Good Lord, I'll never experience the
ultimate reward for a life well lived...
the gentle slumber
of death.
Marge, I made a
terrible mistake!
The fact that kids grow up is what
makes time with them special.
I think I need to go back.
I wish you'd told me that before
I bought all these groceries.
But I understand.
Lego Marge, you're just
as cool as Real Marge.
- Who?!
- Nobody, nobody.
Plastic Comic Book Guy,
I need to go back home.
Home? But you've discovered
the joy of living in a world
made of toys where nothing
bad can ever happen.
But I miss burning
my mouth on pizza,
and David Blaine stunts
where he could really die.
Now tell me how to
get out of here!
All you need to do is open the box
back to your so-called reality.
But I can't let
that happen.
Huh? You're the bad guy?
I thought you were the
rule-explainer guy.
As an adult who surrounds
himself with child's toys,
I represent the part of your psyche
that prefers this artificial world.
(rhythmic clicking,
gate clangs shut)
How did you do that?!
Because, as the ultimate collector,
I have every play set ever made.
(creaking)
Huh?
(gasps) Pirates!
(whooshing, grunting)
Pajama guys!
(gasps)
I'll never get home. Who could build
something awesome enough to save me?
Who?
Who?! Who?!
Don't you even think about it.
(whirring)
You are thinking about
it, aren't you?
(whimpering)
(loud, rhythmic thudding)
You are going back
where you came from...
Denmark.
What is that thing?
I have no idea, but it's
gonna kick his butt.
That robot is made
out of Batmobile,
Hobbit Hole and
SpongeBob play sets.
That's... that's
mis-set-genation.
(in robotic voice):
Kid power.
BART: Lion blast!
(whirring, rapid gunfire)
Lightsaber barf!
(click, whirring, whooshing)
Fire Principal!
This is strangely
exhilarating.
No. No.
(crying): No!
I am going to enjoy playing
with this thing forever!
(Bart grunting)
I'm a creative but
undisciplined builder!
(Homer grunts,
Comic Book Guy groans)
(anxious whimpering)
(magical whirring)
Good-bye, Homie.
Your squishy meat family is lucky
to have a good man like you.
Oh, baby, no matter what the reality,
you're the best thing in it.
Hmm. That was a
little weird, right?
(laughs)
A little bit.
(whirring)
(yelling)
LISA:
Dad, wake up.
Wake up.
Oh, Meat Lisa, it's you.
Are you okay?
Oh, I had this crazy dream where I
was in a world made of Lego bricks
and learned important
lessons about parenting.
Mmm, isn't that kind of
the plot of the...?
No. No, it's not.
It's a new plot.
Honey, what are you doing here? I
thought you were going to your movie.
I changed my mind. I knew
how much this meant to you.
No, no, go to the movie
with your friends.
If there's one thing I've learned, it's
that I can't stop you from growing up.
I love you, Dad.
Me, too, little girl.
♪ ♪
Thayson, Joshuel, don't make
me pick between you two
on the night before I reenter
the Struggle Dome again.
We'll never stop loving you, even
if you string us along forever.
- Forever.
How can I choose between two boys, one
who's dangerous but good-looking,
the other who's strong
but super cute?
ALL (sighing):
Ah!
Oh, my God, this
is terrible.
When do they get to
killing the children?
Shh!
Wait a second.
You're not into this...
Shh! She's trying
on dresses.
Oh, I just wanted to see kids
fight to the death, is all.
Shh...!
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
Shh!