CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(school bell ringing)
(Barney belches)
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
(grunts)
(trumpets)
(croaking)
George, I'm sorry
to see you up here.
Well, yes, but I died
for a worthy cause.
As we speak, my body
is about to be dissected
by a budding
young scientist.
Let's observe
the dedication to learning
of this ten-year-old scholar
by the name of Bart Simpson.
♪ Stab, stab, stab, stab,
stab, die ♪
♪ Stab, stab, die, die,
death, kill ♪
Well, his passion
is undeniable.
Yes, very...
very impressive.
By examining my specimen's
pyloric sphincter valve,
I deduced that she had
an affinity for fruit flies.
By examining my specimen's
natty dreads,
I was able to deduce that he was
a jammin' Rasta-frogian.
My body,
my little green body.
Okay, but surely
his portrayal
of Rastafarianism
will be culturally sensitive.
Pass the Dutchie.
We be smokin' slabba-slabba
wit da Babylon.
Ribbit, ribbit, mon.
(panting loudly)
Come now, George.
At least this Scottish
groundskeeper
will give your remains
a respectful burial.
WILLIE: Into the crapper you go,
useless froggy garbage.
(toilet flushing)
Are you going to put
a good spin on that, too?
Hmm? Are you?!
Well, are you?
Well, uh... ribbit?
MARGE: I can't put these grades
on the refrigerator.
I can't even put them
on the garage refrigerator.
It's not my fault.
-I blame "so-key-ity."
-What?!
You know, so-key-ity.
That's what everyone
blames for everything.
You mean "society"?
-Yeah, that's the guy.
-Honey,
I know you're a bright boy,
but if you don't try harder
in school,
you could end up...
...not a success.
Oh, that.
Don't worry, Mom.
As long as I can stand on a corner
and spin a sign reading "new condos,"
I'll be just fine.
(groaning)
(Marge groaning)
All that pacing
isn't gonna fix the boy.
Just get him some pills.
Two pinks and a blue,
and it's off to the races.
Everything we've tried
with Bart has failed.
What if there's nothing
we can do?
Mm, "nothing we can do"
is a whole lot better
than "it'll take all we've got."
I wonder if anyone talks
about parenting online.
Look at this one!
HOMER:
They're skiing.
Skiing means happy.
Hmm, an expert with
a new book to promote.
Oh, I wonder if she'd be willing
to speak to a group for a fee.
Getting your child established
on the path to success
isn't easy.
I was driving my daughter
from her falconry tournament
to lute class
when she turned to me asked...
(speaks Mandarin)
...which is Mandarin for,
"How do you do it?"
She and I are learning Mandarin.
The answer?
(speaks Mandarin)
Positive reinforcement.
(inquisitive chatter)
In a recent study,
this mouse was denied food
whenever he failed
to find his way through a maze.
The mouse ended up dying...
of low self-esteem.
(shocked and excited chatter)
I had a nightmare
where that happened to Bart,
but I never told you about it.
I love it when you
don't tell me things.
This mouse was given food
whether he got
through the maze or not.
And this fall,
he'll be in a lab at Harvard.
(excited gasps and chatter)
Low self-esteem can cripple
your child's chances of success.
The cure: praise.
(excited chatter)
Praise they can hold
in their hands.
Certificates, ribbons and, yes,
even trophies.
(crowd gasps)
(gasps) Trophies.
So that's the easy answer.
If Ralphie's shelf
says he's a winner,
then he'll be one!
And Moe yells a third thing
to feel part of the group!
Yes! Trophies--
that's what Bart needs.
This is how we save him.
(scoffs) Give Bart a trophy?
What for?
Most boogers wiped
on a bedroom wall?
They're giving trophies
for that now?
I weep for this country.
Bart's future is at stake.
Besides, I'm tired
of Springfield missing out
on every parenting trend.
Like the time-out and the diaper.
I never got a trophy
when I was a kid,
and I turned out just...
(gulping)
(slowly)
...fine.
He's my son, and he's getting
a trophy for nothing.
You hear me?
For nothing!
Huh. Huh?
(screams)
Good morning.
How's my special
little winner?
How'd you get that thing
in my bed without waking me up?
Because you're
a champion sleeper.
It's the craziest thing.
She will not give up
on that kid.
Trophies can
boost self-esteem.
If you actually win them,
like I did.
But what's the point
of just handing out
unearned statues?
And statuettes.
Well, it's just a waste
of gullible parents' money.
(echoing) Waste of gullible
parents' money.
Gullible parents' money.
Money. Money.
-(bell dings)
-Hmm.
Step right up!
Every kid's a winner!
The more you spend,
the more you love!
Mm-hmm.
I thought you agreed
that trophies should be earned.
I'm earning nature's
trophy: money.
(wind whistles softly)
Remember, folks.
Nothing but a genuine
Trophyland trophy says
to your kids that...
HOMER:
♪ You're the best around ♪
♪ Nothing's gonna ever
keep you down ♪
♪ You're the best around ♪
♪ Nothing's gonna ever
keep you down ♪
♪ You're the best around ♪
♪ Nothing's gonna ever
keep you down ♪
♪ You're the best around ♪
♪ Nothing's gonna ♪
♪ Ever keep you down ♪
♪ You're the best around ♪
♪ Nothing's gonna ever
keep you down ♪
♪ You're the best ♪
(chuckles) These stupid,
loving parents will buy trophies
for any accomplishment.
Not wetting the bed,
using your inside voice,
even "go watch TV
in the other room."
I still think these things
are good for their self-esteem.
Not to mention
the self-esteem
that comes from
wad riffling.
(wind whistles softly)
Look, I even put the boy to work.
Well, then he should get
a trophy for that.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
We have a saying in
the participation trophy business.
"Don't get high--
self-esteem--
on your own supply--
of self-esteem."
I don't care.
I'm giving him this.
What?
Why did it break?
The parts are of
the highest quality.
They come from
the China of China: India.
Boy, did you glue this trophy together
with bubblegum?
Eh, sticky is sticky.
I'm taking my break.
HOMER: See?
Giving him trophies did nothing.
You've showered him
with praise,
and he's just
as lazy as ever.
Shh!
What if he heard you say that?
Hey, if Bart is as bad
at eavesdropping
as he is at everything else,
we've got nothing
to worry about.
I say we keep
talking loudly.
But what about
his confidence?
Face it.
Our son is a screw-up.
He was born a screw-up,
and no matter how hard he tries--
which he never will--
Bart will always
be a screw-up.
(groans)
And have you ever heard that sound
he makes when he's sad?
Pathetic.
(sighs)
Queen's bishop Lomotil
takes king's Ativan.
Oh, looks like I'll be
having a panic attack
on the toilet tonight.
(scoffs) Look at that
whimpering little crybaby.
(mocking)
Wah! Wah!
Abe, that's your grandson.
Come visit me!
I'm so lonely!
(crying)
Wah! Wah!
What's got you down, kiddo?
My dad says I'm terrible
at everything.
Oh, he's just repeating
what he heard as a boy from me.
Oh, I was an awful father,
just like my old man.
Your dad didn't
believe in you, either?
It wasn't his fault.
He was just focused
on his career
as a professional child-beater.
Men would come
from five towns over
to study my father's technique.
But no matter
how many strangles he patented,
his father never approved.
(choking loudly)
Even if only a little bit
of that really happened,
I'll never escape
being a loser.
That's loser talk!
You're a great kid,
and I'm gonna prove it to you.
Boy, this here's a real trophy.
Our family's
most prized possession:
a Baumont Chrono-master Elite.
It's been a Simpson heirloom
ever since it was stolen
off a dead body at Gettysburg.
In 1982.
Whoa!
Wait. Is this just another
gold shiny thing
to trick me into
feeling special when I'm not?
You are special!
You're like my prostate--
a spiky little troublemaker
who plays by his own rules.
You don't take hooey
from Louie.
Never have, never will.
(shudders)
I feel something.
It's like a sunburn
on the inside.
It's called "pride."
Every tick will remind you
you've got a grandpa
who believes in you.
The same way I believe
the retirement home
has been taken over by robots.
(Eastern European accent)
I am not a robot.
I just have
light-up sneakers.
♪ ♪
(Ralph humming)
Why is my trophy the smallest?
You all lost-- to me!
(confused murmurs)
Lisa, are you suggesting
we engage in excellence bias?
(crying)
She's loser-shaming me.
(growls)
(students gasp)
Why do you always have
to make trouble, ya wee harpy?
How am I supposed to stay silent
when parents are just blindly
chasing the latest trend?
Ugh, parents.
Those lazy lunch-packers.
They just want to be told
what to do.
And there's no shortage of experts
who want to tell 'em.
WILLIE: (echoing)
No shortage of experts.
Experts. Experts. Experts.
(bell dings)
LISA: (thinking)
Another parenting expert, eh?
Clearly,
this is a community in the grip
of an addiction to trophies.
Now, parents,
I warn you, too much praise
creates millennials--
a generation of soft,
entitled narcissists,
who drop out of college
to become deejays.
That only pays well
at the very highest levels.
Instead of showering
your kids with gifts,
you should prod them
to greatness with G.R.I.T.
Get up. Retry.
I don't care if you're...
Tired.
He's got a word made
of other words.
(chuckles) He must know
what he's talking about.
Oh, it is an end to praise.
Praise Vishnu.
(crowd exclaims, murmurs)
Remember,
G.R.I.T. also stands for:
Get Rid of Idiotic Trophies.
Another word word!
He did it again!
Why does the word "of"
sometimes count in the acronym
and sometimes not?
Shut up, Mel! Your kids live
in Nebraska with your mom.
CROWD: (chanting)
No more trophies! No more trophies!
Uh-oh.
You are scum, sir!
-(crowd booing)
-Burn in hell!
Kill him with G.R.I.T.!
Hi, Homer.
How's the trophy business?
Nobody wants them anymore,
thanks to G.R.I.T.
Stupid parenting method
I can't exploit for money.
Actually kinda makes sense.
Hate it so much.
(Homer gasps)
I know that.
That's my dad's
old pocket watch.
How did you get it?
Oh, Grampa said I earned it.
I guess someone
in this family's proud of me.
Oh, you didn't want it, did you?
(scoffs)
Yeah, right.
That watch means
nothing to me.
Really? Then how do you
explain that case you made?
I built it to always remind me
of what not to want.
What about your
self-published novel?
Well, the character
of John Homer
is only partly based on me.
Well, if I didn't know better,
I'd say you were obsessed
with getting Grampa's watch.
Ooh, thanks for the analysis,
Dr. Freud.
Next you'll be telling me
that this whole trophy business,
and in fact, all my get-rich-quick
schemes over the years,
are borne of a desperate need
for approval
from a father
who couldn't show love.
Likely because
of his traumatic relationship
with his own father,
and his before him, and so on.
But, unfortunately, Dr. Freud,
that couldn't be further
from the truth, Doctor.
If you say so.
Now I'm gonna take this out
and see what life is like
with real love and encouragement
ticking in my pocket.
Stupid watch.
Doesn't even have a fob.
Bart, where's the fob?
Bart, you look like a fool!
(groaning slowly)
♪ You're the best around ♪
♪ Nothing's gonna ever
keep you down ♪
♪ You're the best around ♪
♪ Nothing's gonna ever
keep you down ♪
♪ You're the best around ♪
♪ Nothing's gonna ever
keep you down ♪
♪ Down ♪
♪ Fight till the end
'cause your life will depend ♪
♪ On the strength
that you have inside you ♪
♪ Ah, got to be proud,
staring... ♪
No!
HOMER:
♪ You're the worst around ♪
♪ Everything's gonna
bring you down ♪
Okay, Milhouse, I'll drop a rock,
you watch it come down.
That should be where
Grampa's watch landed.
-(thud)
-MILHOUSE: Ow!
Did you see
where the rock landed?
In my eye!
Oh. That watch was the only thing
that made me not terrible.
I can't lose it.
I'll drop another rock
a few feet to the left.
My other eye!
Ow!
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
Not a single one
has missed me!
What are you doing?
That expert at the school
said trophies are bad for kids.
It's all part of G.R.I.T.
No, no.
My trophies were earned.
Even the soccer one?
I went to most
of the practices.
Yeah, but what happens
when another parenting expert
comes along with a whole
new theory on self-esteem?
Another expert?
Who are they?
What are they saying?
Aw.
Okay, the watch is gone.
I guess I can live with being
a useless, worthless nothing
as long as no one finds out.
Sweetie, your grampa's
on the phone.
Hello.
Great news, kiddo.
Remember That magazine
is putting out
their annual
family heirlooms issue.
They want us for the cover.
You, me and the pocket watch.
Um...
It's a great story.
Passing a beloved heirloom
from grandfather to grandson.
A gift that restored
a child's faith in himself.
Uh, Grampa, there's something
I have to tell you.
Hold on one second.
I'm just finishing up
a mandatory
pre-article heart exam.
Doc says as long
as I don't suffer
any major disappointments,
I'll be fine.
Now, what did you want
to tell me?
Uh, helmets ruined football.
Exactly! If you want
to protect your head,
grow your hair long.
Anyway, I'll see you tomorrow
at 10:00 a.m.
And you won't be late
because you've got that watch.
(groans)
Stupid parenting experts.
Why don't they write a book
called Stop Buying These Books?
Everybody'd buy that.
Even if I was listening
to what you said, it doesn't matter.
Nothing matters.
My trophy business
has failed
and Bart has
the thing I wanted most:
Grampa's watch.
What watch?
The one you get
for being a success.
Well, then I should have it.
Uh, that never really came up.
All that's left to do now
is bring these to the needy.
Best I can do
is charge you ten dollars
to throw them
in my Dumpster.
How about I give you a trophy
that says "Best Pawn Shop"?
Not unless I earned it.
(gasps)
Dad's watch!
Hey, dirtbag shopkeep,
how did this come to you?
Mm.
Some kid brought it in.
Said he was mad
at his friend
for dropping so many rocks
in his eye.
That dude's seen
a lot of living.
Yours for 20 bucks.
That's an insult.
You're talking about
a self-worth-boosting antique
that's been in my family
for generations.
Twenty-two?
You'll take it all,
and you'll like it.
(maniacal laugh)
Yes. I have it.
Some said it would never happen.
Most were unaware
of the situation.
But I finally have
my father's watch!
(maniacal laugh)
(singsongy) Oh, Bart,
look what Daddy's got now.
(Bart crying)
Grampa was the only person
who believed in me.
But when he finds out
I lost the watch,
even he'll give up.
(sobbing)
Stay strong, Homer.
Don't go soft on him now.
This is a once-in-a-lifetime
face-rubbing-in.
Mm. Come on, foot.
Kick, damn you!
(grunts)
(sighs) Son, I found something
that belongs to you.
(gasps) Grampa's watch!
No. I can't take it.
I didn't earn it,
so I don't deserve it.
You were right.
I am a screw-up.
But, boy,
who screwed you up?
(gasps) You.
It was you.
And those who came before.
(choking loudly)
It's stuck in your hand fat.
Oh. You got to wedge something
in there to break the vacuum.
(grunting)
Okay.
Smile, my little watch watcher.
(camera clicking)
That was a nice thing you did.
Which parenting guide
told you to do it?
Well, baby,
sometimes you just
got to trust your gut.
(watch shatters)
(choking)
It's NBA draft day,
and the world waits to see
who will be the first pick.
The consensus choice
is Cody Harris from LSU,
but there's an exciting
dark horse this year.
It's a player from Springfield
by the name of Ralph Wiggum.
Uh-oh.
There's no tape
on this three-foot-six
second-grader,
but he does lead
the nation in trophies.
You can't argue
with trophies.
Boom! Kid's a winner.
(groans)
From the Springfield Elementary
Afterschool Happy Hamsters,
the Philadelphia 76ers select
Ralph Wiggum, power forward.
I'm a millionaire!
(camera clicks)
♪ ♪
HOMER: ♪ Try to be best
'cause you're only a man ♪
♪ And a man's got to learn
to take it ♪
♪ Try to believe,
though the going gets rough ♪
♪ That you got to
hang tough to make it ♪
♪ History repeats itself ♪
♪ Try and you'll succeed ♪
♪ Never doubt
that you're the one ♪
♪ And you can have your dream ♪
♪ You're the best around ♪
♪ Nothing's gonna ever
keep you down ♪
♪ You're the best around ♪
♪ Nothing's gonna ever
keep you down ♪
♪ You're the best around ♪
♪ Nothing's gonna ever
keep you down ♪
♪ You're the best ♪
Subtitled by Jimmy Boots