♪ The Simpsons ♪
(chalk screeches)
(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(tires screeching)
(horn honks)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
Resident, occupant.
Mmm. Free sample of Lemon Time.
Ooh, give it here.
(gulping)
Homer,
that's dishwashing liquid.
Yeah, but what are you
gonna do?
Ooh! They're having
a retirement party
for someone at the plant!
I wish I could retire.
Boy, that would be sweet.
FLANDERS:
Howdy do, neighbor.
Good pipe weather.
Thought I'd fire up the briar.
Can't talk. Busy.
Okley-dokley doo.
Did you notice
how slanted he looked?
All part of God's great plan.
I think one side of our house
is sinking.
Ha ha!
"The Half-assed Approach
to Foundation Repair."
Hello, I'm Troy McClure.
You might remember me
from such instructional videos
as "Mothballing
Your Battleship"
and "Dig Your Own Grave
and Save."
Now, over the next
six hours,
I'll be taking you through
the do's and do not do's
of foundation repair.
-Ready?
-Ready.
First, patch the cracks
in the slab
using a latex patching compound
and a patching trowel.
Hand me my patching trowel, boy.
Hmm.
Now, do you have extruded
poly-vinyl foam insulation?
-No.
-Good.
Assemble the aluminum J-channel
using self-furring screws.
-Install.
-What do I--
After applying brushable
coating to the panels--
-Wait a minute.
-...you'll need some
corrosion-resistant
metal stucco lathe.
-Wait a minute!
-If you can't find
-metal stucco lathe--
-Uh-huh.
...use carbon fiber
stucco lathe.
Ohh!
Now barge the lathe.
(glass breaking)
Did you see the bubble?
I'm afraid the whole west side
of your house is sinking.
I figure it's gonna
cost you--
-Ooh, 8,500.
-Forget it!
You're not the only
foundation guy in town.
Let's see, foundation repair.
Ah, here we are-- D'oh!
...leaving the vice president
in charge.
And now, Leaning Tower of Pisa,
eat your heart out
and move over.
This is one story
that's not on the level.
(all laughing)
Behold the horrors
of the Slanty Shanty.
See the twisted creatures
that dwell within.
Meet Cue Ball,
the man with no hair.
Huh?
(growling)
(gasping)
He's hideous!
-We have to do something.
-(lamp shatters)
Marge,
it will cost $8,500.
We only have 500 in the
bank, and that leaves...
80 hundred we need.
I could get a job.
Hey...
then I could follow my dream:
living in the woods and keeping
a journal of my thoughts.
March 15--
I wish I brought a TV.
Oh, God, how I miss TV.
(chittering)
I think you have
to keep your job, too.
Aw!
It was the most beautiful,
most expensive train ever built.
The Spruce Caboose.
Some people said it was too
big to stay on the tracks.
Heh heh, they were right.
We're here
for the retirement party.
Follow the headless brakeman.
Power plant retirement party.
-Ow! Right this way.
-(glass shatters)
Ow!
(clearing throat)
Ahem.
Tonight, we've all come to honor
a close friend of ours.
Boring.
A man who provided
the Burns Corporation
with 45 years
of faithful service--
Mr. Jack Marley.
Boring.
(angry muttering)
Mr. Burns,
if you don't mind,
I've prepared
a little musical number
for Jack's special night.
♪♪
♪ There is a man ♪
-♪ A certain man ♪
♪ A man whose grace
and handsome face ♪
♪ Are known across the land ♪
-♪ You know his name ♪
-♪ It's Mr. Burns ♪
♪ He loves a smoke ♪
♪ Enjoys a joke ♪
♪ Why, he's worth ten times
what he earns ♪
-♪ He's Mr. Burns ♪
-I'm Mr. Burns.
-He's Monty Burns.
♪ To friends,
he's known as Monty ♪
♪ But to you,
it's Mr. Burns ♪
♪ Bur-bur-bur-bur-burns ♪
Burns!
You mind if I say
a few words?
(mockingly)
Oh, me, me, me.
I need all the attention
just because it's
my party, eh?
(dismissive grunt)
Please don't make me retire.
My job is the only thing
that keeps me alive.
I never married,
and my dog is dead.
♪♪ ("For He's
a Jolly Good Fellow")
I'm not finished!
Oh, yes, you are.
-(screams)
-(crashing)
With the departure
of Mr. Marley,
there will now be
an entry-level position
open in sector 7-G.
Now get out.
The bar is closed.
(all moan)
MARGE: Maybe I should
apply for that job.
Forget it, Marge.
We already live together.
We shouldn't work together.
As the bible says,
"Thou shalt not horn in
on thy husband's racket."
Where does the bible
say racket?
It's in there.
Look, Marge we just don't
need the money that bad.
Wahh!
(grunts)
Well, Lisa,
I finished my resumé.
Uh, I think it needs
a little padding.
What are you putting
in there?
Bup, bup, bup.
When I'm done.
Chauffeur, seamstress.
Curator of large mammals?
Marge, have you seen
my lunch box?
-Oh, I see.
-(chuckles)
Mom, they expect you
to lie a little.
Worked for
the Carter Administration?
Well, you voted
for him twice.
Lisa, shh. Someone might be
listening.
Mm-hmm.
Uh-huh.
Oh, I thought Muddy Waters
wrote that song.
-(groans)
-This resume is very impressive.
Let me be the first to say
kabebu kazini.
-What?
-Welcome aboard.
I guess my Swahili
is not as good as yours.
(chuckling)
Yeah, hmm.
Sorry.
The position has been filled.
(grumbling)
Oh, dear.
Marge, you're making
a big mistake.
I'm gonna see you all day
at work and all night at home...
-(groans)
-And that's good.
But here's the bad part:
Uh, uh...
Ooh, look at that headline.
"Canada to hold referendum."
Sorry, Marge,
can't talk now.
We need the money.
And my life is pretty boring.
Last week, some Jehovah's
Witnesses came to the door,
and I wouldn't
let them leave.
They snuck away when
I went in the kitchen
to get more lemonade.
Yeah, lemonade is good.
I think it's wonderful.
Mom and Dad, side-by-side
at the power plant.
You'll be just like
Marie and Pierre Curie.
-What did they do?
-They discovered radium.
Then they both died
of radiation poisoning.
Hmm.
(roaring)
(screaming)
It's the Curies.
We must flee.
(roaring)
Cool!
Now, Marge,
just remember.
If something goes wrong
at the plant,
blame the guy who
can't speak English.
Ah, Tibor, how many times
have you saved my butt?
(chuckles)
Maggie,
your baby-sitter's here.
What's that mean?
Whoa!
You must be sick.
Let's see.
What's old Doc Washburn
prescribe?
Do you have dropsy?
The grippe? Scopula?
The vapors? Jungle rot?
Shanty fever?
Poor man's gout?
Housemaid's knee?
Climactic bouba?
The staggers?
Dum-dum fever?
And this is your office.
That idiot Tibor
lost the key,
but you can jimmy it
open with a credit card.
(computer whirring)
Well, have fun.
-What do I do?
-(chuckles)
Marge, please,
according to your resumé
you invented this machine.
(electronic humming)
(explosion, men shouting)
Put away your books,
children.
It's time
for your English test.
(moaning)
Sick on test day.
Why? Why?
Bart have you read
The Boy Who Cried Wolf?
I'm halfway through it.
I swear.
(groaning)
-(door slams)
-(scoffs)
Marge, what are you doing?
It's lunch time.
I'll just be a minute.
I have to finish
this paperwork.
Marge, Marge, Marge.
Let's file this under
"R" for arrivederci.
But where does it go?
Don't worry, baby.
The tube will know what to do.
Good news, boy.
I found a pharmacy
that carries leeches.
Well, it wasn't exactly
a pharmacy.
More of a bait shop.
Look, Grampa, I'm fine.
I really don't need
any more home remedies.
Oral thermometer,
my eye!
Think warm thoughts, boy,
'cause this is mighty cold.
(Bart screams)
♪♪ ("Imperial March" playing)
Jackanapes.
Lollygaggers.
Noodle heads.
Enchantress.
That woman,
she's so captivating.
Smithers, my heart's pounding
like a jackhammer.
I must have her.
Smithers, zoom in.
Closer, closer.
Closer, damn it!
Ow!
Too close.
♪♪ (humming tune)
-Hello.
-Mr. Burns!
Oh, no need for alarm.
I just came to give
you the orchids
and fragrant bath oils
I lavish upon
all my employees.
Oh, aren't you nice.
This makes me wonder
why morale here is so low.
(sobbing)
I am the angel of death.
The time of purification
is at hand.
Oh, who cares?
Marge, what can we do?
Well, you could give them
healthier snacks.
Theme days.
You mean
like Child Labor Day?
Mm, actually I was thinking
of Funny Hat Day.
Oh.
Ooh, and how about piping in
some Tom Jones music?
That always cheers me up.
♪ What's new, pussy cat? ♪
♪ Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa ♪
♪ Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa ♪
It's working.
-It's working!
-(gun cocks)
And the healthy snacks
are on their way.
You can't take our doughnuts!
Yah!
All right, anyone else
want to be a hero?
Ooh.
Marge, I'm giving you a raise
and a new office
right next to mine.
(laughing)
But, sir, that's my office.
Don't worry, Smithers.
I'm putting you
where the action is.
Springtime fresh.
Winter white.
What could be better?
Oh, man, I really gotta--
No!
So, Bart, how are you feeling?
Can't complain.
Well, then you're ready
for your make-up test.
Ohh! My ovaries.
Ha ha ha, suckers.
Have you ever read
The Boy Who Cried Wolf?
I glanced at it.
Boy cries wolf,
has a few laughs.
I forget how it ends.
(stammering)
Bart, is that light green?
-Yeah.
-It better be.
-Hey!
-Oh...
Homie, what's wrong?
I'm used to seeing people
promoted ahead of me--
friends, co-workers, Tibor.
I never thought
it would be my own wife.
Well, maybe you'd get promoted
if you worked a little harder.
Are you kidding?
I work like a Japanese beaver.
Oh, really? I came to see you
three times today.
Twice, you were sleeping,
and once,
you were kicking that ball
of electrical tape around.
Well, I won't sleep
in the same bed
with a woman
who thinks I'm lazy.
I'm gonna go right downstairs,
unfold the couch,
unroll the sleeping ba--
Ah, good night.
(snoring)
(sighs)
I dreamed about her again
last night, Smithers.
You know that dream
where you're in bed
and they fly in
through the window?
Ahh.
You've been reading
my wish book, sir.
Yes, well, Smithers,
I want you to arrange
a party for two at my estate.
Marge, me,
and do you think
you could you dig up
Al Jolson?
Ah, do you remember
we did that once before?
Oh, that's right, he's dead...
and rather pungent.
The rest of that night
is something I'd like to forget.
All right then, bring me
that crooner she likes so much--
Tom Jones.
♪♪ (country music playing)
These spurs are killing me.
Hey, sit on it.
Buddy, '50s Day
is next Wednesday.
I got to go home
and change.
(motorcycle revving)
Here's your money.
Well, you know, the problem
here was water leakage.
If you just buy
a 50-cent washer--
I've got a better idea.
-Get the hell out!
-(chuckles)
Look, I got some washers
in my truck.
-I'll give you one.
-Marge, get my gun.
♪♪
(women screaming)
-Tom Jones?
-Yes?
I was wondering
if you'd be interested
in performing
at a private party?
Sorry, mate,
I don't do private parties.
Well, then, perhaps you should
look in this suitcase.
All right, but I don't see--
(coughing)
Pleasant dreams, Mr. Jones.
Bart, to avoid this test,
you've had smallpox, the bends,
and that unfortunate
bout of rabies.
I'm not sure I'm over it.
(clicking)
Shove it, witch.
(barking)
No more excuses.
(muttering and barking)
Her claws are really digging
into my skull.
She can crush
clams with them.
Get it off, get it off,
get it off!
Here we have
an Alaskan timber wolf.
He weighs 240 pounds,
and his jaws can bite
through a parking meter.
He does get spooked
by loud noises.
Loud? That's our secret word
for the day!
(beeping, whirring,
and ringing)
(children cheering)
(snarling)
(all screaming)
-Oh, my God!
-Baaah!
She must think you're
after her eggs!
I only ate one.
(growling)
Nice doggie.
(snarling)
Ivanhoe is the story
of a Russian farmer
and his tool.
(growling)
Wolf! Wolf! Wolf!
I'm afraid you'll have to do
better than that.
-(growling)
-(screaming)
-Sorry, no sale.
-(glass shatters)
You're wasting
valuable test time.
(squeaking)
Mr. Burns, you wanted to see me?
Uh, actually, I was wondering
if you were free
for a little
get-together tonight.
Dinner, dancing, and...
Mr. Tom Jones.
-Hello, Marge.
-That's it, big smile, everybody's happy.
Oh, my goodness!
(thud, grunts)
My husband will be so excited.
You have a husband?
Yes, I can picture him now.
Rugged good looks.
Sweater knotted
about his shoulders.
Curly locks shining in the sun
like spun gold.
Homer, Mr. Burns gave me
another raise today.
(laughing)
The senile old fool.
You're fired!
You can't fire me
just because I'm married.
I'm going to sue
the pants off you.
You don't have to sue me
to get my pants off.
(lusty growl)
Mmm.
(growling)
Wah!
Uhh!
GROUNDSKEEPER WILLIE:
Hey, wolfie.
Put down that hors d'oeuvre.
It's time for the main course.
Aaah!
Gah! Get up!
Back to class, lad.
Nothing to see here.
(grunting)
Here's my test.
Bart, I'm not even
going to grade this
until you tell me the truth
about what happened out there.
The truth is...
There was no wolf.
I faked the whole thing.
I'm just gonna lie
on the floor now.
Please don't let me
swallow my tongue.
(thud)
There, doesn't it feel better
to tell the truth?
Oh, dear.
All right now, boy.
We've got to rub
some garlic on you
before the next full moon.
(gulping)
Don't feel bad for losing.
I was wrestling wolves
back when you were
at your mother's teat.
Why, Marge, look at
all those flies
buzzing around your head.
You're a mess, woman.
(laughing maniacally)
So, do you think
I have a case?
Mrs. Simpson, you're in luck.
Your sexual harassment suit
is just the thing I need
to rebuild
my shattered practice.
Care to join me
in a belt of scotch?
It's 9:30 in the morning.
Yeah, but I haven't slept
in days.
Last chance.
Oh, yeah.
Mr. Burns, we've got
witnesses, precedent,
and a paper trail
a mile long.
Yes, well, I have
ten high-priced lawyers.
(screaming)
He left his briefcase.
Hey, it's full
of shredded newspapers.
Well, I guess that's it.
People like us
can't afford justice.
Come on, Homie.
Let's go before
he fires you, too.
No! Mr. Burns,
I'm not leaving
until you say you're sorry
for what you did
to my wife.
You love her, too?
Damn right.
Homer, I want you
to show this woman
-the time of her life.
-Gotcha. Marge,
we're getting some drive-thru,
then we're doing it twice.
No, no, no.
I've got something
even more special in mind.
♪ It's not unusual ♪
♪ To be loved by anyone ♪
♪ To have fun with anyone ♪
-(kissing noises)
-Ooh!
-(giggling)
-Get help, love.
Call Interpol.
Get me a hacksaw,
anything.
♪ It's not unusual ♪
♪ It happens every day ♪
♪ No matter what you say ♪
♪ You'll find it happens
all the time ♪
♪ And love will never do ♪
♪ What you want it to ♪
♪ Why can't this crazy love
be mine? ♪
♪ It's not unusual ♪
♪ To be mad with anyone ♪
♪ To be sad with anyone ♪
♪ But if I ever find that ♪
♪ You've changed at any time ♪
♪ It's not unusual to find ♪
♪ That I'm in love with you ♪
♪ Whoa-whoa, oh-oh,
whoa-oh, whoa-whoa, whoa-oh ♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.