D'oh!
Is she gonna be okay, Doc?
She's just fine.
And here's the baby.
I know how to hold
one of these.
D'oh!
You're watching
The Learning Network,
where minds grow.
Stay tuned for...
But first...
The following film,
made in 1982,
was thought to be lost forever.
Actually, it was misplaced
in a box
for the comedy Doctor Detroit.
But its predictions are
more terrifying than ever.
Hello, I'm Orson Welles,
director of Citizen Kane...
Boring.
As well as the lower
left-hand square
on Hollywood Squares.
Ooh, right next to Ruth Buzzi.
In 1555,
the prophet Nostradamus
foretold a terrifying series
of predictions,
all of which came to pass.
First, his own death.
Second,
large wars in Europe,
similar to the large wars
he observed in Europe.
And the breakup
of Fleetwood Mac.
But Nostradamus's
final quatrain contained
one more prediction
yet to come...
that shortly after the
Antichrist becomes president...
This champagne is terrible.
It tastes like dryer sheets.
But what does
said mushroom signify?
Nothing less than World War III.
Who'd fall for this malarkey?
Smithers, I'm scared.
Release the comforting hounds.
Oh, excellent.
Now, make them into rugs.
Anyone left alive will surely
find themselves envying...
Who?
Who could we possibly envy?
The dead.
Smithers, the end is nigh,
and we must prepare.
Round up this town's
greatest minds.
Should I order pizza?
One large cheese, double-cut.
Attention, fellow members
of the Springfield chapter
of Mensa.
Mr. Burns has called us here
to solve an unknown problem
of global importance.
But first, Tri-Ominoes!
I say we write and solve
our own acrostics.
Yes, after we recite
all the words
in the Declaration of Independence
in alphabetical order.
A, A, A, A, A, A.
Abdicated. Abolish. Abolishing.
Absolute. Absolved.
Silence, you thinkertons.
I summoned you here because
the world is about to end.
No, it isn't.
What are you afraid of?
Global warming?
A.I.?
Some sort of plague?
As smarty-pantalones,
I am asking you to help with
the Montgomery Burns
Doomsday Ark.
This space vehicle will lead
humanity's best and brightest
to a better life
under my stern rule.
Oh, gee heavens.
Will there be someone for
your more personal needs?
Concubines.
Many concubines.
I'll work my way in.
I need you to tell me
who is worthy
of surviving
the apocalypse with me.
I only want the sharpest razors
in this town's Halloween candy.
Oh, don't worry, Mr. Burns,
this is what Mensa does best...
make everyone else feel stupid.
The only word in English
with three consecutive
double letters is...
Gooseberry.
No, coffee. Coffee-oo.
- Balloon-an-ing.
- Bookkeeper.
Damn it.
It's simple.
All we need to do is
give everyone in town
an IQ test.
The highest scores
get on the ark...
Mensa members grandfathered in.
Sounds good to me.
Grandfathered!
Not so fast. Flavin.
Being intelligent people,
I am quite sure
that you will take this well.
IQs are meaningless.
Heresy!
I have the ultimate test
that measures something
far more significant.
Your overall worth as a human.
Impossible.
Intelligence
is the only quotient
that tells you
how important you are.
Ask any of us who did well on
a test we took when we were six.
Well, you may be the brightest,
but you are not the best.
Your worthiness as a human being
is best measured, people,
by the Personal Value Quotient.
That's P.V.Q.
Oh! Ow! All right,
enough with the pelting
and the bonking
and the compass in my neck.
Garvik.
In order to defuse
your obvious hostilities,
I will make my presentation
entertaining, all right?
With a one, and a two,
and a 3.14159.
Forgive me if it seems like
I'm attacking,
but I find the old IQ test
badly lacking.
If you want to find out
just what someone can do,
you need to learn
that subject's P.V.Q.
It tests for
Sympathy and empathy
and group collaboration
Artistry and neatness
and complex socialization
And every single aspect
of a personality
Hey, the P.V.Q.
Is A.O.K. with me
It tests for sarcasm
and prudence
Not if you're Isaac Newton
Confidence, ambition
And the teams for whom
you're rootin'
So it's all
the little foibles
That can make a person whole
Trust the P.V.Q.
The yardstick for the soul
Now, people,
you're all geniuses
- Oh, please...
- My, my, well, thank you.
You can see this is no lark
Emotional intelligence
is needed for the ark
You mean earnestness
and ego
And if they make
a mean burrito
And the social grace to know
When not to wear a Speedo
Every trait that integrates
a winning personality
Yes, the P.V.Q.
Is what we'll do
to find out who
Will see us through
Yes, the P.V.Q.
Is A.O.K.
With me...
Oivik!
Anyone have a song in rebuttal?
You got to have hear...
Oh, balderdash.
We're going with
this man's test.
- Oh, wonderful.
- To determine who is worthy
of a seat on my ark.
But, sir, how do we get
everyone in town
to take a test without
telling them what it's about?
Mandatory test.
Mandatory test!
Mandatory for everyone
not ringing a bell.
What's the point
of this test again?
The way I look at it,
the more things
secret corporations know
about us, the better, huh?
I like when drones show up
bringing me things
I needed but didn't know.
Wow, I am out of deodorant.
We all knew.
Remove all stray marks.
Number two pencil only.
And for God's sake, relax!
This question asks about
the price of underwear,
as if I were some
landed aristocrat.
Hey, can I copy off you?
Be my guest.
Day is to night
as early is to...
Late. Booyah!
Booyah!
The one test I don't
bring my earmuffs.
The results are in.
The newest
and most accurate measure
of our intelligence
on a scale from one to 500...
500 being best.
- Boring.
- Don't shut it off.
I need my score.
Thank you.
Now we'll run everyone's scores
past the screen really fast,
from best to worst,
trusting that you'll pause
at only your name.
Pause it!
475, my sweet spot. Excellent.
But room to improve.
What?!
I am one below Ralph? Ralph?
Honey, it doesn't mean
Ralph's smarter than you.
It just means he's
a more valuable person.
- Ralph?
- Keep scrolling.
Ooh, 311.
Above average, but not enough
to make people mad.
And, it's the number you call
to complain about potholes.
Ooh. H. Simpson, 265.
Exactly the number
of days in a year.
Well, that's good.
Let's change the channel.
But we don't know your score.
Like I said, that's good.
Hmm, not there.
Not there. Not there.
I don't need any test.
I'm street-smart.
I refuse to accept that
my little guy has no future.
He can learn how to
put in adding machine tape.
That's how I got through
the Depression,
and letting the FBI know
which bugle boys
were about to turn
boogie-woogie.
We're not giving up on Bart.
And I'm not giving up
on you, Homer.
What, you're still trying?
In what way?
My will is 38 pages
of me yelling at you.
Ooh, I'm in the will.
Charles. Listen to me, Charles.
Not now, Satan.
I'm not Satan, I'm Orson Welles.
Satan would sell wine
before its time.
Yes. Now, have you taken
my warning seriously?
Oh, but I did.
I've already started the ark.
Very good. Now I must go.
God commissioned me
to direct a rainbow,
and I've spent half
my budget on indigo.
The only answer
is to play red myself.
Smithers. Speed up production
on the ark.
Put everyone on it.
Ply them with all the rum
and salt it takes.
There's no nap
like a scaffold nap.
Hey, what do you think
we're building, anyway?
I'm betting it's a new
Rock and Roll Hall of Fame.
Maybe this one
will keep somebody out.
How can Ralph score higher
than me?
That's just wrong.
But all my self-esteem comes
from tests.
Should I really be pulling
on this string?
I am not worse than Ralph!
- Hi, Ralph.
Hi, Ralph.
I miss the string
through my ears.
All right, Lisa.
Watch, do not judge.
What makes him superior?
I'm okay.
You have
reached the Wiggum residence.
If Ralph is stuck in something,
press one.
If something is stuck in Ralph,
press two.
If this is Ralph,
Daddy is not in the phone.
Do not open the phone
looking for me.
What are you doing?
The only thing I'm good at.
Nothing.
That tears it.
We're going to see
Professor Frink,
and find out exactly
what happened on that test.
Got a little present
for you, Bart.
It's called
The Bible For The Slow.
He's not going to take it.
Okily-dokily.
Professor Frink, your stupid
test ruined my son's life.
Hey, that test
is like a son to me.
I raised it from a quiz.
I've known my son
since he was born,
and he's not anywhere
near as stupid
as your stupid test says he is.
And if you think so,
you're stupid, stupid, stupid!
Wow, Marge.
You really love Bart.
All right, all right,
let me recheck it.
Rechecking, rechecking.
Put-upon sigh.
Oivik.
Rechecking... Here we are.
Simpson, B.
That's not a B.
Well, yes, it is,
you see, the two...
Oh, my garvik!
There was a mistake.
Well, your son
has above-average intelligence.
You did it, boy.
No, that just looks like a B.
The real unfortunate
is H. Simpson.
I mean, what a clod!
Worst handwriting
and brain in town.
- D'oh!
- Hey!
I'm H. Simpson.
Oh, well, it's very nice
to meet you.
Would you like some water?
- Smartwater?
- No.
- Homie, aren't you coming?
- Bye-bye.
I can't. I'll be a laughing
stock when everyone finds out
I'm the stupidest man in town.
How are they gonna find out?
I just tweeted it.
Marge, you have to get ahead
of these stories.
I'm sorry, sir, you belong here.
Look thou be true.
Do not give dalliance.
Too much of the rein.
Why does Oscar skate
in his trash can?
It makes no sense!
I'll cheer up here.
One stupid, please?
Okay, you gave me $40.
Here's two dollars back.
Unless you want
splash insurance.
- How much is that?
- Another ten.
Here's $20.
And two more for you.
Insurance doesn't
cover entryway splashes.
D'oh!
Hey, Homer, we was watching
Jeopardy! But...
tell you what, we'll just talk
about shapes and colors now.
I like blue rectangles.
Rectangles. You know, Homer.
The ones with four sides.
Listen, you.
I've known my shapes
since I was 16!
Put him down, Homer,
and I'll give you a cookie.
That's a coaster.
Dummy's wising up.
I'll take the cookie.
I never thought I'd say this,
but I'm too depressed for Moe's.
Heya, Homer.
I'm sorry. I know I'm taking up
too much of the bed.
Oh, sweetie.
What the entire world thinks
doesn't affect how I see you.
Well, how do you see me?
The hair and body
of a dashing Friar Tuck.
But what about my brains?
My favorite character
in The Wizard of Oz
was always the Scarecrow.
I knew it. Thanks to that test,
you see me as stupid first
and Homer third.
I mean, second.
I know second.
I won't let you give up.
We're going to start
improving you.
Oh, Marge. No one ever did
anything useful
after the age of 39.
George W. Bush sobered up.
And became president.
Too huge mistakes.
Homie, this whole mix-up
happened
because of
your sloppy handwriting.
We'll start with that,
improving your handwriting.
Right now, my hand just wants
to crawl in my pocket and cry.
Now this hand is jealous.
I know where this is going.
I do too,
but you say it first.
Snuggling.
What is his secret?
What is his secret?!
I'm going to Dizzyland.
Want to see me do a cartwheel?
- No! No, no, no!
- Good point.
On the other hand, whee!
Don't worry, Lou,
I've seen that in cartoons.
Swee'Pea, Mr. Magoo,
they were fine.
What about Sylvester the Cat?
Never be a cat
in a cartoon, Lou.
Never.
The beam must have
a fulcrum I can move to
that would stabilize it.
Think, Lisa, think.
Two for two.
Young man, didn't I tell you
to sit and stay in that house?
I thought you were talking
to the dog.
We don't have a dog.
Then what's been pooping
in my bedroom?
Professor, how on Earth did he
get a higher score than me?
Okay, Lisa, I am going
to give you ten more points
for one of the most important
skills of all...
Discovering huge flaws in
my test without telling anyone.
You mean, after all this,
after all I've gone through,
you're just gonna fudge my score
and I should be happy?
Well, after all,
that's how I got into...
Oh, I can't say it.
The lowest of the Ivys.
Oh, God, help me, Cornell!
Cornell! God!
It's okay, you're fine.
Oh, gloyvik.
Okay, Homie, buckle up.
Because there's no limit to how
neat your handwriting can get.
Marge, I don't know.
You can't teach
an old dog new tricks.
I'll help you.
My love...
Lisa, turn off
that oldies station!
My darl...
Dearest Marjorie,
what words are adequate
to describe your beauty?
Like, a bowling ball,
fresh out of a polisher.
I've always dreamed
Homie would write me
cursive love letters.
You are as beautiful
as your sisters are hideous.
Oh, Homie.
I'm married to a writer.
I really am.
Welcome, all of you.
You are the chosen people.
Chosen to be my slaves.
I am no one's slave.
Well, doesn't matter
what you think.
The doors are sealed.
Not this one.
Wait, wait, you haven't heard
about the retirement plan.
There isn't one.
Fine, I don't need them.
I don't need anyone.
Why did you have me go back
for your slippers?
How could you turn on me
so quickly?