CHORUS [SINGS]:
The Simpsons
The Great Louse Detective
D'oh! Ah!
[HUMMING]
Three minutes, 40 seconds...
...a new personal best.
Maggie?
[MAGGIE COUGHS]
No one will ever know.
HOMER: Mail call.
- Anything good?
The "George Foreman Mail Sorter"
will let us know.
Mm. "Your family is invited
to a free weekend...
...at Stagnant Springs Spa."
Oh, that place is famous.
It's where J-Lo hit P. Diddy
upside the head with Gary Coleman.
Our attendants can take
10 years off your face...
...and stick it in your boobs.
And this place isn't
just for gals anymore.
It's also for vain, effeminate men.
Kent Brockman?
Well, if you find this shocking,
look at Tom Brokaw.
Truly, that was
the greatest regeneration.
This place blows. I'm gonna go float
a Baby Ruth down a mineral bath.
Don't worry, kids. We've got
something just for you.
Do you like Dr. Seuss?
- No.
- Then you'll love Dr. Mas-Seuss.
[WHIMSICAL MUSIC
PLAYING ON STEREO]
Bad posture has floobled
and snozzled your neck.
I'll stop talking like this
if you write me a check.
Ooh! These turtles know
just where the knots are.
It just shows you God
has a plan for every creature.
Yes, yes indeed.
Ooh, ahh, oh!
Help! Please!
Someone throw me a stick!
Don't struggle. You'll only sink faster.
Roll your eyes back into your head,
focusing on your breathing.
You should feel a pleasant tingling.
Oh, I do! I do!
Now, get down on all fours
with your rear in the air.
What position is this?
[AS JOHNNY CARSON]
The American taxpayer!
The American taxpayer.
MARGE:
Hmm.
[SIGHS]
[GASPS]
Oh, my God.
A naked celebrity. Be cool.
Don't stare at his famous wang.
Ha-ha-ha. Go ahead, look.
The whole world already saw it
in Nudist Camp Commandant.
"I wore nothing!"
HOMER:
"Do not use steam room...
...if you are overweight
or have a heart condition."
[GULPS]
Wait a minute.
I'm not wearing a shirt.
[MOANING]
[SHOUTING]
[GROANS]
[HUMMING]
[HOMER SHOUTS]
Who ordered the steamed gentile?
Mm, steamed gentile.
Don't worry.
Us pigs will catch this killer.
Now, Mr. Simpson, is it
possible you're living a double...
...or triple life that your wife
doesn't know about?
Triple? No. Definitely no.
You have to do something
to protect my husband.
Where on my badge does it say
anything about protecting people?
Uh, second word, chief.
Thanks, Princeton Pete.
Now, your case requires
someone who understands...
...the twisted mind of a murderer.
And I know just where to find him.
- Paris?
- No. No, not Paris.
I'm never gonna go to Paris.
These are our most
dangerous criminals.
Each one crazier than the last.
Uh, come to think of it...
...he should be there and this
guy, he should be over there.
Wait. You're saying
he's crazier than I am?
That's exactly what I'm saying,
Decapitating Harry. Now move it.
[GIBBERING INCOHERENTLY]
Yeah, yeah. Whatever.
I don't think this was a great place
to bring the children.
- It beats Disney's California Adventure.
- Mm-hm.
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah, that's true.
Which one of these psychos
is gonna help me catch my killer?
WIGGUM:
He's right in here.
COMPUTER: Access denied.
- Oh, fine. I gotta use a fork.
Hello, Bart.
BOTH:
Aah! Sideshow Bob!
Oh, come now. We've been through
so much together. Just call me Bob.
BOTH:
Aah! Bob!
All right, Bob, if you help us
catch the guy trying to kill Homer...
...we'll make it worth your while.
- What could you offer me?
- Your pick of roles in the prison musical.
This year, I think it's
Man of La Mancha.
Yeah. Don Quixote, Sancho Panza...
...Dr. Carrasco, you know,
they're all great parts.
Ugh, what a great show.
I wish it was today.
- So, what do you say, Bob?
- Fair enough.
[GRUNTS]
Now, I will need round-the-clock
access to all the Simpsons...
...especially Bart.
Then you might as well stay with us.
We serve the same meat the prisons do.
Wait, wait, wait.
Bob can't stay with us.
This man has tried to kill me so much,
it's not funny.
Don't worry, son. We have
ways of making him compliant.
Dad, I can't believe you're putting
my life at risk to save your own.
You'll understand someday
when you have kids.
Now, if he even looks at you funny...
...this shock garter will set him straight.
And don't try taking it off
because it's taped to your leg hair.
- And that really hurts.
- Oh, come now.
As gentlemen, surely we
can just agree to... Dear God!
- Sorry.
- Fair enough.
But now that we know what it can do,
there's no need to... Mother!
Wow. You don't even
have to point it at him.
Homer, think carefully.
Of all the people you have known,
who might have reason to do you ill?
Hmm. Well, there's Mr. Burns...
...Fat Tony, the Emperor of Japan,
ex-President Bush.
- The late Frank Grimes.
- PBS, Stephen Hawking...
- ...the fat little Dixie Chick.
- And the state of Florida.
How can one man
have so many enemies?
- I'm a people person. Who drinks.
- Ah.
Homer, in order to identify
your assailant...
...I must follow you through
the course of a normal day.
Just do what you usually do...
- ...and the killer will reveal himself.
- Gotcha.
- This is a normal day?
- I just wanted to impress you.
Welcome to your Springfield
Mardi Gras headquarters.
Cast your vote now
for this year's king.
Mardi Gras, eh?
Didn't last year's king have to abdicate
because he married a commoner?
And I'd do it again.
But I do miss the Royal Crown Cola.
Ah, yes, the Kwik-E-Mart. I haven't been
here since I robbed it dressed as Krusty.
- My one successful crime.
- You were quite the gentleman.
Today's robbers,
they are all smash-and-grab.
You understood the dance.
Our time is passing, old friend.
Uh, if you two country hens
are finished clucking...
...I'd like to buy a copy
of Jugs and Ammo.
Well, we've settled that argument.
You can't read a magazine and drive.
Look, Junior, I expect this
to be fixed with quality GM parts.
But your car was built in Croatia.
It's made from old Soviet tanks.
Just fix it, Mr. Sasswrench.
Homer, please. The last thing
you need is more enemies.
Right, right. I'm counting
the pennies in the ashtray.
There's two.
The trap is set. The killer
will think this dummy is you...
...out for an evening stroll.
Now we lie in wait...
...like hungry Cassius for noble Caesar.
You're so smart. Shock him.
Odds Bodkins!
[SCREAMING]
[GROANS]
Oh, someone's coming.
Now who's the sociopath, huh?
Moe. He's got a dark side
I've never dreamed of.
Well, mystery solved.
Wait a moment.
He's hurt. Go, go, go.
These are Homer's friends and family.
They don't want him dead.
They just want him to suffer.
[SHOUTS]
[GRUNTING]
Thank you, Lord.
[SHOUTING]
Once I kill you, everyone will think
I'm the real Homer. Ha-ha-ha.
- None of this seems odd to you?
- Meh.
Say, Bob, how come you
were never able to kill Bart?
Yeah. A kid should be
real simple to kill.
I'd come up behind him with
a knife and slit his throat real quick.
Guys, Bob is my only hope.
Back off and give him room to think.
Homer, if I could write haikus while
skinheads beat me with soap...
...I can concentrate anywhere.
[GASPS]
- Oh, my God. He's getting closer.
- Ugh.
My poor jar.
Oh, why didn't I take more photos?
[SIGHS]
Memories
Like the corners of my mind
Here's an interesting clue.
Homer's assailant left a black smudge
on the spa invitation.
This could be
the breakthrough we...
Ha, ha. I thought I could get it
while it was in the recharger.
[SHOUTS]
I was wrong.
I don't know how we
ever had fun without him.
ANNOUNCER [ON TV]:
We now return to That '30s Show.
Hey, Pop, where's the
crank on this Victrola?
Why, it's the latest model.
From now on, the only crank in
this house is your Aunt Gladys.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
For your information,
I'm cranky because I've got polio.
AUDIENCE: Aww.
- Oh!
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS
THEN APPLAUDS]
Tom Shales gave this show
a good review and I'm the one in prison.
Bob, I know you're enjoying
fall preview week...
...but I was wondering if you made
progress towards finding Homer's killer?
No, I haven't. Go ahead, shock me.
Well, just a little one.
[GROANING]
Homer, it's stuck.
[SIGHS THEN GASPS]
Listen, Homer,
I don't know who your killer is.
But I do know he'll strike again.
Your only hope is to stay
completely out of sight.
Very well. I am gone.
Aah! Don't look at me.
[KNOCKING]
MAN: Homer Simpson?
- Right here.
[HORNS HONKING
AND UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
You've been elected
king of Mardi Gras.
Whoo-hoo!
Good things do happen to bad people.
Honey, the king of Mardi Gras
has to ride around on a float all day.
You'll be a sitting duck.
Marge, you're embarrassing me
in front of the drag queen.
[DRAG QUEEN GRUNTING]
[NOISEMAKER BLOWS]
Ha, ha.
It's Mardi Gras time in Springfield.
This year's king is
none other than...
...local hothead Homer Simpson.
Long live the king.
In a related story, Homer Simpson
may not have long to live.
Homer, it's a trap. You only won...
...because somebody stuffed
the ballot box with these.
- Nonetheless, the people have spoken.
- But I'm afraid you'll get hurt.
This is a way to flush
this killer out once and for all.
And get drunk on a Tuesday.
Today's Tuesday.
And you've had six beers.
But I'm not drunk.
[CROWD CHEERING
AND UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
WOMAN:
Yeah.
The killer is out there.
I would stake my entire
fortune of cigarettes on it.
Now, Bob, I know you're concerned.
But don't worry.
I have operatives working the crowd.
So, uh, you're from Tempe?
I'm from Chicago.
Whoa, I'm so drunk I'm gonna puke.
You ever get that feeling, beautiful?
America loves its kings,
from George III to Larry.
[GUNFIRE THEN HOMER GASPS]
Phew. Just Italians.
His float's already moving.
I didn't even hear the engine start.
Yeah, it's really running quiet.
Some mechanic tuned it up
before the parade.
A mechanic?
My God. That's it.
Homer, you must get off that float.
The brake line has been cut.
Oh, my God. Attention, drunken idiots.
This is your king.
Sacrifice yourselves
to slow me down.
[GRUNTING]
- Oh, that's heavy.
- Aah!
Hey, how about some beads?
- They're not for dudes.
- That's cool.
LISA: Dad's heading straight
for the Museum of Swordfish.
That museum has been nothing
but trouble since it opened.
Must save buffoon.
[SCREAMING]
Huh?
Ha, ha. I did it.
Wha...? You saved my life.
I saved a life. And it feels wonderful.
And yet, I could just as easily
drop you to your death.
Don't be so sure.
I got my legs wrapped
around your ass pretty tight.
[GUNSHOT]
Everything going dark.
Like Duff Stout, the beer
that made Ireland famous.
I love you, Doris. I... Ooh...
Ooh. We're up so high.
Where could that shot
have come from?
- There's your killer.
- Well, duh.
Your king needs these stilts.
- Jesus is our only king.
- Not anymore.
[GRUNTING]
There he is.
Hey, I know you.
You're my mechanic, Junior.
Frank Grimes, Jr.
Frank Grimes...
Don't you remember?
Your apelike incompetence
drove my father insane.
Frank Grimes...
What's this? "Extremely High Voltage."
Well, I don't need safety gloves,
because I'm Homer Simp...
Oh, yeah. How is old Grimey?
He's dead. Like you should be.
Whoa!
Wait, Frank Grimes wasn't married.
- How could he have a son?
- He happened to like hookers, okay?
Dad, I figured it out!
- The murderer is...
- We know, Frank Grimes, Jr.
Huh?
Precisely.
Take him away, boys.
That's nice work, Bob.
Now give him the rhino tranqs.
[GRUNTS]
[MOANING]
If I can tranq out
just one freak on stilts...
- ...I know I've done my job.
- You're living the dream, chief.
Dad, I'm really glad you're still alive.
Yeah, it's every parent's dream
to outlive their children.
Good night, son
Hello, Bart.
[SCREAMS]
[GRUNTS]
Looking for this?
Now I'm going to take some advice
that was given to me by Lenny...
...and kill you without delay.
One thrust and the deed is done.
I... I can't do it.
Why not?
Well, I guess I've, dear God...
...grown accustomed to your face.
[SINGING]
I've grown accustomed to his face
And dreams of gouging out his eyes
I've grown accustomed to my hate
My plans to lacerate
To disembowel
To hear him howl
The very reason thatl live
Is plotting how to watch him die
[POUNDING ON WALL]
HOMER: Bart, turn down that original
cast recording and go to sleep.
I know this chubby scalawag
Has made my life a living hell
Surely if I drank his blood
I'd be at peace
But well
You've grown accustomed to my face
- This isn't a duet.
- Sorry.
[SINGING]
I've grown accustomed to your fear
Accustomed to revenge
Accustomed to
Your face
We shall meet again, old friend.
But now I must
steal away into the night.
[GROANING]
[English - US -SDH]