(theme music playing)
CHORUS: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
(screams)
Whoop. Oop.
(screaming)
(thuds)
Good evening.
I'm Kent Brockman.
Our top story:
hunks, and lots of them
and all to raise money
for the Springfield Fire Department
to buy a fire engine
so they can get to fires.
Lazy bums.
Yeah, why don't we buy them
mink stoles while we're at it?
(laughing) Yeah. Good one.
And now, let's hear it
for our celebrity auctioneer--
Krusty.
ALL: What? Who? Who's that?
(murmuring continues)
The clown.
AUDIENCE: Oh!
(applauding)
(cheering)
Thank you. Thank you.
Hey, hey!
Heh?
No, I ain't reading that.
No, not that, either.
OK, let's bring on
our first bachelor.
(cheering)
All right, ladies,
this sexy fellow
describes himself
as "a big, thirsty teddy bear."
Say hello to Barney Gumbel.
OK, now, what am I bid?
Hey, now, I got zero,
I got no bid here. I got zero.
I'm standing at zero.
Anybody want to go
higher than zero?
I got zero right now.
OK, over there? No, zero.
I got nada, zilch.
I got bupkes.
I got zero. Nothing. Hey.
Poor Barney.
(sighs)
This lot is withdrawn.
(belches)
(music starts again)
Come on!
He likes sunsets--
what more do you want?
Arr.
I'm... not attractive.
The last bachelor likes women
who take their clothes off
for money.
Let's hear it for Moe.
Why do we have to stand here?
This is so humiliating.
Aren't there any good
bachelors in this town?
Ah, we're never going
to get that fire engine.
Well, I guess that's it, folks.
♪ Had some laughs ♪
♪ Killed some time ♪
Apu, you're a bachelor.
Get up there.
Oh, no, no. please,
I am nothing special.
Don't be shy. Excuse me.
Excuse me. We have
one more bachelor.
♪ Cash the check... ♪
-What?
-Just tell them about yourself.
Oh, um...
(clears throat)
Well, I have a doctorate
in Computer Science.
-Oh.
-Sounds pretty good to me.
Um... I run my own business,
of course.
Well. Well, now.
I do like to cook.
I'm not much of a talker,
but I love to listen,
and in my leisure time,
I like to build furniture
and then, to have a discussion
about where it could be
placed in a room.
-Now you're talking.
-Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
-Fifty dollars.
-Seventy-five.
You better have enough
to pay my alimony, Luann!
-Three hundred.
-Three-fifty.
Nine hundred and twenty-six.
Sold, to the five
desperate chicks.
Whoo! All right, We got him!
Woof!
Holy molly!
Well, look
who's the ladies man.
Come on...
(goofy giggling)
I had a great time, Apu.
And thanks for winning wubbsy.
I had no idea
you were such a great shot.
Oh, yes.
all Kwik-e-mart managers
must be skilled
in the deadly arts.
Oh.
Oh. That date
will not be easy to top,
but we shall see.
(honking)
Anybody up for
some clog dancing?
Why don't you try and stop me?
(tires screeching)
"This is just
a note to say
I think about you every day
and when I get
you all alone..."
Well, it gets
a little bit personal here.
I understand...
Yoink!
-Wow.
-I know.
-Whoa!
-Tell me about it.
(lustful moaning)
Oh. Here's one from my mother.
Ooh. Let's see what she wrote.
(lustful growling)
-(screams)
-You hate lotus flowers, too?
Don't get me started
on lotus flowers.
No, no, it is the sign
that it is time
for my arranged marriage.
Oh, well, congratulations.
No, no. Don't you
know what it means?
Not... really.
It all happened shortly after
my eighth birthday.
OK, here we go.
Ten goats and an electric fan?
You call that a dowry?
OK, we will throw in
a textile factory
but only because Manjula
is getting on in years.
Then it is agreed.
Your third daughter
will marry our first son.
It is done.
Oh, I cannot get married.
I'm just beginning
to enjoy my bachelorhood.
(sighs) What am I going to do?
Tell her the truth, you're
not ready to get married.
No, no. You do not know Mother.
She will never quit
until I am married.
Then just tell her
you're already married.
No. I cannot lie to my mother.
Then get married.
What the hell
do you want from me?
Yes, that is right, Mother.
I already got married.
Why did not I bother
to tell you?
Well... uh...
the reason is, um...
Well, I guess I...
I didn't think you'd understand.
Oh, got to go. Bye-bye-bye.
I love you, love you.
(kissing)
It worked. It worked.
The lie has set me free.
♪ Well, I'm hot-blooded ♪
♪ Check it and see ♪
♪ I got a fever of 103 ♪
♪ Come on, baby,
do you do more than dance? ♪
♪ I'm hot-blooded,
I'm hot-blooded ♪
♪ You don't have
to read my mind ♪
♪ To know what
I have in mind ♪
(song fades)
Loser.
(gasps)
Five hundred dollars.
Apu, wake up.
I want to buy a yodel
and this lottery ticket.
I have... this much.
I'm sorry. You do not have
enough for both.
Oh. Ooh...
Ooh... Oh...
Yodel.
(cash register rings)
(yawning)
Late night, huh?
I'm not the type
to kiss and tell, sir,
but listen to this...
(screams)
Oh, you dog.
It is my mother.
Oh, no. Oh, no.
What am I going to do?
What's the big problem?
Don't you see?
She is here to meet my wife.
The wife that I told her I had.
Ah! I do not have a wife.
Then maybe you shouldn't
have said told her you did.
Oh. She's going to be here
any second.
(grunts)
Oh, yes!
That will buy me some time.
Mm. Homer,
you've got to help me.
(munching) OK.
Seems to me...
(clearing throat)
What you ought to do is, um...
What, what, what, what, what?
Well... you could always
move into my house
and tell your mom
that Marge is your wife.
Is it me, or do your
plans always involve
some horrible web of lies?
-It's you.
(door opens)
Welcome to the Kwik-e-mart.
May I help... (gasps) Mother!
What are you doing here?
I have come to meet
this wife of yours.
And meet her you shall.
It is a very reasonable request
that can easily be granted
-in a timely and efficient...
-Let's go.
And we shall because it is
in the going that we...
Tat-tat-tat-tat-tat.
Oh... that yodel was so good.
-I wish I was eating it right now.
-(car door opens)
Oh, crap! I forgot!
Marge, I need a small favor.
For the next few days,
will you pretend to be Apu's wife?
-What?
-(doorbell rings)
Please. It's just for as long
as his mother's living here.
What?
Honey, I am in my home.
(nervous chuckle)
(groans)
Oh...
How was your day...
sweetheart?
Can you feel the love?
Mother, I would like
for you to meet
my darling wife
for many, many good years,
M... Marge.
Hello. so, what brings
you to America?
I have come to see the woman
for whom Apu was willing
to disgrace his family
and spit on his culture.
Oh.
Here I am!
OK. Gotta run.
Apu, I'm sure you want
to get upstairs
and fix that broken toilet
before Marge yells at you again.
I'm just so honored
to have you here in our home.
Thank you.
and having met you
let me say how deeply,
deeply disappointed I am.
Apu, your arranged
bride, Manjula
is a sweet, refined,
chaste woman.
Are you nuts?
Mother, come on.
You know that
one out of every
25 arranged marriages
ends in divorce.
Oh, Bart and Lisa!
You remember your father, Apu.
Well, this is your father
Apu's mother.
-Oh!
-Hi.
I cannot believe
you did not tell me
I had two grandchildren.
(sucking)
But you can't leave.
We're scamming
an old lady at my house
and I need a place to hide out.
Sorry, Homer.
I've been planning
this vacation for years.
I'm finally going
to see Easter Island.
Oh, right,
with the giant heads.
With the what, now?
-(snoring)
-Hey, Dad,
I've come to spend some time
with my favorite father.
Baloney!
You came here
to put me in a home!
You're already in a home.
Oh, how could you?
Abraham Simpson.
Cornelius Talmadge.
Oh, no, I'm not...
Oh, well, let's see
what you got here.
The pink ones
keep you from screaming.
All right, folks,
it's supper time.
Supper at 4:00?
Oh-ho, what a sweet deal.
Hey, they got chairs
with wheels,
and here I am,
using my legs like a sucker.
(wheelchair squeaking)
(motor humming)
Whoo! I must apologize
for the inconvenience, Marge.
You are a real sport.
Right. How much longer
is she going to be here?
Homer was a little
sketchy on the details.
It should not be more
than a few days.
She really, truly hates you.
Can I ask you about your dot?
What would you like to know?
What's the deal with that dot?
Yeah, can you see out of it?
Does it change colors
when you're ticked off?
You tell me.
Nothing yet.
Surely, you children are aware
of your Brahman heritage?
As long as you have
absolutely no follow-up
questions, yes.
Yes, we are.
Fully.
We have to go now.
(whistling)
Jasper.
Gladys.
Beatrice.
Looking good, Hattie.
Asa.
Hazel. Hazel.
Hazel!
Oh, the hell with her.
Hester.
Emil. Prudence.
Lemuel. Increase.
-Dad.
-Cornelius.
-(bell tinkling)
-WARDEN: Supper time!
(grunts)
Oh, no, you don't!
Oh, yes, I do.
(grinding)
Eat my dust.
Wow, someone sure likes
his kidney mush.
Damn right.
Mm. Who knew that Lays
made liquid potato chips?
I can't suck just one.
-(buzzing)
-Another bag of chips, Mr. Talmadge?
Please.
Also, I'm getting a bed-sore.
What do you have to do
to get turned around here?
(monitor beeping)
(grunting)
Hey, what's Lucky hooked up to?
A respirator.
It breathes for him.
And here I am,
using my own lungs
like a sucker.
And how come everyone
gets a bedpan
and I have to walk
all the way over there?
You mean, there?
Yeah!
Hello. I'm Cornelius Talmadge.
My family brought me here
on Monday
but I broke free
and went on a bit of a bender.
Wait a minute.
If you're Cornelius Talmadge,
then who's...
HOMER: When I get old, Marge,
I want you to promise
you'll put me in a home.
It's like being a baby,
only you're old enough
to appreciate it.
Well, I'm glad
you were having fun
because I've had my hands full
with Apu's mother.
Oh, right, right.
The fake marriage thing.
How's that going?
(door creaking)
OK, Apu, I am packed
and ready to go
to the airport... (screams)
Oh, my God.
Marge, how could you?
Oh, Apu, give it up.
(groans)
Mother, I am so sorry.
I lied to you
about being married.
Lied to his mother.
Tsk-tsk-tsk.
But the fact that I would stage
this ridiculous farce
surely proves to you
how much I do not want
to go through with
this arranged marriage.
I had no idea
how strongly you felt, Apu.
Now wipe that smile
off your face.
We have a wedding to plan.
(groans)
You know what you
could do, Apu?
Yeah, shut up.
You could fake your own death.
Oh, would you shut up?
All you need
is a car bomb and...
I can't believe
you don't shut up!
Yes, yes, Manjula.
I will take care
of all the wedding plans.
You just get on a plane
and come to America.
(clearing throat)
I have to go.
(speaking native language)
Believe me, I'd like to.
(laughing)
Good-bye.
I've been looking over
this list of things for the ceremony.
I've got the extra wine glasses
but I'm still short
a tandoori oven, an elephant
and four castrati.
What's a castrati?
I don't know,
but I'm sure it's spicy.
-Why is that woman still living here?
-Mm-mm.
Hey, you seen Apu lately?
He looks terrible.
Yeah, rumor has it
Marge threw him out.
Ah, tough break.
She's a beautiful lady.
You got that straight, Barn.
ALL: To Marge!
Moe, what do you recommend
for severe depression?
Booze, booze and more booze.
Huh! Nothing like a depressant
to chase the blues away.
Yeah, you got that right.
Oof. Manjula and I have not seen
each other in 20 years.
Two people cannot fall
in love sight-unseen.
Hey, hold on there.
I'm counting on that.
Well, just 24 hours
of freedom left.
Actually, it's more like 12.
No. I'm so stupid.
Seven-- it's seven hours.
You have seven hours.
See? Seven.
(groaning)
(singing sadly)
♪ Well, I'm hot-blooded ♪
♪ Check it and see ♪
♪ I got a fever of 103 ♪
Come on, you shouldn't be spending
your last hours of bachelorhood
in a dump like this.
You should be living
like there's no tomorrow
and I know just the place.
Ah, is this the life or what?
You want me
to turn on the bubbles?
Which Bombay
to Springfield flight is she on?
The 10:00, the 10:15,
or the 10:30?
I am so terribly sorry, sir.
It appears that your tiger
has been sent to St. Louis.
Mm-hmm. I should send you
to St. Louis.
No. no. He's not worth it.
Can you please indicate
your tiger type on this chart.
BOTH: Mm...
Number six.
How's that fire ring coming?
Is it sacred yet?
Almost.
I... can't...
Can you believe it?
Tradition forbids me
even to speak
to the woman I'm about
to spend my life with.
Has the whole world gone crazy?
Nah, just your screwy country.
(sighs) Your old friend Apu
is a lamb being led to the slaughter.
Don't worry, Apu.
Someday, you'll meet
someone you really love.
I'm really doomed.
Only the gods could stop
this wedding now.
Gods, eh?
(indistinct chatter)
No, no, no, no, no.
No pansies for me.
It's the tradition in India.
Yeah, all right.
It'll cover the gravy stains.
-Hey!
-Tradition.
Thanks for helping
us out, Reverend.
I know you've never performed
a Hindu ceremony.
Well, Christ is Christ.
Plus, I consulted
a Hindu web site.
(playing fanfare)
(gloomily) Hello, everyone.
What a happy, happy day.
Wow, I wish I had an elephant.
You did. His name was Stampy.
-You loved him.
-Oh, yeah.
(squeaking)
(trumpeting)
(gasping)
Lucky mouse.
(fanfare plays)
(all gasping)
Oh... Manjula?
Apu, remember me?
Obviously not.
(crashing)
HOMER: I am the God Ganesh!
This wedding angers me!
All will die
unless it is stopped!
-Oh, God.
-Please! listen to me!
(wailing)
(speaking in Hindi)
(screams)
Stop chasing Ganesh!
You're just going
to get more wrath.
Oh, I'm afraid
this is all my fault, Manjula.
To be perfectly honest
with you,
I have not exactly
been looking forward
to this arranged marriage.
(scoffs) Nor have I.
Marrying a complete stranger?
It is crazy.
All right.
Ganesh has been subdued.
HOMER (whimpering):
All will die.
Resume the ceremony.
Quickly, tell me. What is your favorite
movie, book and food?
Uh, the answer to all three
is fried green tomatoes.
(laughing)
That... that is good.
(clears throat)
Double-parked.
Oh, I am so torn.
You are clearly
so quick-witted and beautiful.
And when I look in your eyes,
I see that sweet little boy
who sold me my very first kiss
and I liked it.
Oh, do you think this marriage
could really work?
Who knows?
We can always get divorced.
Of course.
God bless America.
And now, ladies and gentlemen,
let me be the first
to present to you
Mr. and Mrs. Apu
Nahasapeemapetilan.
(cheering)
Ah, geez.
I am no good at weddings.
(singing "Close To You"
in Hindi)
Dad, those peanuts
aren't for you.
They're for the elephant.
Screw him.
(gasping)
Put me down!
Ganesh commands you!
Oh-ho-ho-ho!
Well, so far so good,
don't you think?
I cannot wait to show you
our apartment.
Apartment?
Oh, no, no, no.
You must buy me a house,
and you're getting a haircut.
-Oh.
-Got you.
(laughing)
Homer (screaming):
Come on, elephant! Stop!
(yelping, groaning)
Hey, everybody's upside-down.
(laughing)
(theme music playing)
Shh!
Captioned by
Visual Data Media Services