♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screech)
D'oh!
Aah!
(tires screech)
D'oh!
♪ They fight and bite ♪
♪ They fight and fight
and bite ♪
♪ Bite-bite-bite,
fight-fight-fight ♪
♪ The Itchy & Scratchy
Show! ♪
(Bart laughs)
Shh...
MAN: Cinq...
quartre...
trois...
deux...
(giggling)
MAN:
Un... maintenant!
(explosion)
Turn it down!
We don't want to
wake up Mom and Dad.
Shh!
(muffled laughter)
(laughing loudly)
(snoring)
(clearing throat)
Oh, my goodness!
Kids! Homer!
We're late for church!
I'm glad I dressed
last night.
Oh, I'd love to go
with you, honey,
but I got a lot of work
to do around the bed.
Homer, the Lord only asks
for an hour a week.
In that case,
he should've made
the week an hour longer.
-Lousy God.
-(groaning)
...and the very same
goes for Ezekiel.
Which brings us back
to our starting point:
The nine tenets
of constancy.
Damn it!
(clears throat)
Well, I seem to have
lost my place...
so I'll start over.
MAN: Aw, for the love
of crumb cake...
Our sermon today
is on constancy.
In as much as the...
moreover, by dint
of our application
of these principles,
we can learn...
...the auspices of constancy
sweet constancy.
(all snoring)
(bird shrieking)
Hey... wha...?
-Yay!
-Oh, man!
Am I glad to get
out of there!
Hey, calm down--
you're wrinkling
your church clothes.
Who cares? This is
the best part of the week.
It's the longest possible time
before more church!
Church shouldn't be
a chore.
It should help you
in your daily life.
It should,
but it doesn't.
Now, who's going with Daddy
to the dump?
-BOTH: Me!
-The dump?
We're going to get rid
of the Christmas tree.
It's starting
to turn brown.
-Want to come with?
-No, no,
I don't feel like
going to a trash pile today.
It's your life.
We'll bring you back
something nice.
(humming)
Can you believe it?
They give you five Q's
and only two U's.
What a world.
It's crazy.
So, what's on
your mind, Marge?
Sermons about constancy
and prudissitude
are all very well and good,
but the church could be
doing so much more
to reach out to people.
Oh, I don't see you volunteering
to make things better.
Well...
Okay, I will volunteer.
I wasn't prepared for that.
(grunting)
Come on, Christmas tree...
(coughing)
Okay, who's up
for some scrounging?
Hey! Here's a perfectly good
basketball half!
I found a Malibu Stacy
with no head.
(screeching)
(screaming)
(laughing)
Oh, my God!
Help me, Lisa!
BART: Lisa, Dad--
come here quick!
There is something
that you won't believe!
What the heck is that?
BART: Maybe it's a box
from the future.
LISA:
It looks Japanese.
Wha-- What's going on?
Why-- Why am I on
a Japanese box?
(high-pitched whimpering)
Oh, my God...
what is that?
MARGE: All done!
I swept the aisles,
and put all the collection plates
in the dishwasher.
Oh, and you wouldn't
believe
how many dead pigeons
there were in the organ.
Marge, you are
a real time-saver.
Do you know,
thanks to you
I've rediscovered
a form of shame
that's gone unused
for 700 years?
Wow...
(phone rings)
Lovejoy here.
Reverend,
this is Principal Skinner.
I'm facing a crisis,
and I didn't know
to whom to turn.
All right.
Mother's gone too far.
She's put cardboard over her
half of the television.
We rented
"Man Without A Face."
I didn't even know
he had a problem!
What should I do?
Well, maybe you should
read your Bible.
Um, any particular passage?
Oh, it's all good.
All right.
Thanks anyway.
Reverend, I hate to say this,
but it sounded
like that poor man
was reaching out to you.
I'm not sure your advice
was all that helpful.
(chuckling) Oh, Marge.
I was once idealistic
like you.
It was the mid '70s,
and I was fresh out
of seminary.
The '60s were long over
and people were
once again ready
to feel bad
about themselves.
♪ Jesus is just all right
with me ♪
LOVEJOY:
I came to Springfield
ready to roll up my sleeves
and help my fellow man.
There was just one fellow man
I hadn't counted on.
Reverend, I'm--
I'm afraid something
terrible has happened.
Well, sit down and rap
with me, brother.
That's what I'm here for.
Well, I was talked into doing
a dance called "The Bump,"
but my hip slipped, and my--
my buttocks came into contact
with the buttocks
of another young man!
I... see.
Then, the calls began.
FLANDERS: Well, I-I think I may be
coveting my own wife.
I'm meek, but... I could
probably stand to be meeker.
I-I-I think I swallowed
a toothpick!
LOVEJOY: Finally,
I just stopped caring.
Luckily, by then,
it was the '80s
and no one noticed.
But you can't
let a few bad experiences
sour you on helping people.
-Oh, sure I can.
-(phone rings)
Ugh! You handle it.
Me? No, I-- I--
Wait! I can't--
Hello?
Uh, yeah, hi. I'm calling
for Reverend Lovejoy.
Who is this?
Oh, well, this is, um...
the, uh... the listen lady.
Yeah? Well, listen, lady,
I've got so many problems
I-I don't even know
where to begin here.
Okay...
uh, why don't you
start from the top?
All righty.
Uh, number one:
I've lost the will to live.
Oh, that's
ridiculous, Moe.
You've got lots
to live for.
Really?
That's not what
Reverend Lovejoy's
been telling me.
Wow! You're good.
Thanks.
(ringing)
Hi. It's me again.
I got another problem.
Uh, this one's
about my cat.
(meowing)
Yeah! Shut up!!
I'm asking her.
Why would you volunteer
at the church?
I don't know. Guilt?
(scoffs) Volunteering
is for suckers.
Do you know that
so-called "volunteers"
don't even get paid?
Well, I think
volunteering is great.
Deep down,
it makes you feel...
Homer, will get that crazy box
off the dinner table?
It came from the dump.
But, Marge,
I'm obsessed with it.
Where did it come from?
What is it a box of?
How did my face get on it?
Hey, if they got
a picture of you,
that means they can see you.
They're probably watching us
right now.
That's ridiculous.
Nobody is watching us
right now.
Hai! Hai! Hai! Bye.
Hai!
Akira, can you
read this for me?
Ah, yes. This is a product
called "Mr. Sparkle."
Very popular dish detergent.
Hey...
he looks like you.
(laughs)
What's he saying?
He identifies himself as
"a magnet for foodstuffs."
He boasts that he will
"banish dirt
to the land of wind
and ghosts."
Wow!
Yes. You have very lucky dishes,
Mr. Simpson.
This soap is from the
sacred forest of Hokkaido,
renowned for its countless
soap factories.
Hokkaido, eh?
See, all along,
I been telling Carl
I'm married to
a beauty queen.
Now, he's coming
over for dinner.
Lenny, I'm sure
he'll like your wife
no matter what she looks like.
Oh, no, no. No.
It's worse than that.
I don't even have a wife.
I just said I did to,
you know, be a big-shot.
Oh. Well, it's time
to start telling the truth.
Now, when I have to tell
my husband the truth,
I cook him a big,
delicious dinner.
By the time
he's done eating
he's too full and tired
to care what I have to say.
Wow, that's great!
When Carl comes over,
I'll stuff him
till he don't know
what's what.
Seymour, I'm getting tired.
Tell them we're going next.
Well, I'm not principal
of the line, Mother.
And you never will be.
I'd like the phone book
for Hokkaido, Japan, please.
Okay.
Here you go.
The phone book
for Hokkaido, Japan.
Thank you.
May I please use your phone?
Is it a local call?
Y... yes.
(touch tones)
(phone ringing)
Mooshi-mooshi?
Yes. This is Homer Simpson
from America.
Who may I say
is speaking to me?
(speaking Japanese)
Hello, chief?
Let's talk, why not?
Uh, hello?
Why am I Mr. Sparkle?
Oh, you like Mr. Sparkle?
Well, I am Mr. Sparkle.
Oh, you have
many question, Mr. Sparkle.
I send you premium answer question
hundred percent.
The Lord will hear
your lamentations
and give solace to your spirit.
The Lord or Marge Simpson!
LENNY:
Amen to that.
(all exclaiming)
Um... could we please
not yell out things
in the church?
(bell ringing)
(overlapping dialog)
Wait a minute, please.
One at a time.
One at a time!
Now, who has
the most urgent problem?
I have a recurring dream
in which I'm falling.
Come right this way,
Mel, I--
Tim, hold my calls.
Mm...
I'm a shepherd
without a flock.
What have I done
to lose them?
The real question is
"what have you done
to keep them?"
(gasps)
St. Eleutherius of Nicomedia.
That's my name,
don't wear it out.
To inspire men,
you must be brave.
I introduced Christianity
to Mongolia.
It didn't take,
but it was worth a try.
Tell us, good reverend,
what great deeds
have you done
to inspire
the hearts of men?
Well, I had the vestibule
re-carpeted.
I've appeared
in over 8,000 visions
and that's the lamest reply
I've ever heard.
Oh, now, please, I--
I thought saints
were supposed to be friendly.
Oh, you're just lucky
God isn't here.
(phone ringing)
Hello. Listen Lady.
Marge, people say
you've got a real knack
for solving problems.
Well... this is
a little awkward
but, um, Tim came home
from church
so despondent today,
he's just been playing with
his trains all afternoon.
We all need a little time
to ourselves, Helen.
Just give him a day or two
and I'm sure he'll be back
to his old dynamic self.
Okay.
Attention,
H-O scale passengers:
The dining car is closed.
Root beer is still available,
but the cost is now $6.50.
If the passengers
will look to the right
you will see a sad man.
That is all.
Look, we got a package
from the Mr. Sparkle
company in Japan.
Ooh!
Ow!
It's a videotape.
Put it in! Put it in!
Oh, hello,
American investor.
I see you are interested
in distributing Mr. Sparkle
in your home prefecture.
You have chosen wisely,
but please,
don't believe me.
Observe this commercial.
(whistle blows)
Aka ni taishite burei da!
Yogore o yaburu!
Honki da yo.
(xylophone plays)
Doke, mina doke!
Burabura
shitero tokoro ja nai!
Ore to issho ni
nasu ka shinu ki ka?
ALL:
Isamashii honin rogo desu ne!
Mister Sparkle no charenji
ni ojimasu!
Awesome power!
(drumming)
(giggling)
Natsu yasumi no keikaku
wa do desho?
Mister Sparkle!
Un no yoi besto washu!
Boring!
That didn't
explain anything.
All I know is
they stole my face
and used it
for their stupid logo.
There's no other explanation.
Wait, look.
ANNOUNCER:
Mr. Sparkle,
a joint venture
of Matsumura Fishworks,
and Tamaribuchi
Heavy Manufacturing Concern.
Hey, it was all
a coincidence.
Yep. There's your answer,
fish bulb.
Well, it was a good
ride while it lasted.
Come on, kids,
let's go home.
We are home.
That was fast.
You've just got to accept it.
Your Gameboy is gone.
It's at the bottom
of the ocean.
Aye, aye.
Aye.
(phone rings)
Hello. Listen Lady.
Uh... I'm in some
hot soup here, Marge.
Some teenagers are hanging out
in front of the store.
I-I think they could start
slacking at any moment.
Well, Ned, you don't have
to stand for that.
You just march
right up to those youngsters
and tell them to vamoose.
Yeah, well...
if you're sure
that will help...
Hey, let's go over
to the one-hour photo
and breathe some fumes.
Uh, excuse me, fellas.
I couldn't help thinking
it might be nice
if you could, uh,
vamoose, you know?
(nervous chuckle)
If possible.
(phone ringing)
Hello. Listen Lady.
Uh... Marge I-I appreciate
your advice
but, uh, things have gotten--
(chuckles)
Well, they-they're, uh,
a lot worse.
(ominous laughter)
Now, Ned, troubled boys
need rules and discipline.
They crave it!
You just lay down the law.
Well, yeah, I know,
but they--
They're on their mini-bikes
and all.
Oh, all right,
let me talk to them.
Put me on with the lead boy.
Boys, there's a call here
for you.
(dial tone)
Hmm. Oh, well.
(water gurgles)
(doorbell rings)
Oh, good morning, Maude.
Morning, Marge.
Um, did your husband
come home last night?
Of course he did.
Really? Oh...
because the thing is, um...
mine didn't.
(gasps)
Oh, my God, Ned!
(gasping)
Yes, Marge?
Reverend, I gave Ned Flanders
some bad advice.
Now he could be
in real trouble.
(groaning)
What happened now?
Did he swallow a paper clip?
No. He's disappeared.
Oh, I'm in way over my head.
I mean, where do
the helpers turn
when they
need help?
♪♪ (organ)
Sorry.
(phone rings)
Marge, why don't you
let me handle this?
(ringing)
Hello? Church basement.
(panting)
Yeah, it's Ned Flanders.
The teens have been
chasing me all night.
They-They finally stopped
to gas up their scooters.
Ned! Where are you?!
Well, I can't see
the name of the station
but the gas costs 1.49
and 8/10.
Eight tenths?
Donny's Discount Gas!
(tires screeching)
Thanks for swinging by
the house, Reverend.
-Donny?
-What?
Did you see a man
being chased
by some young
hooligans?
I see lots of stuff.
Did you see that?
Yes.
Huh. Looks like
we lost him.
Yeah. Well, we proved
our point.
He'll think twice
next time he tries to defend
his business.
(yawning)
I'm sleepy.
Let's go to school.
(sighs)
They're leaving.
The ordeal is over.
(screeching)
(screaming)
Ned!
-Mr. Flanders!
Flanders, where
are you?!
(all yelling)
Hey, Flanders, it's me!
Heh Mr. Sparkaru!
Mr. Sparkaru!
Konnichi-wa.
(Flanders screaming)
(gasping)
(gasps) That came from
Baboon County, USA!
Help! What do I do?!
Play dead!
No! Run around in circles!
No! Act like a lion!
Swipe at the dominant male!
Come on, Ned!
Knock that monkey down!
Jumpin' kangaroo rats!
You've got to get
him out of there.
Geez, I'd like to,
but if they don't
kill the intruder
it's really bad
for their society.
-They're going to kill him?
-Eventually.
First, they'll
eat his skin.
-(gasping)
-Eww.
Tell Maude I want
a fancy funeral!
Big coffin! Lots of jewels!
(whistle blows)
Look!
It's Reverend Lovejoy!
Thank heavens!
Entrust your hand to mine, Ned.
(groaning)
(howling and screeching)
Oh! Oh--
Thank the Lord.
He's truly watching
over--
-(screaming)
-(screeching)
Say your prayers,
you heathen baboons!
(grunting)
Wow.
Oh! Those
poor monkeys.
They started it.
(gasping)
You saved me,
Reverend.
You really went
above and beyond.
Thank you.
Oh, don't thank me.
Thank Marge Simpson.
She taught me that there's
more to being a minister
than not caring
about people.
(chuckling)
Amen!
(baboons screeching)
...baboons to the left of me,
baboons to the right,
the speeding locomotive
tore through
a sea of inhuman fangs.
A pair of the great apes
rose up at me, but biff-bam!
I sent them flying
like two hairy footballs.
A third came screaming at me--
(imitating baboon hissing)
And that's when I got mad.
Now that's religion!
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.