(SlNGlNG) The Simpsons
(SCHOOL BELL RlNGlNG)
(TlRES SCREECHlNG)
D'oh !
(SCREAMlNG)
(TlRES SCREECHlNG)
(ALSO SPRACH ZARATHUSTRA
PLAYlNG)
Wow!
The WiId DingIeberries?
lt's a movie version
of a cartoon family
you can see for free on TV.
But they
stretched out the plot
and added a wildebeest
from the hood !
l am so there!
Sorry, pally.
The DingIeberries
are sold out.
But looking at you,
l'm sure your kids
are used to disappointment.
How about
Diet Coke: The Movie?
Sold out.
President Air Bud:
Tail to the Chief?
Sorry.
My Big Fat Greek Salad?
Not a movie.
The only movies
starting now are
The Re-Deadening
and Teenage Sex Wager.
Ooh ! Well, l am curious
to see if those teens
lose their virginity.
And the wager only
sweetens the deal.
Mr. Simpson,
that movie is condemned
by our church's movie guide.
(HOMER READlNG)
Refresh my memory.
These dweebs are
with us, why?
Because Mr. Flanders
volunteered to
take the senior citizens
out for ice cream.
Mmm. . . Ow!
This ice cream's too cold !
Ow! l cut myself
on the cone!
(CHUCKLlNG)
Now, now,
remember why we're here.
To celebrate
Jasper's birthday.
(SlGHlNG)
Birthday?
(SlREN BLARlNG)
(SENlORS GASPlNG)
Yo, yo, yo!
Give it up for
M.C. Birthday!
(SlNGlNG)
I say a birth, a day,
a birth-a-de-day
Now my good time gang
wiII bIow you away
(ALL SCREAMlNG)
Never leave the day room.
Okay, kids.
Forget the movie.
We'll just go to
the furniture store
and sit down.
Two for
The Re-Deadening, please.
Huh?
The Re-Deadening?
ls that any good?
Good? l'm in it.
l had a small
speaking role.
Yeah. l went to visit him
and was banned from the set.
Mr. Leonard,
how do you get
in a movie?
Ha! Classic Hollywood story.
The director saw my photo
in a medical book.
Hey, Lenny. ls your film
appropriate for kids?
Oh, yeah.
There are lots
of kids in it.
They fall victim
to a vicious. . .
(lNTERRUPTlNG)
Don't ruin it for me!
One adult and four children
for The Re-Deadening.
CHlLD'S VOlCE:
La, la, la, la,
la, la, la
What's that,
Baby Button-Eyes?
You want me to kill Mummy?
(GASPS)
But Mummy is ever so kind.
What?
Your buttons came from
the trousers of
a psychotic killer?
Then l have no choice.
(WlND BLOWlNG)
(SCREAMS)
(BOTH SCREAMlNG)
Hey, l paid for this popcorn,
and l'm eating it.
Mr. Simpson, l'm scared.
(LAUGHlNG)
Relax, stupid.
Everything you
see is make-believe.
Although it is
based on a true story.
Some of which happened
in this very theater.
Oh, oh ! Here comes my part!
Baby Button-Eyes!
What are you doing
possessed at this hour?
l'd better tell
the governess. . .
(GROWLS)
Oh ! God ! The prophecy
has been fulfilled !
(SCREAMlNG)
The buttons look like
they're sewn to my eyes.
But they're really
held on with hot wax.
Dad, l don't like
this movie.
Can we go home?
Oh, honey, don't be scared.
Look, they killed
the evil doll.
(MAN SCREAMlNG ON SCREEN)
(WHlMPERlNG)
Well, what do you know?
lt's unkillable.
(WHlMPERS)
Honey, can Daddy rest
his soda on your head?
Mmm-hmm.
That's my girl.
You took little children
to The Re-Deadening?
Homer, this is a rare lapse
in judgment for you.
But scaring kids
is good for them.
lt hardens them
against future terrors,
like roofing
and driveway scams.
CHlLD'S VOlCE:
La, la, la, la...
(BOTH SCREAMlNG)
Oh, sorry. l forgot l bought
the soundtrack album.
Honey, l know you're scared.
But there's no boogie woogies
or wooly bullies out there.
Oh. Your nightlight's
burned out.
And the only
bulbs we have left
are these red ones.
lt was only a movie
filmed in Vancouver
with Donald Sutherland
as the priest
who stopped believing. . .
(LOUD BANGlNG)
Ah !
(MALE VOlCE GROWLlNG)
Both of us heard
mysterious noises
coming from this very spot.
Bart and l will
explore the attic
until we find their source.
(LOUD CREAKlNG)
(LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
Must be the pipes.
What do you think, Bart?
l think you're
on your own, toots!
(GASPlNG FEARFULLY)
Okay. l'll just stay calm
and approach
this scientifically.
(LOUD BANGlNG)
Oh, God ! Oh, God !
(CRYlNG) Oh, no!
lf l don't make it out alive,
l love you, Mom and Dad.
Maggie, you can
have my books.
And Bart,
l'll see you in hell,
you booger-eating wuss!
That's right! We all know!
(CRUNCHlNG)
Ah ! Bones!
Copyright Pink
Pony Productions.
Visit us on the web
at lisathemovie.com.
Ah !
(MUSlC PLAYlNG ON TV)
Homie, that Kojak
is sexier than Cannon
and Barnaby Jones
put together.
l think he looks
a little like you.
(CHUCKLlNG)
Who loves ya, baby?
How about
a little interrogation?
Okay. You have
the right to remain sexy.
Anything you touch
can and will be
held against you
in a court of sex.
lf you cannot
afford a sex-torney. . .
(MOANlNG)
Mom, Dad, there's a ghost
in the house!
Good. Can you play with him
for half an hour?
Oh !
l don't see any ghosts.
l did find this
Newsweek from 1 986.
Why America
loves Saddam Hussein.
(EERlE WHlSTLlNG)
That's it!
lt's one thing for a ghost
to terrorize my children !
But quite another for him
to play my theremin !
(WHlSTLlNG CONTlNUES)
Hello, Simpsons.
Artie Ziff!
None other!
l've been hiding
in your attic
living off the moisture
l can suck from the rafters!
l thought we killed him !
No, we didn't.
But l did delete him from
my bulk e-mail list.
No, you didn't.
That's right.
Twice a week,
l get your e-mail
of the monkey peeing
in his own mouth.
Oh, yeah. (CHUCKLlNG)
That monkey got America
through some tough times.
Artie Ziff! Why are
you living in our attic?
Let me explain.
l was an
lnternet billionaire.
Say no more.
l would stop,
but l love my voice.
ARTlE: It was the go-go '90s.
And I was partying
with Newt Gingrich,
Janeane Garofalo
and Scottie Pippen.
Everyone Ioved my corporation.
And then, the bubble burst.
Wait! Don't go!
My stock will have
a slight rebound in 2003.
I had nothing.
(TlRES SCREECHlNG)
They even took my repo vans.
l had nowhere to go.
So l came here because
Marge is the closest thing
l've ever had to true love.
We had one date!
And you were not a gentleman !
(GRUMBLES)
ARTlE: Oh.
Don't worry.
lf you let me stay,
l'll be on my best behavior.
Not even a fresh remark,
except this one.
Wowie, wow, wow, wow!
Zazooga!
Well, l don't know, Artie.
Forgive me. l'm just
so envious of the happiness
you all have.
Can l please be part of it?
Just till l get
back on my feet?
No way! He's an
annoying sneak who's
out to steal my wife!
Come on, Dad.
With his brains
and your musky smell,
l've got a full
male role model.
And it would be nice
to have someone
here l can beat up.
Ow! No fair! l'm telling.
(LAUGHlNG)
Okay, kids.
You can keep him.
Yay!
(GROANlNG)
"When she pressed her
lips to his forehead
"and walked out
with Denise and Gary
"into the warm spring night,
"she felt that nothing could
kill her hope now."
Nothing !
Ah. Thanks for
reading me The Corrections.
lt makes me feel better
about my own family.
Doesn't your
father ever read to you?
He tried once.
But he got confused
and thought the book
was real.
He's still looking for
that chocolate factory.
lt consumes him.
Hey, Mom, can l
sleep over at Milhouse's?
l thought you were
playing catch with Artie.
Yeah. But after
the ice cream man cut up
his credit card,
he got a little depressed.
Oh, my!
Well, Homer, maybe you should
take him to Moe's.
Come on, little fella.
You're hanging
with me tonight.
Guys, l'd like you
to meet Artie Ziff.
Hello, handsome!
Hello!
Losers.
KENT: Coming up.
Can yodeling cure cancer?
Of course not. But first,
where is Artie Ziff?
(GASPS)
The SEC wants to know.
lt seems Ziff Corp.
spent stockhoIders'
money on everything
from marble toothbrushes
to soIid goId underpants.
Small investors
have been wiped out.
l lost all me
"screw you" money.
l'm very sorry to
hear that, Willie.
Screw you !
Authorities are
currentIy operating
under the theory
that Ziff is Iiving
in a cave somewhere.
He's not in here, Chief.
That's some good
speIunking, Lou.
Mighty fine speIunking.
Okay, read 'em and weep.
l don't know why l'm losing.
Maybe l have
some kind of "tell."
Hot mamma,
l'm living in flushtown !
Population Artie!
Uh, l guess l'm in
for 50 cents.
l fold.
Me, too.
l'm out.
l'm done.
l'll see your
50 cents and raise you $1 .
Whoa!
Well, l'm out of cash.
But would you accept 98%
of the outstanding shares
of Ziff Corp. stock?
And the peanuts
in your mouth.
Very well.
(HACKlNG COUGH)
All of them.
Flush. What have you got?
Four Jacks.
(LAUGHlNG)
Check it out.
l own a multinational
corporation.
(LAUGHlNG)
l always knew
someday l'd be a C.O. D.
(GLASS SHATTERlNG)
Freeze! Securities and
Exchange Commission !
Artie Ziff, you're wanted
for stock manipulation
and securities fraud.
lt's scum like you
that undermine
investor confidence.
lnvestor confidence?
Perhaps this affects me?
l own 230 million
shares of Ziff Corp. stock.
You're
the majority shareholder?
l sure am.
With all the inherent
legal liabilities.
(GUNS COCKlNG)
Hey, what are you. . .
You're under arrest.
Wait a minute.
How can you arrest Homer?
This guy's the one what done
the thing that
why you're here for.
l'm talking malfeasance here.
All right. l admit it.
l did run Ziff Corp.
into the ground.
And this man took me
into his home when
no one else would.
And now as the result
of his brilliant
card playing,
he's the one you want!
(GASPlNG)
Tape his mouth so
he can't deny it!
Don't tell my kids
l'm going to jail !
Tell them l joined
the Blue Man Group!
l'm the fat one!
WOMAN: Homer Simpson,
how do you respond
to the charge that
your company has
betrayed the public trust?
(WHlSPERlNG lNAUDlBLY)
Plead the Fifth Amend. . .
What?
(WHlSPERlNG lNAUDlBLY)
Refuse to
answer on the grounds
that l. . . What?
(WHlSPERlNG lNAUDlBLY)
lnseminate myself?
(QUlETLY)
Dudes, l think this
guy's coming on to me.
You, sir, are a moron !
A Mormon?
But l'm from earth !
Oh, for heaven sakes!
Your majesty,
can l go home now?
Your company's crimes
have left a scar
on this great nation.
And she was so beautiful.
But what man
would want her now?
MAN: l wouldn't want her. . .
KRUSTY: Yeah, she was hot.
My husband's going to jail,
and it's all your fault!
Do you know why
no one likes you?
Anti-Semitism?
No!
Your problem is you never
think of anyone
besides yourself.
Marge,
l think about a lot more
than just moi.
(SlNGlNG)
Artie, Artie, Artie, Artie
Artie, Artie,
Artie, Artie
(SCATTlNG)
Oh, my God.
She's right.
l never want you
in this house again !
lf he's out,
can l move back in?
What do you think?
And she's the nice one.
Okay, kids.
This book should help you
deal with your feelings.
Look, Maggie. lt's a pop-up.
"Daddy's made a shiv.
"Can you help him
ice Johnny Shakes,
the jailhouse stoolie?"
Uh, ew.
Hey, let me read it to her.
"Johnny's friends
get some payback on
Daddy while he's sleeping."
Daddy's on fire.
Daddy's not on fire.
Daddy's on fire. . .
MARGE: Daddy's not on fire!
(CRYlNG)
Okay, fine. He is.
(COOlNG)
l miss you guys so much.
The smell of
Marge's pork chops.
The way you kids kiss
my owies when l go boom.
(SOBBlNG)
This place has become
like a prison to me!
Hey, Dad.
Maybe this will
cheer you up.
Why you little. . .
(lMlTATES CHOKlNG)
Aw. lt's no use, son.
By the time
l get out of here,
you'll be grown.
(SlNGlNG)
Turn around, turn around
Turn around
and you're a young man
(VOlCE BREAKlNG)
And you're too big to choke
(SOBBlNG)
Well, well,
look who showed his face.
The louse who
sold out his only friend.
You've got a lot
of nerve coming here.
But since you did,
what'll it be?
First one's on the house.
ls this dump open?
We were jogging and
ran out of cigarettes.
Pardon me for intruding.
But l believe
teenage girls
shouldn't smoke.
(LAUGHlNG)
(COUGHlNG VlOLENTLY)
Are you still
living with Marge?
No.
She kicked me out for sending
her husband to prison.
You put Homer in jail?
(SHUDDERS)
The hair is standing up
on the back of my knees.
Keep your Odor-Eaters
on, Selma.
l've seen you get
hurt too many times.
l'm not gonna let him into
my heart or my bedroom.
Just 1 0 minutes
on the beanbag.
Come on, Short Round.
We're going back
to my temple of doom.
Be gentle!
You know,
they say that
the love of a good woman
can save any man.
Except you, freak!
Well, if you
change your mind,
you know where l am.
ln my nightmares!
l'm gonna stop now.
(ARTlE GRUNTlNG SOFTLY)
SELMA: What the hell
are you doing?
l can't get my socks off.
Ah, leave 'em on.
l like a man with
a little mystery.
l'm done.
My kinda man.
ARTlE: Oh !
Wonderful,
glorious, magnificent.
And you were
pretty good, too.
(LAUGHlNG)
Oh ! (lNHALES DEEPLY)
Selma, you've made
a new man of me.
Thanks to your angry love,
l can no longer
sit by selfishly while
another suffers
for my book cooking.
What are you gonna do?
First,
l'm gonna read the paper,
have a little nosh.
And then,
l'm gonna rinse out
a few things.
And then, finally,
l will get
an innocent man
out of jail.
Well, he can't break
my heart, 'cause he kind
of makes me sick.
This could work.
Artie Ziff shocked
investigators today
by turning over
a second set of books
detaiIing his own
financiaI cuIpabiIity
and exonerating stumbIing,
bumbling boob Homer Simpson.
Simpson's grateful family
had this to say.
I'm so happy to be getting
my husband back.
And I'm happy to
listen to FM 95.3,
home of Boomer and the Diz!
Bart!
Chill out, Mom.
They gave me this hat.
Mmm...
Sorry you were
wrongfully imprisoned,
Simpson.
Can l apply my time
toward a future crime?
You can either steal a car
or kick me in the crotch.
(GRUNTS) No one
ever chooses the car.
Oh, Dad !
Mmm. l missed you so much !
Oh, my God !
Maggie, you're talking !
Homer, l believe
that's Lisa.
Oh, Bart,
what a man you've become.
Artie, thank you for
doing the right thing,
eventually.
All l needed was
the love of a good woman.
And since you're
not interested. . .
l'm not!
Merely checking.
Because l'm into that.
l'll visit you
in two weeks.
l have to admit,
l'll miss having him around.
(LAUGHlNG)
l don't think we've seen
the last of Artie Ziff.
Yo, hobbit.
l'm like your roommate.
Oh, a smoker, eh?
Well, l have ways
of dealing with you.
Squirt, squirt, squirt.
Your lungs will thank me.
Kids, you better take your
last look at Uncle Artie.
Oh, look!
There's a whole bunch of you !
Squirt, squirt, squirt!
That's it. Circle around me.
Squirt, squirt, squirt,
squirt, squirt,
squirt, squirt.
Oh, l'm gonna
need more water.
English - US - PSDH