(horse neighs)
(laughing)
(laughing louder)
(roaring with laughter)
-(splat)
-(Krusty groans)
Ah, the Miracle Mile.
Where value wears
a neon sombrero,
and there's not a single church
or library to offend the eye.
There it is!
The chain that put the "fat"
in "fat Southern sheriffs."
I want a colossal donut
just like the one
on the sign.
D'oh! Nuts.
That's false advertising.
Sorry, sir.
No refunds.
I paid for a colossal donut,
and I'm going
to get a colossal donut.
-You don't scare us.
-(thunderclap)
(tires screech)
(thunderclap)
RADIO ANNOUNCER:
Astronomers from Tacoma to Vladivostok
have just reported
an ionic disturbance
in the vicinity
of the Van Allen Belt.
Scientists are recommending that all
necessary precautions be taken.
(snorting)
Eggheads.
What do they know?
-(metal scraping)
-Hee hee hee!
I got your donut, Lard Lad!
And what are you going
to do about it?
(thunderclap)
-(metal creaking)
-(stomping)
(Godzilla-like roar)
(thunderclap)
(Marge grunting)
Homer, where
did you get that?
Get what?
That giant donut.
Well, I acquired it legally,
you can be sure of that.
(cheering)
Dude, you're huge!
Yeah, let's party, baby.
(yelling)
(grumbling)
Fellas!
Where are you going
at this hour?
Hey! Don't scratch up
them heads!
Good morning, everybody.
Panic is gripping Springfield,
as giant advertising mascots
rampage through the city.
Perhaps it's part of some
daring new ad campaign,
but what new product
could justify such carnage?
A cleanser?
A fat-free fudge cake
that doesn't let you down
in the flavor department
like so many others?
(yells)
Let me go--
No, stop! Stop! No!
-(tires screeching)
-(kids screaming)
Whoa. Another acid flashback.
Man, I'd hate to be driving
a bus right now.
-(screaming)
-(gulps)
Aw, they're not
so tough.
Uh, Chief, that
wasn't a monster.
That was the captain
of the high school
basketball team.
Uh, yeah...
well, he was turning
into a monster, though.
BART:
What are you waiting for?
Wreck the school.
You know you wanna.
-Hmm.
-I agree.
-Destroy the school.
-Hmm.
(shouts)
(doorbell rings)
Hello? Yes? Oh.
(laughs nervously)
If you're looking
for that big donut of yours,
uh, Flanders has it.
Just smash open his house.
He came to life.
Good for him.
-(glass shattering)
-(rubble falling)
(approching stomps)
(doorbell)
-Help me, Lord!
-I told you!
Flanders has it.
Or Moe. Go kill Moe.
-(tires screeching)
-Homer, just give him the donut.
Once he has it, that'll be
the end of all this horror.
Well... okay.
If it'll end horror.
(barking)
(whimpers)
Don't you ever get tired
of being wrong
all the time?
Sometimes.
(Godzilla-like roar)
These monsters
are destroying
everything and everyone
we hold dear...
and you kids should
have jackets on.
Hey, what's that
in his footprint?
Hmm.
If your advertising agency
created all those
giant characters,
you must know
how to stop them.
Well, sir, advertising
is a funny thing.
If people stop
paying attention to it,
pretty soon,
it goes away.
Like that old woman
who couldn't find the beef?
Exactly.
If you stop paying attention
to the monsters,
they'll lose their powers.
But people can't help
looking at them.
They're wrecking
the town.
(roaring in distance)
You know, maybe
a jingle would help.
-(playing piano)
-♪ Don't watch the mo-- ♪
(changes key)
♪ Don't watch the-- ♪
♪ Monsterss-s-s... ♪
(chuckles)
Well, it'll sound a lot better
coming out of Paul Anka.
LISA:
Hey, Springfield!
Are you suffering
from the heartbreak of...
monsteritis?
Then take a tip
from Mr. Paul Anka!
♪ To stop those monsters
one, two, three ♪
♪ Here's a fresh new way
that's trouble-free ♪
♪ It's got Paul Anka's
guarantee... ♪
♪ Guarantee void
in Tennessee ♪
BOTH: ♪ Just don't look,
just don't look ♪
♪ Just don't look,
It worked!
They're all dead!
Well, except for chubsy-ubsy
over there.
(crowd clamors)
Mmm... sprinkles.
Homer, stop looking!
Don't make us poke
your eyes out, Dad.
Oh!
Here comes something.
Remember the story.
We're newlyweds on our way
to Earth capital.
D'oh. Shazbot!
Even as I speak,
the scourge of advertising
could be heading
toward your town.
Lock your doors,
bar your windows,
because the next
advertisement you see
could destroy your house
and eat your family.
We'll be right back.
Okay boy,
catch the Frisbee.
Good catch, boy.
(English accent)
Thanks, Bart.
(boinging sound)
-(cash register bell dinging)
-(birds chirping)
Oh, hard luck.
(stammering babble)
Ah!
Glad to rake
your acquaintance.
(laughing)
(laughing louder)
(roaring with laughter)
(screams)
(sighs)
It was only a dream.
(yells)
HOMER:
Bart! Is that you?
-Yes.
-Take out the garbage.
And then he raked me
across the chest.
And the weirdest thing was
it was that school janitor
who mysteriously disappeared,
Groundskeeper Willie.
Oh, my God, Bart,
Groundskeeper Willie
was in my nightmare, too,
but he got me
with hedge clippers.
He ran his floor buffer over me.
(chuckling) Children, I couldn't help
monitoring your conversation.
There's no mystery
about Willie.
Why, he simply disappeared.
Now, let's have
no more curiosity
about this bizarre cover-up.
Remember, class, the worse you do
on this standardized test,
the more funding
the school gets.
So don't knock yourselves out.
You have three hours to--
-Finished!
-Ugh.
Then put your head down
on your desk and sit quietly.
Ah... a duet of pleasures.
I am the wondrous wizard
of Latin!
I am a dervish of declension
and a conjuror of conjugation
with a million hit points
and maximum charisma!
Ha ha! Morire: to die.
Morit: he, she or it dies!
Moris: you die.
(screams)
(chortling)
You've mastered a dead tongue,
but can you handle a live one?
(choking)
(yelps)
(shrieks)
Ha ha!
Wheel him out quietly.
It's best the children
don't see him.
(all screaming)
Oh, just get it out of here.
Not into the kindergarten.
(high-pitched screams)
Mom, Dad!
Martin died
at school today.
Ooh.... I don't see
what that has to do
with Groundskeeper Willie.
Um...
We didn't mention
Groundskeeper Willie, Mom.
Mm...
Kids, it's time we told you
the true story
and put your fears to rest.
It's a story of murder
and revenge
from beyond the grave.
It all started on the 13th hour
of the 13th day
of the 13th month.
We were there to discuss
the misprinted calendars
the school had purchased.
(shuddering)
Oh, lousy Smarch weather.
"Do not touch Willie."
Good advice.
(ratcheting)
♪♪
Huh?
(screaming)
Our next budget item:
$12 for doorknob repair.
ALL:
Nay.
(Willie screaming)
Recharge fire extinguishers.
This is a free service
of the fire department.
-ALL: Nay.
-Nay.
G-aah!
G-aah! Help!
Please help me!
Willie, please.
Mr. Van Houten
has the floor.
I for one
would like to see
the cafeteria menus
in advance
so parents can adjust their
dinner menus accordingly.
I don't like the idea
of Milhouse having
two spaghetti meals
in one day.
-(fire roaring)
-(anguished screaming)
You'll pay for this,
with your children's blood!
Oh, right. How you going to
get them? "Skeleton power"?
I'll strike where you
cannot protect them:
in their dreams.
Bart, don't you realize
what this means?
The next time we fall asleep,
we could die.
Welcome to my world.
(snoring)
(yawning)
TV ANNOUNCER: ...On this edition
of Asian Market Wrap-up:
there's a volcano waiting
to erupt in the Pacific rim.
Its name?
Medium-term
convertible debentures.
It's no use, Bart.
We can't
stay up forever.
You're right.
The only thing left to do
is go into my dream
and force Willie
into a final showdown.
You stay awake.
If it looks like I'm
in trouble, wake me up.
Okay.
But promise you won't be
grouchy.
(yawning)
Come on, Willie.
I know you're out there.
(screams)
(laughs)
The sandbox.
(grunts)
Hey, lawn boy!
You missed a spot!
When I'm done with you,
they'll have to do
a compost-mortem.
Ach! Sinky sand!
Ah! Ah! Ah! Oh!
(gurgling)
(sighs)
Willie's gone for good.
Now I can get back
to my normal dreams.
Me and Krusty
winning the Super Bowl.
Bart, there's
two seconds left.
Now, listen up.
It's your basic
Statue of Liberty play
with one twist:
you throw it to me.
Knute Rockne called it
the forward pass.
Now, the clock's still running,
so it's important
we start this play as
quickly as possible.
(screams)
Oh, boy.
Don't dream
about me no more, kid.
Help. Lisa, help!
Bart, you're in trouble!
Wake up!
Wait a minute.
If you're here,
then you've fallen asleep too.
I'm not asleep.
I'm just resting my eye...
Uh-oh.
Good-bye, Bart.
Good-bye, Lise.
Hope you get
reincarnated as someone
who can stay awake
for 15 minutes.
(gasps)
(screams)
You saved us, Maggie.
I don't know, Bart.
Something tells me
Willie's still out there
and that he could come back
any time in any form
and kill us in ways
we can't even imagine.
Boo!
Ohh! Aah! Eeh!
Yu, um... yah!
(blubbering)
Oh!
Stop!
I left my gun on the seat!
Hey!
(panting and gasping)
Wait here, please.
Ah, jeez.
(panting and gasping)
MARGE:
Homer, get ready.
Patty and Selma
will be here any minute.
D'oh. Oh, no.
Better ride this one
out in the closet.
Sorry, Dad.
This is our spot.
Oh, yeah? Well, it's my house,
so it's my spot.
Na-aw. Cause we
called it.
-Did not.
-Well, we're calling it now.
-You are?
-'Fraid so.
They got me with
legal mumbo-jumbo.
-(growling)
-(doorbell rings)
MARGE:
Just a second!
Doo-ooh.
Huh?
I never looked behind this
what-cha-ma-call-it case before.
(laughing)
Huh? That's weird.
It's like something out of that
twilighty show about that zone.
How's it hanging, Marge?
Uck, I'm baking like a meat loaf
under this wet wool.
Uh, may I take
your coat, Aunt Selma?
Um, I would also like
to take your coat.
Have we got a family
activity for you.
A pillowcase full of seashells
from our trip to Sulfur Bay.
You're going to help us
clean and organize them.
And pry out all the
dead hermit crabs.
Get a screwdriver.
(squeals)
I'll take my chances
in the mystery wall.
HOMER'S BRAIN:
Oh, glory of glories.
Oh, heavenly testament
to the eternal majesty
of God's creation.
Holy macaroni!
(hawking)
Hey. You can
just suck them out.
HOMER (reverberating voice):
Hello?
Can anybody hear me?
Homer, where are you?
Uh, I'm somewhere,
where I don't know where I am.
Do you see towels?
If you see towels,
you're probably
in the linen closet again.
Just a second.
No. It's a place
I've never been before.
Ah, the shower.
(laughing)
Hey!
I don't want to alarm you,
Marge,
but I seem to be
trapped in here.
We better call Ned.
He has a ladder.
What's going on here?
I'm so bulgy.
My stomach sticks way out
in front and my...
(screams)
Well, as the tree said
to the lumberjack,
I'm stumped.
It's like he just
disappeared into fat air.
(laughing)
Hey, shut up!
Mmm...
unprocessed fish sticks.
Man,
this place looks expensive.
I feel like I'm wasting
a fortune just standing here.
(humming)
Better make the most of it.
(burps)
Ow!
Watch it, coney!
(grunts)
(whistling sound)
Oops.
Do you see
a light, Homer?
Yes.
Move into the light,
my son.
(sizzling noise)
Ow!
Homer, this is
your physician
Dr. Julius Hibbert.
Can you tell us what
it's like in there?
Um... it's like, uh...
Did anyone see the
movie "Tron"?
-No.
Yes.
I mean, no. No.
Well, where's my Dad?
Well, it
should be obvious
to even the most
dimwitted individual
who holds an advanced degree
in hyperbolic topology
that Homer Simpson
has stumbled into...
the third dimension.
Sorry.
Here is an ordinary square.
Whoa, whoa,
slow down, egghead.
But suppose we
extend the square
beyond the two dimensions
of our universe
along the hypothetical
"z" axis there.
(all gasping)
This forms a three-dimensional
object known as a cube
or a frinkahedron in honor
of its discoverer.
Hoo-hey, hoo-hey.
Help me!
Are you helping me
or are you going on and on?
Oh, right.
And of course, within, we find
the doomed individual.
Enough of your borax,
Poindexter!
A man's life is at stake.
We need action.
Take that
you lousy dimension!
Huh? Huh?
Ah!
Oh, there's so much I don't know
about astrophysics.
I wish I read that book
by that wheelchair guy.
(screaming)
(whimpering)
I'll save Homer.
All I needs is four stout men
to work the bellows.
No, pops. It's too risky.
For all we know,
there could be cubes in there
the size of gorillas
and other large...
Help! I don't have much time!
That does it.
I'm going in.
Bart, no!
Cool, man.
Oh, my God, I'm going
to be sucked into a black hole.
I'm going to be sucked
into oblivion.
I'm going to be nothing.
And what's gonna be
coming out the other side,
I don't know.
I'll save you, Dad.
Oh, I can't get any closer.
You'll have to jump.
Piece of cake, son.
Crap, crap, crap, crap,
crap, crap, crap, crap
crap, crap, crap, crap...
(screaming)
Bart, what happened?
Well, we hit a little snag
when the universe sort
of collapsed on itself
but Dad seemed
cautiously optimistic.
Craaaap!
Homie.
Be strong, Marge.
I'm sure he's gone
to a better place.
(sizzling noise)
(Homer screaming)
D'oh!
Eww, this is
the worst place yet.
Oh.
Oh, my God, look at this.
(whimpering)
Ooh, erotic cakes.
♪♪
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.