I'm scared, Mom.
What if they take me?
Don't worry, Barterfinger.
You're always the last.
Even boxes of stale raisins go
before you, Butterfinger...
I mean, Barterfinger.
No one ever wants the apple.
They must be afraid
there's a razor blade in me.
Yeah. That's the reason.
Maybe you'll be
dipped in caramel.
Oh, whoop-dee-doo.
What the... Where am I going?
You're going to heaven, Dad.
Those pearly gates
look a lot like teeth!
Change is always hard.
Well, I guess that...
Cigarette breath!
Oh, thank God.
We made it through the night.
And now you're on a high shelf,
where they'll forget
about you forever!
Why won't the earth take me?
I hear you, my friend.
Mmm, candy.
Homer, no!
Don't be silly, honey.
Chocolate doesn't feel anything.
No! God, no!
Dad...!
I can't listen to this horror!
Okay, I'm on it.
Thank you.
It's here!
Maggie's first Pazuzu!
Your father
ordered this because...
Why did you order this?
I thought it was pizza.
Yeah, I'll send it back
tomorrow.
Tonight we have
a cocktail party.
And we came early.
And I left my face
on your hand towel.
Don't worry, Maggie.
While Mommy and Daddy
carouse downstairs,
you'll be here
in the dark with Pazuzu!
When Pazuzu's eyes
Are glaring
It's time to go to bed
You'll see
demon shadows fighting
But it's just
inside your head
When Pazuzu's eyes
are staring
The moonlight will turn red
'Cause Pazuzu's
in your nightmares
Until we all
Are dead
Sweet dreams, Maggie.
Don't let the Beelzebubs bite.
Nobody's eating my chowder.
Maybe I can take it
back home with me.
Maggie, sweetie,
you should be in bed.
No one leaves alive.
Oh, her first words!
Did someone get that
on their phone?
She's got red eye.
She's a demon from hell!
Also, generic cola?
Really?
Cocktail fail.
Thank you.
Well, at least
we still got the liquor.
My chowder!
Someone's starting
the terrible twos.
Someone's having an affair
with his nurse.
- Say ah.
- A... dulterer.
179? I...
I'm afraid that little devil
needs an exorcism.
I'm afraid they didn't
teach me those at Pepperdine.
Bible ribbons, that'll hold her.
Oh, good, the police are here.
When is that exorcist
gonna get here?
Marge, we'll be fine.
Maggie just learned
what a circle is.
Okay, whoever she stops
at has to change her diaper,
which appears to contain
flaming lava.
Oh, you just never
want to change a diaper.
I'll handle this.
Sorry about that.
First thing,
we'll see just how powerful
our demon here truly is.
The chicken goes...
Well, there's only
one answer here...
- Cut her loose!
- Are you sure?
If you can't trust
a Catholic priest with a child,
who can you trust?
By the power of Christ,
I say devil be out!
That's all you've got?
Well, I say it three times.
This guy's good.
Devil be out!
I am Pazuzu,
demon of the southwest wind.
Wait, wait, so you're not even
as powerful as the south wind
or the west wind?
How lame is that?
I used to be very important.
Google it.
Devil be out!
Google it!
Your baby is saved.
Fantastic.
She's not going to be
a religious weirdo, is she?
- No.
- Fantastic.
Now hush.
Pazuzu is still among us.
But where?
Bart?
Let me out, let me out!
This boy has the darkest soul
I've ever seen.
It's worse than working
for David Schwimmer!
Yo, Pazuzu, grow me some horns.
Those aren't horns,
those are nubs.
No, no, no!
Well, at least it will
get me out of jury duty.
D'oh!
Lisa, Lisa
wants a better life
Lisa, Lisa,
go under the knife
Homer, Homer
got a button wife
So, anyone want to pick up
litter at the park today?
How about you, Maggie?
She's still got
a touch of Pazuzu.
At least she never threw up.
That's just great.
Everywhere but the sink.
Sometimes I think
I was born in the wrong family.
Hey, Mr. Cat.
What are you playing with?
A secret door?
We don't have smoke alarms,
but we have this?
Smoke is its own alarm.
No, no, Snowball, come back!
It's too dangerous!
Sometimes tiny doors
lead to big opportunities.
- You could talk?
- Indeed.
For centuries, the cat has been
the symbol of intelligence,
the otherworld savoir faire...
Oh, shiny!
Oh, there it is.
Where'd it go?
There it is.
Enough.
Let's go meet your other family.
Other family?
Already the talking cat isn't
the most interesting thing.
Whoa! For a Halloween show
middle segment, this is amazing.
Every girl's dream,
a perfect family.
Good morning, sleepyhead.
For breakfast, tofu or kale?
Oh, that's nice.
But what's with the button eyes?
We don't all have
button eyes, silly.
Some have button mouths.
What's up?!
Lisa, would you like
to jam with us?
You like jazz?
You're all good,
but not better than me.
I wish I could stay forever.
Oh, but you can.
All right. Let me guess.
Do you have to sew buttons
over my eyes?
Don't worry, sugar plum,
we'll give you
a button to bite on
while we sew 'em on.
Hold steady.
Oh, sweetie,
you're just in time.
I killed a snake
with your saxophone and...
Can you blow its head out?
Here, let me just wipe the blood
off the mouthpiece.
Buttons, please.
Hmm, something's missing.
Didn't we have a kid
between Bart and the baby?
Little smarty pants,
plays the flute, I think.
Lisa. She's been gone for days.
And the police
have been no help.
That's not true. I helped you
reassemble that high chair.
Damn it!
Well, we got two kids now,
so no favoritism.
Maggie will get Lisa's room,
Maggie will get Lisa's clothes,
Bart will get Lisa's homework.
Cowabunga!
Bart! How'd you find me?
I had an informant.
I know, he can talk.
He can? I just followed him in.
Oh, God. Now I'll
have to talk to him.
I don't think
he's coming back.
How can you be so calm?
I bore both those children.
Hey, your stories aren't great,
but I wouldn't call them boring.
I'm going in there now.
You really did it
this time, Homer.
You lost your family.
Wait, you can speak
on this side?
Yes, I just don't like to.
Makes the dog feel inferior.
All right.
So tight.
Why did I eat
that second lunch at lunch?
Someone kick me in the ass!
Thank you!
What is it about this world
that's so great?
The Homer in this world
doesn't pass gas.
That was a three-button job.
Would you like to have two eyes?
We can talk to each other
while you watch TV.
Just what Homer needs,
an excuse to get lazier.
Why, you little...
I'll lazy you,
you otherworldly...
- What the...
- That was my Bart!
Boy, sure is hard to see
with buttons on your eyes.
D'oh!
You killed my husband!
Spider wife, dead son,
two girls with button eyes?
I think this marriage has
finally gotten out of its rut.
Yep, I got everything
just the way I want it,
including an extra me to go
to parent-teacher conferences.
Bart drew this picture
of his family.
Now we're getting visits
from a social worker
and an exterminator.
I'll be ready.
And I've learned,
no matter how bad things are,
they can get much, much worse.
Huh, you're telling me.
No one will be seated
during the third act
of this Halloween show.
What you're about to see
is so disgusting
you'll watch Game of Thrones
to calm down.
You have been warned.
Man, am I jealous of you guys.
Two weeks in Lima, Ohio,
with Patty and Selma
while I'm stuck here working.
It's gonna be lonely.
So lonely.
Well, if you really
want us to stay...
We've already kissed good-bye
and the car heard it!
They're gone.
Not a second to waste.
Left alone again
Yes, I'm eating
provolone again
Food just tastes better
in the bathroom now and then
I just love being
left alone again
Left alone for days
I ate two dozen bags
of Frito-Lays
I'm gonna brush my teeth
with mayonnaise
Now my sweat tastes
just like doughnut glaze
Not a single morsel
in the house!
A forgotten hot dog.
Oh, you're shivering.
I'll take care of that.
Happy birthday to meat
I can't wait to eat
Now to slit it down the middle.
I'm not splitting it with you.
I'm just teaching you
how it's done.
Still frozen.
My finger!
My hot dog!
My finger! My poor...
delicious finger.
Wait a minute.
I can't eat my own finger.
It's unholy.
Also, it's not quite done.
But sometimes a man has to do
the unthinkable,
like eat something medium-rare.
Hey, you ate you
You tasted great, you
Hey, you ate you,
hey, you ate you
You cooked and ate you
It makes complete sense.
I eat more and exercise less
than the most succulent pig.
Of course I'm delicious!
But I must never
eat me again. Never!
On the other hand
is my other finger.
And one thing I love
is consistency.
Hey, there, Homer Aloner.
In the absence of the missus,
you want something delicious?
Don't worry, I'll be back.
Oh, disgusting.
Homer Simpson,
you don't like steak anymore?
Actually, I've become
a bit of a me-gan.
Do you have any spaghetti
with my-balls? Meatballs?
Me-gan? My-balls?
Are you eating forbidden fruit?
Fruit?
Sorry, Flanders,
but I've got more delicious meat
in my little finger
than you have
on this whole picnic table.
Speaking of which...
I have really gone
to a lot of trouble
not to leave the house.
Homie, we're home!
What's with the gloves?
I was watching
Breakfast at Tiffany's,
and I thought I could be
more elegant.
Elegant? With your waistline?
I don't think so.
Actually, Homer, you look like
you've lost 20 pounds.
Well, I have been cutting back.
That means something different
to me than you.
What's wrong with your leg?
Nothing. It was perfect.
Homie, you shouldn't be snacking
in the middle of the night.
It can't be good for your...
This is, without question,
the worst moment
of our entire marriage.
- What about...
- This is worse.
Opa!
Marge, I admit it,
this is a rough patch.
But I know when to stop.
And when would that be?
When you're just a mouth?
You see how she is, Doc?
Always negative.
She makes me feel like nothing.
You are almost nothing!
Almost nothing.
Homer, have you considered
your wife's feelings?
Perhaps she takes
this new diet of yours
as a comment on her cooking.
Marge?
I won't deny
that's a part of it.
See? Progress.
Now, excuse me.
I need to go get famous
talking about you.
Homie, I'm afraid this is it.
Your self-destructive behavior
has gone too far.
But, Marge...
Good-bye, my love.
Maybe, deep down,
that's why I ate myself...
because I hate myself.
Sounds like
someone had a breakthrough.
Hi. I'm famous cooker-upper
Mario Batali.
- You mean chef?
- I don't care for that term.
Well, I know I don't belong
in therapy, but why are you?
I got depressed
because I ran out
of exciting new ingredients.
Homer, we need to talk.
Could we wok and talk?
Well, sure.
My dearest family,
I love you so much.
And I think I've found a way
to earn your forgiveness.
Please come home.
Come home to flavor.
He wanted me to pass on
these final words.
I've failed as a man,
but I have succeeded
as an ingredient.
I call the brain!
He's gone.
Well, I guess I can be proud
that he succeeded at something.
Oh, it's a lot more
than something.
Homer's the biggest thing
in food since free refills.
Hey, you ate you
You tasted great, you
Hey, you ate you,
hey, you ate you
You cooked and ate you
How did they get so much meat
out of Homer?
Well, they mixed in some Barney,
Comic Book Guy and horse.
Horse?!
Do you know what it's like
to have everyone
eat of your body?
Yeah, like, every Sunday, pal.
You know,
you don't get more of those.