-♪ Wake up in the morning
feeling like P Diddy ♪
-♪ Hey, what up girl? ♪
♪ Grab my glasses,
I'm out the door ♪
-♪ I'm gonna hit this city ♪
-♪ Let's go ♪
♪ Before I leave,
brush my teeth ♪
♪ With a bottle of Jack ♪
♪ 'Cause when I leave
for the night ♪
♪ I ain't coming back ♪
♪ I'm talking pedicure
on our toes, toes ♪
♪ Trying on all our clothes,
clothes ♪
♪ Boys blowing up
our phones, phones ♪
♪ Drop-topping,
playing our favorite CDs ♪
♪ Pulling up to the parties ♪
♪ Tryin' to get
a little bit tipsy ♪
♪ Don't stop, make it pop ♪
♪ DJ, blow my speakers up ♪
♪ Tonight, I'm-a fight ♪
♪ Till we see the sunlight ♪
♪ Tick-tock, on the clock ♪
♪ But the party don't stop ♪
♪ No, oh, ooh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, ooh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Don't stop, make it pop ♪
♪ DJ, blow my speakers up ♪
♪ Tonight, I'm-a fight ♪
♪ Till we see the sunlight ♪
♪ Tick-tock, on the clock ♪
♪ But the party don't stop ♪
♪ No, oh, ooh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, ooh, oh, oh, oh... ♪
(wind whipping)
-(upbeat instrumental
rock music plays)
-(sighs)
Oh, yeah!
Ooh,yeah!
Duffman is here
to refill your beers!
Okay. Thank you.
Now, for the only thing better
than Duff.
-(overlapping chatter)
-Better than Duff?
Free Duff stuff!
-Oh, yeah!
-Oh!
Now, who wants...
beer cozies?!
A shirt that says "Yo!"
Sassy seat cushions!
And flash drives for your PC
so you can take your data and
back it up!
-Whoa!
-I need some of that.
And now, Duffman
has a dinner date
with his estranged
daughter.
Must not bring up why she
dropped out of college.
It's too sad!
Huh. Huh. Hey.
Ha! Ha!
Guess what company
had a giveaway at
Moe's last night?
No, I won't.
Keep guessing.
What's it say, boy?
Responsibly.
Oh!
Kid, you've
been staring
at these gelatin
desserts for 15 minutes.
Pick one!
It's so hard to decide.
Is the yellow one lemon
or pineapple?
It's your
pet canary.
Now scram!
(groans)
-Hey.
-Haw haw!
You're a spaz!
That's not true.
First of all, Milhouse fell
because you tripped him.
Secondly, spaz is short
for spastic diplegic,
someone who suffers from a
serious medical condition.
Thirdly, your "haw haw,"
through overuse,
has lost its power.
Wow.
I bow before your logic.
(grunts)
(groaning)
Excuse me.
I couldn't help but notice
how logically you argue.
(laughs)
Well, I am one: flattered,
and two: intrigued.
Lisa Simpson.
Ms. Dubinsky.
I'd like to invite you
to join our debate team.
I didn't know
we had a debate team.
Well, it's the one
extracurricular activity
that can't be cut, because
it requires no equipment.
We're low on funding,
so Ralph Wiggum will be
standing in as your lectern.
I'm a furniture!
And that is why
hybrid car buyers
should be given rebates
paid for by taxes
on hamburgers.
(blows horn)
Thank you, Lisa.
Excuse me.
The podiums
are needed
in the art
room as easels.
BOTH:
Yay!
Megan, cross-examination.
What if someone's driving an
old, but functioning, car?
Wouldn't the
carbon required
to create a new hybrid
exceed the savings in gas?
Initially yes, but...
And isn't most electricity
in the United States
ultimately derived
from the burning of coal?
Currently. However,
solar and wind are...
The sun and the breeze-- the
two things you know a lot about.
Right, Blondie?
Blondie?!
Like, totally.
Why don't we get a
bitchin' new perm
with daddy's
credit card?
(laughter)
First of all,
my father no longer has
any functioning credit cards.
Secondly, how dare
you refer to...
-Ooh, you can
count to two.
-Aah.
Do you need some
ice on your head?
-(laughter)
-(gasps)
I... I...
(horn blows)
The winner by a hair--
a brown hair-- Megan!
Ooh!
Sir, that hollow mountain
in Nevada
that was supposed
to hold a million years
of nuclear waste is full.
Did they jump on the pile
to smoosh it down?
It went down in one place
and up in another.
We need somewhere else
to dispose of this plutonium.
Eh, just find the biggest idiot
on our payroll
and slip it in his bag.
(humming)
BURNS:
Ooh!
That's a bingo.
Mmm. Good mac
and cheese.
I've had better.
Down at the
train station.
I'll have to check it out
sometime.
Mmm!
The best mac and
cheese I've ever had
is at a bowling
alley in Ogdenville.
Mm, I am pretty full.
Bread crumbs on the top.
I'm on my way!
That bag--
surely it's attended.
Unattended bag!
(screaming)
All panic!
(screaming and shouting)
So, what do you think?
I think we're
gonna blow it up
and let the bleeding heart
liberals ask questions later.
Well, now, why can't it be
blown up by a woman of color?
Five, four.
No time for a full countdown.
Ooh, it's dinner time!
(grunts, sighs)
(humming)
This just in.
The suspicious bag detonated at
Springfield Union Station today
contained deadly plutonium,
which can only mean one thing--
a terrorist plot.
Enough radioactivity
was released
to create 17 Hulks
and a Spider-Man.
Here's an artist's conception.
Quite disturbing.
(excited, overlapping chatter)
(gavel bangs)
I admit it.
Everything I've said
about terrorism till now
was fear-mongering.
But today,
I monger the truth.
To protect our city
from all future bombings,
dirty, clean, dive or carpet,
we have hired
an outside consultant
from London,
England.
Does he have
a cute accent?
(with English accent):
Why don't you be the judge,
young lady?
Ooh, he sounds just
like Paddington Bear!
My name is Nigel Bakerbutcher.
(whirring)
Sleepy London town.
Once upon a time,
the only problem we had here
was from overzealous
Cockney flower sellers.
Flowers, guv'nor?
A pretty for
your buttonhole?
'Ello, 'ello, 'ello.
(men muttering)
But in London
of the 21st Century,
the watchword is vigilance.
London is now ringed
by the most comprehensive array
of surveillance cameras
mankind has ever seen.
(murmuring)
Excuse me.
Is this what the framers
of the Constitution would want?
Well, I'm Wally of
Wally's Framers,
and this is exactly
what I want.
How many personal freedoms
are we willing to give up
in the name of security?
(chuckles)
That blonde girl thinks
she's smart, like us dark hairs.
Again with the blonde!
Why in the world
would the color of the hair
on someone's head
have anything to do
with the intelligence within?
Yeah, you're
so right.
I'm smart, too.
I got Joe to promise to leave
his wife when I turn 50.
Eh, uh, yes.
Now, all in favor
of these cameras say cheese.
ALL (except Lisa):
Cheese!
Those opposed say,
"I hate America."
I ha...
Oh, wait.
Oh.
Motion carries.
Next up: motion to limit
terms of city officials.
All in favor say,
"I have sex with animals."
I do have sex with animals,
but I am not in favor
of term limits.
Mm-hmm.
Lisa, I know kids
have been making fun
of your blonde hair,
so I got you this book
from the Being Different
section of the bookstore.
Hmm?
"Sally Circle was eating donuts
and Ovaltine
when her father came in
with terrible news."
We're moving to
Rectangu-Land!
Round up the family
and let's roll!
-(mocking laughter)
-LISA:
"Everyone was mean to Sally.
She was too well-rounded.
She felt cornered.
They wouldn't let her play
four-square
or invite her
to the box social.
The end."
That's a rather
unambitious book.
I want a camera on
every light pole.
I want two hidden cameras
there, open camera there.
Hidden. Hidden.
(echoing):
Hidden.
Cluster! Right there! Yes!
Um, you ain't gonna
like what you see.
KRUSTY:
Did you hear about the blonde
who couldn't make ice?
-She lost the recipe.
-(laughter)
You know why it takes longer
to build a blonde snowman?
You have to hollow out the head.
(laughter)
(Bart laughs)
He sure nailed you, Lis.
You're blond, too.
Blonde guys aren't dumb.
They're evil.
Like in The Karate Kid
and World War II.
All right, boys.
Let's see the dark
underbelly of our fair burg.
Okay, we got a litterbug
on F-6, double homicide
in progress on Q-20...
A woman sunbathing topless
on R-15!
Uh, Chief, I think
we got a misuse
of police equipment on ZZ-99.
Killjoy.
Gas station customer
washing windshield
without buying gas.
Girl using Wite-Out
as nail polish.
Oh, man, this is hard.
Hey, did you get that guy
who was parading around naked?
He was just jogging
in a tan sweat suit, Chief.
Are you sure?
I thought I saw his...
That was a fanny pack,
worn on the front.
-But there was a...
-Water bottle...
-But it was...
-Leaking.
That's it! That's it!
I can't take another minute
of these stupid screens!
Go-Go find
some concerned citizens
to pick up the slack.
Well, how many should I get?
Uh, well, we've got, uh,
eight chairs, so...
Oh, no, wait.
Put one chair in my office
facing my desk,
so-so I'll seem
like a meetings guy.
Yeah. Oh, uh...
Oh, have a seat.
Uh, I'll be with you
in one minute. Yeah.
Ah, that's a new low.
We have chosen you
to help out,
because you are all
that rare combination.
Prying, but not pervy.
(polite laughter)
Now just follow a little formula
called P.B. and J.:
Peer at the monitor,
Be judgmental, and Jot it down.
One way to remember
that is A.B.C.:
Always Be Considering
P.B. and J.
But the single most important
rule is the four A's:
Always Act According to A.B.C.
Uh-oh.
What is it, Ned?
I've got two teens
in a public park
goin' at it like
a couple of gibbons
in the back seat of Noah's Ark!
Should we inform
the Chief?
Hmm, maybe.
But I feel a little like
I'm the Tom Voyeur
to these Huckleberry
Sinners.
Or you could correct
the behavior yourself
with our Nag-a-sonic speakers.
Oi! Snogging people!
What the hell was that?!
Tongues where I can see them,
please.
I ain't lettin' you touch me
with somebody watchin'.
Come on, baby, it's
just a voice.
Don't push it, Kearney.
-I'm Jimbo!
-Oh, great.
Make me look easy
in front of the voice.
But you are easy!
Don't be ashamed
of what you are!
Shauna...
I've gone from lookie-loo
to talkie-too.
Excuse me,
that's your salad fork.
That Wi-Fi's
for hotel guests only.
What's the matter, sir, too cool
to sing "Happy Birthday?"
Isn't this great, Marge?
We're like Jiminy Cricket
for the whole ding-dang town.
A half-man, half-bug that knows
what's best for everybody.
Mm-hmm.
I don't know.
I'm starting to think
we're prying too much
into people's lives.
And this room isn't really
the best place
for Maggie to hang out.
That's not Sesame Street,
that's a gay bar.
(dance music playing)
(grunts)
Although I guess
this would teach her
sharing and caring,
but... we're going home.
(sinister laugh)
Dye! Dye! Dye!
(maniacally laughing)
Tomorrow's forecast is...
Okay, place your bets.
-Partly cloudy.
-Partly sunny.
Golf ball-sized hail!
A chance of severe thunderstorms
with golf ball-sized hail!
Whoo-hoo!
(Flanders clears throat)
I spy, with my electronic eye,
illegal wagering!
Hey, weren't these
cameras installed
to keep America's enemies
from blowin' up our homeland?
Well, sir, how many times
have you been blown up
since the cameras went in?
Zero times.
Mm-hmm!
Now I'm gonna go (clicks tongue)
till you give the money back.
(clicking tongue)
Mm-mm, mm-mm, mm-mm!
(grunting)
Cut it out...
Cut it out!
(mumbling)
(clicking tongue):
Mm-mm, mm-mm, mm-mm!
All right!
I'm goin' home.
It's not safe in here.
(thunder crashes)
(grunting)
FLANDERS:
Don't use that dog as a ramp.
Less radical...
Less radical!
(camera whirring)
Stop gleaming that cube!
(grunting)
So, you like to watch, huh?
Well, take a look at this!
Huh?
Hmm.
FLANDERS:
Buttocks!
Tushie!
(groans)
Ugh!
-(Flanders sighs)
-Whoa, a blind spot!
FLANDERS:
Boy cheeks!
Fanny!
Derriere!
Hiney!
Backside!
Cover up that coin slot!
Hey, boy, whatcha doing?
Experimenting
with my butt.
(chuckles)
My little Einstein.
Welcome to Chaos Corners,
the Pleasure Patch,
Satan's Triangle--
the one place in town no
cameras can see you,
and no laws can
touch you.
Oh, yeah, that stopped
the kicking.
Inspiration Point looks
pretty uninspired.
All's quiet in Murder Town.
Yep, Springfield is cleaner
than the Lord's hand towels.
Sour ball, take me away!
Mm-mm-mmm.
Mmm! Mm-mmm... mmm.
(cheering, laughter)
(engines revving)
(tires screeching)
Another tie.
Followed by three hours
of parachute repacking.
(gasps)
Koo-koo-roo!
A phony bird call?!
That means Marge is coming!
Everyone, act legal!
(jaunty, old-fashioned
melody playing)
(humming)
Homer, Maggie has to wear
that clown mask for Halloween.
What's going on?
Well, uh...
the one place the cameras
can't see is right here
in our backyard,
so I'm charging people to
do whatever they want.
Isn't that wonderful?
I don't see what's so wonderful.
Remember how you wanted me to
get that expensive operation?
Well, now I can
afford a motorcycle!
Ever hear of the expression
"Not in my backyard"?
Well... that!
Nothin'.
Nothin'. Somethin'.
I don't want to get Homer
in trouble,
but it's just plain wrong
to use that blind spot
to turn our backyard into
a Mecca of misdemeanors!
(gasps) Blind spot?!
Mecca?!
Rod, hold up Daddy's shaving
mirror out the window, would ya?
(overlapping chatter)
I see you now.
Rod, you and Todd
stay in the house.
Todd's not in the house.
(gerbils squealing)
No!
And that's why school uniforms
should not be mandatory.
Lisa, rebuttal?
(all gasp)
Dressing in uniforms
is a good thing.
If everyone looks the same,
it levels the playing field.
Hmm, very smart.
-That's well-reasoned.
-A true brunette.
It's better to just fit in
with the crowd.
-She's as bright as
her hair is dark!
-So smart!
Great point!
Oh, I can't go on!
This rebuttal is a sham!
(all gasp)
You aren't being persuaded
by the content of my argument.
You're being convinced
by the color of my hair!
-Well, that-- that's absurd!
-Ridiculous!
Although her brown hair makes
a persuasive case.
Well guess what?
I am not a brunette!
I'm a blonde!
(screams)
Roots!
(sighs)
We must rid ourselves
of these outdated clichés.
Not all blondes are dumb!
Not all fat people are jolly.
Would you be jolly
if you thought Comic-Con
was moving to Anaheim?
And not all old people
are bad drivers.
This building
cut me off!
(horn honking)
(gunshot)
(crackling, whistling)
Who wants feet steak?
ALL:
Me! Me!
Over here!
De-meat those feet!
Oh, no! I don't have
to listen to you.
If I'm not on camera,
you can't see me!
I'm standin' right here!
Everyone in this town
is sick and tired
of you looking over
their shoulder.
"Don't leave your sprinklers
on in the rain!
Don't burn that pile of
ventriloquist dummies!"
Oh, but you promised!
Later. Later.
But, neighbor, why did you
have to do this?
I've tattled this town
into a paradise!
This used to be just
a little part of me.
You see, Ned, your
citywide nagging
compressed all of our
town's misbehavior
into one small place.
Creating a glittering diamond
of super evil.
(sighs)
I guess I did create this.
Like God created the devil.
God created the devil?
Finally, He did something cool.
(sighs)
Oh, I never wanted to turn
into Big Brother.
I just wanted
to be little sister,
tattlin' on everyone so the town
would be a nicer place.
Well, if you ask me,
you were trying to play God.
(gasps)
That's the worst sin of all,
for some reason.
What can I do
to make things right?
You can help me take
out those cameras.
Neighbor, we got
some work to do.
(grunting)
Yes!
(glass shattering)
(gunfire)
So, sadly, the most popular
reality show in England
is no more.
I'll miss that Ralph Wiggum.
Reminds me of my boy.
Oh, Mummy, my cat's breath
smells like cat food.
♪ Y'all ready for this... ♪
(people talking)
Shh!
Enhanced by Fotokem