CHORUS [SINGS]:
The Simpsons
The Strong Arms of the Ma
[BELL RINGING]
[WHISTLE BLOWING]
[BEEPING]
[LISA PLAYS SOLO]
D'oh! Ah!
Hello, I'm Kent Brockman,
and this is Eye on Springfield.
[UPBEAT ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm here
with actor Rainier Wolfcastle...
...who surprisingly
has filed for bankruptcy.
Rainier, what went wrong?
Three divorces in three months.
What can I say, Kent? I'm a romantic.
But this personal tragedy...
...translates into a good
old-fashioned bankruptcy sale.
Yeah. Everything must go.
Even the painting of my nana.
This was done on her wedding day.
Or should I say "deading" day?
How the mighty have fallen...
...into my price range.
I wanna go there.
- Dad, we are there.
- Woo-hoo!
Oh, Rainier, I really don't think it's right
to sell these Playdude centerfolds.
[CHUCKLES]
Zip it, Holy Joe.
- Are you taking us to another mansion?
- Uh, yeah.
Uh, Miss September...
- ...you're gonna have to get in the trunk.
WOMAN: Oh.
Whoa, a sword cane.
Everything here is sword.
Sword baseball bat, sword rifle,
sword pineapple...
...sword sword sharpener, sword pie.
It's...
Hey, what happened to the sword pie?
What do I do now?
Hey, look, a cyborg hand.
This could really come in useful.
Well, well,
look who's gone Hollywood.
Oh! Eh, mm, eh.
Do you need some assistance...
...picking over the tattered remains
of my life?
Nope, I'm good.
Hey, your early porno movies.
Oh, wait, are any of these hetero?
What's there is there.
You got any junk that will go up in value
after you die?
Right this way.
My first weight set.
[GASPS]
The weights that changed you
from a Bavarian cream puff...
...to a mass of twitching muscles?
[CHUCKLES]
They know
you are talking about them.
I'll take it.
Who's up for coconut oil?
There's no way this junk
is gonna fit in that car.
Don't worry.
This is what all those hours
of playing Tetris were for.
[TETRIS THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
No.
- Huh. Perfect.
- But there's no room for you.
D'oh!
- Do you think you could give me a lift?
- Sure. I'll carry you in this giant Snugli.
I used it to carry Rob Schneider
in the movie My Baby is an Ugly Man.
Hmm? Ooh!
[GRUNTS]
[HOMER SIGHS]
Your heartbeat is so soothing.
Shh. Time for sleep, little fatso.
Oh!
Ew! Mom,
I think Maggie fudged her Huggies.
Bart, don't say it like that.
You'll hurt her feelings.
[SNIFFS]
Jeez, Louise.
How did you turn cinnamon applesauce
into that?
Don't try to pin this on me, sister.
MARGE:
Sorry, emergency.
[GRUNTS]
Hello, Mrs. Homer.
Apu, where's your bathroom?
The bathroom is not for customers.
Please use the crack house.
[SNIFFS]
Aah! That is the most pungent thing
I've ever smelled and I am from India.
All right, all right,
but speak of this to no one.
Don't worry. That sign is just a ruse,
like all high voltage signs.
[MARGE GROANS]
There's a happy baby. Aren't you?
[GIGGLES]
Aren't you?
MAN:
Give me your purse.
- Oh, God, oh, God, oh, God.
- Shut up.
[GASPS]
- It's not a purse. It's a diaper bag.
- What?
It looks like a purse,
that's why I bought it.
- But it's really a...
- Shut up!
[GASPS]
Fine. I'll just take this.
[MAN GRUNTS]
[MARGE GASPS]
Come on, Mom, let's go.
Mom, are you okay?
[CRYING]
It's all my fault my wife got mugged.
There you have it, boys. Case closed.
Look,
this really made me feel vulnerable.
I wanna know how soon you think
you'll catch this guy.
Don't worry, Marge, I swear to you
I'll put my best man on it.
LOU & EDDIE:
Hmm?
Oh, boy, is this awkward.
Wait, Marge. I don't want you
to leave the house without this.
Emergency whistle, pepper spray...
...and this map of the most vulnerable
parts of a man's body.
Why is it Ned Flanders?
Oh, like, I'm gonna kick Chief Wiggum
in the groin.
Okay, Marge, you can do this.
You've done it
a thousand times before.
- Hi, Mrs. Simpson.
- Aah!
[COUGHING]
Oh, no. I pepper-sprayed Ralph.
[WHIMPERING]
Even my boogers are spicy.
Sorry.
Let's go home.
There's nothing dangerous there
except for the electrical wiring.
[TIRES SQUEALING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Mom, you didn't get the milk.
And you parked
on top of the mailman.
It's okay. All part of the job.
Can you believe
I get paid to wear short pants?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'll come right out and help you.
[GRUNTS]
I gave your necklace
to my cheap girlfriend.
I just throw it in a drawer at night.
[CACKLES]
No, it'll tangle!
[GRUNTS]
Sorry, I can't go outside.
I'll call for help.
No hurry, I got plenty to read.
Ooh, Twilight Zone Magazine. It...
[WHIMPERING]
Oh, no, my glasses are broken.
[TWILIGHTZONE
THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
Marge, I'm afraid
you've developed agoraphobia:
A fear of leaving the home.
I recommend
watching this Lifetime Channel movie.
It's called
The Woman Who Died in Her Home.
[LAUGHS]
Oh, my God.
Isn't there anything I can do?
Marge, I suggest you slowly desensitize
yourself to the fear of going outside.
Create controlled situations where you
can leave without pain or panic.
What if I can't feel comfortable
outside again?
- I hope you like throwing dinner parties.
- I do.
No one wants to eat dinner
at a crazy lady's house. Get real.
Don't worry, Mom. This first time
we'll only take a few steps outside.
[SIGHS]
All right, just to the mailbox and back.
Now, Dr. Hibbert said
to use a number from one to 10...
...to describe how anxious you are.
Two, three, two...
Don't worry. Everything is fine.
[BEES BUZZING]
- What the hell is that?
- Eight.
- Dad, it's just a bug.
- Two...
Not just a bug.
It's the queen of something.
Ten, 10, 10.
Don't worry. I'll set fire to the hive.
Twelve. Fifteen.
Seven hundred and three.
Run!
Oh, my goodness.
It looks just like the Kwik-E-Mart.
Yup, but you're still safe at home.
After a few practice trips here...
...the real Kwik-E-Mart
will be a piece of cake.
- Now, Bart will play Apu.
- Mm-hm.
I'm a magazine rack.
Look, I'm the first to admit it.
I don't write good parts for women.
I'm a robber.
[GRUNTS]
- Aah! Help!
- All this does is shoot bubbles.
[SCREAMS]
Silly String!
Kids, I'll find your mother. Dad,
we're canceling the rest of the play.
What play?
What the hell is he talking about?
- Marge?
- I'm gonna sleep down here tonight.
Listen, kids. Your mom
is going to be living in the basement.
But with our love,
she'll get better soon.
- [AS APU] What if she doesn't?
- We'll have to smoke her out.
And may the peace of God be with you.
Amen.
MARGE [OVER RADIO]:
Amen. Over.
Breaker, Bartman to shut-in.
The big guy's asleep.
Please advise. Over.
MARGE:
Whack him with the hymnal. Over.
- I roger that big time.
- D'oh!
HOMER [OVER RADIO]: Why, you little...
Oh, ha, ha, hi, Jesus. I was just...
[HOMER CHOMPING]
Wow, honey,
eating dinner downstairs is great.
Isn't it, kids?
The air hockey table
makes passing the carrots a breeze.
Bart, eat your spinach, unh.
No way, unh.
Yes way.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[CHUCKLES]
Stop it, please. I'm trying to eat.
And all those feet going by the window
are really creeping me out.
It's like we're at Cheers.
I loved that show
because you always knew...
...it was only a half-hour till Wings.
Then you could just sleep till Monday.
[IN UNISON]
Bye, Mom.
MARGE: I'm sending the cat up
with your lunches.
[MEOWING]
Goodbye, kids.
[SIGHS]
What to do now?
Too crazy to go outside.
Not crazy enough
to have imaginary friends.
Why did Homer buy those?
No one's ever gonna use them.
Hmm.
[GRUNTING]
MAN [ON TV]:
Three, four and five eggs.
Ladies, feel that burn.
If you don't, the oven's not on.
Ten, 11, 12.
[SIGHS]
I can bench twice as much
as when I started.
And look at my abs.
BOTH:
Mom.
[BARKING]
I'm married to Joey Heatherton.
Ooh, you know what would zest up
this hollandaise? A lemon.
- Dad, do you plan to get in shape?
- No.
- Actually, I'm gonna eat twice as much.
- Excellent.
Uh, guys, Mom just left the basement.
[GASPS]
She's in the backyard.
I got all the way out to the tree
before I realized I'd left the house.
[GRUNTS]
[GASPS]
I'm stronger than I've ever been.
I don't have to go back inside.
I'm not afraid.
- All right, Mom.
- Yay, Mom.
- Woo-hoo!
I'm not afraid.
Ned, I'm not afraid.
Well,
aren't you a super-duper recouper?
MARGE:
Grampa, I'm not afraid.
Then you're not paying
close enough attention.
[GASPS]
- You?
- What you been up to? Living in fear?
Not anymore.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
You've just been Marge-inalized.
[CROWD CHEERING]
Marge, that was amazing.
[POLICE SIREN WAILS]
It's like I'm married to Shaft.
Chief, I think that's the guy
who mugged her.
Yeah. She caught her own criminal
unlike the rest of you lazy bones.
You're not gonna find those criminals
looking at your feet, people.
[ROCKY THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[ALL GRUNTING]
Marge Simpson? It's Ruth.
Ruth Powers.
Ruth Powers? My old neighbor?
Oh, my goodness. Look at you.
I got this body in prison.
I was Miss Mexican Mafia
three years in a row.
Wow.
You know, another 4 inches
on your neck and you'd look pretty hot.
Ever thought of competing?
I don't have those kind of muscles.
Well, you could if you use these.
MARGE:
Steroids?
I can't take drugs.
I have many anti-drug bumper stickers
I'd be making a liar out of my tailgate.
Steroids aren't drugs.
They occur naturally in the body...
...like sweat or tumors.
But aren't there side effects?
Yes.
Their main side effect is greatness.
But if you'd rather be weak
and helpless...
No, no.
I feel good with no repercussions.
[MARGE HUMMING]
MARGE:
A little of this, a little of that.
Bulkanoids for my lats,
Miso-Max for my delts...
...and estrogen blockers
for that minty taste.
Whoa!
[SCHOOL BUS HORN HONKS]
Hurry up, kids, you'll miss the bus.
BART & LISA:
Wait, Otto, come back!
[GRUNTS]
Not so fast, bus boy.
Man, what am I smoking?
Oh, yeah, pot.
BOTH:
Thanks, Mom.
[TIRES SQUEALING]
Bye, kids.
Bye-bye.
Ha, ha, your mom changed.
Hey, hot stuff.
I've got a competition tomorrow.
- I could use a good luck snuggle.
- I'd rather talk about our feelings.
I feel that illegal
performance-enhancing drugs...
...are too common these days.
Rebuttal?
[BOTH GRUNT]
Let's do it.
Uh, listen, my bulky flower...
- ...I have an early day tomorrow...
- I wasn't asking.
[WHIMPERING]
Kids, I made your lunches.
They're on the table.
Huh?
Why didn't mom make our lunch?
Your mom has a lot of stuff to shave.
Ow. Ow. Ow. Ow.
ANNOUNCER: Now, let's meet the ladies
who our doctors assure us are women.
The iron maidens.
Ay caramba. I'm off women forever.
[GRUNTS]
Support the arts.
MAN 1:
Yeah, that's rad, that's rad, yeah.
This is the cheapest vacation
you've ever taken me on.
[SINGING]
The man who shot Liberty Valance
He shot Liberty Valance
He was the bravest of them all
Nice lady.
In second place, Marge Simpson.
MAN 2:
All right. Yeah. Yeah!
[AUDIENCE APPLAUDING]
Second place?
Oh, man, this will just encourage her.
I'm tired
of her criticizing my saggy glutes.
Quiet. Her muscular ears can hear us.
[GROANS]
So then I popped my delts, clench
and bam! Not a dry eye in the house.
I'm so proud of you, honey.
You bulked up
but managed to keep your femininity.
And that's why I didn't win.
Sorry, sir. Sorry.
Starting tomorrow,
I'm gonna up my glyco load...
- ...use a denser ripping gel...
- Denser?
Damn straight. I didn't sacrifice
my period for second place.
[CHUCKLES]
I hear that.
Uh, listen, Marge...
Um, how can I put this delicately?
I don't got enough booze in this place
to make you look good.
[GROANS]
- Maybe death will stop your yammering.
- Marge, easy.
Ah! Oh!
[CROWD GROANS]
LENNY:
Everyone pile on Homer's wife.
[ALL GRUNTING]
["LOVE IS A BATTLEFIELD"
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
Huh? Huh? Huh?
[ALL GRUNTING]
["AT LAST" PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS]
["RELAX" PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
[MUSIC STOPS]
DISCO STU: Disco Stu
should have disco ducked. Ow.
[WHISTLES]
[ALL GRUNTING]
[ALL GROANING]
[POLICE SIREN WAILING]
Marge.
Somewhere in that sea of bull hormones
is the sweet, wonderful girl I married.
The woman
who instead of swatting a fly...
...will give it a bath
and send it on its way.
I'd sure like to go home
and have Jiffy Pop with her.
Oh, my gosh. You're right.
Steroids have turned me
into everything I hate.
Let's go home, sweetie.
Club soda will get that blood out.
[MAN GROANS]
Well, there's only one way
to recoup my losses.
Whoa, Moe, wait a minute.
Don't you have to buy insurance first?
Oh, crap.
[GASPS]
[GRUNTS]
You know,
I really do miss being a lady.
And I miss being your knight
in flabby armor.
Oh, Homie.
[CHUCKLES]
HOMER:
Ready for a real workout, Marge?
MARGE:
Mm-hm.
HOMER:
Good. Can you wax the car?
Ow. Ow. Ow. I'm kidding. I'm kidding.
WOMAN:
Shh.
[English - US -SDH]