CHOIR: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(theme music playing)
D'oh!
-(tires screech)
-(grunts)
(belches)
(tennis ball thudding)
ANNOUNCER (on TV): It's been
a brilliant day of women's tennis,
with Petrevkova
narrowly edging Mashakova.
We take you now to doubles action
between Pavlyuchenkeka-Vilnikova
and Strakova-Mishtnupetrateva.
(laughs)
To me, it's legs versus boobs.
What the-- Change the channel?
But I'm watching soft-core tennis.
-BOTH: Ki-Ya Karate Monsters!
-What the hell is that?
-It's our favorite show.
-Mom said we could watch it.
Did she really say that?
Are you gonna walk upstairs
and ask her?
(thunder rumbles)
-No.
-(theme song playing on TV)
NARRATOR (on TV):
From a Shaolin monastery
in darkest Transylvania
come helpful hell-spawn.
With homicidal honor,
they rampage for peace.
Ki-Ya!
BOTH: Ki-Ya!
You like this now?
What about Planet Jackson
and the Earth Brigade?
Dad, we don't watch that show anymore.
It's for babies.
TOY: Planet power!
(Bart and Lisa grunting)
-Kung Fu Werewolf chop!
-Blob Jitsu kick!
Stop it. No Karate Monsters
at the dinner table.
It's Ki-Ya Karate Monsters.
Samurai shampoo blast!
Ninja throwing soap!
No Karate Monsters in the bathtub.
Ki-Ya Karate Monsters.
-HOMER: Happy birthday, Dad.
-BART: Happy birthday.
LISA: Happy birthday, Grampa.
(Grampa gasps)
Did this really happen?
-Pill attack!
-Actual-sword attack!
I've had it.
No more Karate Monsters.
-Ki-Ya--
-(grumbles)
That's it. Tomorrow,
we're doing something educational.
We're going to the science museum.
Damn it.
(Bart and Lisa laughing)
(both grunting)
(Marge sighs)
Finally, actual science.
(both groan)
You did it, baby.
You promised no fun,
and you delivered.
(French accent)
Ah, hello there.
I am Blaise Pascal,
inventor of the probability theory.
What are the odds
of meeting you here?
Excellent, I would say.
(dings)
My friend Silly Squirrel
is about to buy a lottery ticket.
Silly Squirrel,
do you know the probability
of winning the lottery?
I don't know.
Why, you are more likely
to be run over by a car.
Or be hit by lightning.
Or murdered by an acquaintance.
If you understood probability,
you would never play the lottery.
(laughs)
Guys, this science exhibit
told me how stupid it is
to play the lottery.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
So you didn't buy our weekly ticket?
Are you nuts?
You can't win if you don't play.
Hey, it's time.
Turn it on, turn it on!
Four lucky numbers
for four best friends.
Yeah, I always go with three,
the number of brothers and sisters
I, uh, Hunger Games-ed in the womb.
19 for me.
Uh, for the best year of my life, 1996.
My number's 22.
No reason. Just... 22.
And I'm 69.
Because people always laugh
when you say "69."
(laughs)
No one knows why.
And the winning numbers are...
three, 19,
22 and 69. (chuckles)
Oh, my gosh. We won.
We won the Springfield Lottery.
That's 200 grand.
That's 50,000 bucks each!
(all cheering)
Guys, guys, we got to celebrate,
throw a raging party!
I'll cash the ticket.
Homer, Homer, you get the food.
I'll get mini dumpsters of wings
from Garbage Wings.
And, Lenny, you get the drinks.
But we're already at a bar.
Oh, no. That's just gasoline
and hot dog water.
Who cares?
We got the money.
(laughing)
I'm so happy.
To the best feeling in the world...
money.
(glass clinking)
Guys, I got big plans
for these winnings.
I'm going to build...
a swimming pool.
In-ground?
So freaking far in the ground, baby.
What about you, Carl?
What are you gonna do
with your share of the money?
(crowd murmuring)
Oh, uh, I guess Carl ain't back yet
from cashing in the ticket.
I'm sure he just got held up in traffic.
Yeah, that's probably what happened.
I wonder what's keeping Carl.
I hope our friend wasn't in an accident.
I'm glad we're the kind of people
who are worried about Carl's safety
instead of thinking
that he ripped us off.
I wasn't thinking that.
-Carl's our good friend.
-Our good friend.
Yeah, good old Carl.
Good old Carl's phone
went straight to voice mail. Again.
(tires screeching)
The power of friendship is so amazing,
I don't feel at all suspicious of Carl.
Drive faster because
of the power of friendship.
(tires screech)
(door creaks)
-Carl's gone.
-Our money's gone.
We've been betrayed.
By good old Carl!
Guys, I think we might need a new song.
♪ Four best friends ♪
♪ Who never quarrel ♪
♪ Homer Simpson, Lenny, Moe, and... ♪
♪ And... ♪
And no one.
All our lottery money, gone!
If I ever see that Carl again,
I'm gonna freeze him,
chop him up into ice cubes,
and scoop him into the urinal trough
at the Gathering of the Juggalos!
Guys, give Carl a chance.
I'm sure he's gonna come back.
I don't think so.
His travel neck pillow's gone
from its pedestal.
-Fellas, he ain't coming back.
-You don't know that.
I'm gonna keep looking
till we figure out what really happened.
I bet he flew to Quebec to bring us back
authentic French-Canadian sugar pie.
(chuckles)
I can taste it already.
Mmm.
Thanks for the sugar pie, Carl.
Hey, what's this?
"I've gone home.
Good-bye forever, Carl Carlson."
Where'd you go, Carl?
Had plans for that money, too.
I was gonna be one of those guys
who's really into hot sauce, you know?
Hot sauce suspenders,
hot sauce pajamas.
Bolo tie with a little
chili pepper on it.
I still can't believe it was Carl
who took your winnings.
I thought it would've been you.
Or you. Or you.
I know. Me, too.
It's the ultimate screw-over.
Maybe he had a good reason
to give you the ultimate screw-over.
He said he went home,
and his passport is gone.
What country is he from?
-Uh...
-Uh... I don't know.
You don't know where Carl is from?
Come on, you know how dudes are.
We don't go digging into the past.
We talk about guy stuff.
Like baseball and trucks
and when guys lift too much weight
and their bungus drops out.
You know, guy stuff.
Maybe if you'd talked less
about guy stuff,
you'd know more about
your so-called friend.
Well, it don't matter no more, Midge.
Carl is gone, and we're already
auditioning replacements.
This could not be more offensive.
Man!
Oh, of course.
-Ugh!
-Hmm.
Hey, hey, get that out of here!
I don't ever want to see that
moolah-stealing jackpot thief again!
Wait a minute.
Something's reflected in the lenses
of Carl's sunglasses.
I just need to get closer.
He's looking at a geyser.
And there's a sign in front of it!
Oh... it's too small to read.
LENNY: Oh, it's backwards.
MOE: Try this.
LENNY: "Strokkur Geysir."
Hmm.
The geyser is one of the most famous
natural wonders in Iceland.
I guess that's where Carl's from.
Ice-land?
Is that even a real place?
I thought it was
Superman's Superman cave.
Iceland keeps the most detailed
family records
of any country in the world.
There! Carl was adopted...
...by a couple who lives
outside Reykjavik.
Well, if that's Carl's home,
then that's where our money is!
And that's where we're going.
We got to pack.
HOMER: (whistles)
50 bucks per bag?
I guess I'm only bringing
one guitar on this revenge trip.
You're going so far away.
I'll miss you.
Baby, I'm going for us.
That money is going to
dig us a swimming pool
that'll take our broken family
and make it whole.
We're not broken.
-We're broken.
-We're pretty broken.
(grumbles)
How am I going to sleep
if someone isn't pushing me
all the way to the very edge of the bed?
I've already taken care of that.
Oh... oh, that's perfect.
I can't wait to see the smile
on Carl's face when we surprise him.
I call first hug.
Hey, Lenny,
when are you gonna wise up?
Carl never wants to see us again.
I'm done talking to you!
This is funny.
It says here Iceland is green,
and Greenland is icy.
The Vikings switched the names
to trick everybody.
-(all laughing)
-Those Vikings.
-That's pretty good.
-Great gag!
Hey, Vikings,
it's still pretty damn cold!
I only packed shorts.
Excuse me, uh,
we're looking for our friend.
He's, uh... he's about so tall,
uh, wears a jacket,
he's, um, got no visible tattoos...
-Just say he's black, Moe.
-You say he's black!
His name is Carl Carlson.
Carl Carlson!
His family has been hated
for 1,000 years.
How do you know about Carl's family?
Our country is very small,
very judgmental, and very nosy.
Ingimar Ogmundsson,
how progresses your gonorrhea?
It heals, but slowly.
Why does everybody hate Carl's family?
MAN: Here's why.
This saga tells of how
Carl Carlson's family
were the watchmen of the coast,
always keeping an eye out
for invading hordes.
Iceland's safety depended
on their vigilance.
But the Carlsons failed in their duty.
The enemy invaded,
laying waste to our lava fields,
burning our sweaters,
and feasting upon our tiny horses.
Apparently, screwing over your friends
is in Carl's blood-- his adopted blood.
All right, this is it,
Carl's family home.
Twenty-two...
Ooh, phew, oh, that's a lot of letters.
22 Hjorleifsstrati.
So that's why 22
was Carl's lottery number.
Yeah, and that's why his sweatpants
say "Hjorleifsstrati" across the butt.
(grunts)
The gates are locked.
Well, then we'll just have to wait
for him to come out.
(yawns)
Oh, man, stakeouts are so boring.
I wish I had something to look at.
Well, I guess I'll just read
the car rental contract again.
Damage waiver, check.
Return with full tank of gas, check.
All drivers must be over the age of 25...
and check.
Love you, Mom. See you, Dad.
-It's Carl! Wake up, wake up!
-BOTH: Huh?
♪♪
(tires screech)
Ah, damn it, we lost him!
There he is.
And he's got our money!
(panting)
It's no use.
We're perfectly matched.
(grunting)
HOMER: We did it!
Give us some answers,
or you'll get a mouthful
of rotten shark
fermented in its own urine.
No, no, anything but the inedible,
repulsive food of my native land.
Yeah, Carl, tell them the good reason
you had for borrowing the money.
All right, look, I admit it.
I gave you the ultimate screw-over.
But I did it to clear my family's name.
Everyone blames the barbarian invasion
on my ancestors.
But that saga had a missing page.
Oh, yeah... a page was torn out.
My family's always believed
that we fought bravely
against the invaders,
and the missing page will prove it.
I took the lottery money
to buy that page
and restore my family's honor.
Why didn't you just tell us?
We're your friends.
I didn't tell you because...
we're not friends.
(all gasp)
Friends share their feelings,
their hopes, their dreams.
Friends know their friends
are from Iceland!
We are just guys who
sit next to each other at a bar
and talk about... ugh... guy stuff.
So all those years
of hanging out meant nothing?
-Not to me.
-Sorry, Lenny.
That's all right. Now we know.
It's all out in the open.
I guess it kind of makes it
easier now for me to...
to kill Carl!
(chuckles)
When the nice ones snap,
it's always a good show.
(clattering, punches landing)
(grunting)
-Ow, my eye!
-My eye!
Hey, hey, hey, Lenny,
forget him, forget him!
Look, we still got the money.
-LENNY: What the...
-(Homer groans)
What the hell is this?
That's the missing page from the saga.
That's what I spent
our lottery money on.
Then this belongs to us.
Please, give it back! Please!
It'll restore my family's honor!
Maybe we'd give it back to our friend,
but we're not friends, remember?
Sorry, Carl.
It's World War II all over again.
America kicks Iceland's ass.
No!
Guys, do you think Carl was right?
What if we're not real friends?
Maybe we are just lonely guys who do...
guy stuff.
♪♪
(people screaming)
(computer chimes)
Hi, Homie!
Did you get the money?
The kids have been stocking up
on pool noodles.
Put the noodles in the shed.
There isn't gonna be a swimming pool.
-Hmm?
-Carl spent all our money
on this stupid page from a stupid saga.
I say we make it into saga soup
and have ourselves a soup sip.
(slurps)
That'll show Carl for
de-friending us in real life!
I know Carl did you wrong,
but is destroying something
he cares that much about
really going to make you feel good?
Well, we won't know that till after.
Just read the saga
and see what it says.
But how can we learn to read
ancient Icelandic?
With these.
Yeah, my doctor says
it's better for me not to sleep.
-Thorn?
-Yes!
Forvitinn.
I can't do this, I can't do this!
You can't not do it!
Okay, let's see what this thing says.
"When the barbarian invaders came,
the Carlsons met them
with their weapons ready..."
LENNY:
Wow, Carl's family really was brave.
HOMER: "...weapons which they immediately
threw down in surrender.
The Carlsons then
let the barbarians in the back gate
and joined in the sacking, the looting,
and the volcano-ing
of the village elders.
The Carlsons then wrote down this saga
so no one would ever forget
their treachery and cowardice."
Carl's family was even worse
than people thought.
They were the original ultimate scumbags.
Carl betrayed his friends,
blew the lottery money...
-all for nothing.
-Hey, guys...
I think I feel bad for Carl.
(speaking Icelandic)
Attention, everyone in Iceland.
We have an important announcement.
Take a break from your dreary lives
to hear Americans lecture you.
(all exclaim)
Is this everyone?
No.
Yes.
I've learned something
about the people of Iceland.
You have endured barbarian invasions,
total financial collapse,
and a lesbian prime minister.
You've managed to survive
on a craphole island
that looks like the moon
and smells like rotten eggs.
And to do that,
you have to be stubborn.
But I ask you to put aside
your stubbornness
while I tell you about Carl Carlson.
Shame on Carl's family!
The blood of 1,000 tiny horses
is on their hands.
Doesn't matter what happened
1,000 years ago,
for Carl Carlson's honor
has been redeemed
by the deeds of Carl Carlson.
Carl Carlson who helped me move,
-even though I moved the week before.
-(crowd gasping and murmuring)
Yeah, and when we were
painting my house,
Carl Carlson brought
that blue tape,
you know, that makes you really look
like you know what you're doing.
You peel it off, and you got that
super straight line there.
-(crowd gasping)
-And when he brings
a six-pack to my house,
he doesn't take the extras home with him.
Carl Carlson leaves them in the fridge.
(crowd gasping)
Carl Carlson is our friend,
even if he doesn't believe it.
If we can forgive Carl
for stealing our lottery winnings,
maybe youse can find it
in youse's hearts
to forgive his ancestors.
The many small kindnesses
of Carl Carlson
have redeemed his family forever.
Mom, Dad,
our family can show our face in public
for the first time in 1,000 years.
Ai. Ai.
How can you say these men
are not your true friends?
I... I can't!
(sobbing) I can't!
CROWD: Ai.
Guys, thanks for teaching me
the true meaning of male friendship.
The stuff that comes from in here...
that is guy stuff.
We don't get together
to share our emotions.
We get together to escape them.
Yeah, I'd tell you guys
I love you, but, uh,
I don't want to say it,
and you don't want to hear it.
To nothing!
Okay, everyone,
get ready to see your brand-new...
-Oh, oh! (laughs)
-What is it, what is it, what is it?
-...keg-pools!
-Yay!
Hey! Aah!
(kids laughing)
(grunting)
Fine. I'm going home.
♪♪
Subtitled by A. Vandelay