(SlNGlNG) The Simpsons
(TlRES SCREECHlNG)
D'oh !
(SCREAMlNG)
(TlRES SCREECHlNG)
Oh, God, l love to smoke.
We're live at the opening
of the latest chapter
of the epic space saga,
Cosmic Wars.
And the nerds
have emerged from
their basements,
wearing strange costumes
to shield
their pasty skin
from the moonlight.
Simpsons, your lack
of costumes ill befits
line positions two,
three and four.
Where's your costume?
Your ignorance
is amusing and sad.
l am dressed in
the actual clothing
worn by Cosmic Wars
creator Randall Curtis.
l bought them at auction,
then added pregnancy panels
to fit my unique body type.
One ticket
for the space show.
l want to see
if any of them aliens
match up to the one
l got in my root cellar.
One ticket for Cosmic Wars.
Uh, sir, this is the line for
The Momentum of Things,
starring Ellen Burstyn
and Jim Broadbent.
Oh, man ! l waited
three weeks at the
wrong ticket window!
MAN: Oh, boy. . .
Man, even l think
movie popcorn
has gotten too big.
Ow!
Get your own, mooch !
JEFF: Yes! Finally.
"Amendments"?
"Regulatory agencies"?
What the farq butt?
Don't worry.
They're just
getting the plot
out of the way so it
won't slow down the. . .
(lMlTATES LlGHTSABER FlRlNG)
(lMlTATES
LlGHTSABER WHOOSHlNG)
(ROARS)
Before
the Galactic Senate votes,
we shall call roll.
Star System Avatan.
Here.
Star System Acroilius.
ACROlLlUS SENATOR:
Mugong-mugong.
Star System Trebulon Prime.
Whoa, mama!
Finally some action !
Mr. Chairman, l propose
a proceduraI amendment
to Space Bill number 371 .
You'll wait your turn !
Very weII.
Trebulon Minor.
Oh, l'm so bored.
Maybe l'll clean out
my wallet.
Hey, my car insurance
expired quite a while ago.
(CHUCKLES)
Son, if you don't
dig more coaI,
they'II put you on
the dynamite gang.
No dynamite!
(SOBBlNG)
l didn't realize
British coal miners
had it so bad.
There's blood on your hands,
Mrs. Thatcher!
(SNORlNG)
Jim-Jam, what happened
to the wheel covers of
my landing gear?
Me-sa sell them
to buy me-sa some
space spliff.
That character is
just a tired stereotype.
Yes. And it's making me
so mad,
how am l gonna throw
the meatballs at the screen?
But first, l gotta pose
for a pizza box.
The decision is final.
Tabled this motion is.
Or is it?
That sucked !
l can't believe
The Gathering Shadow
was senate redistricting.
Worst Cosmic Wars ever!
l will only see it
three more times today.
That's it!
From now on, l'm not
looking forward to anything !
Oh, my God !
Tomorrow,
there's a two-for-one sale
on piano benches!
l can't wait!
Ooh, ooh, ooh !
l feel so ripped off
by that crappy movie.
l'm gonna chip
a big hole in the floor.
Kids, why don't you
write a complaint letter?
That's how l got
the Channel 6 weather girl
to start wearing a bra.
That was you?
Mmm-hmm.
A letter, huh?
Okay, Lise. Get this down.
"Dear Randall Curtis,
"your movie
stunk smelly butt.
l am fine. Sincerely. . ."
l'll write the letter.
Marge, you destroyed
my interest in weather!
"Dear Cosmic Wars fan,
l'm glad you loved my film.
"Here's a photo of
your favorite new character,
Jim-Jam Bonks.
"May the power
be on your side,
Randall Curtis."
He ignored our criticisms!
We're gonna have to
track Randall Curtis down
and make him listen to us.
And l know just
where to find him.
742 Evergreen Terrace.
Dad, that's our address.
Ah ! He's in the house?
No.
He lives
at the Cosmic Wars Ranch
in Northern California.
(lN UNlSON)
Can we go? Can we go?
Please, please, please,
please, please?
Well, Northern California
is wine country.
We could take a tour.
And it's a perfect time.
l just got fired again.
Enjoy your tour.
And take it easy
on Mr. Curtis.
Your father and l
will be across the street
at the Lush Valley Winery.
Marge, are you sure
we should go
drinking together?
l mean, who am l gonna
complain about
while l'm drinking?
We should do more together.
You're my best friend, Homie.
Well, yeah, legally.
But if we're
really best friends,
how come we never play hoops?
The doctor said
if you tried running again,
your ankles would shatter.
All right.
We'll go on the winery tour.
But you have
to catch me first!
(SNAPPlNG)
(SCREAMS lN PAlN)
Oh, my ankle snapped !
This is the Creature Works,
where if you dream it,
we can make it.
Unless it has
too many fingers,
which are tough.
TOURlST: Where's the aliens?
Who knows what
fantastic creature
these two men are creating?
lt's a hip-hop loaf
of garlic bread
for an
Olive Garden commercial.
(RAPPlNG) Yo, yo, yo!
Entrees start at $6.95
Offer not good
on a Sunday, fool
Come on, Bart.
Here's our chance.
But the bread's
still dancing.
The Mediterranean climate
is reproduced by
cool Pacific winds
mixed with exhaust fumes
from the highway.
(HONKlNG)
Ah. Summer in Tuscany.
Mmm. . .
lt goes great with
the Jolly Rancher
l'm sucking on.
Pleasant aroma,
rich, full body, well-aged
and the wine's
not bad either.
(BOTH LAUGHlNG)
Oh, stop it, Seinfeld.
(CHUCKLlNG)
We always get
the hicks on Saturdays.
"Lord Krylac, if you
want to take that deduction,
"then you'll have to
bring your receipts."
"Then bring them, l shall."
This is awesome!
Hey, what are
you doing here?
We come from the real world.
And we're here to tell you
that your movies
have lost their way.
No, they haven't.
My characters are
getting better all the time
now that we've perfected
digital eyelash rendering.
Better technology
doesn't mean
better storytelling.
Well, now l know
you're crazy.
Wait. Before you
have us killed, hear us out.
l will wait 1 0 of
your Earth seconds.
Your early movies
are timeless classics.
Please, Mr. Curtis,
go back to what
made your first
films so great.
You know what? You're right.
l'm going back to my roots.
Plots and characters
lifted from westerns
and samurai films.
To the video store!
Kids, please accept
these boxes of
Jim-Jam cereal.
lt's just
Alpha-Bits with extra J's.
Hyah !
Well, we've learned
if you don't like something,
just go to
the office and complain.
What's our next stop?
"Fox Broadcasting,
"1 0201 West Pico,
Building 203."
l drank this much !
(LAUGHS DRUNKENLY)
Mom's not gonna like this.
Don't tell Mama
what Mama don't like.
Come here, you big lug.
(BOTH LAUGHlNG)
Wow. Mom and Dad
sure are having fun.
Hey, as long as
they're not hurting anybody.
Uh-oh.
Whoa.
l will give you money.
Okay, l am going to tell.
Homie, to store
the extra wine we bought,
l made a little wine cellar.
Ooh ! Can l have
my special cup?
Well, l've been using it
for laundry soap, but, okay.
Homie, you are so cute.
(GlGGLlNG)
Oh, honey,
l love to hear you laugh.
(lMlTATES MARGE GlGGLlNG)
l don't talk like that.
(lMlTATlNG MARGE)
Yes, you do.
Well, you talk like,
(lMlTATlNG HOMER)
"Oh, Marge,
"sorry l set the bed
on fire. D'oh !"
(LAUGHlNG)
Hey, you do
a great me, Marge.
You gotta show
the guys at Moe's!
Moe's Tavern?
That's your fun place,
like me and the lamp store.
(CHUCKLES) Come on.
We'll have a blast.
Kids, while we're out,
the TV's in charge.
Go to bed when it says.
Two glasses of wine, Moe.
Wine? Geez,
no one ever orders that.
Um. . . All l got's
this old stuff here.
Chateau Latour 1 886.
l should just
throw this out.
No. lt'll have to do.
That'll be four bucks.
Now, in a step l perhaps
should've taken initially,
let me look up
the value of that bottle
in this wine
collector's guide here.
Oh, what have l done?
Let me dry my tears
with this lost
Shakespeare play.
(SOBBlNG)
Come here, you little. . .
(GlGGLlNG) Oh !
Did you guys get home
at 2:00 last night?
Yup. Your mother and l
have become a legendary
party couple,
like Scott and Zelda Munster.
The best part is
l don't have to ask
your father where
he was all night,
because l was there.
Why are your keys
in my scrambled eggs?
And why is Krusty
on the couch?
This'll cover what
l did to the fireplace.
(GROANS)
(SlNGlNG) We're aII aIone
No chaperone
can get our number
The world's in slumber,
let's misbehave
(MARGE GROANS)
My head.
(CHlRPlNG)
(GROANlNG)
(TlCKlNG LOUDLY)
(DRlPPlNG LOUDLY)
(LOUD BRUSHlNG)
(STOMPlNG)
(DOOR CREAKlNG)
You have to make
such an unholy racket?
Sorry, Marge.
l gotta break in my
ski boots sometime.
Maybe we should put this
booze cruise in
dry dock for awhile.
No problem.
We can still have fun
without you drinking.
Okay. And maybe you
could cut back, too.
You got it!
And when l feel weak,
l will draw
strength from the Bible.
(STOMACH GRUMBLlNG)
Uh-oh.
Here comes the gospel
according to puke!
l hope l can still have fun
while everyone else
is drinking.
Don't worry, honey.
l don't even know
if they serve
alcohol at this thing.
(FESTlVE MUSlC PLAYlNG)
Duffmensch
orders you to party!
This Reich will
last a thousand beers.
Oh ja!
l do this and l'm Jewish.
Eins, zwei, drei, beer!
(SlGHS)
The Germans.
You just can't
stay mad at 'em.
Well, l don't want
to be a Gloom-Hilda.
l guess one beer won't hurt.
lsn't that a little big?
You can just nurse it!
(SLURPS)
Nurse it. Nurse it.
Have you ever
walked on stilts?
lt's not that great.
Yes. And you've said that
several times now.
Why do people
worry about stuff?
lt's all gonna work out.
All good points. Sleep tight,
my drunken angel.
(HONKlNG)
l'm in no condition to drive.
Wait! l shouldn't
listen to myself.
l'm drunk!
(TlRES SQUEAL)
Okay, okay.
Remember the rules
for drinking and driving.
Drive slow, but not too slow.
Drink some cola to
keep yourself alert.
What the. . .
(GROANS)
Nice work, cruise control.
Are we home yet?
ln a minute, honey.
(SlREN BLARlNG)
(GASPS)
Oh, my God !
lf l get one more DUl,
they'll take away my license!
And what will l leave
when l rent rollerblades?
(GASPS)
(SNlFFS)
Oh, boy. l smell beer.
(CLlCKS TONGUE)
Devil's mouthwash.
You weren't calling it that
at the Christmas party.
Okay. l'm gonna need you
to let that go, Chief.
Oh, my God !
This DUl is a She-Ul !
Oh, no! (HlCCUPPlNG)
l'm gonna be. . .
l'm going to jail.
(TWlG SNAPS)
What was that?
Maybe someone else is here.
And maybe he'll step forward
and admit to being
the real culprit.
(WHlSTLlNG)
(CAWlNG)
This is a new low for me.
(WHlSTLlNG AND CAWlNG)
l paid your bail, honey.
You're free to go.
l can't believe
l drove drunk.
But you do
believe it, right?
l don't know what
to believe anymore.
That's my girl.
Just take me home.
Where's your
wife tonight, Homer?
She's not coming anymore.
What?
lt's 'cause of her
l put in a bidet!
Well, it's actually
just a stepladder by
the water fountain.
Listen, Moe. l did
something really terrible
to someone l love.
Hey, look. l've been
in the bartender business
for a long time, all right?
l've heard it all.
Well, what l did was l. . .
(WHlSPERlNG)
(EXCLAlMS lN DlSGUST)
What are you?
You're like a monster!
That's like the worst thing
l've ever heard
anybody do to anybody!
You should be drinking
watered-down beer
in a chipped glass
on a stool with a nail
sticking up out of it!
You know what?
(SOBBlNG)
Can l have some peanuts?
All right. But l get to
poke you with a stick.
(GRUNTS lN PAlN)
So, hey, did you see
the game last night?
The blood of Christ.
Hey, save some for
the rest of us, alkie!
Don't bogart our Lord !
l'm not a drunk!
(CHUCKLES)
Now, Marge,
we do not judge here.
Today's service
is concluded.
l suggest you all
get on the road before Marge.
(ALL SCREAM)
(GROANS)
Marge, when l finally
decided to stop drinking,
there was a place that
really helped me out.
Maybe they can help you.
MARGE: This is
a pamphlet for
chimney sweeping.
ls it, Marge?
ls it? Oh, it is.
Here you go.
This place is great.
They cured me five times!
My drinking problem
is out of control.
At Oktoberfest,
all l could
think about was beer.
l couldn't even
celebrate the harvest!
l can't talk to
my wife for 28 days?
Sir, she is not
an alcoholic.
You can't put me on hold !
l'll put you on hold !
(SlNGlNG) I am a Iineman
for the county
Your call is important to us.
Please continue to hold.
And l drive the main road
There are eight calls
ahead of you.
And the Wichita lineman
is still on the
(VOCALlZlNG)
line
Dad, l still have a couple
of questions about this.
Mom never drives drunk.
And the crash
was in your car.
Also, the driver's seat was
adjusted for your stomach.
Lisa, Lisa, your suspicions
are important to me
and will be answered
in the order received.
MacArthur Park is
meIting in the dark
All that sweet
green icing roIIing down
Someone left my
cake out in the...
(VOCALlZlNG)
(SHOUTS)
(DOOR SLAMS)
You know how some
people are chocoholics?
Well, l'm an alcoholic.
(ALL GASP)
Look, l'm not sure
this place is working.
The drinkers are smoking.
The smokers are drinking.
And the gamblers
are having sex with
everything that moves.
Hey, baby, do you want
to play Caribbean stud?
l'll show you
what l'm holding.
Get away from me!
Your loss, stupid lady.
Flanders, can you
watch my kids while
l'm at the rehab clinic?
Oh, thank God you're finally
fighting your demons!
My demons and l
are closer than ever.
Next year, we're gonna visit
every Major League
Baseball park.
l'm just going in
to bust Marge out.
Well, that's good, too,
l guess.
Feed my pets
and tape my shows!
(FUNNY VOlCE)
l'm here to deliver a package
to Marge Simpson.
Where's the package?
Damn it!
Homer?
Marge, l have
an awful confession to make.
You didn't crash that car.
lt was me!
l put you behind the wheel,
and l'm so, so, so sorry!
You let me believe
that l'd done such
a terrible thing?
Marge, l did it out of love!
Love of not being arrested !
l realize now that nothing
is more important than you.
l can't believe
you did that to me!
That woman means
the world to me.
Would it be all right
if l read from my Bible?
Of course.
(GULPS)
No wonder they
call it the Good Book.
l am so cheesed off!
l need a drink!
Then you should thank God
you're in a rehab center,
'cause we're packin'!
Yar. A couple of these
and your first mate turns
into Reese Witherspoon.
Pour me another!
Just take the whole leg.
What's with all those
rapping grannies
in the movies?
lf l ever start rapping,
just shoot me in the head.
How you doing, Big Blue?
Well, l feel a buzz,
but l don't feel happier.
Not like when l was
drinking with Homer.
Maybe it wasn't
the alcohol you liked.
Hey, you are right!
What l enjoyed was spending
time with my husband !
You're hooked on love, Marge.
l know that feeling.
Nine months later,
Seymour plopped out of me.
l would've kept walking,
but there were
cops everywhere.
Well, l love my husband.
And l'm glad l do.
My name is Marge S.
and l'm a Homer-holic!
Hey,
you're drinking Homer-hol?
l'll take a swig.
l'm afraid what
l like can't be swallowed,
sniffed or smoked.
Hmm. Then you better
inject it between my toes,
because my mom
checks my arms.
Thanks for everything, Kyle.
Yes. l really don't think
you two should leave.
He's a chronic alcoholic,
and you're in
complete denial.
Aw, shut up,
Captain Bringdown !
(GRUNTS)
Homie,
l want you to promise me
you'll cut down
on the drinking.
Okay, Marge.
For you, l'll give up
rum-based cocktails,
except mojitos
and rum and Cokes.
Well, that's no promise
at all.
lt's important
for me to see you
take at least one step.
Then maybe we can have
some memories together
that aren't just
a nauseous blur.
All right. For you,
l will give up
all clear liquors.
Really? Even Zima?
Hey, l only drink that
when l'm already drunk.
You really mean it?
Hey, anything's possible
with a little help
from my Bible.
Oh, no! lt's a real one!
No!
Why, God? Why?
English - US - PSDH