♪ The Simpsons ♪
D'oh!
-Ahh!
-(tires screech)
(hocking)
Milhouse, do
you ever think
about the people
in those cars?
I try not to.
It makes it harder
to spit on them.
Sometimes I wonder about
all the people in this town.
Do you think
anything interesting
ever happens to them?
I mean,
there must be
thousands of great
stories out there.
What do you think, Milhouse?
-Milhouse?
-Huh?
Oh, sorry, I saw
a convertible.
-You were saying?
-Forget it.
Come on, it's 11:00.
I need some sugar.
I wish you'd come
to my party, Apu.
You could use
some merriment.
Listen, serving the customer
is merriment enough for me.
Thank you. Come again.
You see? Most enjoyable.
Oh, I guarantee a wingding
of titanic proportions.
You will be there
or kindly be square.
Well, I don't like
to leave the store, but...
for the next five minutes
I'm going to party
like it's on sale for 19.99.
Quick, quick,
no time to cook them.
They will plump in my stomach.
(belches)
Whoo! Hello, beautiful.
No ring I see.
So you are only arranged
to be married.
♪♪ (synthesizer)
Oh, I love this song.
Let us boogie.
♪ I am a freak-a-zoid ♪
♪ Come on and wind me up ♪
Whoo, I am hot.
Let us get out of here.
Don't worry.
Ill tell everybody
you were untouchable.
Whoo! Woo-hoo.
Oh, Sanjay, never have
I partied so hearty.
-Same time next year, ya?
-Yes!
Made it. And with
one minute to spare.
You took four minutes
of my life and I want them back.
Oh, I'd only
waste them anyway.
♪♪
MAN: Swing Serenade is brought
to you by Gorman's Ear Guards.
(loudly)
Guard your ears...
(softly)
with Gorman's.
Mom, Dad threw his beer can
at the Miracle-Gro guy on TV.
Can I recycle it?
Why not.
Waa!
Uhh!
There's gum in my hair!
Mom, someone threw
gum in my hair!
Are you sure?
Maybe it's just shampoo.
That washes right out.
No, it's somebody's gross gum!
Get it out!
Ow! Ow!
It's pulling out my hair!
Wait-- if I remember
my Heloise,
the trick to getting out
gum is peanut butter.
There.
Now that gum should
lift right out.
-(grunting)
-Ow.
Hmm?
Maybe it needs
a little mayonnaise
to get going.
Okay, you go sit in the sun
and let it melt in.
Why me?
Yuck. I smell like a sandwich.
(buzzing)
(screaming)
Smithers, what's the meaning
of this slacking off?
There's a bee
in my eye, Sir.
And?
I'm allergic
to bee-stings.
They cause me
to, uh... die.
But we're running out
of forward momentum.
Uh, perhaps you
could pedal
for just a little
while, Sir?
Quite impossible.
I can try to bat him off
if you like.
Really, that's ok--
(moaning)
Holy cats, man,
we're starting to wobble.
(thickly)
Get me to a hospital.
You have... to... pedal.
Oh, Tuttle's Sunday trousers.
Fear not, I'll get you
to a hospital
the only way I know how.
Smithers,
you infernal ninny!
Stick your left hoof
on that flange now!
Now, if you can get it through
your bug-addled brain
jam that second mephitic
clod-hopper of yours
on the right doodad!
Now pump those scrawny
chicken legs,
you stuporous funker!
(panting)
One more jostle,
you wretched shirkaday.
(groaning)
Help me.
Holy smokes!
You need booze.
Hi, everybody.
ALL: Hi, Dr. Nick.
Dr. Nick,
this malpractice committee
has received a few complaints
against you.
Of the 160 gravest charges,
the most troubling are
performing major operations
with a knife and fork
from a seafood restaurant--
But I cleaned them
with my napkin.
Misuse of the cadavers--
I get here earlier when I drive
in the car-pool lane.
(door opens)
(panting) There's a crazy man
with a scalpel in E.R.!
He's demanding to see a quack.
Hi, everybody.
Now tell Dr. Nick
where is the trouble.
I'm edgy!
I got ants in my pants!
I'm discombobulated!
Give me a calmative!
Slow down, sir.
You're going to give
yourself skin failure.
Okay, now the symptoms
you describe
point to "bonus eruptus."
It's a terrible
disorder
where the skeleton
tries to leap out
the mouth
and escape the body.
Now you're talking.
Our one chance is
trans-dental electromicide.
I'll need a golf-cart motor with
1,000 volt capacimator, stat.
Doctor, I can't in good
conscience--
Now there's no time, man.
We'll have to improvise.
(electricity crackling)
(screaming)
Keep doing that
every five seconds.
Dr. Nick, we owe
you an apology.
Consider the
charges dropped.
All right!
Free nose jobs
for everybody.
Yi! You first.
Give me a Van Heflin.
-(electricity crackling)
-(screaming)
Say, Barn...
uh, remember when I said
I'd have to send away to NASA
to calculate your bar tab?
(laughs)
Oh, yeah.
We all had
a good laugh, Moe.
The results
came back today.
(grunts)
You owe me $70 billion.
Hmm?
No, wait, wait wait,
that's for
the Voyager spacecraft.
Um, your tab's $14 billion.
Well, alls I got is
2,000 bucks.
Well, that's
halfway there.
Freeze, dude.
Move a muscle and I'll
blow this wino's head off.
(grunts)
I'm behind three inches
of bullet-proof glass.
Do your worst.
All right.
No, stay out of there.
Stay out of there!
Oh, good God, no!
Oh, good-bye
student loan payments.
Ha-ha.
Come back here, you stinking...
Hey, I wonder
how much air is in here.
(doorbell rings)
Well, Seymour, I made it,
despite your directions.
Ah, Superintendent
Chalmers, welcome.
I hope you're prepared for
an unforgettable luncheon.
Yeah.
(gasps)
Oh, ye Gods!
My roast is ruined.
But what if...
I were to purchase fast food
and disguise it
as my own cooking?
Ho-ho-ho-ho-ho.
Delightfully devilish, Seymour.
♪ Skinner, with his
crazy explanations ♪
♪ The superintendent's
gonna need his medication ♪
♪ When he hears Skinner's
lame exaggerations ♪
♪ There'll be trouble
in town tonight ♪
Seymour!
Superintendent!
I was just...
uh, stretching my calves
on the windowsill.
Isometric exercise--
care to join me?
Why is there smoke coming out
of your oven, Seymour?
Uh... oh! That isn't smoke.
It's steam.
Steam from the steamed clams
we're having.
Mmm, steamed clams.
Whoo.
Superintendent,
I hope you're ready
for mouth-watering
hamburgers.
I thought we were having
steamed clams.
Oh, no, I said
"steamed hams."
That's what I
call hamburgers.
You call hamburgers
"steamed hams"?
Yes, it's a regional dialect.
Uh-huh. What region?
Uh... upstate New York.
Really? Well, I'm from Utica,
and I've never heard anyone use
the phrase "steamed hams."
Oh, not in Utica, no,
it's an Albany expression.
I see.
You know, these hamburgers
are quite similar
to the ones they have
at Krusty Burger.
(laughing)
Oh, no.
Patented Skinner burgers,
old family recipe.
-For steamed hams.
-Yes.
Yes, and you call them
steamed hams
despite the fact they are
obviously grilled.
Y-You know th--
One thing I sh--
Excuse me for one second.
Of course.
Ah, well,
that was wonderful.
Good time was had by all.
I'm pooped.
Yes, I should be--
Good Lord! What is
happening in there?
Aurora borealis.
Aurora borealis?!
At this time of year,
at this time of day,
in this part of the country,
localized entirely
within your kitchen?
-Yes.
-May I see it?
No.
SKINNER'S MOTHER:
Seymour, the house is on fire!
No, Mother, it's just
the Northern Lights.
Well, Seymour,
you are an odd fellow,
but I must say,
you steam a good ham.
SKINNER'S MOTHER:
Help! Help!
(siren blaring)
"Helms calls for donut tax."
(gasping)
(door slamming)
There! Done and done.
(shrieks)
Oh!
Why did I have to stop
at the railroad tracks?
Better get some change.
(sucking loudly)
It's okay. It's okay.
I'm back.
See? Daddy's here.
(grunting)
Come on, Maggie.
Maybe if you just
squeeze a little...
(grunting)
That's it. That's it. I--
D'oh!
(giggling)
Okay, okay, think, Homer.
-(dog barks)
-The dog!
(mumbling)
Okay, go, boy.
Go find help.
Go find help, boy.
D'oh, bad dog.
Bad dog!
(sucking)
Oh...
Don't worry, Maggie.
I'll think of something.
(Homer speaking gibberish)
Where's that lil' baby?
(giggling)
(babbling)
You know,
I went to the McDonald's
in, uh, Shelbyville
on Friday night.
The Mc-what?
Uh, McDonald's restaurant.
I never heard
of it either
but, uh, they have over
2,000 locations
in this state alone.
Must have sprung up
overnight.
You know the funniest thing,
though?
It's the little differences.
-Example.
-Well, at McDonald's,
you can buy a Krusty Burger
with cheese, right?
But they don't call it
a Krusty Burger with cheese.
Get out! What do they call it?
A Quarter Pounder with cheese.
Quarter Pounder with cheese?
Well, I can picture the cheese,
but, uh, do they have
Krusty partially gelatinated,
nondairy, gum-based beverages?
Mm-hmm. They
call them shakes.
Huh, shakes.
You don't know
what you're getting.
Well, I know what I'm getting--
some donuts.
(grunting)
Uh, help me out
of the booth, boys.
(air hissing)
♪♪ ("La Cucaracha"
on radio)
Mmm-ahh!
(yipping)
Ay, que dia miserable
a trabajo.
Primero, el attaque
del woodpeckero loco.
(canned laughter)
Luego, un disastro
de electricidad.
(electricity crackling)
(canned laughter)
Y finalmente
una catastrofia
con una pelota de beisbol.
(crack of a bat)
(ball whistling)
(canned laughter)
(sighs)
Tiempo para relaxar
en paz y quieto.
Ay! Naranjas en la cabeza!
(yips)
♪♪ ("Mexican Hat Dance"
on radio)
Ay, una candelabra
precariosa!
(yells)
(dog yipping)
Ooh! Ooh!
(screams)
Mira que cosa tan terrible
no puedo entender
algo como esto
como puedo vivir con
alguien tan irresponsible.
No, no, no, no!
-(yipping)
-(sighs)
¿ Donde esta mi tequila?
♪♪ (hard rock version of
"The Simpsons" theme on radio)
♪ Donuts ♪
♪ I got donuts, I g-- ♪
Hey, I know you!
(engine revving)
(tires squealing)
Ooh!
(children laughing)
Huh... huh!
Hey, hey, wait up!
We got to swap
insurance info.
(panting)
(grunting)
Hey!
-Whoa, whoa, whoa...
-Huh, huh, huh...
-Whoa... uh!
-(gun cocks)
Hold it right there.
Looks like the spider caught
himself a couple of flies.
(chuckles)
Come on, boy.
This is the spot right here.
That's a good boy.
Good boy.
Do your dirty, sinful business.
Well, howdy,
Reverend Lovejoy.
Nice to see you there...
on my lawn with...
your dog.
Oh, uh, ooh... bad dog.
Look at that.
Right on Ned's lawn.
Now, how could you
do such a thing?
(quietly)
Good boy. Don't stop now.
Bad dog!
I condemn you to hell.
Better get
the ol' snow shovel
back from Homer, huh?
Good boy.
Don't stop the music.
Marge Simpson,
still making juice
the old-fashioned way?
No, I've got gum in my hair.
Oh, we've tried everything--
olive oil, lemon juice,
tartar sauce, chocolate syrup,
gravy, bacon fat,
hummus and baba ganoush.
My scalp hurts
from horsefly bites.
Why don't you freeze it
with an ice cube,
and hit it with a hammer?
Works for me when I get
bubbly-gum
in the ol' push broom.
That sounds okay.
Ah!
Stop! Stop!
Hmm...
I seem to have
mashed more hair into it.
Oh, well.
Ice cubes
are useless, man.
Chewing gum's got
to be chewed out.
Does the whole town
have to hear about this?
Gar, have ye tried
a Baltic squid?
They can suck the bolts
out of a submarine's hull.
All right.
Fangoria will give me
25 bucks for this shot.
I can give you the name
of a good gum-and-hair man.
(laughs)
I have a word of advice:
don't try to dig gum out
with a bone.
It just makes things worse.
Leave it in as evidence.
Bazooka Joe's got deep pockets.
Perhaps I can help.
My papa is foreman
of the Dusseldorf gum-works.
(honking)
♪♪ (Bluegrass)
Hey, what's going on
on this side?
Hey, Brandine,
you might could wear these
to your job interview.
And scuff up the topless
dancing runway?
Naw. You best
bring them back
where from
you got them.
Okay.
Back you go--
to waits for a woman
of less discriminating tastes.
♪♪ (Bluegrass)
Hey, you know what?
I could call my ma
while I'm up here.
Hey, Ma!
Get off the dang roof!
Yes, and one with extra cheese.
Thank you.
Can I use your bathroom?
No, you may not.
The bathroom is for
paying customers only.
If you purchase an item,
you may use the bathroom.
Uh... okay.
Um... how about that?
That is a rare photo
of Sean Connery
signed by Roger Moore.
It is worth $150.
Oh... what can I get
for 75 cents?
You may purchase this charming
Hamburglar adventure.
A child has already solved the
jumble using crayons.
The answer is "fries."
Milhouse,
What's going on?
You said you just needed
to use the bathroom.
Now I find you
buying comics!
Our transaction
is completed.
You may take the boy.
Wait!
As soon as Zed gets here,
the party will begin.
(doorbell rings)
(buzzing)
There he is now.
Who are you?
Uh, can my son use
your bathroom?
You got to say "yes"!
Okay, but be quick.
It's in back.
(muffled grunts)
Uh... so, uh... n-nice store.
(louder muffled grunts)
Uh, you know,
when I was a kid,
this used to be a pet store.
(nervous chuckle)
Yeah, right over there
against that wall
-there was the cutest little--
-(gun cocks)
-Get in the corner.
-(gulps)
Hey, Dad, can we
get this, please?
Oh, my gosh!
Sorry, mister.
(muffled grunt)
Want me to cut
off the gum
or just style it?
Cut if off, but be careful.
Don't worry, sweetheart.
I know how important hair is
to a little girl.
(screams)
You keep squirming
there's going to be
a little bald girl
with no lollipop.
(gasps)
I love it!
I finally look like
a real person.
Thanks!
Ha! Ha!
(groans)
(screams)
Ha! Ha!
(brakes screeching)
Crud.
(panting)
He's down there.
NELSON: Crud!
Do you find something comical
about my appearance
when I'm driving
my automobile?
Yeah.
Everyone needs to drive
a vehicle, even the very tall.
This was the largest auto
that I could afford.
Should I, therefore,
be made the subject of fun?
I guess so.
(frustrated grunt)
Would you like it
if I laughed
at your misfortune?
Huh?!
Maybe we should find out.
(grunts)
Now... march!
(horn honking)
Hey, everybody,
look at this!
It's that boy
who laughs at everyone.
Let's laugh at him.
ALL: Ha! Ha!
Wave to the people!
Blow them kisses!
(bawling)
(guffawing)
Well, Milhouse,
I guess interesting stuff
does happen to people
in Springfield.
Yep. Everybody in town's
got their story to tell.
There's just
not enough time
to hear them all.
(panting)
Oh, sorry I'm late.
There was trouble at the lab--
with the running,
the exploding and the crying.
One of the monkeys
stole the glasses off my head!
No, wait. Please, no!
Please, I have a funny story--
if you listen.
I even wrote theme music.
Yeah, listen--
(clears throat)
♪ Hey, hey ♪
♪ Professor Frink,
Professor Frink ♪
♪ He'll make you laugh,
he'll make you think ♪
♪ He likes to run, and then
the thing with the... ♪
♪ Person... ♪
Ah, boy, that monkey
is going to pay.
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.