(SlNGlNG) The Simpsons
(TlRES SCREECHlNG)
D'oh !
(BRAKES SCREECHlNG)
Look, Smithers.
Crackle-berries!
Spot me a federal,
will you?
Sir, l've spotted you over
$1 00,000 this year.
Perhaps you could
carry your own money.
(LAUGHlNG)
Money is for the poor.
Why don't you use
your ATM card?
Ah ! Yes. The automated teller
machine-eola-trola-maton.
(GRUNTlNG)
Oh, Smithers,
guide me in.
My pleasure, sir.
Smithers,
what's my password?
lt's your age, sir.
Excellent.
Let's see.
What's the smallest amount
of money l can think of?
A thousand dollars!
Oh !
Oh ! My moolah !
lt's escaping
my clutches!
(BUZZlNG)
Your kid sucks!
Bring it on!
ANNOUNCER: Hockey Dads.
Commence fighting!
Hockey Dad rules!
Feel the drunken wrath
of Chuck Shadowski !
Dad, stop! It's onIy assauIt.
Don't make it murder!
lgnore. lgnore.
ANNOUNCER: You are a big man.
Big man!
(GASPS)
What?
There's a ladybug
in your hair.
Get it out!
Got it.
You're a good
friend, Bart.
The best you'll
ever have.
$1 ,000.
Do you know how much furniture
we could rent with this?
You'll rent nothing !
This money is mine.
l found it.
Which means
someone lost it.
You'll have to put up flyers
and see if anyone claims it.
(BOTH GASPlNG)
Marge, this is why people
don't tell you things.
(CHUCKLlNG)
Well, we put up a flyer.
Let's see someone
claim that money now.
(CHUCKLlNG)
Hey, what does
that flyer say?
What if it's for
guitar lessons?
We must know!
l'm on it.
Uh-oh !
You know the drill.
Try to land on my back-fat.
Can you describe
the bill?
Describe? Sure.
Of course.
Whose picture's on it?
lt would have to be
somebody famous.
l'm gonna say, Hitler.
Next.
Does the bill have
bank teller blood on it?
No, it doesn't.
l'm sorry
l wasted your time.
That's the last of them.
You did the right thing, Bart.
And now you can
keep the money.
Sweet.
What am l gonna do
with $1 ,000?
(SlNGlNG) It's Bart's moon
party from outer space
With R2-D2
pIaying the bass
Hmm.
No one's touching
the hors d'oeuvres.
(lN SlNG-SONG)
lt's Bart's moon party
from outer space. . . What?
Bart, why don't you
spend the money on
something for Mom?
She does
so much for us.
Well, someday l'd like
to go on a nice vacation.
We've gone on plenty
of great vacations.
Yeah. But you always
wind up kidnapped
or on a chain gang.
And l don't even want
to get into what happened
on our honeymoon.
HOMER: l still
don't know why you had
that photo enlarged.
Oh, forget it.
Bart, don't waste
your money on me.
(SlGHlNG)
Great, lady.
MlLHOUSE:
Look at the cross-hatching
on Grover Cleveland's tie.
l completely buy
the illusion of shadow.
This must be worth
like a million dollars!
(CLOCK DlNGS)
Time's up.
Beat it, do-rags.
l want to see
it some more.
lf you let me
keep looking at it,
l'll give you a quarter.
Hmm.
This gives me an idea.
(CLASSlCAL MUSlC PLAYlNG)
(ALL GASPlNG lN ADMlRATlON)
What's all this
other stuff?
Hey, l'm charging
five bucks to get in.
They deserve to see
the boy behind the bill.
Bart, that exhibit
over there is biased,
insensitive,
and anti-feminist!
Ugh !
You can't whitewash
history, Lise.
What do l get
if l join the museum
as a "Friend of Bart"?
A subscription to
BARTFORUM Magazine,
and Bart will say
"Eat my shorts"
on your home
answering machine.
How much to have
Bart crank call me?
(CHUCKLlNG) That
would be hilarious.
That's just me, though.
You know, l love to laugh.
Young man, l believe
you have something
that belongs to me.
Prove it,
Bony Curtis.
When the errant bill
struck my chest, it left
a distinctive bruise.
Had my heart been
inside at the time,
it could've been fatal.
BART:
lt's a perfect match !
Yoink!
(SCOFFS)
Without that bill,
this ain't a museum.
The Hard Rock Cafe
in Phoenix
has better crap.
l'm recycling
this pin in disgust!
Bart, your museum
took in over $3,000.
Finally, l can get
what l've always wanted.
A used Toyota.
Bart, l don't care
what Mom said.
l think you should use
this money to take her
on a nice vacation.
Well. . . Okay.
For Mom, l'll do it.
Where should we go?
Well, l'd like
to return to Brazil,
but l hear the
monkey problem
is even worse now.
l wanna go to England.
How come?
Back in 1 944, l was
stationed over there.
And l met
a beautiful girl.
Edwina, my slowly
opening flower,
l'm shipping out
in the morning.
Won't you make this
night memorable?
Anything for you,
my brave Yank.
EDWlNA: l say.
Ohhh ! Nice.
ABE: Little did l know
I reaIIy was shipping out
in the morning!
l'll never forget you,
Edwina!
But l did. . .
Until just now!
Grampa, that's
so romantic.
We gotta go
to England !
That sounds great.
But only if your father
promises to behave.
Marge, l'll be on
my best behavior.
You have my word
as a gentleman and a lady.
Now let's see.
Which rifle should l bring?
(GRUNTS lN DESPAlR)
Hello. Welcome to
the United Kingdom.
Prime Minister
Tony Blair?
Why are you
greeting lowlifes
like us at the airport?
Because l want
to encourage
all the world
to come see the beauty
of 21 st century Britain.
Would an American dollar
encourage you to leave us
alone?
No! But thank you.
Tony. . .
l mean, Mister Prime Minister,
what shall we see first?
There's so much to see here.
Parliament, Stratford-on-Avon,
the White Cliffs of Dover.
Oh, and you Americans
love castles.
There's a huge one
in Edinburgh, the city
where l was born.
The place l was born
is now a gator farm.
Smashing.
Maybe you could give us
a personal tour
of your country.
l'd love to but l'm late
for an appointment.
l'm greeting
a lovely Dutch couple
at Gate 23. Cheerio.
Wow! l can't believe
we met Mr. Bean !
England is so classy.
Every cab has
its own butler.
Actually,
l'm not a butler.
l had already
hired this cab
when you got in.
But the more the merrier,
and all that. (CHUCKLlNG)
Make with the tea, Jeeves.
Yes. Very good, sir.
We're big shot tourists
from everyone's
favorite country,
the USA.
We saved your ass
in Vietnam and shared our
prostitutes with Hugh Grant!
So give me some free maps
and none of that
dry British wit!
l wouldn't
dream of it, sir.
Thank you.
Hmm.
Did you spend an unforgettable
night with a soldier
from the US Army in 1 944?
You did?
Was he from the
1 st lnfantry Division?
He was?
And was he a gentle,
caring lover?
He was?
Sorry l bothered you.
l don't know if
l'm ever gonna find her.
Aw, Dad. l wish there
was something l could do.
Touch that mini bar
and you're dead !
Oh. . .
Look. lt's J. K. Rowling,
author of
the Harry Potter books.
You've turned a generation
of kids on to reading.
Thank you, young muggle.
Can you tell me what happens
at the end of the series?
He grows up
and marries you.
ls that what
you want to hear?
Yes.
AII right,
who's hungry?
We're right near a
Judi Dench's Fish & Chips.
SQUEAKY-VOlCED BRlTlSH TEEN:
Welcome to Judi Dench's
Fish & Chips.
Now completely free
of "Mad Fish Disease."
Fish? l don't know.
l'm not really
a vegetarian.
Please order
or Miss Dench'll
be furious.
She'll beat us, she will.
JUDl DENCH:
Who are you taIking to?
TEEN: No one, Mum!
l swear!
JUDl DENCH:
I'II "mum" you!
(CRYlNG OUT lN PAlN)
TEEN: BIimey!
Well, Marge. You gotta admit,
l've been on my best
behavior this trip.
You punched out three
people on the street.
That was over
soccer results.
Can you believe
they gave Giggs
a yellow card in the box?
Do you understand any part
of what you just said?
l understand the word "gave,"
unless it means something
else in this country!
Word to the wise.
British candy is a bit
sweeter than what you're
used to across the pond.
Look, teabag,
just fork over the brown.
BOTH: Mmm !
(UPBEAT MUSlC PLAYlNG)
(BOTH GlGGLlNG MANlACALLY)
Homie,
l don't think we'll be able
to find the kids from up here.
Now, now.
Let's just look.
There's Big Ben.
There's Piccadilly Circus.
There's Jimmy Page,
one of the greatest thieves
of American black music
who ever walked the earth.
There's the kids.
(DRAMATlC MUSlC PLAYlNG)
(BOTH GROANlNG)
Well, look at those
filthy urchins.
Surely they could never be
taught proper manners.
One gold sovereign says
l could do just that.
(CHUCKLlNG)
lt's a bet,
Lord Daftwager!
You can't bet on my kids!
This is America, pal !
Don't worry.
We'll find more wagers.
l love you,
Lord Daftwager.
Yes. And l you.
Yes, quite.
Ohhh ! Look at all these
classy British plays.
l don't have
a cherry orchard.
(GASPS)
Sir lan McKellen !
You're my favorite
Shakespearean actor.
Thank you, my dear.
Please take these
free tickets to my play.
What? What play?
We thespians believe
it's bad luck to mention
the name of this
particular play out loud.
You mean Macbeth?
Quiet, you blundering fool !
You'll curse us all !
What?
By saying Macbeth?
Stop saying it!
Saying what?
Macbeth !
Ah !
Now l've said it!
(CRACKLlNG)
Ohhh ! This is cool !
Macbeth !
Macbeth ! Macbeth !
Bart!
Stop saying Macbeth !
(CRACKLlNG)
Mom, you said Macbeth !
Mr. Macbeth,
l'm really sorry.
That's quite all right.
You didn't know.
Now if you'll excuse me,
l have a performance to give.
Good luck!
lt's bad luck
to say that, too!
(ALL GASPlNG)
Homie, you're doing
a great job driving
on the left.
This is turning out
to be our most
enjoyable trip ever.
Yes, this trip is
entirely uneventful.
(CHUCKLlNG)
(TlRES SCREECHlNG)
Dad, no! You turned
into a roundabout!
ALL: Whoa!
Whoa!
MARGE: Turn,
turn, keep turning.
Keep turning,
keep turning,
keep turning.
HOMER:
l see an opening !
MARGE: No, it's too risky!
We'll just wait till
the traffic thins out!
Turn, turn. Keep turning,
keep turning, keep turning.
(GROGGlLY)
Keep turning, keep turning.
That's it!
l'm acting the way
America acts best!
Unilaterally!
(CARS HONKlNG)
(ALL SCREAMlNG)
Ahhh !
Okay, l'm gonna go
over there and see
if they're cool.
Okay, let's see.
Oh, you can
buff that out.
We can buff that out.
That's factory error.
Oh, that thing is
supposed to be on fire.
Lady, please.
Get back in your
overturned car.
Let the guys
handle this.
We'll deal with him,
Your Majesty.
(SCOFFS) Your Majesty?
(MlMlCS WHlPPlNG)
Dad, you rear-ended
the Queen of England !
The Queen of what?
(CRYlNG OUT lN PAlN)
(TRUMPET BLOWlNG)
MAN: Changing of the guard !
(GROANlNG)
HOMER: Wait! We have
to exchange insurance!
(CRYlNG OUT lN PAlN)
(JUDGE POUNDlNG GAVEL)
Homer Simpson,
you are hereby charged with
damaging the Royal Coach
and putting several dents
in the Royal Horse.
How do you plead?
M'Lord,
we Americans
love queens.
Be they homecoming
or dairy.
This woman, however,
is an imposter!
(ALL GASPlNG)
Her luggage is inscribed
"H. R. H."
Which means her
real name must be. . .
Henrietta R. Hippo!
Why did you let him
be his own barrister?
What difference could it make?
He hit the friggin' Queen !
l guess
it's just too much for me
to ask for one vacation
where we don't go to jail
or to a condo sales pitch.
Your Honor,
l've completely
disappointed my wife.
That's punishment enough.
You understand these things.
You're a grandmother.
l'm a man !
(CHUCKLlNG NERVOUSLY)
And a very manly one
if l may say so, m'Lord.
lf l might say a word?
(ALL GASPlNG)
l haven't had
an easy life.
l've seen my country
ravaged by war,
my family torn
by tragedy,
and then as l was
innocently making
my way to the shops
to buy light bulbs,
l was blindsided
by this great
lumbering brute!
Boy, she's good.
lf she were 1 00 years younger
and l were 1 00 years older. . .
Oh !
lf there is any love
left in you for me,
destroy him !
America rules! Our Beatles
are way better than your
precious Rolling Stones!
(BlRD CAWlNG)
ln this cell
sits Homer Simpson,
the most villainous blackguard
to be held in this tower
since Edward
the Puppy Eater.
(ALL EXCLAlMlNG lN HORROR)
Look at his great
staring eyes.
Like saucers they are.
(lN MOCK BRlTlSH ACCENT)
He claimed he was
me father, he did.
Bart, you're not helping.
Poke the monster
with a stick!
Tuppence a jab!
Come on,
queue up, lads.
Oh, Marge,
l am so sorry.
l should've listened
to whatever it was
you were saying.
lt's partly my fault.
l've been nagging you
so much on this trip,
you couldn't know
which nags to focus on.
Well, Marge, if l die here,
there's one thing l
want you to remember.
Don't buy any
videotapes in England !
They won't work
in our VCR!
(SOBBlNG)
Dear God of England,
please let me go.
ln return,
l will spell the word
"color" with a "U."
And l will use the metric
system with every cubic
milliliter of blood in my. . .
Oh, l can't do it!
lt's so stupid !
BART: Dad !
Huh? Oh !
We found a secret tunnel
out of the Tower!
lt was used by
Sir Walter Raleigh !
A secret tunnel?
l don't know.
Won't that get me
in more trouble?
Homer, you couldn't
be in more trouble.
They're going to put
your head on a pike.
They're practicing
with melons.
Smash it on ! Don't worry it.
Let the pike do the work.
Okay, what do l do?
Push the gray brick
in the back of the
fireplace!
Sweet freedom, here l. . .
Ahhh !
(SlZZLlNG)
Put out the fire first!
Boy, it's a good thing
l'm leaving before
l went nuts.
Goodbye, sparkly elves!
ALL: Goodbye!
Oh, my God.
We've made
a terrible mistake.
This tunnel comes out
in the worst possible place!
An elephant's butt?
Yes, Bart.
An elephant's butt.
Boy, a Krispy Kreme would
really clean up down here.
Hey, this place
is amazing !
lt's fit for a Duke,
or even an Earl. . .
Oh !
(BLOWS SHRlLL BLAST)
Uh-oh.
The Queen's
in trouble!
And you didn't want
to give her a whistle!
(SCREAMS)
Please, Your Majesty.
l know that l,
like many other Americans,
have behaved like
a total buffoon.
But we Americans are
England's children.
l know we don't call
as often as we should
and we aren't as
well-behaved as our goody
two-shoes brother Canada,
who by the way
has never had a girlfriend.
l'm just saying.
But please, find it
in your jewel-encrusted
heart to forgive me.
That was very sweet
of the Queen
letting you go
in exchange for taking
Madonna back to America.
MADONNA:
(lN FAKE BRlTlSH ACCENT)
l'm telling you, l'm English.
English women
don't pump gas naked.
See you in
Atlanta, bitch !
EDWlNA: Abe Simpson.
Are you leaving again
without saying goodbye?
Edwina,
you got my message!
Sorry l never
saw you again.
l just felt
the cultural differences
between us were too great.
Plus, as the boat
pulled away from the dock,
l thought you looked fat.
You don't have
to apologize, Abe.
You Yanks
saved our bacon.
Mmm !
Bacon.
(DROOLlNG)
Abe, this is
my daughter Abbey.
She's 58,
this month.
Fifty-eight?
Well, 59 years ago,
your mother and l
were have. . . Oh !
Well, gotta go!
See you in heaven !
Mummy, he's everything
you said he was.
Lady,
you're gorgeous.
You make Dame Edna
look like a dude.
Why, thank you.
You're all right, love.
(MAJESTlC lNSTRUMENTAL
MUSlC PLAYlNG)
English - US - PSDH