♪ The Simpsons ♪
-(chalk screeches)
-(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(tires screeching)
(horn honks)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
Take two!
Take three!
Human roaches feeding off
each other's garbage.
The only thing
you can't buy here is dignity.
Welcome, swappers,
to the Springfield Swap Meet!
Ich bin ein
Springfield Swap Meet patron.
(whistling)
I need a drink and a shower.
Oyster shells!
Hand-painted to resemble
Lucille Ball!
You'll love Oyster Lucy!
Oh, Mr. Mooney, I just
got to meet Bob Cummings.
Viv!
Oh, boy! Free trading cards.
Wow!
Joseph of Arimathea!
Twenty-six conversions
in A .D. 46.
Whoa! A Methuselah rookie card!
Heh, heh. Well, boys,
who'd have thought
learning about religion
could be fun?
-Religion?
-Learning?
-Let's get out of here!
-Hey!
Wow! An original Malibu Stacy
from 1958.
Oh.
Yeah, they took her
off the market
after some kid put
both his eyes out.
Oh, my.
Prisoner 24601.
(chuckles)
God...
I wore this for two years
in a Viet Cong
internment center.
Never thought I'd see
the old girl again.
Still fits.
Small world, huh?
It is.
It really, really is.
Ooh! Five cents each.
Junk.
The airplane's upside down.
Stradi-who-vius?
(violin clatters)
Your teenage son
or daughter will think
this wishbone necklace
is really cool.
I doubt my son or daughter
is that stupid.
(groans)
Hmm.
Nah.
-What the hell's this?
-"Melvin and the Squirrels."
Part of the Rodent Invasion
of the early'60s.
♪ Put a feather in his cap ♪
♪ And called it Rice-A-Roni ♪
MAN: Melvin!
(gasps)
Bart, look.
It's Dad.
Dad, when did you record
an album?
I'm surprised
you don't remember, son.
It was only eight years ago.
Dad, thanks to television,
I can't remember
what happened
eight minutes ago.
(laughing)
No, really, I can't.
It's a serious problem.
(laughing)
What are we all
laughing about?
Who cares?
Anyway, it all happened
during that magical summer
of 1985.
A maturing Joe Piscopo
left Saturday Night Live
to conquer Hollywood.
People Express introduced
a generation of hicks
to plane travel.
And I was in a barbershop
quartet.
(plays tone)
♪ Hello, hello ♪
♪ Hello, my baby ♪
♪ Hello, my honey ♪
♪ Hello, my ragtime,
ragtime gal ♪
HOMER: Every afternoon
at Moe's, Chief Wiggum,
Principal Skinner,
Apu, and I
would get together and sing.
And the crowds went wild.
Yoo-hoo!
♪ Then you'll be left alone ♪
Barbershop?
That ain't been popular
since aught-six, dagnab it.
Bart, what did I tell you?
No talking like a grizzled
1890s prospector, consarn it.
Anyway, rock and roll
had become stagnant.
"Achy Breaky Heart"
was seven years away.
Something had to fill the void.
And that something
was barbershop.
♪ Good-bye ♪
-♪ Good-bye ♪
♪ Good-bye,
my Coney Island baby ♪
That's my son up there.
What, the balding fat ass?
No, the Hindu guy.
♪ Never to see you any ♪
♪ Never gonna see you any ♪
I'm going to nail that cop
right between the eyes.
♪ Never to return again ♪
Right after this song is over.
♪ Good-bye,
my Coney Island babe ♪
(applause, whistling)
(laughing)
♪♪ (organ playing)
♪ Good-bye,
my Coney Island baby ♪
♪ Farewell, my own true love ♪
♪ True love, my baby,
I'm gonna go... ♪
Ching, ching!
You know, Reverend,
this really isn't a hymn.
Ned, there's an oil stain
in the parking lot
-that looks just like St. Barnabas.
-Oh, my stars.
♪ Never to return again ♪
-♪ So, good-bye ♪
-♪ Farewell ♪
♪ Shop Quick-E-Mart and save ♪
♪ Good-bye, my Coney Isle ♪
♪ Good-bye,
my Coney Island babe ♪
Homer, I'm a theatrical agent.
And I want to represent
your group.
-Really?
-Yeah. You've got it.
All except
that police officer.
Yuck! Too "Village People."
-You have to replace him.
-Just leave it to me.
Where we goin'? Where we goin'?
(panting)
Run along, boy.
You're free now!
No! No!
(baying)
No!
Principal Seymour Skinner.
Apu Nasapimapetalon.
Never fit on a marquee, luv.
From now on, your name is
Apu de Beaumarchais.
That is a great dishonor to
my ancestors and my god, but okay.
HOMER:
The next day, we started auditioning
for Chief Wiggum's replacement.
♪ Old MacDonald had a farm ♪
♪ E-I-E-I-O ♪
♪ And on this farm,
he had a chick ♪
♪ The swingin'est chick
I know ♪
♪ With a wiggle-wiggle here ♪
♪ And a wiggle-wiggle there...♪
-Get off the stage.
-I want to, but I can't.
♪ When you're alone ♪
♪ And life is
gettin' you lonely ♪
♪ Ye can always go ♪
♪ Ach! "Doontown" ♪
Next!
♪ Theme ♪
♪ From "A Summer Place" ♪
♪ The theme ♪
-♪ It's the theme ♪
-ALL: Next!
♪ If I could walk
with the animals ♪
♪ Talk with the animals ♪
♪ Run and squeak and squawk
with the animals ♪
Good Lord!
Dr. Dolittle is Chief Wiggum.
This bird's going to fly.
(yells)
HOMER: It was one lousy
applicant after another.
And then...
MAN:
♪ Over in Killarney ♪
♪ So many years ago... ♪
-Such a voice.
-Who is that?
♪ Me mother sang
this song to me ♪
♪ In tones so soft and... ♪
-(burping)
-ALL: Barney!
♪ Just a little Irish ditty ♪
Barney! How'd you like
to sing for our group?
Sure. Why not?
Now, where's me toothpick?
♪ Too-ra loo-ra loo-ra ♪
♪ Too-ra loo-ra-li ♪
ALL (chanting):
Wiggum forever!
Barney never!
-(chuckles)
-Wiggum forever!
♪ Sweet Adeline ♪
♪ My Adeline ♪
(cheers and screams)
ALL (chanting):
Barney forever!
Wiggum never!
Hey, those girls you paid
to scream are doing a great job.
I didn't pay any girls
to scream.
Huh?
BARNEY:
My, did we sound great! Huh?
Only one question remains,
gentlemen.
What do we call ourselves?
How about...
"Handsome Homer Simpson
Plus Three"?
-I like it!
-Wait, I do not.
We need a name
that's witty at first
but that seems less funny
each time you hear it.
How about "The Be Sharps"?
(laughing)
Perfect.
The Be Sharps.
SKINNER:
ALL:
The Be Sharps.
WIGGUM:
Ha, ha, ha.
Heh, heh.
Well, you can't blame
a guy for trying.
Heh, heh... heh.
Aw, you're all
under arrest.
-What did you kids get?
-I bought this cool pencil holder.
(chuckles)
Far out, man.
I haven't seen a bong in years.
(chuckles)
No one bought
a wishbone necklace.
Well, one of us made some money.
I sold a guy our spare tire.
-(explosion)
-D-ohh!
-(bird screeches)
-It will be a long time
before your mother gets back
with the tire,
so why don't I tell you
more of the story?
Now that we had a name,
the Be Sharps needed a hit--
something new, something exciting,
something mid-1980s.
♪ There was nothing
in Al Capone's vault ♪
♪ But it wasn't
Geraldo's fault ♪
D-oh!
-Huh.
-Look what I got.
Now people will stop
intentionally ramming our car.
Hmm. "Baby on board."
♪ Baby on board ♪
♪ Something, something,
Burt Ward ♪
This thing writes itself.
♪ I'm telling you
it's mighty nice ♪
♪ Each trip's a trip
to paradise ♪
♪ With my ♪
♪ Baby ♪
♪ On board ♪
Gentlemen, you've just recorded
your first number one.
-Oh, yes!
-Yes!
Wait till I tell Marge.
Oh, yes.
Bouffant Betty.
Well, I would prefer we kept
your marriage a secret.
You see, a lot of women are going to
want to have sex with you,
and, uh, we want them
to think they can.
Well, if I explain it
to Marge that way,
I'm sure she'll understand.
(sobbing)
Come on, honey.
It will only be till
we finish our tour of Sweden.
(sobbing)
♪♪ (bass intro plays)
♪ Baby on board ♪
♪ How I adore ♪
♪ That sign
on my car's windowpane ♪
That's my boy Homer singing.
-Hmm. Paul Harvey's on.
-Oh!
HARVEY: And that little boy
whom nobody liked
grew up to be...
Roy Cohn.
BOTH: Wow!
And now you know
the rest of the story.
♪'Cause I'm driving ♪
♪ In the carpool lane ♪
Ah, Squiddy,
I got nothing against you.
I just heard there was gold
in your belly.
(laughing)
♪ With my baby ♪
♪ On board ♪
Homer, you're going
to be famous.
Yeah, but I'm not going
to let it change our lives.
I'll be the same loving father
I've always been.
-Hmm, have you seen Bart?
-I stuck him somewhere.
(clanging)
Look what I got
for you, Dad.
Oh, Hom-- Ah, ah... ah!
Give me the key.
(crowd screaming)
I have a question
for Apu De Beaumarchais.
Isn't it true that
you're really an Indian?
By the many arms of Vishnu,
I swear it is a lie.
Barney, how did you join
the group?
They found me
on the men's room floor.
(laughter)
-Principal Skinner.
-Mm-hmm.
You've been referred to
as "the funny one."
Is that reputation
justified?
Yes. Yes, it is.
-(laughter)
-(explosions)
-♪ Be-hi... ♪
-♪ Good-bye, my Coney Isle ♪
-♪ Be-ho... ♪
♪ Good-bye,
my Coney Island girl ♪
my Coney Island babe ♪
Damn ceremonies.
This is time
I could be working, Mommy.
We'd like to dedicate
this next number
to a very special woman.
She's a hundred years old
and she weighs over
200... tons.
This enormous woman
will devour us all!
(screaming)
I meant the statue.
Okay, Gilligan, the Skipper,
and Chief Wiggum.
"Name three castaways."
-Hey-oh!
-Ooh.
Clancy, use the remote.
Oh, yeah.
Uh! Can we talk
about Chief Wiggum?
Uh, uh, uh!
We had fame and fortune.
Now all we needed
was the approval
of record company lowlifes.
-(drum roll)
-And the Grammy for outstanding soul
spoken-word, or barbershop
album of the year
goes to...
The Be Sharps!
(cheering)
-Congratulations.
-David Crosby? You're my hero.
-Oh, you like my music?
-You're a musician?
HOMER: Then came the greatest
thrill of my life.
Hello, Homer.
I'm George Harrison.
Oh, my God!
Where did you get
that brownie?
Over there.
There's a big pile of them.
(laughs crazily)
Oh, man.
Wow, what a nice fellow.
Lisa, did you see the Grammys?
You beat
Dexy's Midnight Runners.
Well, you haven't heard
the last of them.
I miss you, Daddy.
I miss you, too, honey.
Oh...
Here's that champagne
you ordered, Mr. Simpson.
Oh, thanks.
Here.
Wow! An award statue!
Oh... it's a Grammy.
(clunk)
MAN: Hey, don't throw
your garbage down here.
Wow! Look at all this Be Sharps
merchandise.
Lunch boxes,
coffee mugs,
funny foam.
They took the foam off
the market,
because they found out
it was poisonous.
But if ask me,
if you're dumb enough to eat it,
you deserve to die.
-Bart!
-What?
I can't believe
you're not still popular.
What'd you do?
Screw up like the Beatles
and say you were
bigger than Jesus?
All the time. It was the title
of our second album.
But we were about to learn
an iron law of show business--
what goes up must come down.
What about Bob Hope?
He's been consistently popular
for over 50 years.
So is Sinatra.
Well, anyway, we were all
getting tired of--
Dean Martin still packs
them in.
-Ditto Tom Jones.
-Shut up!
With your father
on the road all the time,
I tried to compensate
for his absence.
Hi, kids.
I love...
(tape rewinds)
(both scream)
-(pop)
-(screaming)
HOMER:
Meanwhile, the group
was having problems
of its own.
♪ For all the latest ♪
♪ Medical poop ♪
♪ Call Surgeon General ♪
♪ C. Everett Koop ♪
♪ Poo, poo, pa-doop ♪
This is worse than
your song about Mr. T.
I pity the fool
who doesn't like he.
-And where's Barney?
-Oh, he's with his new girlfriend,
the Japanese
conceptual artist.
BARNEY: Barbershop is
in danger of growing stale.
I'm taking it
to strange, new places.
-GIRLFRIEND: Number eight.
-(Barney belches)
-Number eight.
Then came the day
we knew we were finished.
Gentlemen, this magazine
just came out
with its "What's hot
and what's not" issue.
-Are we hot?
-We are not.
HOMER: We all went
our separate ways.
Well, William,
I'm back.
So how did you
spend your summer?
I made millions in software
and lost it at the track, och!
It may not be glamorous,
but it's good, honest work.
-How much is this quart of milk?
-12 dollars.
Hey, Barney, what will it be?
I'd like a beer, Moe.
I'd like a single plum
floating in perfume,
served in a man's hat.
Here you go.
Hey, fellas,
I'm back.
Oh, that's great.
Your replacement
was getting tired.
(clucking)
Hey, Queeny, you can go now.
I'll give her a good home.
And I did.
I'll never forget
my five and a half weeks
-at the top.
-Man, that's some story.
But there are still
a few things I don't get.
Like, how come we never
heard about this until today?
Yeah, and what happened
to the money you made?
Why haven't you hung up
your gold records?
Since when could you
write a song?
There are perfectly good answers
to those questions,
but they'll have to wait
for another night.
Now off to bed.
I can't remember the last time
we were all together.
Last year on that stupid
Dame Edna special.
And a-one and a-two
and a-three.
♪ Ba-bom, bom, bom ♪
♪ Baby on board ♪
♪ How I've adored ♪
♪ That sign ♪
♪ On my car's ♪
♪ Windowpane ♪
Hello! Human fly here.
Come on! I stayed up all night
dyeing my underwear.
Extra, extra!
Be Sharps sing on rooftop!
What?
Give me one of those.
Wait a minute.
There's nothing in here
about the Be Sharps.
-Come back here!
-Ha-ha!
It's been done.
♪ That window sign can't ♪
♪ Be ignored ♪
Pretty, huh, Chief?
It sure is, Lou.
It sure is.
Get the tear gas.
♪ A trip to paradise ♪
♪ With my baby ♪
♪ On board ♪
(applause)
HOMER: I'd like to thank you
on behalf of the group,
and I hope we passed
the audition.
(laughter)
(Barney laughing)
BARNEY: I don't get it.
♪♪
Shh.
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.