(SINGING) The Simpsons
(TIRES SCREECHING)
D'oh!
(SCREAMS)
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
(ALL SCREAMING)
(GIANT FISH GULPS)
LISA AND JANEY: (SINGING)
Miss Lucy had a steamboat
The steamboat had a bell
Miss Lucy went to heaven
And the steamboat went to...
(GASPS)
Hell-o operator
(SIGHS)
Get me number nine
And if you disconnect me
I'll chop off your be...
(LOUD GASP)
...hind the 'frigerator...
Phew.
There was a piece of glass
Miss Lucy sat upon it
And it cut her big fat...
(GASPING)
Ask me no more questions
I'll tell you no more...
Ow!
Spitball!
I'm using your
unfinished novel.
LISA: Oh!
Mmm. (GRUNTING)
No. (GASPS)
(PANTING)
You're in big
trouble, mister!
I'm bleeding!
Huh, there's no
cut on your cheek.
Where'd the blood
come from?
Hey, I got a loose tooth!
Ew!
Gross!
I bet you can't twist it.
Of course I can twist it.
I'm great.
(BART SCREAMING)
This is my
last baby tooth.
That's the money tooth.
I heard the Tooth Fairy
pays triple for it.
Then let's hurry up
and rip it out of my head.
Skinner! Your bus driver
just totaled my Camry!
Can I offer you
the use of my Merkur?
Filled with your Burger
King cups and wrappers?
No, thank you.
(GRUNTS)
Lousy drawer.
Potato masher's stuck
in small spoon slot.
What kinda
madman would do that?
(GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS)
(GASPS)
Ooh. Bart!
Honey, I'm so sorry!
No problem.
Huh. No harm done.
HOMER:
I wouldn't say that.
Mmm-hmm.
God, please give your
daughter, the Tooth Fairy,
the strength
to carry my cash
and the integrity
not to dip her
wand in the till.
What the...
The Tooth Fairy
has made a donation
in my name to the United Way!
That gossamer witch!
Maybe when the Tooth Fairy saw
it was your last baby tooth,
she realized you're not
a little boy anymore.
So she gave you
a grownup gift.
I'm not gonna grow up!
(CHUCKLES)
Oh! Yes, you are.
Why in the right light,
you're starting to
get your own muzzle.
I thought it was
chocolate milk.
Yeah. That's how it starts.
No!
I'm still a kid.
And what do kids love?
Kid stuff, like this!
(GRUNTING)
Vroom-vroom, vroom,
vroom, vroom, vroom.
(MOANS)
Whatcha realizing,
jerk?
That I'm not a kid anymore.
That's harsh.
I knew I was an adult
the day the judge said,
"We're trying
you as an adult."
Well, there's one thing
no one can take away,
My childlike imagination.
Sergeant Activity,
your mission is
to scale the icy
walls of Mount Bloodkill.
Must defeat Doctor Blizzard
and the Avalanchoids.
(GRUNTS)
Lieutenant Adventure,
what are you doing here?
You're quite
the daredevil,
Sergeant Activity.
It's high time you
protected yourself
with supplemental
disability insurance.
At my age?
Can I qualify?
You'd be surprised.
If you're a non-smoker,
it can costjust
a few dollars a month.
What's happening to me?
Maybe I'm not a kid anymore.
Goodbye, Spirogram.
Goodbye, Sketch N Etch.
Goodbye,
Ravenous Ravenous Rhinos,
Duopoly, Parchoosey,
Humor Putty
and Sock 'Em
Knock 'Em Cyborgs.
Goodbye, childhood.
Dust in the wind
All we are is dust in the wind
Goodbye, friends.
OLD SEA CAPTAIN:
"So Eden sank to grief.
"So dawn goes down today.
Nothing gold can stay."
Yarr.
Hey, Sea Captain.
Giving your toys
a Viking funeral, eh?
I really don't
want to talk about it.
If you change your mind,
I won't be far.
Thanks, but...
I've been told
I'm a good listener.
But when you're a captain,
you never know when
people are just flattering ya.
Yarr.
He's gone.
Darn it!
I just want a friend
who isn't a work friend.
Bart, if you don't get up now,
good luck getting a pancake.
Dad's pulled his chair
right up to the stove.
Lise, I think I'm
having a midlife crisis.
If you're feeling
depressed, do what I do
and write something.
A novel, a play...
Or I could write
something that's not gay.
(GASPS)
Bart, someone wrote
something cynical
on your shirt!
Mmm-hmm.
Let me wash it off.
Leave me alone.
This expresses my
rage at the machine.
Well, I like
T-shirts with a nice joke
like, "Support our troops."
Bart's shirt is
a classic, Marge. Just
like "Keep on truckin'."
As if I would ever
want to stop truckin'.
Whoa!
(EXCITED CHATTER)
KID 1: Check it out!
KID 2: Whoa, look at that!
Ahh... l wish I had
that shirt.
It's clever, funny,
and would cover my
boy boobs nicely.
I'm too sexy for my shirt
Too sexy for my shirt
So sexy it hurts
And I'm too sexy for Milan
Too sexy for Milan
Bart, I need
that shirt.
I'll trade you
Puppy Goo Goo for it.
She still has a lot
of her original
strawberry scent.
Forget it. My attitude
isn't for sale.
What am I saying?
Of course it is.
T-shirts!
Get your sassy T-shirts!
50% cotton, 100% awesome!
Daddy, can I buy this one?
Let's see. "Get bent."
Well, the only thing
that could mean
is kneel down and pray.
We'll take the whole box.
"Get bent," everyone!
This could get me out
of a lot of sticky situations.
I'll take a dozen.
(CHUCKLES)
Do you have a T-shirt
with Calvin peeing on Hobbes?
Sorry.
Ah. Well, what do you
got him peeing on?
(SIREN BLARES)
Well, well, well.
Selling T-shirts
without a permit.
And it looks like
one of the lights
in your sneakers is out.
(CLANCY GRUNTS)
Come on, Chief. I can't
afford to pay protection
to you and Nelson.
Mmm-hmm.
Well, then you're
out of business, boy.
Let's go, boys.
Confiscate his merchandise.
Are any of those
my size?
Extra-extra-extra-extra-extra,
(IN HALES) extra-extra large?
Here you go, Chief.
"Proud Nubian Princess."
Score!
(MOANS)
It's no fair.
I just started and
I'm out of business.
Why don't you go legit
and sell your
shirts in stores?
But I'm just a kid.
You're a kid no
longer, Bart. You've
become a man.
Hey, you're right. lam.
And as an adult,
you'll be needing
comprehensive insurance.
I'll just leave
these brochures.
So how can I get
my shirts in stores?
I bet you could
find a distributor
at the Springfield
Novelty Expo.
That's right!
It's tomorrow!
Oh, my God.
It's a small retailer.
He could make or break us.
Mr. Retailer! Over here!
Your customers will love
these mood lollipops.
Every lick
reveals your mood.
It works. If blue is
the color for unimpressed.
T-shirts! Come order
my homemade T-shirts!
My mom thinks they're good!
Y'all ready for this?
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
Hey!
Hey, hey! Krusty Show T-shirts
are made for kids by kids!
And we pass
the "slavings" on to you!
(CHUCKLING)
We've got all your
favorite characters,
Itchy, Scratchy, Poochie,
Austin Powers Itchy,
Itchy Poochie,
Scratchbob Itchpants,
Confederate Itchy
and Osama Bin Scratchy.
(IMPRESSED MURMURS)
Thatsucked.
Well, at least I've
still got my health...
(GRUNTS)
(HONNNG)
Oh, my golly
graciousness! Bad car!
Apologize to
the poor little boy.
(SORROWFUL HONK)
(CHUCKLES)
This shirt is humor-larious.
Let's see what
else you've got.
Amazing,
trailblazing,
insightful,
Delightful,
hysterical, a miracle!
The kids'll go
cuckoo for these!
(CUCKOOS)
(CHUCKLES)
My name's Goose Gladwell.
Of Goose's Gags and Gifts?
That's right. I've got
20 stores in 30 states.
And I want to sell
your shirts in most of them.
You really think
my shirts will sell?
Absotively!
Here, take my card.
Sorry, that's my old number.
Let me give you the new one.
(CHUCKLES)
Darn. It's out of ink.
But my phone
number's on the pen!
Oh, but it's my
old phone number.
I'll call you.
I've been reading
this magazine for years.
But I never dreamed my son
would be on the cover. Hmm.
(CAR HONKING)
It's Goose!
What the...
Huh?
Hello, Simpsons.
ALL: Ooh.
You broke in!
We're big fans,
Mr. Gladwell.
Yeah. Nothing makes
parents happier
than when
an eccentric single man
takes an interest
in their child.
Bart, that's your share
of the T-shirt profits so far.
ALL: Ooh.
Look at all that cash!
And now it's time
for me to leave!
What a delightful sprite!
(SNORING)
Smithers! There seems
to be some sort
of communiqué on
that man's blouse.
I believe it says,
"Don't wake me,
I'm working."
Bolshevism! Sheer bolshevism!
Ripe for the quashing!
(GRUNTING)
You're suspended
without pay. Take your
clacking balls and go.
And on your way out,
remove all
the fillings you got
under our dental plan.
You know what, Mr. Burns?
I'm never coming back!
My son's making so much
cash in the T-shirt game
that I don't have
to work another
day in my life,
assuming my health does
not deteriorate as I age.
Good riddance
to bad blubber.
Smithers, want to go
get a cup of coffee?
I just had one, sir.
What the...
Why is everyone
so insolent today?
Well, today
is Christmas, sir.
I say when it's Christmas.
TELEVISION ANNOUNCER:
Too much change around
the house got you down?
Help me,
Ronco Change Magician!
ANNOUNCER: The Change
Magician will change
your life for the better.
(ANNOUNCER READING)
Order today.
(GASPS) Bart, can I ask you
an important question?
How much?
$29.99.
(SIGHS) Here's fifty.
Woo-hoo.
That's your donut
money, too, mister.
(MOANING)
Lenny, Carl, how
you doing?
Hey, Homer.
How's retirement?
It's awesome.
You know what
I've gotten into?
Sleeping till noon.
Yeah, well,
we better get going.
Some of us have
to get up for work tomorrow.
Hey, just because
I'm not working
doesn't mean I can't
gripe like you guys.
Don't you hate it
when people steal
your lunch out of
the break room fridge?
Actually, that stopped
after you left, Homer.
Yeah. Well, enjoy
the autumn of your
years, jerk!
Oh, I see what's going on!
You can't stand
to be around a guy
who's got total
financial independence.
Your bill, sir.
(EXCLAIMS)
No problem.
Bart, I need $200.
Dad, the bill's
only a hundred.
I broke some
bathroom fixtures.
Oh!
Pathetic.
I'm pathetic?
Because I take money
from my 10-year-old son?
Well, let me
tell you something!
I still call
the shots around here!
Homer, use your
inside voice.
I don't have
an inside voice!
DECLAN DESMOND:
The wild Serengeti.
Home of Africa's equivalent
to the mountain lion,
the regular lion.
These toothy Tarzan-munchers
have a rigid hierarchy
With a single alpha
male ruling the pride.
(ROARING)
(BIG LION-LIKE YAWN)
Until a younger,
more aggressive
lion challenges his power.
(WHIMPERS)
(GRUNTS)
Oh.
The couch is like that tree!
The displaced
male has two choices.
Either spend
the rest of his days among
The other
broken-down old lions...
All the good graves are taken.
Or find inclusion in
the tribe by caring
for vulnerable young cubs.
Hmm.
Lisa, basic cable said
I should nurture you.
Great! Will you play
Malibu Stacy with me?
Okay. You be the girl
and I'll be the car.
(HUMS) I'm going to
the organic market.
(MIMICS CAR ENGINE RUNNING)
Screw the market!
We're going to Mexico!
(LAUGHS)
LISA: Wheel
(BOTH LAUGHING)
HOMER: It's El Flanderito!
Run him down!
I can't run.
I'm wearing flip-flops!
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Hey, what's that dealie?
It's my entry
for the all-school
science fair.
It shows the history of
nuclear physics from
Marie Curie's laboratory
to a scale model
of the first nuclear reactor.
Oh, you'll win
for sure.
You and science go together
like Lenny and Carl.
The science is Carl.
MARTIN: Oh, Lisa!
I'd like to introduce you
to the next winner
of the science fair!
Behold, my project!
Childlike Humanoid
Urban Muchacho!
Or CHUM!
Don't hold my hand.
It's creepy.
Hush, my pet.
Now let us gather
our rosebuds while we may.
(SHUDDERS)
A robot?
Last year the winner was
a jar of owl pellets.
Oh, I don't have
a chance now.
Honey, all you need's
a little help from your dad.
Remember,
I did use to work
at a science factory.
Well, we're supposed to do
this without parental help.
Sweetie, that's orphan talk.
(GRUNTING)
Stupid atomic pile.
How hard could it be
to build a reactor?
Korea did it. And look
at the quality of
their animation.
Hmm.
What to do?
Hey, maybe the Internet
has the information I need.
It certainly answered
a lot of my questions
about wang enhancement.
www.nuclearsecrets.com
"Are you a terrorist?" No.
"Would you like to
meet someone special
"but are tired
of the bar scene?"
No! I will never
tire of the bar scene!
Let's see. I can make that.
You can get that
by smashing open a golf ball.
That you can find
in any player piano.
All I need is some plutonium.
And I know just
the place to get it!
(CHUCKLES) Mmm.
Dad?
Hub-bub-bub-bub-bub.
Don't look!
Dad, what did you do?
Sweetie,
your daddy's gonna show you
just how much he loves you.
You know that non-functioning
nuclear reactor you built?
Yes...
ljuiced it up a little.
(GIGGLES)
Dad, that could explode!
Oh, that's ridiculous.
(BEEPING)
KRUSTY:
That thing's gonna blow!
Drop this toy and run!
Mom! Dad built a device
that would be deadly
in the wrong hands!
And he's holding it!
Homer, I want you to get
that gamma-radiating
whatsit out of my home.
(WHINING) on...
(SNORTS)
I never complain
about your frilly pillows.
How many T-shirts
do you have here?
Just one.
It takes a Marine
honor guard to fold it.
It used to be a dust
cover for a Hummer.
I could go on and on.
Gravies and Lentilmen,
I have an exciting
announcement.
I have sold the rights
to the Bart Simpson
T-shirt line...
(GASPING)
...to the Disney Company,
which will turn
each one into a movie!
Really?
How much money do I get?
You get nothing.
In fact, thanks to my team
of loopy lawyers...
(CLEARS THROAT)
...I never have to
give you another penny.
All you get is
a very valuable lesson.
Never trust a weirdo!
Azoot!
I'm stuck on a nail!
(CHUCKUNG)
Oh, God, that's painful.
(GROANS)
I can't feel my...
(WHISTLE)
What's the matter, boy?
Goose Gladwell ripped me off.
And there's nothing
I can do about it.
I'm just a stupid kid!
(SOBBING)
Son, when you
grew up, I grew down.
Now I can see you need
your dad more than ever.
And Homer, I can see
you need me more than ever.
Get back in the
garage, old man.
But there's
spiders in the boxes.
Stay out of my boxes!
You give my son
what he deserves
or I'll knock you
on your delightfully
offbeat ass.
(CHUCKLES) Oh, I must
warn you, sir, I was a
Green Beret in Vietnam.
The things I saw there
are what made me crazy!
Sir, this is a class two
plutonium fissure reactor.
If I turn this dial,
the resulting
blast would destroy
the entire tri-city area,
Including that guy
who sells those
Blu-Blocker sunglasses
people sometimes wear.
Damn him to hell.
You can't be serious.
Are you prepared
to take that chance?
Okay, okay. Here's
all the money I've got.
Not so fast. I also want
some dribble glasses,
fake boobs,
two of Bart's T-shirts
and that rapping
toilet seat.
Yo, yo, yo
Keep it on the low flow
(CHUCKUNG)
I'm hanging this
over the mantle.
Thanks, Dad.
Well, I'm just glad
we're back to me
being the father
and you being the son.
Are you sure that thing
could really explode?
Oh, I doubt it.
But we'll let the seagulls
at the dump figure it out.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
There's more than one
way to lose a tooth.
Hey, idiot, you're fat.
And your mom's
naked on the Internet.
You also smell.
Hmm.
You've given me
a lot to think about.