♪ The Simpsons ♪
D'oh!
-Ahh!
-(tires screeching)
(Homer screaming)
Uh, why do they have
to put all this crud
in my newspaper?
"World," "The Arts,"
"Religion."
A-ha! Here it is.
"Kickin' Back!"
Hey, who cut something
out of my paper?
Not me.
Not me. I'm more
of a mail-tamperer.
Well, don't look at me,
just because I'm holding
a pair of scissors.
Scissors, which I need
to, uh, to...
gussy up these curtains.
(rings)
Hello.
Oh, hi, Lenny.
No, why would I need
a ride this afternoon?
(noisy vacuuming)
Where?!
To the big annual what?!
Lenny? Aw, well,
if it was big and annual
I'm sure they'd have
mentioned it in the newspaper.
(dog growling)
Yeah, it's a lazy,
dog-dangling afternoon.
But something's
a little off.
Hey, Marge, you don't smoke.
Well, I just felt
like filling the house
with the rich,
satisfying smell of tobacco.
(coughs)
(whistles)
You're nuts.
I got to get some fresh air.
-No, Homie, wait.
-What's wrong with you?
What are you trying
to hide from me?
(sniffing)
What's that smell?
Onions... chili powder...
cumin... juicy ground chuck!
It's chili! Oh, my God!
I'm missing the chili cook-off!
I'm missing the cook-off.
It's going on right now
and I'm missing it.
All right, I was trying
to keep it from you,
but I had a good reason.
Every time you go
to that cook-off
you get drunk
as a poet on payday.
Remember last year?
Look at me.
I'm a puffy pink cloud.
Yee-hee-hee-ha-ha!
Oh!
Oh, well, of course
everything looks bad
if you remember it.
Now, where are
my chili boots?
Ah!
(grunting)
Okay, we'll go
to the chili cook-off.
But I want you to promise me
you won't have any beer.
Okay, quit nagging me.
I won't have any beer.
Geez, why don't you have
a cigarette or something?
Mm, I suppose I could.
I'm gonna go get
some vegetarian chili
before they get desperate
and add meat.
I'm gonna go
claim some valuables
at the lost and found.
Ooh, look at that
adorable spice rack.
Eight spices?
Oh, some must be doubles.
"Oregano"?
What the hell...
Marge, we're
missing the chili.
Less artsy, more fartsy.
Homer, I happen
to like handicrafts
much more than
stuffing my face.
Fine. I'll come find you
when I'm ready
to stop having fun.
Remember your promise--
no drinking.
Stupor pooper.
♪♪ (country)
Howdy, howdy,
Marge and Hom--
Oh, my mistake.
Homer's not even with you.
Probably just knocking back
a few "refreshments."
Thank you for your
concern, Helen.
Homer isn't drinking today.
Oh, I think it's lovely
that he said that
and that you believed him.
Now, Helen, let us not glory
in Homer's binge-drinking.
There but for the grace of God
goes Marge herself.
Ooh, man, he's here--
The dude with
the fireproof stomach.
CROWD (gasping): Whoa!
Spoon! Spoon! Spoon!
They say he
carved it himself
from a bigger spoon.
Five-alarm chili, eh?
Mm-hmm.
One... two...
Hey, what's the big idea?
Oh, I admit it.
It's only two-alarm,
two-and-a-half, tops.
I just wanted to be a big man
in front of the kids.
Daddy, are you
going to jail?
We'll see, son.
We'll see.
Evenin', little lady.
Do you reckon a square
could get a dance?
Oh... it looks so complicated.
Do you know how?
Ma'am, I wouldn't honk the honk
if I couldn't tonk the tonk.
Woo-woo!
Hmm.
A bland, timid entry
suitable, perhaps, for patients
recovering from surgery.
WIGGUM: That Simpson,
he thinks he's
the pope of chili town.
Well, this year
I am ready for him.
HOMER: Hello, Chief.
Afternoon, Homer.
Care for some chili?
I've added an extra ingredient
just for you--
The merciless peppers
of Quetzlzacatenango!
(crowd gasps)
Grown deep
in the jungle primeval
by the inmates of
a Guatemalan insane asylum.
Uh, Wiggy?
My chili's getting cold.
(gasping)
(sizzling)
(screaming)
Hot! Hot! Hot! Hot!
D'oh!
Oh, my tongue is burning up!
Beer! Baby needs a beer!
Homer!
You promised you wouldn't drink.
But I need it!
Yeah.
Oh, lousy Wiggum.
Now the whole town
thinks I'm a chili wuss.
Wait, Mister.
You're drinking a candle.
You don't want to get wax
in your mouth, do you?
Maybe I do, son.
Maybe I do.
(gags)
Outstanding.
Hey, everybody,
look who's back.
It's the big baby!
Oh, this porridge is too hot.
Oh, waa-waa-waa!
(laughing)
Want some more, do you?
Well, sure.
Heck, it's not my job
to talk people out of
killing themselves.
Ah...
(gasps)
(murmuring)
More, please.
(gulping)
Good Lord,
this can't be happening.
By all medical logic
steam should be shooting
out of his ears.
His ears if we're lucky.
Well, Chief,
don't quit your day job--
(chuckles)
whatever that is.
(laughter, applause)
Heh-heh.
My finest hour...
and Marge wasn't
even here to see it.
(rumbling)
Ooh, I don't feel so good.
(groaning)
Flanders,
you've got to help me.
Sure, buddy.
I'd be happy to help out.
What can I do... diddly do...
diddily-doodily-diddily-hoobily-
hobbily-hibbily-gooble-gobble...
gooble gabba-gabba-hey?
(gasps)
Huh?
Goo-goo-ga-joob?
Haw! Haw!
Haw haw!
(waa-waa trumpet sound)
(distorted belch)
(screams)
Mister, do you
need some help?
Let him go, Ralph.
He knows what he's doing.
(wailing)
(panting)
What's happening to me?
Okay, retrace your steps.
Woke up,
fought with Marge,
ate Guatemalan
insanity peppers.
Then I-- Ohh.
Where am I? Shelbyville?
(screams)
Man, this is crazy.
I hope I didn't brain my damage.
I better check my pupils.
(hissing)
Oh... kay.
I think I'm gonna be
leaving now.
Huh?
Sunrise, sunset...
Sunrise, sunset,
sunrise, sunset,
sunrise, sunset, sunrise...
(screams)
Note to self:
Stop doing anything.
Has anyone seen Homer?
Marge, better
you hear it from me
than some gossipy neighbor.
Homer made a total
jackass of himself.
Oh, Helen, that's enough.
Call off your dogs.
But someone had
to tell her.
And I got here first.
-Helen, zip it.
-Oh please. Tim.
Zip it. Ziparoo.
No beer, huh?
(grumbling)
I guess I know what a promise
from Homer J. Simpson is worth.
Hey, buddy, get back there
with the other rocks.
Huh?
A tortoise?
"Follow... the..."
(gasps)
This must be why I'm here!
Follow the what?
Hurry up!
Get moving you stupid--
When I'm kicking you,
that means hurry up.
Come on.
Oh, you want me
to climb that, huh?
No problemo.
(rumbling)
Oh!
This is 'cause I kicked you,
isn't it?
(grunting)
Lis, check it out.
I saw it, Bart.
You're just mad
'cause there's
no clock in your hat.
What hat?
Ah, this baby's wasted
on an idiot like you.
Where's Homer?
Your father decided
that he'd rather come home
in a taxi... or a police car.
(grunting)
(gasping)
Marge, thank God
you're here.
Where's the car?
Marge? Marge?
Oh, now what?
If you're still mad at me,
I'm gonna be really mad.
Come on, Marge,
will you..?
Fight fair.
I never do this to you.
Talk to me!
(wind blowing)
Oh, I hate this place.
Why am I here?
VOICE: You are on
a quest for knowledge.
Who said that?
Fear not, Homer.
I am your spirit guide.
Hiya.
There is a lesson
you must learn.
If it's about laying off
the insanity peppers
I'm way ahead of you.
No, I speak of a deeper wisdom.
The problem, Homer,
is that the mind is
always chattering away
with a thousand thoughts
at once.
Yeah, that's me all right.
(wind blowing)
Clarity is the path
to inner peace.
Well, what should I do?
Should I meditate?
Should I get rid
of all my possessions?
Are you kidding?!
(chuckles)
If anything, you should
get more possessions.
You don't even have
a computer.
You know, I have been meaning
to take a spiritual journey
and I--
(growling)
Hey, knock it off!
Sorry.
I am a coyote.
Look, just give me
some inner peace
or I'll mop the floor
with you.
Good. Your mind is in
a state of readiness.
So listen well.
To make yourself complete,
you must find your soul mate.
Soul mate?
Your kindred spirit.
The one with whom you share
an unspoken bond,
a profound mystical
understanding.
That's it?
Well, that's Marge.
Big deal.
Great spiritual quest,
Wolfie.
My soul mate is Marge.
Is it?
Hey wait. Come back.
Oh.
(horn blowing)
Oh! A ghost train!
And so little time
to get out of the way.
Now less...
Now none!
(screams)
D'oh!
Hey, get off the course,
you bum!
Security.
(whistle blowing)
Wha-- Golf course?
Did I dream that whole thing?
Maybe the desert
was just a sand trap.
Oh, and I bet
that crazy pyramid
was just the Pro Shop.
And that talking coyote
was really just a talking dog.
Hi, Homer.
Find your soul mate.
Hey, wait a minute.
There's no such thing
as a talking dog.
(barking)
Damn straight.
So then I says to Mabel,
I says--
Hi, kids.
I'll finish this later.
Hi Dad.
-Where is your mother?
-Out back.
So anyway,
I says to Mabel, I says--
Hi, honey.
(singsongy)
Oh, I guess you're cranky
because I didn't
come home last night.
I'm "cranky" because
my husband got drunk
and humiliated me
in front of the entire town.
You broke
your promise, Homer.
Oh, honey,
I didn't get drunk.
I just went to a strange
fantasy world.
Come on, you got
to believe me.
You're my soul mate.
Don't "soul mate" me!
Okay.
(snoring)
That coyote said my soul mate
would understand me
but Marge doesn't understand me
at all.
Maybe we're not kindred spirits.
We don't have
anything in common.
Look at these records.
Jim Nabors, Glen Campbell,
The Doodletown Pipers.
Now look at her records.
They stink!
Oh. Maybe I had
that crazy dream for a reason.
Wherever my soul mate is,
it's not here.
I always just figured
my wife was my soul mate,
but if it's not Marge,
then who is it?
Where do I begin looking?
This really goes
beyond my training
as a furniture
salesman, sir.
Now, if you
don't want the sofa
I'll have to ask you
to leave.
Hey, Barney, soul mate,
let me buy you a beer.
Okay, but I'm not
your soul mate.
I'm really more
of a chum.
-What about you, Lenny?
-I'm a crony.
-Carl?
-I'd say acquaintance.
-Colleague.
-Sympathizer.
-Compadre.
-Associate.
Contemporary.
I'm a well-wisher
in that I don't wish you
any specific harm.
(sighs)
Hello? Is this, uh...
G.B.M.?
Uh, yeah.
I read in the personals
you were seeking a soul mate.
Well, I also like
rainy days and movies.
Uh-huh.
Uh... no...
I don't like that...
or that.
No, it's not that I'm afraid.
I'm gonna hang up now.
Bye-bye.
Oh... I give up.
COYOTE:
Find your soul mate, Homer.
Find your soul mate.
Where? Where?
This is just your memory.
I can't give you
any new information.
♪♪
♪ I learned the truth at 17 ♪
♪ That love was meant
for beauty queens ♪
♪ And high school girls ♪
♪ With clear-skin smiles ♪
♪ Who married young
and then retired ♪
♪ The valentines
I never knew ♪
♪ The Friday night
charades of you ♪
♪ Were spent on one
more beautiful... ♪
(sighs)
Huh?
What's that blinking light?
(gasps)
The lighthouse keeper.
The loneliest man in the world.
He'll understand me.
(panting)
Earl.
My new friend's name is Earl.
Here I come, buddy!
No more loneliness
for Homer and Earl.
A machine?
Earl's a machine?
Oh, that's just perfect.
Homer's desperate search
for a soul mate has yielded
a lighthouse-keeping robot.
Oh, wow.
Hey, look, is that Dad?
Either that or Batman's
really let himself go.
Alone.
Oh, I'm alone.
I'm a lonely,
insignificant speck
on a has-been planet orbited
by a cold, indifferent sun.
(horn blows)
A ship.
A ship with people.
I know.
I'll bring them to me.
And then they'll
have to be my friends.
Come here, people.
(laughing)
Arr, matey.
Nary a warning
light to be seen.
'Tis clear sailing ahead
for our precious cargo.
Uh... would that be
the hot pants, sir?
Aye, the hot pants.
(giggling)
Well, I won't be lonely
for long.
(giggling hysterically)
(footsteps approaching)
Huh? Who's there?
Oh, Homer, thank
goodness you're safe.
-Marge?
-I woke up,
and you weren't there,
and I was so worried.
Really? You were?
But how did you find me?
Well... I was sure
you'd be on foot
because you always say
public transportation
is for losers,
and I was sure you'd head west
because Springfield
slopes down that way,
and then I saw the lighthouse,
and I remembered
how you love blinking lights--
like the one on
the waffle iron.
Or that little guy on
the "don't walk" sign.
-Yeah.
-Wow, Marge,
you really
do understand me.
See, I thought we weren't
soul mates because--
We had a fight?
Right, and we don't like
the same things.
-It's like you're from Venus--
-And you're from Mars.
Oh sure, give me the one
with all the monsters.
Homer, don't you see?
Our differences are
only skin deep.
But our sames go
right down to the bone.
Maybe we do have--
A profound mystical
understanding?
Hey. We do!
Oh, Marge!
We're number one!
In your face, space coyote.
Space coyote?
-(horn blowing)
-Oh, my God!
-The ship!
-We'll all be killed!
The light.
We got to get
the light back on.
Jonathan Livingston
Seagull!
We're on
a collision course!
Hard a-starboard!
Uh, port?
Aye, port.
They see us.
They're starting
to turn.
We did it.
We sure did...
soul mate.
(moaning)
(metal scraping)
(clamoring)
(whistles)
Look at all them hot pants.
Hey, who likes short shorts?
ALL:
We like short shorts!
♪♪ (rock intro)
♪ Who wears short shorts? ♪
♪ We wear short shorts ♪
♪ They're such short shorts ♪
♪ We like short shorts ♪
♪ Who wears short shorts? ♪
♪ We wear short shorts ♪
(saxophone solo)
♪ Who wears short shorts... ♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.