CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
D'oh!
(tires screech)
(grunts)
(wails)
(spray paint hisses)
(Homer snoring)
(muttering)
(snoring)
Power's out.
Oh, your father must be
sleeping on his side again.
(snoring)
-(choking)
-From downtown!
And it counts!
(choking)
Think he's okay?
Eh...
(raspy)
Thank you.
Just drink some water,
you're all right.
Oh, yeah, you don't
want to go to the hospital
at 5:00 on a Friday.
Whoo-hoo!
Thank God it's TGIF!
MR. BURNS (over P.A.):
Attention, wage worms.
It's time for
afternoon announcements.
(jaunty swing music playing)
This Monday,
the plant will be conducting
physical examinations
of all employees.
And anyone testing positive
for narcotics
will be terminated
immediately!
Bad news, Lang-Soo.
Some casual Friday this is.
You're outta here, drug-o.
And don't forget,
federal law mandates
that we consider alcohol a drug.
(echoing thunderously)
D'oh...!
(twittering)
I told them to make
these track d'oh-proof!
(rumbling)
(yells)
(moans)
Homie!
You're home early!
Well, I didn't feel like
going to Moe's today.
Thought I might hang out here
for as long as I could take it.
Company physical coming up,
huh?
Yeah, but a weekend without
drinking is no big deal.
I did it when I was in
that alcohol-induced coma.
So, what's on the agenda?
Well, we're having brunch
with my sisters.
(moans)
You're hosting my
Preteen Braves meeting.
(moans louder)
And we're gonna make
dreamcatchers
-out of litter we pick up.
-(moans loudly)
You promised
to help me write a haiku.
Why did I do that?
It sounds so dull and boring.
What was I thinking?
-Thank you!
-Huh?!
And you and I
were going to study
the municipal voter's guide.
What the...?
Section 1 of Article 21
of the State Constitution
is amended to read: Section 1.
In the year following the year
in which the national census
is taken under
the direction of Congress
at the beginning of each decade,
the Legislature shall adjust
the boundary lines
of Congressional, State Senate
and Assembly districts--
(wailing)
Liquor,
mustn't think of liquor...
GRAMPA'S VOICE: Hey, there!
What's cookin'?
Come on, boy, crack my seal
and drink your father.
(screaming)
Owwww!
(stammering)
Wait a minute--
that feels good.
Mm!
So, a sober weekend
hasn't been that hard.
Let me just take a few
antidepressants here.
(gulping)
I feel sorry for people
without willpower.
I truly do.
Homie,
what are you drinking?
A surprisingly not-horrible
fruit drink called a mimosa.
There's champagne in those!
(shrieks)
Then there's champagne in me!
Oh, what am I gonna do?
It's less than 24 hours
till my drug test!
Maybe I can sweat it out.
(grunting, panting)
Oh, man, I'd better have
some coffee and iced tea.
No!
Irish and Long Island!
What about this lemonade?
Mike's Hard!
Then I better soak up
the alcohol with some food!
-Whoo! Cake!
-Rum cake!
-Crepes!
-Suzette!
Cherries!
Whoo! Jubilee!
(brunchers gasping in awe)
(applause)
(bird squawks)
Wow,
passed with flying colors!
I've sure earned this!
O, Lord,
I have once again besotted
my liver with
Thy fermented gifts.
If You can weasel me out
of this physical,
I will blow Your mind
by doing something
incredibly holy,
at some point. Amen.
Now to mumble
in a religious fashion.
Dear God, O, Lord,
O, God, O, Lord...
O, Lord, O, God,
O, Lord Almighty.
(jabbering, muttering)
Hm...
your cells have been
overexposed to gamma radiation.
Like the Hulk?
Well,
sort of like the Hulk.
But instead of getting powerful,
you're going to get
very, very sick.
(moans)
Hulk smash...
Yes, Hulk smash.
(chuckles)
Mr. Burns, you are liable
for thousands
of dollars per employee,
not to mention
my extensive fees which...
(screams)
This trapdoor app
works like a charm.
Excellent.
LAWYER:
You'll still have to pay!
(sighs)
This is the last time
I pay the price
for the irritating mortality
of the human worker.
Smithers,
it's time to re-staff with
the super-intelligent
kangaroos we've been breeding!
I'm sorry, sir, but they
just filled their pouches
with office supplies
and hopped away.
Even the joeys?
You know, sir, there is
a more high-tech solution.
More high-tech
than kangaroos?
Ladies and gentlemen,
meet the future masters
of the human race.
(Night on Bald Mountain playing)
(shrieks)
Comicon nerds!
You fool!
These are robots!
You will train them
and they will replace you.
I give you permission to shake
your fists in anger twice.
(employees growl twice)
I didn't say, Monty Says.
Now I have cause
to terminate.
-(angry muttering)
-LENNY: This is crap.
-Now get out.
-You didn't say Monty Says.
This is no game!
Excellent.
Sir, I'm afraid we do need
to keep one human worker--
to sign for packages,
a scapegoat for meltdowns,
things that would be
a waste of the robots' time.
(groans) So we need one
meat sock on the payroll.
-But who?
-Mr. Burns, before I leave,
I got a few things
to get off my chest.
One, I like the new microwave
in the break room.
Just push "popcorn," you don't
have to know how long.
Two, replacing us with robots
is heartless and despicable.
Three, how about a farewell
party with a caricature artist?
You know, it's something both
kids and adults can enjoy.
So, to sum up:
nicely done,
we hate you,
and food for thought.
Simpson, wait!
As it turns out,
there is one job available.
But be forewarned,
it promises naught
but soul-crushing boredom.
Does the chair go back
like this?
-Yes.
-Whoo-hoo!
(groans)
Well, looks like
we've found this plant's
one remaining worker
of bone and sinew.
(chuckles) Sir, I believe there
are two, including yours truly.
It's one, excluding
mine falsely!
Well, surely no robot
can replace me.
Oh!
Mmm!
(whirring)
I can do that.
(imitates whirring)
What about this?
(jaunty 1920s music playing)
(groans)
(tires screeching)
(scoffs)
Nice parking, idiot.
So, uh, you guys
are my new coworkers.
So, workin' hard
or hardly workin'?
(chuckles)
I said, workin' hard
or hardly workin'?
Workin' hard
or hardly working?!
Working hard or
hardly working?!
It's a simple question!
Are you A) working hard
or B)-- Ow!
(giddy laughter)
I guess I just met
the joker of the group.
Better watch out for you
on April Fool's, am I right?
I said, am I right?
Am I... (yells)
So, you guys have any luck
finding a new job?
Does it look like
I've got a job?
No, I didn't.
Homer,
show a little more sensitivity
around these
jobless washouts, eh?
Hey, I gotta tell ya,
I'm miserable there.
I'm all alone,
and when there's some problem
due to human error,
guess who gets blamed?
Hey, Homer, you know what
I'm playing for ya?
The world's smallest violin.
And now I got to sell it,
just to make my rent!
Oh, my God!
Where's the bow?
I can't sell it
without the bow!
Easy, easy there, Lenny.
You can always
play it pizzicato.
The buyer clearly specified
violin and bow!
(Lenny crying)
Um, maybe I should be
heading home.
-(crunch)
-Oh, no!
He stepped on the bow!
Boy, this place
has gotten so grim.
I'm gonna do something
I've never done:
Make myself a drink.
Ugh!
You call this beer?
It's watered-down swill!
Oh, you got a problem?
Well, here's
the complaint department.
MOE: You know what I think, Moe?
I think you ain't got the guts!
-(gun fires)
-Ha! Missed, ya son-of-a...
♪ When the moon hits your eye ♪
♪ Like a big pizza pie ♪
♪ That's amore ♪
♪ When the world seems... ♪
(moans)
When you do chair gondola
all by yourself,
it almost seems stupid.
(moans)
(grunts)
(gulps)
Ah, here it is--
Hydraulic systems flush...
EEPROM bios auto boot ...
conversation mode?!
They can talk?!
I just have to press
this button, right...
Well, at least it
doesn't feel pain.
Wait a minute...
D'oh!
"Override self-destruct protocol
with authorization code
7... 2... 2... 5."
Human interaction mode
activated.
Initiate conversation.
Will you be my friend?
Friendship cannot exist
between man and machine.
But I can simulate
interest in your statements.
(gasps)
You're not a friend...
you're my best friend.
Uh, just don't ask me
to drive you to the airport.
It's no fun to live in a town
with a 99% unemployment rate.
Things are so bad.
Look at what happened
to the man on my pizza box.
Mr. Burns seemed
like such a nice man
the day he arrived.
(marching band playing brightly)
(elephant trumpeting)
Cheap power, plentiful jobs,
and all your swimming holes
shall be warm and bubbling.
Can I pet the elephant?
(laughs)
Of course.
(coos happily)
(screams)
(wailing)
(groans)
Guess I'll just have to become
beautiful on the inside.
MARGE:
Which he didn't.
I ain't paying!
Two of my shortbreads
were broken!
Hey, check it out!
Lenny's hit a new low!
I don't want my window washed!
Too late!
I don't want
my squeegee wiped!
I got what I needed.
That's it, boy.
Live one more day.
Good morning, class.
I'm your substitute teacher...
All right, who did that?
(coughs)
Fine. We will not be reading
Death in Venice today.
(collective groan)
Someone's in a mood.
Barney?
Hey, if we learned anything
from The Full Monty,
it's that in a tough economy,
ugly people strip for money.
Do a lot of people pay?
No, but I can also play
three-card full Monty.
Follow the hats,
where's the wiener?
Follow the hats, where's
the wiener?
Now you see it,
now you don't.
So, Bart, the little dickens,
is going through that phase
where young boys
think their dad's an idiot.
Sounds like you are having
family difficulties.
That's exactly what I'm having!
You guys totally get me.
We are programmed to respond
to your verbal prompts.
Could you give my
wife a few lessons?
-(chuckles)
-Hmm.
Your laughter indicates you do not
wish us to give your wife lessons.
(laughing)
Yeah.
So, uh, it's 5:00.
Time for Moe's.
My watch says 3:00.
-4:00... 5:00.
-Let's go.
Automated workers
are not able to leave the plant.
What happened to you guys?
You used to be cool.
We are the same temperature
we have always been.
(mocking) "We're the same
temperature we've always been."
Our programming
restricts our movement
to yellow guidance lines.
Hmm...
Play ball!
(grunting)
Okay, I'm up again.
According to the on-line rules
of baseball,
all players get a turn "at bat."
Uh, right, right.
Uh, actually,
I'm the designated hitter
for all you guys.
The designated hitter
corrupts the purity
of an otherwise elegant game...
Illogical, illogical.
Fine. Don't get your
circuits in a bunch.
Circuit-bunching has
yielded important advances
in modern robotics.
To wit...
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
Hey, Dad, can we play?
We cannot take
the inferior one.
My heart makes up
for my shortcomings, like Rudy.
Rudy was only put in at the end
of a meaningless game.
We will notify you
if this game
becomes meaningless.
I got it!
I said I've got it!
That could've been
my motherboard
lying in the street!
Our primary directive...
is to preserve human life.
And here I was
waiting till you slept
to rob you of your copper.
You know, it's crazy, but...
Homer, move away from me.
You are still in the road.
Hush, bionic prince,
as I cradle your waning form.
Such a peaceful end.
(high-pitched
electronic screams)
Oh, geez!
-(horn honking)
-Get out of the road!
-(horn honks)
-Hey!
(horn blares)
-(horn honks)
-You stupid jerk!
-(horn beeping)
-(man shouts angrily)
(Lisa plays slow,
melancholy blues melody)
Axles to axles,
rust to rust, amen.
-Amen.
Dearly beloved, we are not here
to mourn their deactivation,
but to celebrate
their period of function.
Can I hollow out this one's head
and use it as a turtle tank?
No! I'm already using
it to put my keys in.
Now, let me
raise this beer to toast...
(shrieks)
What the...?
Alcohol is harmful to humans.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
save your breath.
We have no breath.
We do vent nitrogen
once a year.
You do not want
to be around for that.
D'oh! I have some
adjustments to make.
Homer...
when am I getting
my power drill back?
When I'm done
with my robo-botomies.
Primary directive deactivated.
Our new primary directive
becomes removing
all impediments to the plant.
Uh, Homer, I'm afraid this is the part
of God's perfect plan
where you're
murdered by robots.
Flanders,
I don't judge a robot
by the color of their eyes,
I look at their hands...
which have turned
into buzz saws.
(screams)
Son of a...!
Why did you do that?
(muttering)
ROBOTS:
Eliminate impediment. Eliminate...
Just say "kill me," jerks!
ROBOTS:
Kill him. Kill him.
Dad, they can only go
three miles an hour!
I'm doomed!
Can they climb stairs?
With great difficulty.
I'm doomed!
(knocking on door)
(panting)
Robots... trying to kill me.
And now they'll kill you,
'cause I led them here!
Now see here!
You are so not
the heartless automatons
I was looking for.
There's one thing man has
that machines can never match:
hounds!
(snarling)
(yelps)
(all whining)
Fine, slink away.
And guess what?
All those times I said
"you're a good boy,"
it was a lie!
(growling, barking)
No, stop!
I'll give you the combination
to the num-num safe!
(growling)
Flee, you fool!
Aren't we getting num-nums?
(shuddering)
(dogs barking)
Ah. The solarium.
We'll be safely cornered
in this glass room
with one door.
(grunts)
Stop brandishing me.
Sorry.
Before we die,
can you tell me
how old you really are?
-Well, it has four digits...
-(crash)
Unemployed Springfielders
to the rescue!
And underemployed.
To servos with love.
Guys, thank you.
The words "prime directive"
get thrown around
a lot these days,
but I'm glad yours
was saving me.
The saddest part is:
none of this had to happen.
If Mr. Burns
had simply trusted
the human worker.
Or if someone,
anyone, had told me
that robots were
incapable of human feelings.
I told you precisely
that fact 1,562...
(laughs)
And his arm
can be my back-scratcher.
(electricity buzzes,
Homer screams)
Well, I've learned
the robotic worker is no match
for the old-fashioned
man of labor.
You're all hired back...
as temps.
(workers cheering)
ROBOT: Homer, why have you
reprogrammed me for this?
I'm giving you your wish:
to be a real boy.
I am real
and I do not have wishes.
Then take us out to sea!
I am not a transformer.
I cannot turn into
an outboard motor.
Oh, I believe you,
but Flanders' drill doesn't.
(imitates motor revving)
Ah, this is the life.
Hey.
(gentle intro playing)
♪ There's electric cars,
there's electric trains ♪
♪ Here comes a robot
with electric brains ♪
♪ Robot parade, robot parade ♪
♪ Wave the flags
that the robots made ♪
♪ Robot parade, robot parade ♪
♪ Robots obey
what the children say ♪
-(crowd murmuring)
-Shh!
Subtitled by A. Vandelay