(SINGING) The Simpsons
(TIRES SCREECHING)
D'oh!
(EXCLAIMING)
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
(ORGAN MUSIC PLAYING)
(LAUGHING EVILLY)
Some sucker will
think he's getting beer,
but he's really gonna get
a face full of melon!
Seedless melon!
(LAUGHING)
Shh. Don't ruin the moment.
Oh, boy, free beer!
Oh, man.
(CHUCKLES)
Easy, Barney. Easy.
Remember the 12 Steps.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6,
7, 8, 9, 10,11,12.
(GRUNTS)
Nice try, boys.
Now, as the Road Runner
said to the Coyote,
"Meep meep!"
(MOANS) Everyone in
town is wise to us.
We need someone
new we can prank.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(GRUNTS)
(TRUCK RECEDING)
(CHUCKLING EVILLY)
Sweet. Fresh meat.
Meat's not sweet.
It's savory.
Hi, bean sprouts.
The name's Howell Huser.
I travel the country
Gawking and talking, and I was
hoping to take in your town.
We can show you around
if you don't mind a heaping
helping of local color.
Why my favorite
color is local.
Ooh! Watermelon!
Want to plant the seeds?
It's seedless.
(GROANS)
(GASPS)
HOWELL: Radioactivity?
That means it's a place
where we do radio activities.
(LET'S TWIST AGAIN PLAYiNG)
(LAUGHING) I'm happy
to be exposed to that
kind of radioactivity.
(LAUGHING)
You know, the fish here
are so friendly, you can
walk right up and feed them.
Hmm. (CHUCKLES)
Well, howdy, little feller.
(GROWLS)
OW! Oh! OW! Oh!
I can't wait
till this is over! Ow!
(BOTH LAUGHING)
I was thinking maybe we could
visit the hospital now?
Perhaps a stick of gum
will lighten your mood.
It always has in the past.
Ow!
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Finger pain?
I thought I had gum coming!
That tears it! (GROANS)
I've been smiling
for 47 years, and you
two broke my streak!
Shame on you,
and shame on you.
And shame on your whole
ill-mannered town!
Hey, that guy's shaming us.
My self-esteem
sure didn't need that!
(ALL GRUNTING)
Ow!
JIMBO: Loser!
(BOYS GRUNTING)
DOLPH: Yeah, get out, shamey.
(CHUCKLES)
I don't think we'll be
hearing from him again.
So, Kitchen Wizard,
I understand you
have a book coming out.
Yes, it's about
Winston Churchill's
life between the wars.
Up next on
the Soft News Network,
let's hear from
our own wide-eyed
wanderer, Howell Huser.
Uh-oh.
I've ambled and rambled
across this country
and never found
a town I didn't like,
till now,
and the name of that
town is Springfield.
(GASPING)
I was attacked, humiliated,
and fed misleading gum.
I give Springfield the lowest
rating I've ever given a city,
a six out of 10.
(CLATTERING)
I hope this bad publicity
doesn't affect tourism.
Eh, who needs tourists?
They never buy my maps
to stars' homes anyway.
HOMER: Have you read
them all? Okay, good.
(DOG HOWLING)
We need to bring tourism
back to Springfield.
As usual, I will open
the floor to all crazy ideas
that jump to people's minds.
Stronger beer!
Gladiator fights!
Poetry slam!
Giant rats!
H...
I have a real suggestion.
Yarr.
Why don't we legalize
same-sex marriage?
We can attract
a growing segment
of the marriage market
And strike a blow
for civil rights.
Yeah, them gay guys got
lots of disposable income.
I can serve fancy drinks
and charge 10 bucks a pop.
What's in a martini?
Gin and vermouth.
And that makes a what?
A martini.
Never heard of it,
but I'm still in favor of
that same-sex marriage deal.
Then it's settled.
We'll legalize gay money...
I mean, gay marriage.
(ALL CHEERING)
I propose we also
legalize gay funerals,
starting with this guy.
I'm not gay.
I'm nothing yet!
Okay, now let's say I put
a Lean Cuisine in a blender
and I pour some beer on it.
What do you call that?
A lean cuisini?
Wrong.
(SINGING) When my man and I
shop for wedding gowns
We were mocked and shunned
and pushed around
But yesterday,
we found a place to be gay
I'm going to marry my Harry
in Springfield town
Gay-o, it's okay-o
Tie the knot and spend
all your dough
Gay-o, come stay-o
Visit our web site
for further info
Springfield, a place where
everyone can marry.
Even dudes.
We're just off Route 202.
Do not take
the Jefferson Avenue exit.
For God's sake,
do not take that exit.
(ALL CHATTERING)
While I have no opinion
for or against your
sinful lifestyles,
I cannot marry two
people of the same sex
any more than I
can put a hamburger
on a hot dog bun.
Now, go back to working
behind the scenes in every
facet of entertainment.
Excuse me, Reverend.
Yes?
As long as two people
love each other,
I don't think God cares
whether they both have
the same hoo-hoo or ha-ha.
Ha-ha!
The Bible forbids
same-sex relations.
Which book?
Which book? The Bible!
But, Reverend,
(CHURCH BELL TOLLING)
scriptural scholars disagree
on the significance
of depictions of marriage in
Old Testament's descriptions.
Jesus' teachings stress
inclusiveness and compassion.
(BELL CONTINUES TOLLING)
Lovejoy's an idiot.
His church is giving up
hot gobs of gay green.
He could get
200 bucks a couple.
200 bucks a couple, eh?
Hey, I got to get in on this!
These people have rights!
The right to buy
me a 62-inch TV!
(GRUNTS)
(CHUCKLES)
HOMER: Now begins the long
and spiritual journey to
becoming an ordained minister.
"Name?
Homer Simpson.
MALE VOICE: You are now
an ordained minister.
(CHURCH MUSIC PLAYING
ON COMPUTER)
Now to answer all the pop-ups.
Ooh! A talking moose wants
my credit card number.
That's only fair.
(STRAINING)
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
And do you, Julio,
take Thad to be your
lawful wedded life partner
in Massachusetts and Vermont,
maybe Canada,
stay out of Texas,
as long as you both are gay?
I do.
It brings me greatjoy to
unite two such loving people.
Photo mouse pads
for sale out back.
(SHUTTER CLICKING)
Okay, what's next,
Adam and Steve
or Madam and Eve?
Homie, you married
every gay couple in town.
Eh, what can I say?
I love love.
Well, all you can do
now is wait for some
other guys to turn.
Hmm, where's Lenny and Carl?
Don't you push them!
They've got to work
that out for themselves.
Oh. But I'm only
$200 short of $14,800!
Well, what about people
of the opposite sex who
want to get married?
Opposite? Yuck.
I mean a man and a woman.
Hmm. Well, maybe marriage
isn't just for gays.
What's that thing called when
a guy is gay for a girl?
Straight.
(CHUCKLES) Look at me!
I'm as straight as a $1 bill.
La-dee-da! Ooh!
(PIG OINKING)
Do you, Cletus,
take Brandine to be...
Wait a minute.
Are you two
brother and sister?
We's all kind of things!
Hmm.
A new epidemic is
raging through Springfield,
and this one didn't start
with Krustyburgeﬂs
Whatchamacarcass Sandwich.
I'm talking about
an outbreak of marriage fever.
Reverend Simpson...
Please, Kent,
call me Your Holiness.
(CHUCKLES)
I can't. I just can't.
Homer, have we started
down a slippery slope,
where marriage becomes
so meaningless that anyone
could marry anything?
Oh, Kent, not anything.
It has to exist.
Or does it?
Well, call me old-fashioned,
but I believe that marriage
described in the Bible...
If you love the Bible so much,
why don't you marry it?
In fact,
I now pronounce you and
the Bible man and wife.
And you're the wife!
(CHUCKLING)
Hey, you owe me 200 bucks.
Homer, your impulsive
marriages are gonna
lead to a lot of divorces.
Which will lead
to a lot more
impulsive marriages,
which will put more
green in the blue.
The blue being my pants.
I'm sorry, Homer,
but I'm gonna have to
leave you hanging there.
KRUSTY: If I may say a word?
Why, we're joined live now
by Krusty the Clown. Krusty?
I want to clear up
a misconception about
the Whatchamacarcass Sandwich.
I used non-diseased meat
from diseased animals.
Everyone does it.
(CHUCKLES)
(GROANS)
Oh, Homie,
I'm so proud of you.
You stood up for
people's right to express
love in its most perfect form,
a binding legal contract.
(DOORBELL RINGING)
Hey, saturated fats,
I came to ask you a favor.
Let me get my belt sander.
Maybe I can grind
the ugly off your face.
Very funny.
I wasn't joking.
(WHIRRING)
I'm getting married,
and I need you to
perform the ceremony.
(GASPS)
You're getting married?
Patty, that's wonderful!
So, tell, tell,
who's the lucky man?
What does he do? (GASPS)
Let me guess. Mmm. Does he
work in customer support?
You can guess all
night and never get it.
(INHALING DEEPLY)
Her name's Veronica.
But Veronica's a girl's name.
Did you know that?
I'm marrying a woman.
I'm... I'm gay.
(GASPS SOFTLY)
You're not disappointed,
are you?
Oh, no. No, no.
No, I'm just surprised.
(LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
Yeah, big surprise.
Hey, Marge,
here's another bomb.
I like beer.
(LAUGHING)
So, Patty, you're a woman
who likes women.
I guess that fear I always
had of you stealing Homer
away is unfounded.
(BOTH SPITTING)
Marge, I'd be a lot
more worried about me
leaving you
for a sausage patty
than your sister, Patty.
(LAUGHS)
(SCREAMS)
Next time it'll be your eye.
Marge, did you really
think I was straight?
Well, I guess I should
have seen the signs.
(QUE SERA SERA PLAYING)
Que Sera, Sera
Whatever will be, will be
The future's not ours to see
Que Sera, Sera
What Will be, Will be
You could see it
from space, Marge. This isn't
a problem for you, is it?
Oh, no. No, no.
Why would it be?
(LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
I love you,
I love gay marriage,
so I'd be a super-hypocrite
if I didn't love your
gay marriage, right?
Now, Patty, here's a veil
I picked out just for you.
Mmm.
(SNIFFS)
Smells like cheeseburgers.
Give it back! (SNIFFS)
(SIGHS)
Why are we dressed as
"Sunday Best Simpsons"
for dinner with Aunt Patty?
Because she's bringing over
someone very special.
(SIGHS) Her fiancée.
Is this one of
those reality deals
where a guy gets
a million bucks
for marrying Aunt Patty,
but they have to honeymoon
in a box full of snakes?
Son, that's the stupidest
idea I ever heard.
And I know exactly
who would pay
top dollar for it.
(DIALING)
FEMALE VOICE:
You've reached Fox.
If you're pitching a show
where gold-digging skanks
get what's coming
to them, press one.
If you're pitching a rip-off
of another network's
reality show, press two.
Please stay on the line.
Your half-baked ideas
are all we've got.
Actually,
your aunt is marrying
a very lucky woman.
I thought you said
Aunt Patty was just
waiting for the right man.
As opposed to you,
who grabbed the first
blimp that floated by.
Correction.
The first blimp
who got her pregnant.
Seriously, Dad,
I'm worried.
You should go on a diet.
Why, you little...
(CHOKING)
(DOORBELL RINGING)
Save my place.
LISA: Why you little...
(BART CHOKING)
This is my fiancée,
Veronica.
It's a pleasure
to meet you all.
So, Veronica,
what do you do?
I'm a pro golfer.
No surprises there.
Aunt Patty,
where did you two meet?
Alternative book store?
Ethiopian restaurant?
It was so romantic,
like a scene from
a Hollywood movie.
Yeah, Bride of the Monster.
(PATTY GRUNTS)
(SCREAMING)
I was at the LPGA Ritz Bits
celebrity Pro-Am.
Lady golfers?
I thought we played
this stupid game to get
away from the women.
With the yack-yack-yack
and the spend-spend-spend,
am I right?
ALL: Boo!
Hey, clown. Watch out
for this lady driver.
Huh?
(GRUNTS)
(THUDDING)
Are you all right?
Never better.
(COUGHING)
I'll bet that's
how angels cough.
I've been wearing
that 3-wood ever since.
Whoa, save something
for your wedding night.
Oh, we're saving everything
for our wedding night.
Mmm-hmm.
That's what Mom would want.
I don't think it's exactly
what Mom would want.
Marge, are you sure
you're okay with this?
Of course. Everyone should do
whatever they want.
Take a bear to church.
Read a book with your feet.
Change your name
to Gooble-Glop!
Oh, I get it.
You act all liberal,
but you can't handle it
when your sister finds
love in her own locker room.
Marge, if you can
find it in your heart
to accept me for who I am,
I would love to see
you at the ceremony.
If not, I'll see you
at Homer's funeral.
(BUZZING)
(GRUNTS)
(GIGGLES)
Which should be pretty soon.
HOMER: (GRUNTS)
Got him! Uh-oh.
What am I not
invited to this time?
Gay wedding,
but I can get you in.
You can?
ls there an open bar?
No, cash.
Well, I say this whole
thing is against nature.
So, want to do
a jigsaw puzzle tonight?
Selma, I'm getting
married in an hour.
I know, I know.
I'm just having trouble
getting used to
the idea of being alone.
Don't lay that on me.
You got married three times.
Actually, four.
You see, last week...
Disco Stu just
got an annulment
from John Paul ll.
Boogie down!
Selma, we'll always
be there for each other.
I don't know
about Marge, though.
If she doesn't show up today,
I have no
non-identical sister.
Mmm-hmm.
Oh, Lord, please help me
say the right words
this afternoon,
as I consecrate
another gay union
that angers you so.
And please let
thy holy spirit open
the heart of my wife. Amen.
I just can't believe
my sister would keep me
in the dark all these years,
then expect complete
acceptance on the day
she gets married.
(WOLF WHISTLE)
You handsome devil.
Someday they'll let
you and me get married.
Can you imagine the children?
(CHILDREN CHATTERING)
(MOANING)
I love you, Homer.
I love you, too, Homer.
(BOTH MOANING)
Oh, Homer.
(GASPS)
(TOILET FLUSHES)
The toilet seat's up.
But that wouldn't
happen unless...
(SINGING)
Yeah, dude looks like a lady
Dude looks like a lady
(GASPS) She's a man.
(CHUCKLES) Looks like
Patty's gonna get something
she didn't register for.
(HUMMING WEDDING MARCH)
(WEDDING MARCH PLAYING)
Queerly beloved,
we're here to join Veronica
and Patty in matrimony.
But the news isn't all good.
They've written
their own vows. Patty?
Veronica, in you
I have found a soul mate.
You are the perfect
woman for me,
Truthful, honest,
hiding nothing.
At last I have
found the yin to my yin.
(GROANS)
If anyone knows
a reason why these two
should not be joined,
let them speak now
or forever hold their peace.
No! I can't let this happen!
I knew it!
You think everyone
in the world should have
a big dumb man like you!
People, please,
can we wrap this up?
It's gonna rain
and I got to get
the bikes in here.
Patty,
it's not what you think.
Veronica is a man!
(GULPS)
(ALL GASPING)
Look at the size of
that Adam's apple!
Veronica, how could you?
Patty, I love you,
but long before we met,
I disguised myself as a woman
and lied my way
onto the LPGA tour.
I can see why you
lied to other golfers,
caddies, fans and officials,
but how could you lie to me
and the sponsors?
Because you fell
in love with me
as a woman,
and I didn't want
to lose you.
But now I'm asking you,
not as Veronica,
but as the man I am,
Leslie Robin Swisher.
Patty, will you
marry the real me?
(GROANS)
Hell, no, I like girls!
(GASPS)
(ALL APPLAUDING)
Marge, thank you
for accepting me
for who I am.
Well, I learned a lesson.
Just because you're
a lesbian, it doesn't
make you less of a being.
Patty, I admire your decision.
It takes courage
to follow your heart
and walk out on
a non-refundable
wedding ceremony.
So, I'm gonna waive
the rose petal removal fee
and prorate the
cake-handling surcharge.
(SCOFFS) Thanks. Yeah.
Well, that's the end
of Dad's wedding business.
Why?
Hey, twisted sister,
you still have
that jigsaw puzzle?
Oh, there never was
a jigsaw puzzle.
I was trying to
make you jealous.
Hey, want to go to the airport
and leave a bag unattended?
It is a good way to meet
security personnel.
Let's go!
(BOTH GRUNTING INDISTINCTLY)
(TIGER GROWLING)
(SPRAYING)
Next.
Hurry, before she
changes her mind.