♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
-(screams)
-(tires screeching)
(bird cawing)
(sighs)
Lousy job.
Nothing exciting
ever happens.
-(alarm blaring)
-(bell ringing)
Congratulations,
Homer Simpson!
You've just won
the employee raffle.
Whoo-hoo!
What do I get?
The job of industrial
chimney sweep for a day!
Whoo-hoo!
Whoa!
(grunting)
(groaning)
(coughing)
Hey, this isn't
such a great prize.
Oh, well,
this may be a dirty job,
but the big guys at the top
work even harder.
(chuckling)
Whoa!
(exhales)
Hmm. (sighs)
Will 5:00 never come?
Careful, Smithers!
That sponge has corners, you know.
I'll go find
a spherical one.
(grunts)
Help, Smithers.
I'm sinking.
(gasps)
Life... flashing...
before--
(gurgling)
...eyes.
You're fired!
Dance!
(laughing)
(grunting)
Dance!
(horn blows)
All right.
We're finally gonna stop
those corporate pigs
from dumping
that nuclear waste.
Oh, no!
Our boat is sinking.
It was I, you fools!
The man you trusted
isn't Wavy Gravy at all. (grunts)
And all this time, I've been smoking
harmless tobacco.
(chortles, grunts)
(evil laughter)
I got a mink chamois, sir.
I hope that-- (gasps)
Oh, my God!
Mr. Burns is dead!
(sobbing) Why do the good
always die so young?
(wailing)
(gasps)
You almost killed me!
(grunts)
(gasps)
Please, sir.
You'll catch--
(gags) cold.
Smithers, do you realize,
if I had died,
there would be no one
to carry on my legacy?
Due to my hectic schedule
and lethargic sperm,
I never fathered an heir.
Now I have no one
to leave
my enormous fortune to.
-No one.
-(clears throat)
You, Smithers?
Oh, no, my dear friend.
I have planned a far greater
reward for you.
When I pass on, you shall be
buried alive with me.
Oh. Goody.
(synthesized tones
crescendoing)
-(rumbling)
-(grunting)
(screams)
(cheering)
Turn it up!
Hello.
I am Montgomery Burns.
-(yelps)
-Now then,
I am looking for
a suitable young male heir
to leave my fortune
to when I pass away.
My vast, vast,
vast fortune.
-Vast.
-(excited chattering)
Auditions will be
tomorrow at my estate.
And now,
our feature presentation.
(whispering)
Oh, for--
Oh, very well.
♪ Let's all go to the lobby
let's all go to the lobby ♪
get ourselves some snacks ♪
(chattering)
What are the two E's?
Enunciate and energy.
I have nothing to offer you
but my love.
I specifically said
"No geeks."
But my mom says
I'm cool.
MR. BURNS:
Next.
Give me your fortune or I'll pound
your withered old face in!
Oh, I like his energy.
Put him on the callback list.
(piano playing)
♪ Clang, clang, clang
went the trolley ♪
♪ Ring, ring, ring
went the bell ♪
♪ Zing, zing, zing
went my heart strings ♪
-(grunts)
-Thank you!
Give the bully
an extra point.
(clears throat)
I propose to you that
your heir need not be a boy.
In this phallocentric
society of ours--
I don't know what "phallocentric" means,
but no girls!
So much for plan "B."
That's it, boy.
You're our last hope.
Ohh. I just don't want
to be here, Dad.
Besides, I started a fire
this morning
that I really
should keep an eye on.
Bart, this isn't the kind of thing
I normally would think was a good idea,
but you wouldn't have
to live with Mr. Burns.
You'd just get all
of his money someday.
This could provide
for your entire future.
-(applause)
-Congratulations.
You've just graduated
from the most expensive
and, therefore,
best school there is.
And your discovery of the cure
for the common cold--
Hello, Marge. I'm Lee Majors.
Will you come away with me?
Uh, sure.
(bionic jumping sound)
I've gotta stop fantasizing
about Lee Majors.
Ah, one more.
(faint: bionic jumping sound)
Okay, boy. I wrote down
exactly what to say.
Just read it,
and you're a shoo-in!
"Hello, Mr. Kurns.
I bad want money now.
Me sick."
HOMER:
Ooh, he card reads good.
"So pick, please, me,
Mr. Burns."
-It's Kurns, stupid!
-No, it's not.
-Disregard.
-Oh, he's the worst yet.
That's it.
Everyone out.
Except you.
One step to the left.
(grunting)
Ow!
Excellent.
(laughing)
The boot kicked Bart!
It kicked him right in the butt!
(groans)
I think Bart and Lisa
are feeling
a little upset
right now.
Isn't there something
you'd like to say?
There sure is.
Kids, you tried your best,
and you failed miserably.
The lesson is,
never try.
(laughing)
Right in the butt.
That was great.
(angry grumbling)
It's no use.
I guess I'll have
to leave all my money
to the egg advisory council.
Eggs have gotten quite a bad rap
lately, you know, Smithers.
Oh, look. A bird has
become petrified
and lost its sense
of direction.
I think it's a rock, sir.
We'll see what the lab
has to say about that.
(glass shattering)
Why, that rapscallion
is breaking all my windows.
(sinister chuckling)
-(excited shouting)
-(doorbell ringing)
(chuckling)
Look, Smithers.
A creature
of pure malevolence.
He's the perfect one
to suckle
at my proverbial teat.
You there, boy!
What day is this?
(cockney accent) Today, sir?
Why, it's Christmas day.
I was talking to him.
-You, what day is this?
-Huh?
I'll tell you
what day it is.
Today is the day
you become my heir.
-(Bart grunts)
-(groans)
Ooh, I like him a lot.
Just sign here,
and your son will stand
to inherit my entire estate.
Whoo-hoo!
We're rich.
Bart, get over to the mansion
and open up all the windows.
We want to get the old-people
smell out before we move in.
Dad, Mr. Burns
hasn't passed away yet.
Huh? Oh, right.
So I guess you're
in okay shape, huh?
No heart problems
or anything?
Well, I--
-Boo!
-(groaning)
(groaning continues)
I'm okay.
Now that you've all agreed
to reap the windfall of my death,
I must return to my large,
empty mansion
to rattle around and await
the inevitable alone.
Are you thinking
what I'm thinking?
Yeah. Let's push him
down the steps.
No!
You know, Bart, since he is
giving you all of his money,
maybe it would be nice
if you spent some time with him.
-Well--
-Come on, honey.
All right.
How come Bart
gets to do that,
and I can't spend one night
lurking in the bushes
outside
Chef Boyardee's house?
Bart, I know you children see me
as some sort of "booger man,"
but, uh, I'm really
not such a bad dude.
Oh, your milk's gone cold.
I'll ring for the maid.
Whoa! (muffled grunting)
Oh, sorry. Wrong button.
Um, I think
I'd like to go home.
Oh, if you stay, you can have
anything you want to eat,
even some sort
of gelatin dish.
It's made from hooves,
you know.
Anything, huh?
Okay. I want pizza,
and I want it delivered
by Krusty the Clown.
-Hmm.
Hey, it's Krusty
the Pizza Man!
(chortling)
All right.
Where's my 400 bucks?
Hey, wait.
How can you be here
when your show's on live?
Ah, I just threw on
an old rerun.
No one will
know the difference.
♪♪ (upbeat music plays)
Huh? Huh? Huh?
Eh, children, remain calm.
The Falkland Islands
have just been invaded.
I repeat, the Falkland's
have just been invaded!
The disputed islands lie here,
off the coast of Argentina.
(groans)
This is my pride and joy.
I've had hidden cameras
planted in every home in Springfield.
I got the idea from
that movie, Sliver.
What a delightful romp.
♪♪ (Wiggum humming)
Are you talking to me?
There's no one else here.
You must be
talking to me.
Well, that was an antique.
Crap!
Oh, yeah. So good.
Oh, that explains his
mysterious trip to Holland.
And I had
the greatest time.
Mr. Burns's house
has everything:
a hedge maze, a moat,
bleached hardwood floors
and a bottomless pit.
It couldn't possibly
be bottomless.
Well, for all intents
and purposes.
Hey! Mom!
Bart's throwing peas!
Bart, don't throw peas
at your sister.
Mr. Burns throws peas
at Smithers.
Ow! That was a big one!
-Homer, say something.
-Okay.
Lisa, quit getting in the way
of your wealthy brother's peas.
-(groans)
-Oh, yuck. Meat loaf.
My most hated of all loafs.
(gasps)
That was the end piece!
That's it! Being abusive
to your family is one thing,
but I will not stand idly by
and watch you feed a hungry dog!
-Go to your room!
-No! This family stinks!
Mr. Burns nurtures
my destructive side.
I'm suffocating here.
-Bart, you listen!
-Oh, go eat some flowers!
(screams)
My secret shame.
Smithers, my plan
worked perfectly.
Bart Simpson will
live here as my son,
and I will mold him
in my own graven image.
Who knows?
I may even grow to...
love him.
Bartholomew!
Ugh! Smithers,
get it off me!
Bart, you're coming home.
I want to stay here
with Mr. Burns.
I suggest you leave
immediately.
Or what? You'll release
the dogs or the bees,
or dogs with bees
in their mouth,
and when they bark,
they shoot bees at you?
Well, go ahead.
Do your worst.
(lock slides shut)
He locked the door!
I'll show him!
-(rings)
-(footsteps departing)
I'm very concerned. Mr. Burns has stolen
our son, and he won't give him back.
Oh, for gosh-- Can't you people solve
these problems yourselves?
I mean, we can't be "policing"
the whole city.
♪♪ (Muzak plays)
Damn clogs.
Well, you good folks
can rest easy now
because you've come to the very
best in legal representation.
Uh, excuse me. Is there
an Orange Julius stand on this floor?
I'll sell you this one.
It's almost full.
Well, why don't I drink out
of a toilet bowl?
He'll be back.
And as for your case,
don't you worry.
I've argued in front of every judge
in the state, often as a lawyer.
(slurping)
This court rules in favor
of Montgomery Burns.
I find that he is clearly
the boy's biological father.
(happy chattering)
Uh, Judge, these won't
be ready until Thursday.
You know, we should
really stop hiring him.
(whistle tooting)
Cool train.
Where does it go?
Beats me.
But it won't be back
for three hours and 40 minutes.
-Once it had snow on it.
-Wow, Bart!
Mr. Burns gives you everything
you could ever want.
My parents use
that old love excuse
to screw me out of toys.
Well, I'm sure you'd like to be
alone with your possessions.
Um, Milhouse, if you stay
a little while longer,
you can have this blazer.
It's a Bob Mackie original.
Wow! A Bob Mackie!
Uh... Sorry, Bart.
(groaning)
Oh.
Bartholomew,
you don't need him.
I can be your school yard chum.
Five, 23, skidoo.
Hut, hut!
(grunts, panting)
Oh!
For me? But I don't
know how to drive.
Oh, pish-posh.
There's a jaws of life in the trunk.
(laughing)
Whoa-ho! Whoo-hoo!
Whoa! Oh! Whoo!
(laughing continues)
Whoa! Whoa!
-(grunting)
-(laughing continues)
(screams, sighs)
-That was some ride.
-You're telling me.
MAN:
Mr. And Mrs. Simpson,
your son has clearly
been brainwashed
by the evil
and charismatic Mr. Burns.
Are you sure you can
get him back for us?
Absolutely.
I'm the one who successfully
deprogrammed Jane Fonda, you know.
What about Peter Fonda?
Oh, that was a heartbreaker.
But I did get Paul McCartney
out of Wings.
You idiot! He was
the most talented one!
(muffled grunting)
You do not love Mr. Burns.
You love Homer and Marge.
You are their son.
What you are doing
is wrong, wrong, wrong!
Do you mind? You're killing
the romance in here.
Well, it was a grueling
two weeks,
but you have your son back.
Ooh.
Mom. Dad.
I missed you.
Aww!
(kissing)
Homer, that's Hans Moleman.
Can I keep him anyway?
Huh? Huh?
♪ ...Scratchy Show ♪
♪♪
(muffled whimpering)
(gasps, screaming)
(laughing)
(laughing continues)
Funny.
That was delightful.
Did you see that?
That mouse butchered
that cat like a hog!
Is all TV this wonderful?
Um, I'd kind of like
to go home now.
Like a hog!
I-- What?
What was that?
Mr. Burns, I don't want
to seem ungrateful,
but I want to go home
to my family.
(sighs) I was hoping I wouldn't
have to tell you this,
but I'm afraid your family
doesn't want you back.
(stilted speech)
I do not miss Bart at all.
(shaky voice)
I am glad he's gone.
-As am I.
-B'oh!
It's probably
my imagination,
but something about them
didn't seem quite right.
Really? Excuse me
for just a moment.
People,
that was all wrong!
Homer Simpson doesn't say "B'oh."
He says--
"D'oh."
(British accent)
Sorry, M.B.,
but I'm having trouble
with this character.
Is he supposed to have some kind
of neurological impairment,
like Rain Man
or Awakenings?
I mean, what the hell
am I doing here?
And this dialogue has none of the wit
and sparkle of Murphy Brown.
(low voice) Hey, you know
we're getting into golden time?
Yes, well, just get it right,
or you'll all be back doing
Come Blow Your Horn
at the Westport Dinner Theater.
All right then.
Let's see what the old
Simpson family is up to now.
Duh-oh!
(groans)
That's them, all right.
I can't believe it.
I guess you're
the only one I can trust.
-Hmm? Hmm?
-Dad?
-(bone snaps)
-Oh! That rib always breaks.
(groaning)
Lisa, what are you doing?
Just trying to fill the void of random,
meaningless destruction
that Bart's absence
has left in our hearts.
(yelps)
That's sweet, honey.
It's a little tight.
Yes, that's to correct
your posture.
Soon you'll have
a mighty hump.
Now, you really
are my son.
This calls for a celebration.
Let's fire some employees.
Excellent.
Okay, let's make this
sporting, Leonard.
If you can tell me
why I shouldn't fire you
without using the letter "E,"
you can keep your job.
Uh, okay. Um--
I'm a good work guy.
-You're fired.
-But I didn't say--
You will.
Eeeeeeee!
(chortling)
-Let me try one.
-(switch clicks)
Mmm. Mmm. Hey, the trail
of donuts ended.
-(gasps) Bart!
-(gasps) Homer!
(gasps)
What a coincidence!
And a perfect opportunity
for you to prove your loyalty.
Go ahead, Bartholomew.
You may fire when ready.
-(groans)
-(whimpers)
Hurry. Fire him now or I'll disown you.
You'll lose everything.
The fabulous toys,
a lifetime of wealth and luxury,
the gift certificate
from Blockbuster Video,
the freedom to do
whatever you want.
I'll miss you, son.
I'm sorry, Dad.
You're fired!
What? Fire me?
That does it.
You can never be my son.
-A little to the left.
-Huh? Oh, very well.
You can never be my--
-Eeeeeeee!
-(gasps)
Sir, try to land
on Leonard's carcass!
(sighs)
Son, I know you're upset because
you thought you saw us on TV
saying we didn't want you
in our family,
but those were just
actors playing us.
How do you know?
Because one of them hung out
with me for a week,
trying to get
my character down.
Yeah, me too. That midget
taught me a lot about his native Estonia.
The point is, the real Simpson family
missed you a lot,
and we're really glad
you're home.
(kisses)
-I love you guys.
-Right back at ya, son.
(all sighing)
And now I want you to meet your
new brother, Hans Moleman.
Cowabunga, dudes.
(kissing)
Give it a try.
It's like kissing a peanut.
(chuckling)
(kissing)
MARGE: Homer, I want
that thing out of my house.
(kissing continues)
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.