The Simpsons
D'oh!
Ah, there's nothing better
than relaxing with
my favorite magazine.
Oh, they're showing
the filling now.
Can they do that?
What the hell is that?
Rainbows. Tank tops.
Empowerment.
This is the
gay pride parade!
Woo-hoo!
We're here!
We're queer! Get used to it!
You do this every year!
We are used to it!
Spoil sport!
Uh...
Oh, honey. Think pink!
Look, a salute to safe sex.
We're gay.
We're glad.
But don't tell
Mom and Dad.
Wouldn't it be great
if that man and woman
got together?
Cool! It's Lesbians
of the Caribbean!
Yo, ho, ho
It's an alternative
lifestyle for me
Oh, a salute to brunch!
Wave to brunch, Maggie.
Oh, look at those abs.
Everyone here has a six-pack
and I'm the only one
with a keg.
Oh, God! Cover up!
That's it!
We're out of here!
Four tickets
for Shenani-Goats!
Why is this movie PG-13?
"It may contain
brief rudeness,
adult explosions,
"and scenes with
Garry Shandling. "
These are so easy.
It's obviously Tom Hanks.
Who?
Otm Shank.
He is India's answer
to Brian Dennehy.
Otm Shank.
Uh-oh.
Come on!
Show the movie!
Justin's soccer team
was in last place...
You suck!
No wonder your parents
are getting divorced!
...until they
dug up a new player.
Ed O'Neill is Soccer Mummy.
PLAYING)
I feel good
Go, Soccer Mummy!
You taught me to
believe in myself!
I feel good
Uh-oh!
The professor said
not to let him get a boner!
I'm laughing!
But it's a laugh
of impatience!
Show the movie!
So many previews.
And now,
our feature presentation.
If that's a phrase
you like to hear,
then you'll love Movie Call!
Start the movie!
Start the...
They're out of control!
Well, if we wanted
to live forever,
we wouldn't
have become ushers.
Stop the madness!
Start the movie!
Maybe we should
try to calm Dad down.
I prefer to egg him on.
Hey, Dad, has
the movie started yet?
Homer, you're going
to get in trouble.
I'm not scared
of those ushers.
What are they gonna do?
Advance on me?
This ends here!
And so,
for helping to KO
litter in our community,
I hereby dedicate this statue
of Drederick Tatum!
Litter is my most
treacherous foe.
I would like to
eat its children.
So long, suckers!
My mouth.
My beautiful mouth!
Excellent bout.
Now we go party.
Homer, you've suffered
a broken jaw.
Broken jaw!
He won't be able to talk
for quite some time.
I've wired his jaw shut.
It's all explained
in this pamphlet.
Hmm.
Oh, dear!
You can't eat solid foods!
Those are his favorites!
I can't eat solid food!
Stop it, Homer!
Oh, don't worry.
On a man his size,
that just provides
sexual release.
Uh-oh.
Hey, Dad,
I'm gonna make
a human yo-yo.
If you object,
clearly say no.
No!
No objections, eh?
That's great.
Milhouse,
you ready to imitate
that Jackass show?
All those disclaimers
made me want to do it more!
Oh, yeah!
Hey, Duff lovers!
Does anyone in
this bar love Duff?
Hey, it's Duffman!
Newsweek said you died
of liver failure.
Duffman can never die!
Only the actors who play him!
Oh, yeah!
You must be here for the
Duff Trivia Challenge.
That's right,
local distributor.
One of you could win
a lifetime supply of Duff!
Okay, chug monkeys,
"What beverage
brewed since ancient times
"is made from
hops and grains?"
How about ancient
hop grain juice?
Beer! Beer! Beer!
Wait, wait, wait.
Homer's trying to
make a guess.
Beer, beer, beer!
What are you doing?
You're getting some kind
of booze all over me!
Time's up!
The answer is beer!
Ooh. Duff luck.
I never would've
figured that out.
That's the kind of thing
you just gotta know.
I am not gonna make you
another sparerib smoothie.
Most people with
their jaws wired shut
don't gain weight.
"How was your day?"
Do you really want to know?
Uh-huh.
Well, let's see.
I was in the kitchen
counting the corncobs
on the curtains,
when who should
ring the doorbell
but Ned Flanders.
It seems he wants to
ban culottes in the schools.
Pardon my French,
but sometimes that
man's a goofy-doofy.
Marge thinks
Flanders is annoying.
This marriage
just got interesting.
She's so cute.
Ah!
Uh-oh.
You want to know
what happened?
Really?
We were playing foursquare
and I called no double taps,
and Ralph double taps.
And I said, "You're out,"
and he says, "I can do
a summersault,"
which had nothing
to do with anything!
Aw!
Maybe a hug
will cork her cry hole.
Thanks for listening, Dad.
We gotta coordinate
on this thing.
Uh-huh.
So the substitute
teacher comes in
and says
her name is Mrs. Doody,
and everyone's
looking at me like,
"Take it, Bart. Run with it. "
Then it hits me.
I've become a clown.
A class clown.
And it sickens me.
Wow,
Bart has feelings.
Mrs. Doody.
Three wars back
we called sauerkraut
"liberty cabbage,"
and we called
liberty cabbage "super slaw!"
And back then,
a suitcase was known
as a Swedish lunchbox.
'Course,
nobody knew that but me.
Anyway, "Long story short"
is a phrase whose origins
are complicated and rambling.
You know,
tomorrow is the Annual
Springfield Formal Event.
We weren't going to go
after last year's
unpleasantness.
That donkey is such
a bad influence on you.
But breaking your jaw
has made you so sweet.
Maybe we can go.
Mmm-hmm.
Mmm. I better polish
those jaw wires
for tomorrow.
A formal!
The one place
you can wear a tiara
and not look crazy.
Uh-huh!
So, how are we
enjoying the festivities?
Yes. The music is
from southern Hungary.
That's quite an ear.
Have some money.
Your husband is
quite the gentleman.
Most people laugh
at my googly eye.
Well, I've never
seen a man
politely pass up
so many hors d'oeuvres.
My husband,
Maxtone Witherball,
has already had three shrimp!
Someone's done
her henpecking.
You two are quite the couple.
You must dine with us
at Toad Hall.
Thank you.
This has been
one of the most magical
evenings of my life.
I'm horny.
I don't know what you said,
but I'm sure it
was beautiful.
Oh, Homer. This is
the kind of night
I thought we could
never have together.
Incident-free.
Mmm-mmm.
Oh, Homer,
drop by my office tomorrow
and I can remove
those jaw wires.
You'll be just the way
you used to be.
And Reverend,
I'll put in those
pec implants on Thursday.
Super.
Homer,
your breath smells terrible.
I'll have to
take off my shoes
to cover the odor.
Nicely done.
And when I couldn't talk,
I learned to listen.
I learned so much
about my family.
You'd be surprised
how much you hear
if you just listen
once in awhile.
Really? Let's try it.
Hello?
Yeah. I'd like to arrange
for an escort, please.
To where?
How about Orgasmville!
You... Hello? Hello?
Oh! Hey.
How you doing?
I was just
telling all the guys
how losing
the power of speech
made me a better man.
I couldn't agree more.
You're today's modern,
enlightened man,
the kind
we television producers
have been booking
since the mid '70s.
Hey, what are you
doing in here?
I'm an alcoholic.
Homer, will you appear
on my show?
Sure thing, alky.
Welcome to Afternoon Yak.
Today we will meet a man
who couldn't open his mouth,
so he learned to
open his heart.
Please welcome
Homer and Marge Simpson.
So, Marge, tell.
What's it like
kissing a man with
a mouth full of metal?
My boyfriend has
a metal tongue stud.
Who cares
what's on his tongue,
as long as he's
a stud where it counts!
I'm talking downtown!
Marge,
what was Homer like
before he broke his jaw?
Well, he would eat
all the time.
We'd be making love
and he'd have a mouth full
of Hershey's Miniatures.
Krackel was my favorite.
I hope that was
the only miniature
in the bedroom.
I'm talking downtown!
And before
he broke his jaw
he never listened,
but now he takes to heart
everything I say.
Well, as much
as humanly possible.
Well, Marge told us
when you didn't listen,
it led to weckless,
criminal behavior.
He did such crazy things.
Roll the clip.
Ostrich burgers!
Get your ostrich burgers!
I'll take one.
Okay. You pick one out
and I'll punch it to death.
Hmm.
Hey there,
little sweet...
Dude, I thought
we were friends!
Well, I'm not proud
of that clip.
Homela, it's easy to change,
but what's hard is
not changing back.
Do you promise not to
revive your weckless,
weckless ways?
I don't know.
The Demolition Derby
is next month.
Please, Homie?
No more craziness?
For me?
Well, okay.
For you, I'll be
as dull as Dilbert.
Very good. Our next topic,
"My Son Still Wets the Bed. "
You told me we were
going to Red Lobster!
Hmm. All clean,
just the way I left it.
I'm gonna kill you!
Well, so much for
the new Homer.
What's going on?
We're rehearsing a play.
Yes, and I was
merely reading the title,
I'm Gonna Kill You.
Oh. It's just
a false alarm.
Yep. Nothing to get
excited about.
Well, I'll be in the kitchen
if you need me.
Professor Van Doran,
so good to see you.
Ah. Rehearsing
a play, I see.
This place is so dull.
The 911 button is
covered with dust.
I just poured myself
a new glass of milk.
The old one sat out
for a little while.
Are you coming to bed?
It's 7:30.
Marge, I could stand here
and argue with you,
but then I'd have to get
a new glass of milk.
Good night, honey.
Boy, things are
going really good.
Good, good, good, good,
good, good, good!
Hmm.
Look at that freckle.
I should dig that out.
Good. Good.
That feels good.
This place
is so boring!
If somebody doesn't do
something interesting,
I'm gonna have to!
But what?
The Demolition Derby?
Oh, that'll scratch my itch.
Marge? Marge is gone!
But at least the Demolition
Derby form is...
What? No!
Ooh, listen to
all that revving!
Drivers,
start your engines!
Vendors,
start your gouging!
I'll pay anything!
And now,
smashie-smashie!
Looking good, Mrs. S.
Uh-oh. Come on, old girl.
Show them what you got.
Whoa!
Catch you later, radiator!
Oh, my God. I hit someone.
Then I taunted him.
I've never felt more alive!
What was I thinking
trying to feel alive?
Forget that!
Don't hurt me!
I'm not like you people!
I'm loved!
I caught a head!
Oh, dang!
It's been scooped out.
Go around! Go around!
There she is!
Dad, you've gotta
do something!
But bold moves are
no longer my forte.
She could get hurt!
What do I do?
Wait, I know.
Beer here!
Sure, sonny.
This beer's deliskous.
I'm gonna saves me wife.
Now, let's get this show
on the road.
So many dings.
Quit banging my wife!
A man
on a donkey!
Never in my six
weeks on the job
have I seen
the likes of this.
Looks like
I needs some fuel for me mule.
Gas for me ass.
Looks like a little angel.
Now to save me Marge!
Homer, save me! Save me!
He saved her!
Isn't it great to have
the old Dad back?
I thought you
liked the new Dad.
Whatever.
This family
needs a live wire,
but it's just not me.
That's okay, Marge.
You're a good wet blanket.
The kind I like
wrapped around me.
Aw!
When
Homer's jaw was crushed,
crushed, crushed,
his life took
a nitro-burning funny turn!
Oh, yeah!
It's important to
grow, grow, grow,
but if you take it
to the max, max, max,
it's gonna get ugly!
In the mud!
English - US - PSDH