34, 35...
37?
No!
Oh, I have to go
all the way around again.
I had the locker dream again.
Oh, honey,
that's four nights in a row.
Stupid recurring dreams.
Why can't brains come up
with something new?
That's why they're losing
viewers to Netflix.
Maybe I should talk
to a therapist.
Sweetie, our insurance won't pay
for any more sessions.
Your father used them all up
on grief counseling
after the Halloween candy
ran out.
I've come to accept
that we were lucky to have it
while we did.
But I know a cheap place
where you can see
the therapists of tomorrow
today.
Behold,
Springfield Community College,
where the students practice
on you!
I only paid a student dentist
$12 for this brand-new crown.
See?
I don't think
it's supposed to come out.
That's why I paid
a student paralegal to sue him.
I lost!
TV must be a circle!
Give him the full flea dip
and deluxe under-worming.
I'm not a dog.
And I've been worm-free
for two weeks!
You better muzzle him.
He's a biter.
My name is Annette,
and I'm a therapist-in-training.
I'm also a mother-to-be,
so I know
there's nothing more beautiful
than a child's feelings.
You sound so caring
and professional.
When do I give you
the seven dollars?
There's a shoebox by the door.
So what does
my locker dream mean?
Am I stressed about school?
I mean,
schools are full of lockers.
Hey, who's
the almost-therapist here?
You know, I think you
might benefit from art therapy.
Draw in these empty panels
to tell the story
of a typical day
in the life of you,
Sophia Barnum.
Once again,
learn the patient's name.
Sorry, Professor.
Lisa Simpson.
Excellent. Continue.
Your light's still on.
Art therapy.
Okay, draw a typical day.
Horrible!
It looks like it was drawn
by an eight-year-old!
Oh, boy, I can't wait
to take you to the park.
The other owners
will be so jealous.
You're not my owner.
I kinda am.
I'm hearing
a lot of feelings in here.
You're hearing them
because I am not drawing them!
Sweetie, drawing is tricky.
But you just need to start with
something simple, like people.
Those are people.
It's easy, honey.
Add some eyelashes here,
some crosshatching
to show shadow,
vary the line width here
to accent the outline,
and voilà!
That's great!
Now in the next panel,
I want her to be looking out
a window,
wondering if she'll ever get out
from under the weight
of her own expectations.
Well, I could make the eyebrows
come down in a V.
That says it all.
Hey, Mom, what if I told you
the things I was feeling
and you drew them?
Okay. But I'm warning you,
I'm not good at drawing
turtle feet.
So if there are any turtles
in this,
they're gonna be wearing
sneakers.
Deal.
It starts with the story
of a regular day...
Gosh, I forgot how hard school
can be for a sensitive kid.
It's miserable.
But you captured my feelings
perfectly!
Annette, wait till you see
my art therapy!
You're gonna love it too.
Please try to pretend
I'm not here.
Okay, Stephen.
Hey, where did it go?
Best marriage counseling ever.
But we still need to discuss
your addiction
to unboxing videos.
Do not make me choose
between you and unboxing.
Manga!
It's been a week, and I still
can't find my therapy comic.
I'd be just mortified
if even one person saw
my private thoughts...
Mom, can I have
permission to swear?
Okay, as long
as it's a tier one.
Damn it!
That didn't work.
Can I go to tier two?
- I'm afraid not.
- Damn it!
And with that seal cut,
we have completed the unboxing
of the outer shipping plastic.
Indeed we have.
You published my private
art therapy as a comic book?
Actually,
it's a graphic novel.
The distinctions
are threefold...
- Shut up!
- Okay then.
In my defense,
my wife did it.
Kumiko, how could you?
I have acted shamefully.
I must commit furry cosplay.
There's nothing sexy
about shame!
Except in my native Japan,
where it's our whole thing.
Mr. and Mrs. Book Guy,
you had no right to do this!
These are
my daughter's feelings.
And my doodles.
I shall burn them on a pyre
and disperse them
to the seven winds.
That's all I ask.
One Sad Girl, please.
Sad Girl's the best!
It's tragically delicious!
Wait!
Maybe this isn't so bad.
My Lulus!
Oh, there she is.
Ask for her autograph.
You ask her, man.
I'm freakin' out.
Wow, Lisa, our cartoon book
seems to have really
captured the...
What's that word
I'm looking for?
Zeitgeist!
Oh, hi, Mel!
Say hi to Barbara for me.
I'm not your messenger boy!
What's so great
about graphic novels?
They're just comic books
with no superheroes
and no cool sound effects
like Thwam!
Ack-ack-ack-ack!
- And Fwwwip!
- Snag!
Lisa, Kumiko called.
She sold all her copies
and wants us to make a sequel!
That's like a prequel
but in the future.
What do you say, sweetie?
Do you have more sad in you?
I've got scads of sad!
Oh, no, not again
There they go
With pad and pen
Collaboration
Ooh, collaboration
Okay, now draw me
overhearing the other girls
talking about how
they're not gonna invite me
to a birthday party.
Like this?
Fantastic!
Now let's take a little break.
And you know what that means.
Hot Sharpie!
- Hot Sharpie!
- You almost got me!
- How come we never bond like that?
I don't know,
you never make the first move.
Okay.
There is something I've
always wanted to do with you.
Hey, those guys stole
our fishing poles!
And my skipping stones!
Welcome to Chicks with Pix,
a panel discussion
with women writers and artists.
I'm your moderator, Roz Chast.
You may know
my New Yorker cartoons
that are both funny ha-ha
and funny aha.
Silence!
Joining me today
are Alison Bechdel,
Marjane Satrapi,
and the creators of Sad Girl,
Lisa Simpson...
We love you, Lisa!
And Marge Simpson.
We're wasting time!
Marjane, as the author
of Persepolis
and someone who grew up
in a repressive regime,
what advice would you offer
to young women?
Always remember
nothing is more valuable
than your own unique voice.
Also, when they promise you
a tote bag for doing a panel,
make sure it's not just
a reusable grocery bag.
Look at this.
Alison Bechdel, recently,
a lot of people have been
talking about the Bechdel Test.
Exactly what kind
of drinking game is that?
Actually, it's just
an observation I made
about how movies and TV
rarely show
two women talking about
something other than a man.
That's so interesting.
I'll have to tell my husband
about that.
Bechdel Test, Fail!
Bechdel, Bechdel
Bechdel, fail!
Fail!
Fail...
Okay. We have five minutes
before we have to clear
the room
for the
White Men in Comics panel.
I have a question for Lisa.
I have a question for Lisa
with a follow-up for Lisa.
I want to talk about myself
for a few minutes,
then at the end, pretend it
was all a question for Lisa.
Does anyone have any questions
for my mom?
She does draw every panel.
Yeah, I have a question
for Marge.
How lucky are you
to work with Lisa?
Lisa!
Lisa! Lisa!
Lisa win!
Marge fail.
Honey, I was thinking.
What if we did a chapter
from the mom's point of view?
I took a stab at writing it up.
Give it a read.
In front of you?
Okay.
What are you laughing at?
You left out a word here,
so it just says, I lonely.
So should I start drawing it?
Well, there's a lot
of great stuff here.
Really? Because that's
what I was going for.
But I'm not sure this is
a Sad Girl thing.
Maybe it's a separate book
and I could write the forward.
Oh, I get it.
This isn't a real
collaboration at all.
You agree with those girl
fanboys.
You think it's all about you.
Hey, you can't blame me
if people want to focus on
my contribution.
I can and I do.
I hate to say it, Mom,
but maybe we should
take a break.
Good idea. Hot Sharpie.
No. I mean,
maybe we should take
a real break.
- You mean...?
- That's right.
I want to see other
illustrators.
- I don't even know how you could say that.
- Stupid Lisa.
- It's my vision.
- She's acting like a real B.
Ladies, there's someone here
to see you.
My name is Guthrie Frenel,
visionary theatrical director
and impish genius.
And I want to make Sad Girl
into a smash Broadway show.
I think he came in
through the window.
Oh, tubby, you're a delight.
You want to make Sad Girl
into a stage musical?
If I may borrow a phrase
from my father, woo-hoo!
This is all very exciting,
but before we go any further...
and I ask this just
for clarification...
- What's your deal, weirdo?
- Dad.
Guthrie Frenel is a visionary
director and an impish genius.
He did a version of
Waiting for Godot.
- Where Godot appears in the first scene.
- What?
And that was nothing compared
to my vision for Sad Girl.
I want to do something new
and amazing,
like my all-dog version of Cats.
But I need something from you.
- Anything.
- I need your passion.
I need your joy.
Are we all together for this
three-person toboggan ride
down Mount Collabor-manjaro?
Well, Lisa and I did just have
a little spat.
Yeah, but conflict is part of
the creative process, right?
Not in my experience!
So are you in?
- Yes.
- Absolutely.
Oh, this is gonna take hours.
Bart, there's one thing I know
about Broadway shows,
they always make money.
So I'm already looking forward
to quitting my job.
Can I quit school?
I'd be a pretty lousy dad
if I said no.
It's our duty as artists
to rip up the contract between
audience and performers.
Cell phones will be turned on.
Candy will be unwrapped
during the show.
We'll hire performance artists
to make the line for the
ladies room extra long.
How closely
are we gonna stick
to the story
from my graphic novel?
Oh, yes, story.
All the gimmicky stagecraft
in the world
ain't worth a tinker's damn
without a compelling human story
at the center.
Your story,
the unique expression
of your heart and soul...
will be neatly summed up
in the narrator's first speech.
Once that's out of the way,
we can explore the dazzling
visual buffet of Marge Simpson.
Now feast.
Pass the wonderment, please,
but save room for the Tonys.
Oh, my God.
It's just how I drew it.
It's your artistic vision
writ large.
Or should I say, writ Marge?
You should.
He really shouldn't.
It's all in my style.
Mom, he's ignoring my story
and making this all about
your drawings.
I know.
I'm sorry, Lisa.
But I can't help it
if he wants to focus
on the visual part of...
Oh, my God.
It's Bart and Grampa.
But they aren't even in my book.
And where am I?
Where is Sad Girl?
Sad Girl will be represented
by a voiceless red light
projected into
an empty seat in the balcony.
Bold, no?
But how will they know
it's supposed to be me?
Storytelling.
That impish genius is really
cheesing me off.
All he's kept from Sad Girl
is Mom's drawings,
when it's supposed to be about
my writing and my feelings.
Oh, I'm so sick
of children's feelings.
Feed me. Burp me.
Don't sleep for six years.
You're forgetting the boundary
between patient and therapist.
And you're forgetting
that you did this to me!
Let me tell you something, Lisa.
When you give birth
to something,
you have no control over
what it turns into.
All you can do is surrender
to the nightmare.
Sorry. I'm just so happy.
Never do this.
Here they are.
The official Sad Girl
The Theater Experience T-shirts.
$45 in the lobby,
of which we keep $1.35.
Oh, baby, we can use that money
to buy a sailboat
with a double-ended
spinnaker pole.
Looks good. I like it.
I like everything.
Really? You seemed a little
cheesed off earlier.
A mother notices.
Mom, Sad Girl was like our baby.
And you can't control
what your kid turns into.
If it becomes
a successful show,
that will be good
for our family.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I'm gonna go
sit on a swing alone.
Oh, okay.
Hello, Coast Guard?
Get ready to search for my body
in about a month.
- So you're okay with this?
- Sure.
It's an honor to have something
based on your life.
Even if it's nothing like
your life at all.
Sad Girl
What the hell does
any of this mean?
What? You don't get this?
It's so stimulating
and I love it.
- What is that?!
- D'oh!
Guthrie, is it possible
we strayed
a skoosh too far from what
Lisa's book is about?
Marge, this isn't You're A Good
Man, Charlie Brown.
Or even my production of You're
A Good Man, Charlie Brown,
set in a doomed
Soviet submarine.
This is avant-garde theater,
and it is electric.
Okay, I guess.
Oh, Lisa.
I'm so sorry.
There, honey. Now you're
back in our show.
What the...? That's not
one of my brain babies.
Which one of us
is me?
Run for your cultural lives!
I'm haunted by visions
of Milhouse.
And now to read the reviews.
Greatest...
I like where this is going.
Disaster in theater
history.
Oh, those sons of Bs.
Honey, I'm sorry
I let Guthrie make the play
all about my drawings,
and also terrible.
And I'm sorry I wasn't more open
to your creative input.
I blame both of you
for this disaster.
More wine!
I've got another project
for us to collaborate on.
Getting your dad
in a cab.
Hello, Coast Guard?
I'm gonna live.
Well, I still think
it's good.