(SlNGlNG) The Simpsons
(TlRES SCREECHlNG)
D'oh !
(SCREAMlNG)
(BRAKES SCREECHlNG)
Welcome to
lecture number eight
on the water balloon.
Yesterday l asked everyone
to think of other liquids
you could fill a balloon with.
Water? (GROANS)
Thank you, Nelson.
Anyone else?
Hot sauce.
Kearney, that could
blind someone.
You get an A.
Mmm.
Now for
a practical demonstration.
First, we load the ordnance.
Then select the target.
Hmm, not Otto.
He'd drive us off a cliff.
Off a cliff?
That would solve everything.
(CHUCKLlNG)
Bingo.
Bart!
(LAUGHlNG)
(CHOKlNG)
Why can't you be friends
like me and Mr. Finger?
You've betrayed me
for the last time.
Horseplay on a school bus?
Has the world gone mad?
(BRAKES SCREECHlNG)
Your stop!
Ahhh !
(SNOWBALL ll MEOWlNG)
Shame on you two creeps!
lt's your fault
for giving birth
to my archenemy!
At least l was planned !
(BOTH GRUNTlNG)
Stop it!
No one was planned !
Now we have to pack
for Great Uncle Tyrone's
birthday tomorrow in Dayton.
Dayton, Ohio!
(BOTH GROANlNG)
lt's got Wright-Patterson
Air Force Base
and a zipper museum !
They have a zipper
from every James Bond !
Why are we even going?
Last year,
Uncle Tyrone was
bitter and depressed.
(SlNGlNG)
Happy birthday to you
Why won't l die?
We're staying at
the Dayton Arms Hotel.
lt got three diamonds
from Five Diamond magazine!
Please don't make us go!
lf you make me
get on that plane,
l'll give myself diarrhea.
l know how!
Okay, don't go!
Just stay here
and rot with Grampa!
l'm only rotting
on the right side!
l'll right side you !
All right, kids.
You don't have to go.
But l insist we do
something tonight
as a family.
We'll play board games,
put photos in an album,
measure how much
you've grown, and. . .
What is your deal, anyway?
Well, l. . . l. . .
Let's just rent a movie.
Hmm.
Mmm-hmm.
MOE: Oh, yeah !
That's the stuff!
(EXClTED GASP)
(GROANS lN DlSAPPOlNTMENT)
(MOE CHUCKLlNG)
(GRUNTS)
Brideshead's gonna get
revisited tonight, baby.
(MOANlNG)
l'm sorry, sir.
The computer says the movie
Chocolate Star Wars
doesn't exist.
l say you don't exist!
No, l'm right here,
under "Staff."
What l want is
a really good weeper.
What about Love Story?
lt's about a Harvard chick
that puts out for
a guy and then croaks.
And it saved
Paramount Studios
for Charlie Bluhdorn.
Ooh !
A chick flick?
Say it ain't so, Ho!
Son, seeing sappy
movies with a lady
has certain payoffs.
Like what?
They'll do something
with you that they hate?
Exactly.
(SlNGlNG) Where do I begin
To teII the story of
how great a Iove can be?
The sweet Iove story
that is older than the sea
The simpIe something
that dum-deedle-dum-dee-dee
Now Iet's push pIay
RYAN O'NEAL:
What can you say about
a 25-year-oId girI who died?
BART: l say bury her
before she starts to smell !
(LAUGHlNG)
Bart!
The man
asked a question.
(GRUNTS)
Love means never having
to say you're sorry.
No, it doesn't.
This movie is drivel.
She's wooden and unpleasant.
And no matter what he does,
he's still Ryan O'Neal.
Opinion noted.
Now if you don't mind,
your father and l are trying
to lose ourselves in
this romantic fantasy.
Yeah. We're trying
to create a mood here,
so shut the hell up!
(GROWLlNG)
Homie, if l died,
would you be sad?
Well, l wouldn't be happy.
Oh, Homie.
Love means never
having to say...
A whole canoe
made of baIoney?
(LAUGHlNG)
Bart, stop fooling
with the remote!
Lisa made me with
a witch's spell !
lt's called Wicca,
and it's empowering !
Wicca's a Hollywood fad !
That's Kabbalah, jerk!
(GRUNTlNG)
Stupid kids ruin everything !
So you're not
in the mood anymore,
are you?
Homie,
you know l'm usually good
for a triple-X throw-down.
But between those kids
and going to Uncle Tyrone's,
we can't be alone.
We're alone now.
BART: You're never alone
in this crap shack!
Why, you little. . .
(BART CHOKlNG)
(MAN COUGHlNG)
What kind of an airline
routes all their flights
through Nome, Alaska?
lt's their hub.
Homie, look at them.
(FESTlVE MUSlC PLAYlNG)
Honeymooners.
No kids, no worries.
Here's your future!
(LAUGHlNG)
Not me. l do crunches.
Remember our honeymoon?
(DOG HOWLlNG)
Well, l gotta
get back to work.
Hold that thought.
(RETCHlNG)
GATE ANNOUNCER:
Attention Miami passengers,
Suntan Airlines
is now boarding
rows pina coIada
through daiquiri.
(CHEERlNG)
You know, if we were
younger and crazier,
we'd trade in these tickets
and run off to Miami.
Marge, let's do it!
What about Uncle Tyrone?
We got one weekend
to ourselves
and we gotta spend it
watching some old geezer's
odometer turn over?
As the Bible says,
"Screw that!"
We don't have
boarding passes,
but we need to
get on that plane
for reasons that
are utterly insane!
Go ahead.
What do l care? l'm getting
laid off tomorrow.
(BOTH GlGGLlNG)
We're ditching
our kids and taking
a second honeymoon !
(CHEERlNG)
And we're blowing off
Uncle Tyrone's birthday!
(CHEERlNG LOUDER)
You guys are
such party animals,
we're gonna skip
the safety check
and just take off!
(CHEERlNG LOUDLY)
l'm afraid we've
overbooked this flight.
(SlGHS) So much
for getting my groove back.
So we're upgrading you
to first class.
There's a first class?
Sir, what would
you like for dinner?
A steak or two steaks?
Can l have both?
Of course.
This is so luxurious.
l feel like
l'm Princess Grace and
Princess Di smashed together.
And look at me.
l'm reading The Economist.
Did you know lndonesia
is at a crossroads?
No.
lt is.
KENT: I guess
you couId caII him
the little tortoise
that couldn't.
See our website
for the recipe.
This just in,
a monster tornado
is tearing
through Dayton, Ohio!
(GASPlNG) That's where
Mom and Dad are!
KENT: Looks Iike
the twister is headed
right for
the Dayton Arms HoteI!
ALL: Ahhh !
They might not be dead.
They could be
in the basement.
l'm an orphan.
l'm a legal guardian.
(PHONE RlNGlNG)
How can l be a parent?
l break my teeth
on ribbon candy.
(ABE MOANlNG)
Quiet, Grampa.
Hello? Mom?
Hi, sweetie.
We're just calling
to check in.
Where are you?
Are you okay?
Right here in Dayton.
(GlGGLlNG)
At the Dayton Arms Hotel?
Yup. lt's really boring.
You kids would've hated it.
(GlGGLlNG)
So how's
the weather in Dayton?
Oh, you know,
typical boring
Dayton weather.
(MOANlNG)
Hey, do l hear a backrub?
No. No, that's the noise
the phone makes when
you've been on too long.
Bye now. Love you.
Something's fishy.
They're not in Dayton.
They're somewhere fun.
We're not
enough fun for them?
Well, l know how to find out
where they are.
HOTEL OPERATOR:
Swelldorado Hotel
Miami Beach,
sun and water
without your
son and daughter.
How may I direct your caII?
(SLAMS RECElVER DOWN)
l can't go to Miami !
l'm expecting calls
from telemarketers!
You'll love it.
lt's full of sexy old widows
who don't want to die alone.
(EXCLAlMS EXClTEDLY)
All right, ladies,
get ready to settle!
Boy, it's great being here
without those
children of yours.
Yeah. l've never sat
by a pool this long
without having to
apologize to someone.
And tonight,
we'll finally and
romantically hump.
Here's to life
without children.
Well, we can't wait
to have kids.
(LAUGHlNG HEARTlLY)
"Can't wait."
Seriously.
With the new breast pumps
and Diaper Genies,
and corporate flex-time,
child-rearing
ought to be a snap.
(LAUGHlNG HYSTERlCALLY)
You keep thinking that.
(TlRES SCREECHlNG)
We're here!
And it's a good thing, too.
The car's been
driving funny since Orlando.
(GRUNTlNG)
Everything happens to E-more.
Let's go find Mom and Dad.
First, let's slap on
some Band-Aids
so they feel really
bad for ditching us.
Time to find a woman
who needs some TLC.
A Tired Liver-spotted Coot.
(UPBEAT MUSlC PLAYlNG)
(HONKlNG)
(RAP MUSlC PLAYlNG)
A-blowin' reveille
He's the boogie woogie
bugle boy of Company B
Check out the well-aged beef.
No scar. He must be
on his first heart!
l wouldn't kick him
out of bed for dying.
(PURRS)
Hey, handsome,
pull up a donut
and sit down.
Hey, ladies.
l used to be in movies.
(ALL REACTlNG lN AWE)
You know those
feet sticking out
from under the house
in The Wizard of Oz?
You're looking at 'em.
ALL: Ew!
(SlNGlNG) Come on, everybody
have some sexuaI congress
Not the kind of Congress
that contained PauI Tsongas
(GASPlNG)
The kids tracked us down !
Oh !
Our romantic holiday
just became a stinking
family vacation.
Marge,
l won't let that happen.
We have to grab this chance
for romance now or
we'll never be alone!
Not till Lisa's in college
and we've lost contact
with Bart!
You're right.
But where do we go?
l've got a card
that can take us
anywhere in the world.
MARGE: Step on it!
Those horn dogs!
They ditched us again !
You know what this means?
We have a free
hotel room in Miami
for two days?
No. We're gonna follow them
across this great land
making sure they don't have
one moment of fun.
And l have a card
that can take us
anywhere they go.
l'm sorry. We're not
supposed to give out
passengers' itineraries.
l understand.
Hey, what's that
crazy girl doing?
l'm going into
the Gold Medallion Club
with Silver Level Membership!
(LAUGHlNG EVlLLY)
The hell you are!
(COCKS GUN)
So Mom and Dad
are going to Atlantic City.
But their luggage isn't.
(CHUCKLlNG)
And Homer's
getting a low-fat meal.
HOMER: No!
You're more
boring than my husband.
And he's dead.
Well, l bet l smell better.
At the moment,
it's about even.
l can't wait till
we bury the last
of you Hepburn types.
Really!
(MOANlNG)
Perhaps l can help.
l have a penthouse
from which you can see
all the way to Epcot.
lf you take a woman there,
she will be yours.
Hot-diggity!
lndeed. l am Raoul.
While we walk,
may l place my hand
on your shoulder as
a sign of friendship?
Why not?
Homie, people in
the other elevators
can see us.
Oh, yeah.
Like people in New Jersey
have never seen
a fat man making out.
lt's on
the freakin' state flag.
Oh, my God. Homie, look!
That boy failed
show-and-tell, but he's on
our ass like Sherlock Holmes.
Hey, how you doing?
l'm fighting a white rhino
today at the Tropicana.
Shows at 2:00,
4:00, 6:00, 8:00, 1 0:00,
and midnight.
Check it out. Come on.
Hey, kids,
l'm tying balloons
on the boardwalk
at 3:00, 5:00, 7:00,
9:00, and 1 1 :00.
Check it out. Come on,
don't be ridiculous.
(TlRES SCREECHlNG)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSlC PLAYlNG)
(SNORlNG)
(KNOCKlNG ON DOOR)
Occupied !
(RESUMES SNORlNG)
Okay, Raoul, let's go
meet some senoritas.
Grampa, l must confess,
l am not as
interested in women
as my open shirt
might suggest.
To be frank,
they disgust me.
Uh-oh !
Yes. Now let us enjoy
one of your rambling,
disjointed,
yet somehow erotic tales.
Are you gonna go
lavender on me?
We shall see, uh?
But l promise you
l will treasure every word
that drops from
your beautiful lips.
Really? You're sweet.
Proceed.
For many years,
l was a tater farmer.
But the shameful truth is
the taters farmed me.
Your neck skin
dances when you speak.
At last we're alone.
(SCATTlNG)
Homie, the waiter's
still here.
Oh. Right.
Thank you, sir.
(CHUCKLlNG)
And now, my darling,
it's finally time
for romance.
But before the intercourse,
the dinner course!
Busted !
You guys lied to us!
You probably
do this all the time.
This whole family
is built on a tissue
of lies and romance.
Yeah, it's a tissue
covered in blood
and boogers!
Would you two
just shut up!
Sure, we lied.
We lied so we could
spend a single night
as a married couple
without worrying
about you kids.
Those days are over.
Give it up.
(SlGHlNG)
You win, kids.
Just sleep here tonight
and we'll all go back
to Springfield tomorrow.
Great! What do you
want to play?
How about the floor
is made of lava?
(BOTH LAUGHlNG)
All l wanted was
a second honeymoon
and now the floor
is made of lava.
Lise, you awake?
Yeah, l can't sleep.
Maybe we should give
Mom and Dad a break,
you know?
Go spend the day
at an amusement park
so we're out of their hair.
Yeah, l agree.
l mean, you are
pretty annoying.
l guess the hunt was more fun
than the catch.
Hey, l just zinged you !
l know. My new thing
is to ignore you.
When you grow up,
l'll be outside.
l'm grown up! l'm grown up!
(RATTLlNG)
l knew if we got up
early enough,
we could sneak away
from Bart and Lisa.
Kids don't beat me.
l beat kids.
And nobody does it better.
(ALL YELLlNG)
You monsters!
You followed us!
No. You don't understand.
We came here to give
you some privacy. . .
We understand
perfectly well.
Let me finish my sentence!
Never!
This way!
Quick! We can hide in here!
l don't know.
Homie, why don't
we just go home,
wait till
the kids fall asleep,
and have sex in the car?
Because l was saving
that for my birthday!
Now come on.
(GlGGLlNG)
This must be what
it's like to be in space.
You've been to space.
And yet l've never
been to me.
(GlGGLlNG CONTlNUES)
HOMER: That sliding
should stop soon.
This rolling is
just temporary.
Ah !
That's better.
So why do
they call this place
Niagara Falls, anyway?
BOTH: Ahhh !
(SlRENS WAlLlNG)
Back off, Canadians!
We got 'em.
You back off, hosers.
They're in
Canadian waters, eh?
Beat it,
you puck-sIapping
mapIe-suckers!
Take a hike,
you Shatner-stealing
Mexico-touchers!
SKlPPERS: How about that?
Oh ! Marge,
l guess we'll just have
to make love in Heaven.
l bet it always
works up there.
Shut up and kiss me,
you doomed hunk!
Ahoy, moon bounce!
Is anyone aIive?
More alive than
any of you squares!
(GlGGLlNG DAZEDLY)
(GlGGLlNG)
HOMER: You're on my hair!
Oh, that's better.
Well, it looks like
everything worked out
just fine for everybody.
Credit card bill seems
a little chunky this month.
Let's see what's going
on vis-a-vis the Viza.
This. . . Ahhh !
Ahhh !
English - US - PSDH