♪ The Simpsons ♪
May I sample the Mango Mayhem?
Now you're gonna scream for ice cream,
John Wick Four!
Actually, it's gelato!
[grunts]
[muffled grunting]
The violence Mom won't let me watch
is the best.
- [car crashes]
- [gasps]
Damn it.
Whoa. Live violence.
[Marge] Homie, wake up.
There's been a car crash.
[whimpers]
[grunts]
[panting]
[yawns] What's happening?
There's been an accident.
Ooh, let's go gawk.
- [grunts]
- [Homer] Yeah! [chuckles]
[electricity crackles]
Marge, are you using a charger cord
as a robe belt?
[groans] Well, I lost my belt
and Bart lost this phone, so...
What's that mark on your sleeve?
I used it as an oven mitt.
My Milhouse buys me a new robe
every Christmas.
Ralphie bought me this chenille beauty
with his tooth fairy money.
What, don't you like any of the robes
your kids bought you?
They've never bought me a robe.
- The quintessential mom gift.
- Wha... Un-frigging-believable.
[both groan]
My kids give me homemade gifts,
like hand-turkeys
and macaroni-covered... [stammers] ...stuff.
Sounds like they're just giving you
their art class crap.
Feel this.
I like the thoughtful,
artistic gifts my kids... [gasps]
Oh, my God. That's plush. [gasps]
Yeah, my robe is fine.
It's just a little worn in spots.
Uh, one big spot in the back.
[groans] The top of my crack.
- Oh. [stammers] Come here. [groans]
- [Lisa, Bart grunt]
[chattering]
- [all] Whoa.
- Wow.
It's magical,
but it smells like burning flip-flops.
Ow. Ow. My flip-flops.
Careful! Live wire on the ground!
Whoa. Thank you, Homer.
[sighs] You da man!
Did you hear that?
Kirk said I was "da man."
I mean, it sounded stupid
the way he said it, but still...
Well, uh, if you wanna be "da man"
for everybody,
you should post a warning about
that live wire on Alarmist.
It's this app that alerts neighbors
to local dangers.
Downloading now.
You film dangerous stuff and post it.
You know, traffic accidents,
nighttime animals out during the day.
Uh, hello. This is Homer Simpson.
Username, uh, The Simp.
There's a live wire sparking
on Evergreen Terrace.
Risk of electrocution: 1000%.
[all gasp]
A thousand percent?
My baby could have played with that wire.
He ain't born, but he's 'bout to be.
Congratulations.
You're now part of the Alarmy Army.
Hey. I can barely read my name
without my cheaters.
How do I get a bigger font
like these guys?
Um, those are the top alarmers on the app.
You want your name
in a readable font size?
- You better learn how to spread fear.
- I'll do it!
I'll get to the top of this leaderboard
if it's the most useless thing I ever do!
Bart, we need to talk
about Mom's birthday present.
Finishing it as we speak.
Ta-da!
Uh, it might be time to retire
the pasta art genre.
What? In my vital bucatini phase?
You heard what those judgy women said
about our presents.
We need to buy Mom a present this year.
Where we gonna get money?
Otto stopped paying for clean urine.
Hmm. Mr. Flanders is generous.
I've sold him
so many magazine subscriptions.
Why Cat Fancy?
His cat isn't even that fancy.
[humming]
Yo, Flan-man. We're trying to make
some scratch for our mom's birthday gift.
You need any help cleaning this mess up?
Sorry. I always keep my grass trimmed.
You know the old saying,
"The lawn is the mustache of the house."
[sighs] We get it. We just thought
Mom deserved something nice,
but if you don't think so,
hmm, that's cool.
Now, uh, hold on.
If, uh, you clean those two leaves
on my sidewalk up,
I'll give you $44.
- Both leaves? Ow.
- [Lisa grunts]
Deal.
This store has everything.
[gasps] This will make Mom feel cozy
and loved.
And it'll put a sock in the yaps
of those gossipy hens.
I'm gonna ignore the problematic "hens"
because I support the sentiment.
[both] Whoa.
Is it a toy?
Yes, but it's also gear.
It's got a pen
that's actually a tape recorder,
an eavesdropping device that lets you hear
conversations from miles away,
and when you get in a tight spot,
sour-gummy cyanide capsules.
This could change everything.
Deep down, I know I'm the dingus. [sobs]
[recording of sobbing plays]
Give me your lunch money
or the whole playground hears you blubber.
You too, bow tie.
The eavesdropper could be so useful.
Okay. The meeting of the cool girls
has been called to order.
It's been decided that the new cool thing
is to wear earmuffs in warm weather.
So don't tell any randos bec... [gasps]
Hey, guys. [chuckles]
[gasps] Now Lisa's cool too
and there's nothing we can do about it.
[all crying]
[chuckling] Yes. Cry, Sherri. Cry.
Mkay, just thinking out loud.
This kit is the same price as the robe...
- [gasps] Are you suggesting that we...
- You know I am.
Say yes. Come on, Lis.
I need two keys to launch this missile.
Mom has never really been a gift person.
True. She's more into stuff like hugs
and seeing us happy.
But we can't just buy a spy kit for us
and nothing for Mom, I... [gasps]
Bart?
[panting] Bart, we can't do this.
Would you like to apply
for a Bullseye credit card?
I'm eight.
Yeah, you won't get it.
But if you apply, you get
a free Bullseye ironing board cover.
[gasps] We could buy the spy kit
and give Mom the ironing board cover.
That's like giving her
a whole new ironing board.
Give me an application.
We'll give her two ironing board covers.
♪ Happy birthday to you! ♪
Uh, open my present first.
I gotta hit the streets.
I have citizens to alarm.
Another charm for my charm bracelet.
That bracelet was
the smartest investment ever.
No matter what the occasion,
I always know what you need:
another charm.
You know me so well.
I better after however many years.
Open mine next.
Oh. An ironing board cover.
Yeah, 'cause, you know, you iron.
I sure do.
Open mine. It's in the Bullseye bag.
Mmm. Such clever wrapping. [chuckles]
[mutters] It's another
ironing board cover.
What do you get for the woman
who has only one ironing board cover?
Thank you. Both of you. I love them.
I got to hit the road.
If I find just three more things
to warn people about,
I'll move ahead of Cautionary Gale
and Cry Wolfcastle on the leaderboard.
We'll help clean up. [grunts]
No! I'll do it.
You guys have done so much for me.
[sighs]
[grunts]
[groaning] Oh.
Enjoying your present, huh?
- Don't play with it all day.
- [groans]
We'll know soon enough who broke this va...
[gasps]
[groans]
[Bart] Yellow Sparrow, this is Slingshot.
Prepare for face-to-face discussion.
Roger that. Face is prepared.
This spy kit is great.
All the secrets of this house
are being laid bare.
And Mom loves her present.
She can't stop muttering about it.
- [watch beeps]
- We rule. Over.
Roger that. Over.
Inappropriate billboard
near Noiseland Arcade.
Guaranteed danger of corruption.
Keep children away.
[phone chimes]
Hmm. Whoa. Whoa.
Thanks for warning us
about the vulgar wordplay, Simp.
"Itch, please."
Wait, I get it. Itch rhymes with bi...
[mumbling]
No. Mom hates that word. Trust me.
One more post and I'll be top five.
Homer.
Religious fanatic running through town,
possibly from murder scene.
Avoid outdoors.
[phone beeps]
I did it.
- [yelping] Fanatic!
- I'm number five.
I'm better than everyone.
[static crackles]
[Frink] Uh-uh-uh, your name is not Frink.
You are Frink's monster, you see?
[Frink's monster groans] Frink sad.
[Frink] No, Frink's monster is sad.
What is wrong with you?
[Moe] All right, one of youse rats
has been eating the pool chalk
and leaving chalky pellets
all over the place.
No, no, don't look at each other.
Look at me!
Hey! Steve.
[Ned] Oh. Hey, Marge.
[Marge] Hi, Ned.
Ooh, that's Mom.
What a party yesterday.
I don't usually take my water
on the rocks.
I was buzzing all night.
Yeah, it was fun.
- [sobbing]
- [Lisa] Oh.
Whoa. I didn't mean to bring on
a peeper-puddle. What's wrong?
[Marge] It's silly. I...
I'm embarrassed that my feelings were hurt
by a stupid birthday gift.
[Ned] Oh, now, feelings aren't stupid.
Some of them are evil,
but they're not stupid.
It's just on my one day,
I'm barely an afterthought.
It's like they don't think of me
as a person.
[sighs]
[eavesdropper clicks]
I don't get it. Why is she so sad?
Bart, she's feeling unseen.
What? I always see her.
She's in my phone contacts three times,
under Mom, Mommy and Sandwich.
She does so many things
that we take for granted.
Imagine how we would feel
if she half-tushied our birthdays.
What? I'd be fine if she only...
[groans]
[sighing] Oh.
- [watch beeps]
- We suck. Over.
Roger that. Over.
[watch beeps]
As of this morning,
I am number one on the leaderboard
of the Alarmist App.
[gasps] Look at that.
What? The broken sprinkler?
We need to warn people.
It could cause a sinkhole
or activate a gremlin.
This is your Number One Alarmy,
with a warning that a geyser of water
is pouring onto...
- [phone beeps]
- Huh?
Hey, someone named Silver Bullet already
reported a "vertical tsunami at the park."
Whoa, that's good mongering.
I got scooped?
Silver Bullet is now Alarmy Number One.
What? Who is this guy?
Those fat fingers are too slow
for the Silver Bullet.
Silver Bullet, your days are numbered.
Tell me something my doctor hasn't.
You smell like old lady.
So do you.
I smell like a lot of things.
We have to get Mom a new present.
Something meaningful.
So, let's make a list of everything
we know about Mom.
Yes. Great idea.
[Lisa] Mmm.
Hmm. Her first name is actually Margaret.
Good. Write that down.
[Bart] Hmm.
Ooh, I know.
She loves coming to my jazz recitals.
Uh, no, she doesn't. She hides a copy
of People magazine in the program.
Oh. [groans]
Why is this so hard?
We should know
the woman who gave birth to us.
Maybe she's unknowable.
What if we just give her the spy kit
and breakfast in bed
for the rest of her life?
Or, you know that trunk where
Mom keeps all her memories and stuff?
What if we use the spy kit
to break into it?
Oh, welcome to the dark side.
[Lisa] Huh.
[gasps] Here we are.
I don't know if these lock picking tools
are even gonna work.
- I mean, this is just a toy, and...
- [lock clicks]
[gasps] Oh.
Now I'm concerned
about those gummy cyanide capsules.
Mom's birth announcement.
Oh, her name is Marjorie. Not Margaret.
We officially know nothing about her.
[Lisa] Hmm.
Mom had a parrot named Petey?
Oh, they were best friends.
Like me and Santa's Little Helper.
[dog whines]
Not now, boy. Busy.
[gasps] Look at this one.
[Bart groans] Mom's parents
must've given Petey away.
Hey, we just learned something about her.
Grandma was a jerk-ass.
Wait. Parrots live for, like, 80 years.
Maybe we could find Petey
and then reunite Mom
with her long-lost friend.
That would be like getting her a robe
that tells you it wants crackers.
How do we find this lady?
[Lisa] Well, we need to go
to North Townsburg.
Oh, that place is sketchy.
Milhouse's dad was a sign spinner
for a meth clinic there.
But let's do it. For Margotie!
Marjorie.
Whatever.
[groans] Townsburg is three hours away?
Fine.
I'll just kick the seat in front of me
until that little screw falls out.
- [grunting]
- That is so rude.
Well, you have to kick closer to the screw
like this.
[grunting]
[Chalmers grunts] Great.
[both groaning]
[groans] This place is depressing.
Isn't that the corner
where Nic Cage went crazy?
Yep, there's the statue.
[gasps] There's the mechanic's shop.
Let's do this.
Hey, grease stains. Seen this bird?
Yeah, I remember him.
That's Krista's bird.
He in some kind of trouble?
We'll ask the questions.
What's the skinny
on this Krista character?
Well, she owns the craft store
down the block.
She also sells liquor and weed.
- Let's go.
- Don't leave town.
But my niece's wedding is tomorrow.
I said, don't leave town.
Fine.
Hey, Shirl, it's Vince. I can't make it.
I don't know. Some kid told me
I can't leave town.
I gotta get back to being
Alarmy Number One.
Gotta warn people about... [groans]
...something. [gasps]
Death from above.
Falling branches in Springfield Park.
Stay away!
[phone beeps]
- My God, we have to get out of here.
- I did it!
- [Martin] What? [yelps]
- I'm Alarmy Number One.
Not for long, you toad-faced beanbag.
I will cut you into tiny pieces
like my son's pancakes.
I'm gonna eat you up and crap you out
The air at Springfield Park
is full of pollen.
Individuals with lungs
should avoid the area.
[Homer groans]
Lifeless bodies at the park.
Possible gas leak.
Demented man throwing objects
at the duck pond.
Chemical air attack at the play yard!
UFOs hovering over picnic area.
String-guided dragons,
most likely time travelers, attack...
I saw the kites first, you big galoot!
- [rumbling]
- [both scream]
Wh... What happened?
Ugh, the earth couldn't support
your giant ass.
Maybe Satan heard your voice
and decided to fast-track you to hell.
Okay, we both got one in.
How are we getting out of this sinkhole?
I dropped my phone. Do you have yours?
No, just start shouting.
Someone will hear us.
- Help! Save me, not her!
- Down here!
[passenger] Hurry. The dragons are coming.
[tires squealing]
Oh, yeah, Petey. He was smart as a whip.
Could imitate anything:
political figures of the day,
the "You Lose" horn from Price Is Right.
So many times, I thought contestants lost
when they hadn't.
Why are you talking about him
in the past tense?
Oh, I left his cage open by mistake
and he flew away.
Last I heard,
he joined a flock of wild parrots.
Oh, I guess we came
all this way for nothing.
Stay in town.
But my daughter's wedding is... [sighs]
Shirl. Bad news.
We failed Mom again.
We are losers.
[parrot imitating "You Lose" horn]
Bart, it's Petey.
- How can we lure him down here?
- Uh. Uh.
[gasps] I've got it.
[Marge] Bart,
are you secretly recording me?
I'm on hold to talk about our water bill.
I-I'm sorry. No, I'm not talking to you.
I'm talking to my annoying son.
- [grunts] Got him!
- [Bart] Yes!
[Petey] Annoying son.
[Agnes] Hello?
Can't any of you idiots hear us?
There's no one to save us.
We scared everyone away.
Isn't that ironic?
I guess.
No, I'm asking.
I don't know what ironic means.
Why did we get so crazy?
I was doing a public service.
I warned everyone that broken sprinkler
would cause a sinkhole.
Bull-scat.
You were trying to move up
the leaderboard. We both were.
Now we're stuck down here.
[sighs] I miss the surface world.
Hey, you gotta share that.
We both need strength to fight off CHUDs.
- Hell, no! My Werther's, my choice.
- [growls]
- Mmm.
- [Homer gasps, groans]
Yeah, yeah. You got candy in there.
Stop showing off.
- [chokes]
- Are you choking?
Hang on. I'll save you!
Wait. Is this irony?
Ow, ow!
Okay. I'm doing it. [grunts]
- [coughs, gasps] I can breathe.
- [sighs]
Simpson, instead of mongering fear,
you mongered...
Life itself.
Thank you.
[gasps] This is the feeling I was after,
not some stupid leaderboard.
I'm gonna help you get out of here.
Step in my hands. I'll boost you up.
[Agnes grunting]
- Oh. There's so much to grab onto.
- [Homer grunting]
I'll tell everyone you're down there,
which will make me Alarmy Number One.
Suck it.
Hairless ground hippo stuck in sinkhole.
And while...
She's horrible.
Mom, we have one more
birthday surprise for you.
Oh, really?
We tracked down your best friend.
Petey?
Petey.
How... How is this happening?
How is this happening?
- [screaming, grunting]
- [Petey] How is this happening?
- Get it off! Get it off before he...
- How is this happening?
- [Marge] Oh. Ugh.
- [Lisa] Ew.
- Ow. [screaming]
- [Lisa] Bart, do something!
[Bart grunts]
- Sorry.
- We thought he loved you.
This is how he shows love.
By grooming me and regurgitating on me.
I could never have friends over.
He was so possessive...
[squawking] Mine!
Mine! Mine! Mine! Mine!
[whistles]
[squawking]
So why did you even get him?
I didn't. I wanted a kitten.
Our neighbor was giving away their parrot.
Since Petey can meow,
my dad decided he was close enough.
Meow.
- You're nothing like a kitten! [gasps]
- [Petey screeches]
Don't worry.
We'll take him back to Townsburg.
He's part of a wild flock there.
You went all the way to Townsburg?
We wanted to get you something, you know,
personal for your birthday.
Yeah, we did not make friends
on the bus ride home.
Petey is kind of racist.
Well, that's just...
We're sorry.
We didn't mean to re-traumatize you
with your childhood nightmare bird.
My wonderful babies.
You went to all that trouble for me.
I wasn't an afterthought. I was a thought.
Well, yeah, 'cause, you know,
we see you as a person.
We really do.
[whimpering] Our favorite person.
Oh, that is so...
- [crunches]
- [screaming] Ow!
[groaning] You little... [grunts]
Who wants to help Mommy abandon Petey
in Townsburg?
- We do!
[tires screeching]
[thuds]
[chattering]
[neighbor] Did anybody see what happened?
Marge, what a beautiful robe.
Is that terry cloth?
French terry.
From the Terry province of France.
- Wow.
- Oh, France.
My kids got it for me.
I just threw it on
to see what that noise was.
I think it came from over there.
Look at the fullness in that sleeve.
What was that sound?
I don't see anything.
Meh. It's a mystery we may never know.
- Look at how it moves.
- Poetry in fabric.
[Bernice] You better work!
- [beeping]
- [Bart laughs]
Mission accomplished, over.
[both] Roger that, over.
Shh!