I got a few days left!
D'oh!
Hey, little lady.
You'd be a lot prettier
if you smiled.
What? Who are you?
I'm a man. So I know
what I'm talking about.
Smile and you'll be
a lot more popular.
Are you serious? You know I'll
remember this forever, right?
Well, that's what therapy's for.
And he told me I wouldn't be
pretty unless I smiled.
Sweetie, you are very pretty.
And thanks to the puberty app
on my phone,
we can see what lies ahead.
Wait. This can't be real.
I already had braces.
Well, I'm afraid
you have to get them again.
The man we thought was
your orthodontist
was actually
a rogue periodontist.
Rogue periodontist.
This family cheaps out
on everything.
Homer took me
to a psychiatrist.
After three sessions, I figured
out it was a goat with glasses.
Never went back.
Braces? Again?
Why am I the only one
in this family who needs braces?
Don't look so smug, boy.
Let's try this app on you.
Hello, Aaron Eckhart.
Puberty!
Let's see what comes next.
Cool.
Homie, look.
We got this in the mail today.
Aw, what is it?
Did I get drunk
and buy useless stuff
on eBay again?
Let's get more.
Hello, Simpsons.
It's me, Artie Ziff,
in prerecorded form.
So you can't talk to me.
I can't?
No, you can't.
Pause for laughs.
And thank you.
Artie Ziff?
Isn't that the rich guy
who could have been our dad?
I am the only man
your mother has ever been with,
and she doesn't have
a single regret.
- Well...
- You stay out of this, Marge!
Great news, I'm getting married,
and you're invited!
Why, you ask,
am I getting married?
I've found my soul mate!
Jealous?
April 12th,
very rich man's wedding.
Regrets only.
Chicken or fish.
Or vegan.
Bye!
So, what else is in the mail?
We got a flyer from Lowe's!
Three-quarter plywood.
$20 a sheet!
I'm a-comin'!
Oh, I don't have a car.
You're not really thinking
of going, are you?
That jerk kept trying
to break us up.
Now, I am sensing
conflicted feelings.
If you come, I promise you
a wonderful time.
Champagne, caviar,
deep-fried ice sculptures,
a guy who guesses your weight,
who always guesses low!
Thank you.
And now to celebrate,
here's Tupac Shakur!
Don't be tardy
My boy Artie
is throwing a party
This wedding's gonna be fly
Why won't you people
let me die?
How do you turn this off?
There's no off
to the Artie show.
- I decide when...
- Please set me free.
Oh, here it is.
God bless you.
Now everyone's favorite,
rinse and spit.
And I'm done...
with the top braces.
We'll put the bottoms in
next week.
And after that, just a lifetime
of wearing retainers.
Well, they're
practically invisible.
I can't close my mouth.
The brackets are holding up
your lips at the edges.
They'll adjust.
The main thing is you're happy.
I'm not happy.
Have a little nitrous.
Oh, they should
revoke your license.
More, please.
- That's enough.
- No, it's not!
Yeah, give me that.
I thought your name is
Kidzrule.
Shortened from Kidzrulovitch,
which is Romanian for
kill all the children.
That elevator has the capacity
for 32 people!
We brought a rhino
up here last week.
My headaches are so bad.
Jealous?
Feet.
You're one in a million.
Literally.
Don't fall off the roof.
Homer Simpson!
The man who beat me
to planet Marge.
You've done all right
for a billionaire.
Hey, I'm not made of money.
Although, actually I am.
After my parole, I got rich
selling fireplace logs
that look like cash,
i.e., Money to Burn.
That is the greatest.
It says Money to Burn.
It looks like
you're burning money!
Yes, that's the idea.
No, no, no.
It's so funny.
Don't you get it?
Of course I get it.
I thought of it.
No, no, no.
Listen, it says Money to Burn,
but it's actually...
I know! I know!
Talk to someone else.
Hey, pal, you're a news guy.
Give it to me straight.
Is this wedding on the level?
Here's the scoop.
It's legit!
In other news, local newsman
hopes to score with caterer.
This just in,
she knows I'm married.
Coming up at 11:00
nothing.
Now, Homer,
as this is a bachelor party,
I want to show you something.
But no word to the wives.
How did you meet your wife,
by the way?
Boy meets girl,
girl meets bank account.
Now, shut your eyes.
You've never seen a body
this enticing.
Exactly what I imagined!
Food coma. He'll be fine.
Hey, girlfriend!
Who, me?
Lisa, did you get
your eyebrows waxed?
You look amazing!
I don't have eyebrows.
Well, check out
these twin caterpillars.
What's going on?
Her smile makes me feel full,
like I actually ate dinner
last night.
If you never eat,
how come you're so fat?
Americans can be fat and poor.
That's what makes us so great.
And so, after saving Wilbur,
Charlotte crawled off to die,
as all barn spiders do
in the fall.
Bravo, Lisa.
What a positive note
on which to end the class.
Positive? Positive?
Charlotte died alone
at the saddest place on Earth,
an empty fairground.
Well, your smiling face
made dying alone fun.
And believe me,
that's where I'm headed.
So as long as I'm smiling,
it doesn't matter
what comes out of my mouth?
Or your nose.
I don't need these anymore.
This'll go good
in Willie's stew.
Can it really be
that people are this shallow?
Lisa! Lisa! Lisa!
And am I shallow enough
to enjoy this?
I am!
I'm so happy, I could sing!
Hello, world!
That really hurts
with the braces.
- Take your pick.
- What is it?
No idea.
The labels are in Spanish.
- Hey, gorgeous.
- Hey, Bart.
Lisa? Oh, yuck!
I didn't know that was you.
It's the smile. It's totally
changed how people see me.
Well, I just want you to know,
you'll always be gross to me.
Oh, thank God.
I was having doubts,
trying to figure out
if this is sexist.
And then I found this.
It seems like
ever since the pill,
the workplace has been
full of single women.
Here's your coffee, Jim.
Extra sugar,
just how you like it.
Remind me to get a divorce.
But some women are
having trouble fitting in.
Well, I can't
figure it out, Jim.
I was all prepared
for a big presentation,
but it went over
like a nun at a go-go bar.
Well, there's one thing
you didn't prepare,
and that's your face.
But I'm wearing a pound
of Mary Kay.
Let me touch your body
and show you the problem.
No need to ask.
You've got a secret weapon
sitting in the middle
of your face.
Now you're sure
to get that promotion.
Really?
No.
Don't you see
why I hate this?
'Cause you hate everything?
Because it makes
that jerky old guy right!
I am more popular
because I'm smiling.
Told ya!
Not a single picture
of Artie.
Maybe he has matured.
Well, I guess being here sort of
ends a chapter in my life.
So, lehayim.
That's odd.
Not one person
from the bride's family.
Excuse me. We need someone to
walk the bride down the aisle.
Could you?
First, tell me one thing.
How long is the aisle?
About 20 feet.
All right, I'll do it.
But double cake.
They grow up so fast.
I knew this day would come.
You'll always be
my little girl.
If he ever hurts my baby,
I'll kill him.
Oh, for crying out loud.
Friends, family,
I take great delight
in informing you
that the bride and groom
have written their own vows.
Stick to the script, amateurs!
Oh, my God.
This is too weird.
Artie, you are
the greatest lover ever.
When we make sex,
it is so, so good.
I can't take this anymore.
We're getting out of here.
Yeah. This is really creepy.
Even the rhino's leaving.
You may now kiss the bride.
And this is a picture of us
at our wedding.
You're so happy.
And here's us on our honeymoon.
Two days in Ohio,
two days in Michigan,
and, booyah, up to Ontario
for some international flavor.
I'm not happy.
I have a drawing of
you saying that in Michigan.
This smile is so wrong.
There's nothing
to be happy about.
The world is a mess,
and so is this school.
I mean, how hard is this?
The happy girl put the thing
in the hole!
Wait a minute.
I could use my new power
to change these things,
use it for good.
Indubitably.
Hear, hear! Hear, hear!
I can make it happen.
Hurry!
You posers.
I was for Lisa
before it was cool.
You never liked Lisa.
What?
You got to remember that.
That's my one thing!
No. Your thing is
crying when you're punched.
Prove it.
Aw, you're taking
all the fun out of it.
The polls are in,
and you're doing great.
You're picking up the key group,
girls who don't like Milhouse.
You're big with swing voters,
but the teeter-totters
could go either way.
What about the kids
on the slide?
Eh, they're up and down,
but the kids on the monkey bars
are climbing.
That's all I got.
Like every election
with one week to go,
this is in the bag.
Don't be so sure.
I'm up against a tough opponent.
Dubya Spuckler.
Look at this negative ad he did.
Lisa Simpson says writin'
ends with a G
and 'rithmetic
starts with a A.
You know what I say?
Don't worry.
You just keep smiling.
Well, I do have an orthodontist
appointment tomorrow
for a tune-up.
In the bag, Madam President.
Bup, don't be so sure.
Hey, I drew a picture
of your inauguration.
I don't think
I've ever looked more radiant.
Okay, kid.
Your bottom braces are on.
What happened to my smile?
No, no, no, this is terrible.
I look like I actually feel.
In six months,
you'll have perfect teeth.
Six months?
I have to smile now.
No, I can power through this.
Ralph lost his retainer
in the trash.
What can we do here?
New ones are $500.
So just what is
this secret mission, Chief?
Well, let's just say
you're on retainer.
- Let's see. I'll take this.
- Aw, stop that.
Aw, come on, Marge.
This minibar is paid for.
Do you know the street value
of this Toblerone?
Homer, stop it.
I can't help thinking about
that poor woman.
Artie only married her
because she looks like me.
I mean, a lot like me.
You're right. We have
to find her and tell her.
But, first,
there's something naughty
I want to do with this bed.
Are you sure we should be here?
This is
technically his honeymoon.
Artie?
I'm at the lowest point
of my life!
But come on in.
As a woman,
I just want to tell your wife
what's really going on here.
Sure, why not?
Say it to her face!
Now you know my secret.
I've spent years trying
to build the perfect copy
of the only woman for me,
you, Marge.
But they were all inferior
in some way.
This one lacks kindness.
This one keeps trying
to kill me.
This one's head is a toaster!
And the slots aren't even
big enough for a bagel!
Why would you marry a machine?
I didn't.
It was one last trick.
I thought when you saw
how perfect we look together,
you would realize
that we were meant to be.
I am, as the poet once said,
a dumb schmuck.
- Artie.
- Yes?
You're not dumb. You're smart.
And I think this crazy project
actually had
some brilliance in it.
Imagine if you use
that noodle for good.
Only you could find a pearl
in the flabby oyster that is me.
I will become
a better human being.
Terrific.
And then you'll love me?
No.
Well, then, I finally give up.
Or do I?
Aw, damn it.
Artie, you and your blue crew
of Margekateers
have done so many good deeds.
What's next?
I'm gonna make one of them
my bride.
Hey, I didn't give you wings.
Life finds a way!
Let's quiet down, please.
The sooner we can
get this debate over,
the sooner the teachers
can get ice cream.
None for Seymour.
He gets gassy.
Yeah, I know.
And now we have
a very special moderator,
Governor Mary Bailey.
Our first candidate is
Dubya Spuckler.
Dubya! Dubya!
That's your brother.
He prefers the pronoun they,
on account of the twin
he absorbed in my belly.
Our other candidate is ill,
so she'll be Skyping in.
Lisa Simpson.
Lisa, I'm sorry,
what do you have?
What I have is
an agenda for this school,
an agenda that looks forward.
I can deliver results,
while my opponent
can't even spell results.
Yes, I can.
R-E squiggly letter,
bucket letter, tall man,
little plus sign,
squiggly letter.
Results.
That's not how
you spell results.
Lisa doesn't sound sick at all.
You said
you've done this before.
It was my machismo talking.
Lisa's using a funny-face app.
Listen, I tried to fool you,
and that was wrong.
This is an abomination!
What are you doing
at a school debate?
My illegitimate son goes here.
Oh, the shame.
I still have good ideas.
All I hear is nag, nag, nag.
Dubya! Dubya!
Oh, boy.
I didn't want to believe
my popularity was
based on my stupid smile.
Oh, but it was.
You're just a kid,
and things are changing.
In the future,
women will be judged
by what they say,
not how they look.
Maybe, but the future is
a really long way away.
Told you you should smile more.
The future is now!
A toast. I have finally
perfected you.
You all look just like Marge,
and you will never leave.
Now, which of you lucky girls
wants to party with Arty?
I am in power save mode.
Oh, fine.
What about you two?
Power save.
One percent battery.
I just don't like you.
That counts as a kiss.