♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
Grampa! I don't mind
when you spit at home,
but I have to work
with these people.
Oh, jabberjack.
Schoolhouse don't
put out spittoons.
I ain't responsible.
(spits)
All right, seniors. We'd all love
to share in your wisdom, experience--
Yadda, yadda, yadda.
Let's start
with Milhouse's grandfather.
Uh, how many of you
have a house?
All right.
Now, how many of you
drove your house
to school today?
-(kids muttering)
-Huh?
Well, I did.
(chuckles)
No, I'm not Superman.
I just own an R.V.
Me and the new wife
travel the country
searching for adventure.
Last fall, we won a chili
cook-off in Beaumont, Texas.
CHILDREN:
Wow.
You're living in a
fool's paradise, Van Houten.
If you fell down in the shower,
that thing would be your tomb.
Grampa, hush.
Here, why don't you spit some more?
(chuckles)
No, I'm not Superman.
I'm a judge.
Why, just this morning,
I sentenced my 46th man
to death.
Oh-- No, 47th.
(applause)
Wow, 47.
I love you, Grampa.
Yeah, well-- I may not have
a fancy black bathrobe
and a hammer like Snooty,
but I do have slippers
and an oatmeal spoon. Look.
(kids snickering)
Bart, perhaps
your grandfather
would like to come up front now
and give someone else a chance
to interrupt.
Oh, please, no.
-'Bout time, Knothead.
-Aah!
Now...
Hey, listen!
Now, my story begins
in 19-dickety-two.
We had to say "dickety"
'cause the Kaiser had stolen
our word "twenty."
I chased that rascal
to get it back
but gave up after
dickety-six miles.
(Martin chortles)
"Dickety"?
Highly dubious.
What you cackling at, fatty?
Too much pie,
that's your problem.
Now, I 'd like to digress
from my prepared remarks
to discuss how I invented
the terlet.
"Terlet." Ha!
(all laughing)
Stop your snickering.
I spent three years
on that terlet.
And then he claimed
he was the one
who turned cats and dogs
against each other.
Why is he always making up
those crazy stories?
Maybe it's time we put Grampa
in a home.
You already
put him in a home.
Maybe it's time we put him in
one where he can't get out.
No! Old people
deserve our respect.
Look at Jacques Cousteau
and Goldie Hawn.
You wouldn't shut them away
like second-class citizens.
Second-class?
What about Social Security,
bus discounts,
MedicAlert jewelry,
Gold Bond powder,
pants all the way up
to your armpits,
and all those other
senior perks?
Oh, if you ask me,
old folks have it pretty sweet.
(groans)
Let's see.
Ehh...
(sighs)
(muttering)
Eh, this junk was hardly worth
getting up for.
Maybe if I go back to sleep
for a few days,
some good mail will build up.
Hey, what's this?
"Asa Phelps has--"
(gasps)
The Seventh Hellfish is dead?
That means the fortune's
almost mine.
Asa Phelps spent his entire life
in Springfield
except for
four years' service
in World War II,
and one high school day-trip.
He worked at the United Strut
and Bracing Works
as a molder's boy
until he was replaced
by a molder-matic and died.
Would you do the honors?
Well, Simpson,
seven gone.
As soon as you're in
your pressboard coffin,
I'll be the sole survivor,
and the treasure will be mine.
Over my dead body
it will.
That's exactly the point--
Oh, Simpson,
can't you go five seconds
without humiliating yourself?
(boinging)
How long was that?
Your clownish behavior
notwithstanding,
we have made
a gentlemen's agreement
and sworn on our lives
to honor it.
Smithers, I want
that man killed.
(boinging)
Let's see, "mesmerists,
dowsers, luddites,
alienists, Zoroastrians,
alphabetizers--"
Aha! "Assassins."
I was wondering, sir,
do we really need to, uh,
"settle" Abe Simpson?
I mean, I 'm familiar with
his physical state and--
Perhaps if we wait, nature
will assassinate him for us.
Well, I can't risk it.
I won't allow that Simpson boy
to take the Hellfish bonanza,
and I can't get it
without his key.
Ah, just the man I need.
Fernando Vidal, the world's
most devious assassin.
(phone ringing)
Hola.
BURNS: Fernando, it's M.B.
Ah, Marion Barry.
Is it time
for another shipment already?
This is Montgomery Burns.
Oh, caramba.
I'm sending you a photo
over the faxtrola.
I need you to fly to Springfield
and assassinate this man,
post-haste.
Ah, Del Monte.
Enjoy them, old man.
They will be your last.
(snoring)
(alarm ringing)
I'm up! I'm up!
Ah, he's more clever
than he looks.
-(buzzing)
-WOMAN (on speaker): Abraham Simpson,
your family is here
to visit you.
Hot diggity, my family's
come to visit me!
Wait a minute.
My family never comes to vi--
(yells)
D'oh, not again!
I can't take much more
of your blundering numskullery.
I'll be in the car, dudes.
There is one more way
to kill a man,
but it is
as intricate and precise
as a well-played game of chess.
Was that me,
or was that you?
Nurse! Nurse!
Someone's trying to kill me!
Okay, we'll do something
about that right away.
Let's start
by doubling your medication.
The residents...
are trying...
to nap!
(pounding on door)
Let me in!
Someone's trying
to kill me!
Sweet merciful McGillicuddy,
you got to open the door!
Who is it?
It's Grampa.
And it sounds like he's gotten
into the horseradish again.
And then a knife flew
at my head,
and you were there--
And you were there.
Uh, Grampa, maybe I should
moisten your washcloth.
It's plenty moist!
Listen, Monty Burns
is trying to kill me,
and it's all because--
Of, um-- I can't tell you why.
Well, I 'm sure
you'll make up something.
Maybe you just need
more of my classmates around.
I got to hole up here
for a while.
They might still be after me.
Wow, he's even more
agitated than usual.
Maybe we should
let him stay.
Where are we going
to put him?
-Bart's room.
-Dumpster.
Sorry to crowd you, boy,
but I'll let you in
on a secret.
Burns is after me
'cause he wants
the Hellfish bonanza.
Look, if you're going
to stay in my room,
could you at least
stop making up gibberish?
Gibberish, eh?
Then what's this?
Wrinkly gibberish?
Why, you smart--
I got this in the
second World War II.
Back then, I was known
as sergeant Simpson,
and I commanded
the Flying Hellfish--
the fightingest squad
in the fightingest company
in the third-fightingest
battalion in the army
and we were all
from Springfield.
There was police chief Wiggum's
father, Iggy Wiggum.
Um, if anybody finds a grenade
without a pin, that's mine.
Our radioman,
Sheldon Skinner.
All right, very funny.
Well, I didn't join the service
to make friends.
And watching our backs
was private fifth class
Arnie Gumble.
(loud belch)
Then there was also
Griff, Asa, Ox and Etch.
But every unit has
a troublemaker.
Ours was a cocky little private
named Montgomery Burns.
(yawns)
Haven't you won the war yet?
Duh, hey, you said you was dead.
Yes, dead tired.
But I 'm quite refreshed now.
Thank you.
Mm-hmm.
You bossed around the richest,
most powerful guy in town.
How come you were a sergeant
and he was only a private?
Well, he got busted down
for obstructing a probe
from J. Edgar Hoover.
We got stuck with him.
(Grampa chuckles)
Now they'll never
save your brain, Hitler.
A little help?
(shells whistling
and exploding)
(whimpering)
Boom! Boom, it went.
Boom! Just like that.
They took a photo of my keister
for Stars and Stripes.
At least they told me
it was for Stars and Stripes.
Well, if you saved Burns' life,
why does he want to kill you?
It was the closing days
of the war.
We had just flushed some Germans
out of an abandoned castle--
-Hey, Burnsie found some pictures.
-Wait a minute.
We ain't a-sposed
to steal from civilians.
You want me to report you
to Commander Flanders?
Just leave them, Burnsie.
Leave them for whom,
the Germans?
The folks
who shoot at us all day?
Let's just take them.
We'll all be rich,
rich as Nazis.
-Whoa!
-Yeah.
He's got a point there.
Think of what a guy
could get himself
with that kind of scratch.
I could buy chicken dinners
three times a day.
I could buy a brand new Studebaker
with a fan on the dashboard.
I could buy my way into high--
(belches)
...society.
Well, I don't feel
right about it,
but I could use a nest egg
for retirement.
I'd hate to wind up
in one of them old folks' homes.
Then it's agreed.
Of course, we can't sell
the paintings now.
We'd be caught.
How many of you are familiar
with the concept
of a "tontine"?
All right, Ox. Why don't you
take us through it?
Duh, essentially,
we all enter into a contract
whereby the last
surviving participant
becomes the sole possessor
of all them purty pictures.
Well put, Oxford.
Now, remember, you can't
all sign with an "X."
GRAMPA:
So we sealed up the paintings
knowing only one of us would
ever look upon them again.
Ox was the first to go.
He got a hernia carrying
the crate out of the castle.
Five more men died in the Veterans' Day
float disaster of '79.
Now, with Asa gone,
it's down to me and Burns.
Great story, Grampa.
Could have used
a vampire, though.
'Night.
Oh-- My own grandson
thinks I'm a liar.
(loud buzzing)
(yells)
Don't kill me!
I've tried to meet you
halfway on this, Simpson,
but you had to be
little Johnny Live-A-Lot.
Now, give me your key
to the Hellfish bonanza.
Oh, wow.
There really is a treasure.
Whatever you do,
don't give him the key, Grampa.
Here's the key.
Aw-- Figures.
Hey, Mr. Burns!
Can I go with you
to get the treasure?
I won't eat much,
and I don't know
the difference between
right and wrong.
Oh, you're a good boy,
but the child labor people
have been watching me
like a hawk.
Well, I 'm off
to get the paintings.
As they say, time is "Monets."
As you were, Sergeant.
(chuckles)
Oh, terribly sorry.
Back to sleep, little girl.
LISA:
Santa?
Well, I guess Burns
is finally going to be rich.
Not without
the keys, he isn't.
Hey! You got the keys.
Now we can get the treasure.
Oh, what's the use?
Burns would still find
some way to take it from me.
I can't believe you,
Grampa.
The sergeant
in that story you told
would never be scared
of a dork like Burns.
You got to get
that treasure.
You got to do it for Ox and Asa
and Griff and Burnsie.
Well, not so much Burnsie.
You really think
I can do it?
Uh-- Yes.
But we got to act fast.
Where are you two
going at this hour?
-On a treasure hunt.
-Oh, can I come?
Only if you're ready
to stare danger in the face,
put your manhood
to the ultimate test,
-and take--
-Pass.
Hey, Grampa, do you think
your dead buddies
get up and walk
around at night?
If they're anything like me,
they have to get up twice.
Okay, hold up here.
Fellas, it's me, Sarge.
At ease.
I know I'm bending
the rules tonight,
but I also know
none of you wants
that skunk Burns
to take our treasure.
And I want you to know
that when I die,
you're all welcome
to visit me
in rich man's heaven.
(rumbling)
Now it's going to show us
exactly where to dig.
TOGETHER:
D'oh!
Boy, you borrow us
some diving equipment
while I borrow this boat.
Well, howdy-doodily,
stranger.
Couldn't help but notice
you stealing my boat.
I'll bring it back.
-You ever operated
a power boat?
-No.
-Know anything
about water safety?
-No.
-What do you need it for?
-It's a secret.
Sounds spine-tingly-dingling.
Just promise you'll
have a good time.
Maude, boys, come on up.
We're going to have
a camp-out in the dinghy.
KIDS:
Yay!
Now, remember the plan, boy.
If you run out of air,
tug on the rope--
64 times. No more,
no less. Got it.
No, 63 times
if you're out of air.
64 is if you've
found the treasure.
Gotcha.
Hey, Grampa,
do you think
I could have been
a Flying Hellfish?
You're a gutsy daredevil
with a give-'em-hell attitude
and a fourth-grade
education.
You could have made sergeant.
(gurgling)
Wow!
Sixty-one,
sixty-two,
sixty-three!
Oh, no, 63!
He's out of air!
I've sent my only grandson
to a watery--
Sixty-four!
He found the treasure!
I'm rich!
You're one heck
of a grandson, boy.
Now let's break her open
and have a look-see.
Huh. The light must
have burned out.
I'll thank you to stop
pinching my Botticelli.
(gasps)
Looks like I didn't need
the keys after all.
I'll take the masterpieces,
thank you.
Consarn it.
You coward.
You're an embarrassment
to the name Hellfish.
Oh, am I?
No. Look, take
the art if you want.
Just don't hurt the boy.
Hmm-- I'd rather do both.
(gasping)
So long, Sarge. See you
at the reunion in November.
(gasping)
(gurgling)
I'm sorry I cost you
your fortune, Grampa.
The fortune
doesn't matter, boy.
The important thing
is you're safe.
Now let's get that fortune!
They're gaining on us, sir.
We'll have to jettison
something.
It's been an honor
to serve you, sir.
Consarn it,
he's getting away.
In a pig's eye he is.
Act your age, Simpson.
You look foolish.
Don't kill me.
I ain't gonna kill you.
That would be cowardly,
Monty Burns cowardly.
I just want to watch
you squirm.
Yes, sir.
Is this to your liking?
(grunting)
Now, Burnsie,
there's one thing
we don't stand for
in the Hellfish
and that's trying to kill
your commanding officer.
So consider this
your dishonorable discharge.
You're out of my unit,
you're out of the tontine,
and that means
the paintings are mine.
Private, you are dismissed.
You're rich, Grampa.
You did it.
And Burns can never
take that away from you.
(sirens wailing)
Freeze. U.S. State Department.
We'll take those.
We've been helping
the German government
search for this stolen art
for 50 years.
To avoid
an international incident,
we'll be returning it
to the descendants
of its rightful owner.
Baron von Wortzenburger,
on behalf of the American
people, I apologize--
Ja, ja, ja--
mach schnell mit
der art things, da?
I must get back
to dancecentrum in Stuttgart
in time to see Kraftwerk.
Hey, und, dummkopf,
watch out for the C.D. changer
in my trunk, huh?
Idiot.
(techno-pop playing)
I guess he deserves it
more than I do.
Well, at least
I got to show you
I wasn't always
a pathetic old kook.
You never were, Grampa.
Oh, I'd hug you, but I know
you'd just get embarrassed.
I won't get embarrassed.
I don't care who knows
I love my Grampa.
Hey, fun boys, get a room.
(synthesizer)
♪ Body control ♪
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.