(eerie music plays)
CHORUS SINGS:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
(grunts)
♪♪
(gunshot)
(all breathing heavily)
(annoyed grunt)
♪♪
(humming tune)
Ach, that stump is really eating
into my tractor budget.
I'll have to use me explosives.
Explosives?
Great.
If we put charges
on the load-bearing walls,
we can blow up detention hall
while leaving
the art room unharmed.
-Hmm?
-Hey, I like art, okay?
I'm blowing up the stump,
not the school.
Right, right.
You never saw that.
(chuckling)
Sweeeet!
Well done, boy.
Wait, here comes
the "mykeeyah."
What's a mykeeyah?
My Kia!
(both laughing)
I'm laughing to fit in,
but I still don't get it.
Miss Hoover,
what's our lesson today?
Is it school?
Oh, I don't know. Let's see.
Family trees.
Who here knows
what a family tree is?
Oh, family trees--
the charts representing
genealogical relationships
in a branching structure.
Very good, Lisa.
Class, your assignment
over the weekend will be
to make your own family tree,
emphasizing any notable
or distinguished ancestors.
I can't wait to see
what noble branches lie
in the Simpson family foliage.
(exclaims)
No, this can't be right.
Yech, they're all horrible.
Yeah, the Simpson family is
a long line of horse thieves,
deadbeats, horse beats, dead
thieves, and even a few...
(whispering):
...alcoholics.
There must have been
some good ancestors.
Grampa, don't you know any?
Not a one.
Maybe the nicest was
Abigail Simpson,
who you know
as the Pittsburgh Poisoner.
Listen, Lisa,
you're gonna find
more than you
bargained for.
If I were you, I wouldn't
dig into the past.
I lived in some of that past,
and I got out for a reason.
I won't give up.
I have to know that somewhere
in the muck and the mire
and the Pittsburgh Poisoners,
this family had a noble spark,
and I will find it, even if I
have to go back to Adam and Eve.
Oh, you mean
Adam and Eve
Simpson,
or as you may know them,
Julius and Ethel Rosenberg.
(groans)
(grunting)
Ooh! Whoa!
Well, are you gonna
help me or what?
(slurps)
(cracking)
Thank you.
So, what are you
looking for?
Family records for a school
project on genealogical...
Hey, that's great.
♪♪
Hmm. Dad's idea pad.
Bicentennial issue of
Reader's Digest.
Old ad for Buzz Cola.
(gasps)
So dusty.
The "Diary of Eliza Simpson"?
This entry is dated
April 14, 1860.
I warn you: I don't
know what's in there,
but if it's about a Simpson,
you ain't gonna be proud.
Our ancestors were kicked
out of Australia.
Oh, stop.
It's the journal
of a sweet little girl.
Keep reading, honey.
"Dearest diary,
today I am the happiest girl
in Springfield..."
See, all good.
"...because tomorrow I shall get
my very first slave."
(all gasp)
I can't believe we're descended
from slave owners.
Me neither.
For once, the Simpsons
were in management.
Homer.
Oh, read a little more, honey.
"Saturday, April 14, 1860.
Dear Diary, I must be brief,
for tonight is the grand ball
at Colonel Burns's plantation."
I shall dress myself in finery,
like a well-to-do
Southern belle.
What's for dinner?
-Possum.
-Oh, can't we have opossum?
Not on your salary.
I can't believe I buttoned
my britches for this.
In my elegant gown,
no one will suspect
that I'm actually
on a mission to help
my very first slave
escape to freedom.
Yes! She wasn't
a slave owner.
Our family was on
the Underground Railroad.
We ran a subway station?
No, the Underground Railroad
was a bunch of people who helped
slaves escape to Canada.
There were no actual trains
and it wasn't under ground.
Then they should've called it
the Aboveground Normal-Road.
-Good point, Bart.
-Absolutely right.
-Hadn't thought of that before.
-Very good, Bart.
That's a great
story, Lisa!
And you should stop
reading right there.
(gasps)
Wh-What are you doing?
I want to know
what happens next.
Well, I don't.
The motto of
the Simpsons is:
"Quit while you're ahead."
I made it into
a sampler.
It's like when your
father and I left
the movie Carrie right after
she was crowned prom queen.
She was so happy.
She'd had a lot of problems,
but they were all behind her.
But, but,
but-but-but...
Time for bed, sweetie.
(grunts in protest)
ELIZA:
Lisa. Lisa, it's me.
Eliza, the one good Simpson.
I've got so much more
to tell you.
I must know.
(panting)
(humming)
You still reading
that thing?
I'm warning you: When
something goes into that vent,
it shouldn't come out...
ever.
Well, I am reading it,
and when I'm finished,
I'm gonna use Eliza's diary
for my "Black History Month"
presentation.
Ooh, good idea.
Bart, what are you doing
for Black History Month?
I got an idea:
You can march to Selma,
and tell her she's ugly!
(laughs)
(gags)
Listen.
"April 20, 1860.
A week ago, I had no idea
what the future would bring,
which, I guess, is always true
of everyone all the time.
Anyway, last Saturday night,
I went to Colonel Burns's ball."
("Blue Danube Waltz" playing)
I don't like this
new Viennese dance
craze, "the waltz."
One, two, three,
one, two, three...
Where's the "four"?
All music needs a four!
I'll have the orchestra
adjust its time signature, sir.
See that you do.
♪♪
(whispering)
(music switches
to four-four time)
(all clamoring)
ELIZA:
In the confusion,
I slipped out of the ball
and made my way to the stables,
where I was to meet
Mr. Burns's slave, Virgil.
But when I got to the stables,
he was nowhere to be seen.
Virgil?
Virgil, let's go.
(screeching)
(screaming)
(grunts)
You look like you
could use a little help.
Actually, I'm here
to help you.
-Follow me north to freedom.
-I don't think so.
Why? Because I'm young
and I'm a woman?
No, because you're
pointing south.
(sheepish chuckle)
Oh, right, right. Sorry.
It's my first time.
That's all right.
It's my 14th.
As we made our way northward,
a couple of patrollers
spotted us.
Well, well, well.
Where do you think
you're going?
-(gasps)
-(gasps) Run!
-After them!
-Obviously.
Well, you didn't say it.
(horses neighing)
Hearts pounding,
we fled into the woods,
but their horses were fast.
(horses neighing)
♪♪
Escape seemed impossible.
(neighing)
(crumbling)
MARGE:
What happened next?
Uh, bu...
That's all there is.
The rest of the diary
has turned to dust.
(sniffs, sneezes)
(snapping)
Oh! I'll never know if Eliza
got Virgil safely to freedom.
Cheer up, sweetie.
Maybe we can find the
answer in the library.
To the reference desk!
The library?
Bart, can you believe
we're married to those nerds?
(both laugh)
LIBRARIAN:
There are no books
about an Eliza Simpson,
but I did find this.
MARGE:
Ooh, a cookbook.
(Marge gasps)
That's Eliza's mother!
Martha, you are
the best!
MARGE:
"Pork Butt In Cream,"
"Snout-Fried Neck"
"Frog-Haunch," "Hooves Au Jus,"
"Possum Pouch Pie..."
Please don't
make those recipes.
This one doesn't sound
roadkill-y.
And it comes with a story.
"Many years ago,
my daughter, Eliza,
brought a runaway slave,
Virgil, to the house."
(gasps) They made it back
to the house? How?
MARGE:
The patrollers were too fast
for Eliza and Virgil.
(owl hooting)
Luckily, they chanced
upon a traveling circus...
...where they were helped
by a crusty, old clown.
A little schmutz, a little
schmear, and presto!
You're part of the
under-clown railroad.
So, you got any talent?
Well, I am a bit musical.
♪ The sun shines bright ♪
♪ On my old Kentucky home. ♪
Rule number one:
never be better than me.
And I'm pretty bad.
Nothing to see here--
just a couple of clowns, and the
world's youngest bearded lady.
That I is.
-(spits)
-(dings)
Look at her any longer, you're
gonna have to pay a nickel.
Why do I always ask
for a nickel?
That's like 20 bucks
in 2010 money.
Wait! All that was
in the recipe?
It was a footnote. See?
"Anyway, I was very proud of
Eliza, but my husband Hiram
had not quite caught
abolition fever."
Uh-uh, no way.
He'll get me in trouble.
Maybe you'll change
your mind about me
after you try some
of my wheel cakes.
Wheel cakes?
They're just
honey-sweetened batter...
Go on.
...deep-fried in hog lard.
Lard, you say.
Then dusted with powdered sugar.
(muffled):
You can stay.
You swear
you'll help him?
(gulps)
I give you my word
as a Southern gentleman.
Whoo!
(gulps)
So they did the right thing.
My quest is fulfilled.
Our family has heroes!
Shh.
(softly):
Our family has heroes.
(quiet chuckle)
Martin Luther King had a dream.
Dreams are where
Elmo and Toy Story
had a party and I went there.
Yay. My turn is over.
One of your best, Ralph.
Next up, we have Simpson, L.
My Black History Month
presentation is called
"The Simpsons:
The First Family of Freedom."
No, no, no, not now! Quit, quit!
No, don't quit the program,
just the update, you stupid...
(awkward chuckle)
Computers, right?
Our story begins with
a spunky little spitfire
named Eliza Simpson.
The year was 1860, and the
Underground Railroad was...
("The Battle Hymn
of the Republic" playing)
...though Hiram, Mabel,
and Eliza
are no longer among us,
their truth goes marching on.
-(applause)
-Thank you.
-(applause stops)
-(one person clapping slowly)
Bravo, Lisa.
Very entertaining, but then
again, fairy tales always are.
(all gasping)
What are you talking about?
I hold in my hand another diary.
That of my great-great-great...
(takes hit from inhaler)
...great-great grandfafa,
Milford van Houten.
(audience murmurs)
"April 22nd, 1860..."
(strong Southern accent):
I was reclining beneath
a sarsaparilla tree,
reading about one
of Mr. Thomas Jefferson's
marvelous inventions.
when suddenly I heard
quite a commotion
coming from
the Simpson residence.
BURNS:
You're lying!
HOMER: Leave me alone!
I have shares to crop.
That's one of Virgil's
sugar-sprinkled cake rings.
Now, where is he?
I don't have to answer
to some weak old man
with a walking stick.
Ahh! A beating stick!
Brigand.
-(screams)
-Dastard.
Renegade.
Mooncalf.
I can't tell you where
he is-- I swore an oath.
I see.
You know, Simpson,
every man has his price.
No one is better at
determining said price
than yours truly.
-Hmm.
-(mumbling)
-(grunts)
Hmm.
-(hollow knocking)
-(grunts)
(gnawing)
I would say
your price is...
a pleasant surprise.
That's exactly my price.
Your man Virgil is...
in...
Father, no!
Eliza, hold your tongue!
Don't worry,
I'll handle this one.
Young lady,
in this day and age,
women only express
their opinions in diaries
to be found
long after they're gone.
From the day you were born,
you were brought up
to crave the approval
of a man.
And I know you really want
to be a good girl,
and good girls are seen
and not heard.
(stifled protest)
Yes, sir.
That-a-girl.
Now, where's my man?
In the turnip shed.
Now, what's my surprise?
Your surprise is
a new pair of shoes.
Oh, my God,
that surprise
is so pleasant.
(sobbing)
MILFORD (with Southern accent):
After that fateful day,
(normal voice): "I could never
even look at Eliza again."
It didn't help
that the next day,
he drank bad well water
and went blind.
No! You lie!
Eliza Simpson can't be a coward.
(voice breaking):
She's the only decent
ancestor I have.
Ach. Take it outside, lassie.
We've still got three
"Jackie Robinsons"
and a "Tuskegee Airmen" to go.
-(crying)
-And so many Obamas.
-(all impersonating Obama)
-Yes, we can.
-Audacity of hope.
-Let me be clear.
As I told you,
we don't have any books
pertaining to Eliza Simpson.
But I need to prove
that my ancestor
couldn't have backed down
to Colonel Burns.
Colonel Burns?
Why, I haven't heard
my father's name in years.
(sobbing)
You know, you could
try our film vault.
Huh?
We have a film vault?
It's where we hooked up
during the Christmas party.
Oh.
INTERVIEWER (on film):
So, Miss Eliza, I understand
you just turned 100.
It's been quite a life.
Any regrets?
Just one.
When I was a girl,
I witnessed a grave injustice,
but I held my tongue.
That pat on my head
from a wicked man
has haunted me to this day.
(sobbing)
There's no noble Simpson.
Oh, you were right, Dad.
I should have quit
while I was ahead
instead of learning
the horrible truth
about our family
and Virgil.
Aw, don't cry, meat pie.
Things worked out pretty well
for Virgil in the end.
What are you talking about?
Is there something
you know about Virgil
that you haven't told us?
I'll take that secret
to my grave--
or urn, or medical school
dissecting table,
or wherever you're dumping me.
Listen, Wrinkles,
if you know something that'll
cheer up my little girl,
you'd better spill it.
Or I can make things
very uncomfortable for you.
That enough?
Ah! Okay, I'll talk.
D-day is June 6th.
Repeat: June 6th.
Allied forces will land
on the beaches of Normandy
in the following order--
Utah, Omaha, Gold, Juno.
Are you writing this down,
Fritz?
About Virgil.
Oh, right.
Well, Lisa, Mabel
knew her husband well,
so she had cooked up
a little payback pie.
(gasps)
Get off my property,
Colonel Burns.
And if I ever see you
in these parts again...
(shotgun cocking)
...you're gonna be
a Memphis belle.
Very well.
You may have won this round,
but someday my history
will be told
by my descendants
Ken and Ric Burns.
I knew you'd break
your promise.
Now I'm taking
Virgil to freedom.
You defied your
husband for me?
Man, this is the '60s.
Now let's take you to a place
where a black man can
blend in-- Canada.
GRAMPA:
So, with those words,
Mabel and Virgil headed north,
but their journey was fraught
with peril.
(gasps)
Hmm...
Mabel, why don't I go on alone,
and you go back to Hiram?
No.
There's no life
for me with him.
I just need
to disguise my hair.
But how?
May I be of assistance?
Abraham Lincoln?
(gasps)
Perhaps this hat will
help disguise your hair.
Thank you.
How's it look?
-It makes you look like
a potbellied stove.
-(annoyed grunt)
Hey, hey, "Honest Abe."
(laughs)
Oh, I'm a riot.
GRAMPA:
As the border drew close,
so did Virgil and Mabel.
After you.
By the time they crossed into
Canada, things had changed.
(theme from Ken Burns's
The Civil War playing)
Mabel divorced Hiram
and got one of his shoes
in the settlement.
Mabel and Virgil lived out the
rest of their days in peace.
They got married, and since
Virgil had no last name,
they both took the name Simpson
so that Mabel could keep
all her
monogrammed table linens.
And their son, Abraham Simpson,
was my great-grandfather.
So you're actually descended
from Virgil, not Hiram.
Are ya happy?
Yes. I'm thrilled.
We've regained our family honor,
and we're 1/64th black.
So that's why I'm so cool.
That's why my jazz
is so smooth.
And that's why I earn less
than my white co-workers.
Grampa, why'd you try to
keep us from finding this out?
Well, it's hard to explain
this to a young person,
but people of my
generation are, you know...
-Racists?
-That's it.
I don't know what
the big deal is.
I mean, it never bothered any
of you that my father's French.
You know, Bouvier?
So that's why I love
drinking so much.
I'm French, not you.
C'est la vie, baby.
("La Marseillaise" playing)
(guzzling)
♪♪
(murmuring)
Shh!
Enhanced by Fotokem