D'oh!
Sorry, no room.
I am a broccoli,
I help keep you lean.
My head's on a stalk,
and my color is...
is...
Oh, come on,
you little nitwit.
It's the color of your costume,
for God's sake.
Purple.
Get off my stage,
out of my sight.
- And into your parents' car.
- Okay.
You'll never work in
second grade theater again.
Hooray!
Up next, the heartwarming
story of the origin of veal.
Hello, friend-o.
No, no! You promised
you would cut this scene.
No, no, I cut your scene
because you were such a noodge.
Forget it. Show's over!
Fine.
Can I please get back
my after-show cupcakes?
- We already ate them.
- No!
Oh, I broke the cardinal rule,
never invest
in your own production.
But I'm gonna take back
my duct tape!
And my bulbs...
Hot, hot, hot.
Am I acting? No.
I'm stuck
in my pork chop suit.
I've become everything
I hate.
Huh? Oh, you were
the best one, sweetie.
Wha...? I didn't even
get to do my line.
Oh, I think I'm gonna cry.
Oh, no.
I hate to see a pork chop cry.
Green! Green. Green. Green.
Too late now, boy.
Just play with the siren.
76. 82. 79.
Homer, that's the weather.
D'oh!
Homer, I want you
to do something with Lisa.
I am.
Isn't that right, honey?
You're not speaking to her
or even making eye contact.
Oh, you'd be surprised
at the things
my eyes are in contact with.
Okay. Well, what is she doing
right now?
She's riding her pony?
Blowing her clarinet?
Protesting a whale.
I'm reading
To Kill a Mockingbird.
Now just remember, it's set
in the South a long time ago.
The terrible racism
you're reading about
is now everywhere.
We're gonna shop at all
the stores you like
that have a chair I can sit in,
except the chair store.
I'm not allowed back there.
Kent Brockman here interviewing
three blue-collar men
who voted for Trump.
How do you feel now?
- Please stop interviewing us.
- Never.
Here's the store.
Let's get something sweet
for my little girl.
Sugar and spice and
everything... What the?!
Twerking Girl?
Ho, Sweet Ho?
Baby's First Thong?
Those are just a few
of our high-end brands.
We also have Call of Booty,
Raggedy Anorexic,
The Edge of 13, and, for boys,
Jack the Stripper.
Oh, for crying out loud.
Okay, that's it. I've heard
enough and three past that.
My daughter is still
a sweet little girl.
What the? Oh, come on!
My daughter's not a sex object.
She's a respect object.
Innocent girls.
Knee socks.
Grow up too fast.
I will see you all in court.
Dad, I'm seeing you
through new eyes.
You've become
the hero of my book.
The guy who kills the
mockingbird?
No one kills a mockingbird.
Spoiler alert.
You're like Atticus Finch,
a modest, heroic man
who stands up for what's right.
Yeah, sure.
And I love the way
you just made me feel safer.
She respects me.
This is even better
than the time the Milk Duds
in the vending machine knocked
down a 3 Musketeers bar too.
Man beats machine!
Well, I think
that's all the reading
for tonight, honey.
It's getting late.
What time is it?
8:30.
May I see your watch?
To Atticus,
My Beloved Husband.
Oh, black and white?
The TV's broken.
Hey, we were watching that.
Why, look, it's Bart Simpson
in his short pants
on the davenport.
Are you nuts?
Homer is my hero.
Say it in American.
He stood up for me.
It was magnificent.
- I wish my dad was a hero.
- Wish granted, son!
Now let's move it.
If I hand out 5,000 flyers,
I get all the turkey shreds
I can dig out
of the slicer trap.
And dig I will.
Well, I don't care
if Dad's your hero.
You know whose hero I am?
Maggie's. Come here, girl.
Okay, the dog's your hero,
but I'm your human hero.
Fine.
But I'm your living human hero.
Are you saying I'm dead?
Put up your dukes.
Now put up my dukes.
Now take down your dukes.
I'm the greatest!
Oh, someone put down my dukes.
I'd always liked my dad,
but this was something new
and wonderful.
I admired him.
The way he'd take me to
the science museum once a year.
D'oh!
And now we get ice cream.
Oh, sweetie,
it's starting to melt.
Daddy will give you
a little help.
A little more help.
A little more. A little more.
Oh, Daddy ate yours.
You can have mine.
- Thank you.
- Now let Daddy...
I got it.
And he inspired me in school.
The second grade was grim,
but Jem assured me
that the older I get,
the better school would be.
Who says my class is grim?
Who's Jem?
What are you talking about?
That's from
To Kill a Mockingbird.
Page 67. The book
you assigned us to read.
I assigned you to read
the Wikipedia article.
But my brother
was not so happy.
Mom, why can't we be
like that?
Well...
I taste blue.
Yeah, okay.
I tell you, guys,
having a kid that likes you
is the greatest feeling
in the world.
I never got along
with my old man.
He was always disappointed
I didn't follow him
in the family business.
- What did he do?
- He was editor of Life magazine.
- I thought that was defunct.
- He keeps saying a real son
would've bought it
out of bankruptcy
and launched it
as a digital platform.
Well, angel funders
want too much equity.
Sorry, Dad.
Yeah, my dad left
when I was most vulnerable,
the day after Mom left.
That was a tough week there.
Not a good time
to film a commercial.
Don't worry,
we'll take these cameras
and we'll make
a Netflix documentary.
They will buy anything!
For dessert,
I made blackberry pie.
Oh, I made Dad a blueberry pie.
Oh, what to do, what to do?
In the words of King Solomon,
I shall eat two pies.
I don't think King Solomon
said that.
Maybe it was a king salmon.
The point is, pies are good.
Homer, I think Bart could use
a little attention.
Give attention to Lisa,
give attention to Bart.
What am I, made of attention?
Okay, because of
budget cutbacks,
you got 45 seconds each.
40 after the explanation.
You, get in!
What you're experiencing
is a phenomenon
known as transference,
where you project your feelings
towards your mother
onto your art teacher.
Anytime you find yourself
wanting to hug Mrs. Hakamuchi,
snap this rubber band
on your wrist.
Next!
What are you waiting for?
I'm here for an hour,
then I'm off to
14 other schools.
I eat lunch in my car
'cause they won't let me
counsel kids with food
in my mouth.
Well, I always thought
my dad was a big fat loser
until he started giving
attention to my lame-o sister.
So why do I want
his attention now?
Why does this hurt?
Family members are
locked into roles.
Change that,
and what do you get?
Resentment and acting out.
Acting out can take many forms,
from pouting to armed robbery.
- Time's almost up.
- So, what do I do?
You have no choice.
Act out until somebody
pays attention to you.
Next!
Okay, couples therapy.
You got 90 seconds.
I'm the oldest,
and she won't admit it.
Milhouse,
I'm about to act out.
After we leave an envelope
full of guilt.
Also, we're stopping by
the photo booth.
- And the perfume room.
- Enough.
Come on, sweetie,
pick up the pace.
The sushi's been sitting out
for an hour.
When Willie turned 13, it was
time to work in the mines.
It's go time.
Help. My friend's having
an asthma attack.
Not yet, Bart.
This is a real one.
Even better.
Please, we've got to get him
to the hospital.
I'm gonna meet a nurse.
And now we're gonna party
like it's 5799.
Wait, wait, wait.
Before you leave,
I am going to talk.
And I'm going to tell you
a very long joke.
Please stand.
So, an old rabbi was
confronted with squirrels
in the attic.
Get to the punch line
or your son flunks geometry.
He gave the squirrels
a bar mitzvah
and never saw them
in temple again.
Amen.
I don't drive a minivan.
Do I look like a suburban
soccer mom from Phoenix?
Well, sometimes,
when you're tired.
- Shut up!
- I should be first.
I own a Tesla.
Those are my keys.
Prepare for the boning
of your life.
To repeat, I own a Tesla,
and I'm going to use summon.
Who is responsible
for this meshugana behavior?
He did it.
Hey, Mr. Cunningham.
I said hey, Mr. Cunningham.
I didn't do it.
Nobody saw me do it.
They know I did it.
Protect me, Dad.
Don't you remember me,
Mr. Cunningham?
I'm Jean Louise Finch.
Where's your boy?
What's your hurry, friend?
Now, Homer, don't you try
to disarm us
with your genteel mannerisms
of a bygone era there.
Why, I haven't a notion as to what
you are importuning, good sir.
Excuse me, Mr. Szyslak.
Mr. Szyslak, we know you.
My father likes to drink
at your bar.
You can't say hi to me?
And how 'bout you,
Chief Wiggum?
I go to school
with your boy, Ralph.
Give my regards to Ralph,
would you, please?
All right, let's go, people.
They've defused us.
Everyone get...
get one last mutter in.
Oh, Lisa, sweetie, you saved me.
No, Dad, you saved us all
with your calmness and bravery.
- Thanks. Just one thing.
- Yes, Dad?
Don't tell your mother
about the mob
that almost killed your brother.
She's taken a liking to him.
The what?
You're hearing things
in the shower again, Marge.
Oh, okay.
Sorry.
Okay, Maggie,
you give me your binky,
and I'll give you this
substitution bear doll.
You can't beat addiction, Marge.
I got addicted
to Agatha Christie books.
I always thought the murderer
was that know-it-all Belgian.
Turns out, he was the detective.
41 books, and I never
saw it coming.
- What happened?
- Got in a fight.
Why?
What did the other kid do?
Said Dad was lazy
and incompetent.
And where is this other kid?
Yo.
You got in a fight
with your brother?
I won a fight with my brother.
- Liar.
- Let's go again.
Stop her, Mom.
To combat bed-wetting,
doctors recommend
shifting times for drinking,
scheduling bathroom breaks,
and being encouraging.
I'll deny having said this,
but the next time you wet
your bed, have 'em spank you.
Next.
Wait, you're not a kid.
Doesn't matter.
You've got 45 seconds.
Go.
I'm worried that my daughter
is ruining her family
idolizing her father.
I see.
Marge, it's totally normal
for a little girl to be
infatuated with her father.
It's safe and comes
from a good place,
and when it ends, it's another
thing she'll blame you for.
Yes, well, I'm afraid
my husband isn't always
a perfect influence.
Marge, I've got a legal matter
to deal with.
I'll be outside.
Also, I'm worried that my son
is feeling neglected.
Your husband has to give your
daughter the perfect speech,
which lets her down
but doesn't snap her in two.
And make sure you don't
have any more kids.
Sounds like it'll be a disaster.
Whoa, nice to meet you.
See you in three years.
Now, good-bye.
- Homer?
- What?
Homer, it's sweet that
Lisa idolizes you,
but I think it's gone too far.
You're right.
Tell her she's right.
I just did.
I'm on a five-second delay.
The kids are at
each other's throats.
Look, you can't be my dog
and hers, pick a side.
You can't hide in there forever.
Okay, I'll talk to Bart,
you talk to Lisa.
We've got to put this family
back in place.
Okay. Why do you
always tell me
the most important things just
when I'm about to fall asleep?
Because I think the pillow talk
between a woman and her husband
is the most important...
What? How did I
wind up in church?
What's wrong, sweetie?
I've got that terrible feeling
where I'm almost
at the end of a great book,
and once I finish,
it's over forever.
Well, that's kind of what
I wanted to talk to you about.
You and I have had a lot of fun
these past few weeks,
but you aren't always gonna
look up to your dad
as much as you do now.
Bup, bup, bup.
Great man,
there is nothing you could do
to make me lose one iota
of respect for you.
When I was a kid,
I wanted to be that guy,
but now I can't fit
behind a door.
You'll discover I'm not
the perfect man you think.
Okay, I'll finish my book.
But always remember
you're my dad,
and I'll never forget
the way you and...
Damn it.
I'm home!
She's moved on,
which, let's face it,
is the way things should be.
Kids grow up, daddies die,
and then the wind
whispers, why?
Oh, I don't know.
I've been hurt before.
I don't want to mess you up
by getting close to you.
No problem.
Marge, get in here.
Okay, Bart, because
we treasure you too,
I'm gonna let you do one thing
just for yourself.
Kick Homer in the butt?
Why don't you give it
some thought.
Kick Lisa in the butt.
Have a birthday party every day?
Never brush my teeth again.
Be homeschooled by the dog.
Drive a tank through
Skinner's house.
Open a casino in the basement.
Have an affair?
- You haven't decided yet?
- Don't rush me.
Convert my Roth IRA to a 401K?
Have an affair?
Take a mulligan?
Okay, I've decided.
I'll kick Homer in the butt.
You can kick it
if you can find it.
D'oh.
Well, they say
Time loves a hero
But only time will tell
If he's real
He's a legend from heaven
If he ain't,
he was sent here from hell ♪
Hear me well
Seein' ain't
always believin'
Just make sure it's the truth
that you're seein'
Eyes sometimes lie,
eyes sometimes lie
They can be real deceivin'