The Simpsons
D'oh!
A- ha! A free baseball!
A shiny new dime!
A shinier new dime!
Excuse me.
My refrigeration
unit is broken.
Could you possibly eat
some free ice cream?
What flavor?
Why, super chocolate,
of course. Oh, yes!
This day just keeps
getting better and better.
And here's a new
four-legged friend
for me.
Hiya, boy.
Haven't seen you
around here before.
Mom! A dog ate
my clothes!
Nice try,
but we're still
going to Riverdance.
D'oh!
You know that new
baby brother Ralph's
been bragging about?
It's just a pinecone.
Let's go where
it's quiet.
Help!
Isn't that
your brother?
I said, let's go.
Eh, I'm sick of
this Tarzan movie.
Dad, it's a documentary
on the homeless.
Oh, right.
A crazy dog's
trying to kill me!
Really? Ooh!
This I gotta see.
Oh, he just wants
to make friends.
Ooh! Who's a good dog?
What a goody doggie!
He just a googie...
So, Bart, when does
the killing start?
Look, Bart,
sometimes dogs or people
hate you for no reason.
Bart's a goner.
Anyone want to be
my new best friend?
I will!
Great! Finally,
I'll be the dominant one.
Be quiet.
Yes, sir.
Ha-ha! Bart's
family is poor!
Hurry up,
Bart, or you'll be late
to be killed by the dog!
What?
I said you'll be
late for school!
Eat my short stories!
Phew! Safe at last!
Now, I'll just turn around
and confirm that safety.
Hey, wait a minute.
These animals are stuffed.
Except that one.
Don't worry about
these critters. They're
just props from my movies.
This one's from
Gunfight at the Museum
of Natural History.
You were in movies?
Hold onto your hat, son.
You're talking to Buck McCoy.
Who?
Yeah, that's right.
Buck McCoy.
The most famous movie
cowboy in the world.
No kidding. Anyway,
I climbed over your gate.
A dog was after me.
I'll show you a trick
that you can use on dogs.
Also worked on
David O. Selznick.
Who?
Yeah, that's right.
The David O. Selznick.
Whoa! Keep him
away from me!
Trust me, son.
You'll be fine.
Now, lean down
and put your arms
across his neck.
Whoa! It worked!
Where did you learn that?
Ah, you pick things up.
Do you know how to
catch a wild boar
with a teaspoon?
No!
Well, what do you
kids do all day?
Well, right now
I'm supposed to
be in school.
School? Huh! Why bother?
I quit after fourth grade,
and I ain't not no un-dummy.
It's
like you're living
in a steakhouse!
Well, thank you.
Most people just
mutter that.
Is that horse vacuuming?
If you can
call it that.
He soils as much
as he cleans.
Frank the Wonder Horse
was in 24 of my pictures.
And directed one.
And he got
the "film by" credit.
5:00? I better
get home for dinner.
Well, come back
anytime, pardner.
To the laundry room!
Here we are.
Hi, honey.
Where's that vicious dog?
I made him a biscuit.
Oh, he's not
bothering me anymore.
Buck McCoy helped me.
Buck McCoy?
He was the greatest
of them all!
He was bigger than opium!
I met one of my heroes today.
She started the first...
Buck McCoy!
I still carry this.
Junior Buckaroo, 2nd Class.
Little Grampa Simpson.
Cool!
After that I starred in
Wyatt Earp Meets The Mummy.
Then Six Brides
For Seven Brothers.
They were pictures
that the whole family
could enjoy.
No drugs,
no nudity, no cussing.
Just drinking, fighting
and tripping horses
with wires.
What's this lunchbox made of?
Well, back in my day,
we had a thing called metal.
Everything was made of it.
Lunchboxes, cars, you name it.
Me-tal.
Hey, can you still
do cowboy tricks?
Well, here's one I did
in The Wild Lunch.
Everything tastes better
when it's lassoed!
Would you lasso
me a banana?
Now how the hell
would I do that?
I guess you're not
going to have an
adventure this week.
Huh. Just you wait.
Hey, boy, where'd
you get that hat?
Buck gave it to me.
He's just about
the greatest guy
who ever lived.
I want to grow up
to be just like him.
No kidding? Hey,
speaking of achievers,
they're thinking of
spraying your old man's
workspace for ticks.
That's great, champ.
I know you've
been wanting that.
Well, got to mosey,
Homer. Ma'am.
Bart sure is fond of
that cow gentleman.
It's just not fair.
This Buck fellow's
had all the advantages.
Horse-riding lessons,
the finest makeup,
delicious studio food.
Oh, Homie, you'll always
be my western hero.
Swell.
I can't wait
till I get good.
Buck's here!
Dad, why are you
wearing that?
Because I want
to be your hero.
On top of which,
I don't look bald.
Thanks for coming, Mr. McCoy.
We cooked your favorites.
Rattlesnake meat,
varmint kabobs
and refried whiskey.
I like the sound
of that last one.
Don't listen to them,
Buck! It's an ambush!
They're trying to
jump your claim!
Take him outside.
I love you, Buck!
Gee, Buck,
your old films are
as violent as today's!
One of the wheels
broke off my chair today,
but I didn't make
a movie about it.
In the '50s,
I did a TV show.
It only lasted a year,
but we did 360 episodes,
all of them great.
I did the commercials myself.
Remember kids,
Drunken Cowboy brand
whiskey is smooth as milk!
I'm not sure I approve
of selling whiskey
to children.
Well, that ad was aimed
at children who were
already heavy drinkers.
Oh!
Tonight's
episode... "Excuse Me
While I Kill The Sky. "
Why are you driving a car?
Yeah, in the '70s,
Westerns were out
and detective shows were in.
It seems like all I did
was shoot hippies.
They wrote me out of the show
and it became Room 222.
So that's how you
ended your career?
Yeah, well,
what can you do?
The Western went the way
of the evening newspaper
and polio.
Well, I think Westerns
are due for a comeback.
Yeah! We can have showdowns
at the schoolyard
and use nerds as Indians.
Bart, you look so cool.
I was thinking this
could be a new fad.
What about
Hawaiian shirts?
Hey, you're not fun,
you're fat!
Now, listen up.
When I come back tomorrow,
you better have cowboy suits,
and they better be adorable.
This is Kent Brockman here
at Springfield Elementary,
where a new Western craze
is sweeping the campus.
I'm Annie Oakley!
I'm Kevin Costner
in one of his Western roles!
I'm a gulch!
So I guess you could say
this barely
qualifies as news.
I'm Kent Brockman.
Oh, give me land
Lots of land
Under starry skies above
Don't fence me in
Sir, you cannot pee
Unless you are an employee
Can't keep it in
Krusty, how do you feel
about putting Buck McCoy
on your show?
Pass!
We also represent
Billy Joel.
Who's the first one again?
Buck McCoy.
Forget it!
I'm not putting
some Western star on
just 'cause it's
the flavor of the month.
I want my show to have
a timeless quality.
Here's your hanging
chad sketch, Krusty.
Oh, good, you
worked in Judge Ito.
Please put Buck on!
He's my hero!
Plus, he'll work for scale.
Scale minus 10.
I ain't going on
some clown show.
I'm retired.
No one expects you
to do anything difficult.
They understand
you're too old.
Listen, missy. The last
two city-slickers who used
reverse psychology on me
are pushing up daisies.
They're dead?
No, they just
got lousy jobs.
You know what?
I bet he can't even
fit into his old costume.
I can't, huh?
You two wait
right here.
Let's see,
Texas or Massachusetts?
Texas.
I like the way
you think.
Boy,
that's some
fancy shooting.
Oh, I've seen fancier.
Ooh! Right
in the panhandle!
Write that down.
Buck, this is
a real honor.
I grew up watching
your horse operas
down at the Bijou.
Yeah, things sure
have changed
since the '50s.
I don't care.
You know,
it's been a long time
since I performed live.
You'll do fine.
Just remember,
there'll be millions
of people watching you.
Millions!
And TV Guide's
Cheers and Jeers editor.
And he's already
given out all his cheers.
Live from
the corner of Zany Avenue
and Martin Luther King
Boulevard,
it's The Krusty
the Klown Show,
with special guest
Buck McCoy.
And now, here's Krusty!
We've got such
a great show tonight.
I won't be doing a monologue
because my feet hurt.
And now our opening sketch.
We don't take kindly
to transvestite chimpanzees
here in Pine Corners!
No one can save you now!
I said, no one
can save you now!
Shut up! I'm coming!
Oh! Like you're so perfect
with your plastic mane
and your painted-on spot.
What's real on you? Nothing!
He's drunk!
I've seen drunker.
Oh, right, yeah, the guns.
We're free!
These hilarious
health professionals
will cut me out
of my clothes
after this commercial.
What happened, Buck?
Did I forget to mention
I'm an alcoholic?
For shame.
This is horrible.
My spit-takes all
have blood in them.
Look, I'm really sorry.
Sorry don't suture
my colon! And you're
off my show forever!
Bart, I couldn't
help noticing Buck
is a total fraud,
so I took
the liberty of creating
a new hero for your wall.
That is just grotesque.
I thought if you were
looking to worship someone,
maybe it could
be your old man.
Eh. We could try it.
Yes!
My son lost his hero.
This should be
the greatest night
of my life.
How come I'm not happy?
You care about
Bart's feelings.
Stop saying that!
I think we should
try to restore
Bart's faith in Buck,
and we could start
by getting Buck
to quit drinking.
I'm sorry I let your son down,
but I'm too old to change.
Oh, listen to you!
"I'm too old to change. "
How old are you?
Seventy-six.
Nice old man.
Don't break a hip.
Have we gotten
all the liquor?
That painting is
made of liquor.
I was drinking so much
I forgot what life was about.
Gold! Gold!
Beautiful gold!
Nuggets as big
as your fists!
You guys are sick.
I don't belong here.
Buck, if you walk out
that door, you'll be
branded a quitter forever.
Mmm!
Something smells delicious!
Well, that's it.
This place ain't for me.
Well, we're not giving up.
We're going to
cure you of drinking.
Look, I worked long
and hard, got rich,
and now I'm retired.
Why shouldn't I be
able to drink all I want?
Well, I don't know.
I just naturally
assumed it was
some of my business.
Well, I don't see how
it is. Nobody's even
told me your name yet.
I'm still not
giving up on Buck.
There must be
some harebrained,
half-assed way...
This just in.
A robbery is in progress
at the National Bank
of Springfield.
The robbers are equipped
with the latest in high-tech
weaponry and body armor.
Stay back, coppers!
Uh, please, everyone!
Stay away!
We don't want
anyone to be a hero!
A hero! A hero!
Get me Buck McCoy!
Dad, I'm on the line!
Here you go.
Just stop this bank robbery
and you'll be a hero again.
I'll wait in the car.
Are you crazy?
I'm a movie cowboy.
And you're no Howard Hawks.
That hurts.
But I just have
one question.
Do you want my son
to be disappointed
in you?
Fine.
You don't need that.
Way to go, Buck.
I feel my faith
growing anew!
Better get rid of this, too.
Not to mention this.
Whoa! There's nothing wrong
with a little "hey-hey!"
Fun's over, boys!
Drop the hardware
and mosey!
I'm firing at the lasso,
but the bullets just
go through the middle!
It's the ultimate weapon.
Wow. That sure
made us look bad.
Slink away, boys.
Slink away.
Buck, you're
my hero again.
Aren't you
forgetting someone?
Well, there's Krusty,
Itchy, Scratchy, Poochie,
America's Fire Fighters,
and then you, Dad.
And don't you forget it.
Oh!
Goodbye, Bart!
Never bother me again!
English - US - PSDH