The Simpsons
D'oh!
Give up, Mr. Simpson!
We know you have
the Olympic torch!
For God sakes, Homer!
Give them back their flame!
No! The Olympics have
preempted my favorite shows
for the last time.
You can always find
your favorite shows
next month.
You wait till next month!
Every four years.
We've recovered the flame!
It's beautiful.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
No!
I'm bored.
Hey, a fair!
Springfield
Preparatory School?
Dad, you told me
there were no private
schools in Springfield.
But knowing about it
would make you
want to go here.
Hello and thank you
for coming
to our fundraiser.
I'm headmaster
St. John Van Hookstratten.
10-4, Princess.
Is that your beer tent?
Monkeys point.
Monkeys cry.
This campus is so
lush and verdant.
Yes. You probably recognize
it from the film
Calling All Coeds.
Oh! Is that where
Boozer drank the pee?
It's one of the places.
Sorry.
This school
has everything.
I know. Doesn't it
just honk you off?
Their periodic
table has 250 elements!
And our school board's
cut us back to 16.
All of them lanthanides.
You know, we could get
equipment like this
through a bond issue.
Here's
your bond issue!
Quick. Take these.
Principal Skinner,
you're just stealing.
Welcome to Dick
Cheney's America.
Mmm! All this food
is so froufrou.
Ooh!
Faberge egg salad.
Look, Brandine.
It's Wolfgang Puck.
Mr. Puck, you make the only
grub what satisfies
my gut worm, I swear.
Try my Rice Krispie squares.
They are wasabi-infused
with a portobello glaze.
And you can buy
them at the airport.
I make mine with M&M's.
With M&M's?
Now that's what
I call fusion.
I could sell them
on the Internet.
To the Puck-mobile!
Ha! Go, go, go!
No one's doing any bumping.
Time to ram-a-lam
these ding-dongs.
Good show.
Hey, Marge.
Watch me burn Flanders.
"Ned Flanders bids $50."
And the winner
of the $100 bill
is Ned Flanders!
This is going
right to the orphanage.
We have a winner!
These will be great
for advancing our research.
Yes. Our research.
Hey, that's my
backpack!
Look at her cry!
New money always cries!
Drop the backpack, Jack.
The name is Jackington.
Retreat!
To the Hamptons!
Tra-la-la, la-la-la!
You were so brave
to take on
all those bullies.
Those weren't bullies.
That's a bully.
Hey, butler,
stop butling yourself.
Would that I could, sir.
Time to go, Greta.
Your mother's custody
starts at 1800 hours.
Your dad's McBain?
I've played
many characters.
McBain,
Officer Nick Vengeance,
Sergeant Murder,
and I was a voice
on the Frasier.
Would you like to come
to my house sometime?
If it's okay with my dad.
Come. We play Uno.
I chase you with hose.
No biggie.
Wow. Cool!
I guess we're leaving, too.
No, I belong here! Please!
Don't worry, honey.
We can't afford this now,
but when it's time
for college,
I promise my darling daughter
can go to the finest school
there is.
In South Carolina.
Oh! I will not be
a Gamecock!
You will too!
No!
Go Gamecocks!
It's so cute you're going
to a little girl's house.
Look, boy, here's my
advice on women.
Don't give them nicknames
like "Jumbo" or "Boxcar,"
and always get receipts.
Makes you look
like a business guy.
What the hell is that?
That car's as big
as all outdoors!
Wow. What kind of
mileage does it get?
One highway, zero city.
Mmm-hmm.
Bart, your little tie
makes me smile.
Excuse me, but you don't
sound as tough as you do
in the movies.
If you don't
shut your big yap,
I will rip off your face
and use it as a napkin!
Laughing time is over.
These are props from
one of my dad's movies,
The Incredible
Shrinking McBain.
Wow! The Q-tip he
used to kill Ross Perot.
Everything
in your house is so cool.
What's your house like?
Oh, it's okay. My bed
is stuffed with hay.
Bart,
you're so funny.
Yeah.
You haven't seen
Itchy & Scratchy till
you've seen it on DVD.
The Itchy & Scratchy Show
Oh, my body!
Check out
the audio commentary.
We shot this at
4:00 in the morning,
and the crew was
getting a little cranky.
You can never
get enough takes
for Steven Soderbergh.
Always wants more...
I hope you enjoy
these German sausages.
I've been grinding
all day, so I'm not
sure what organ meat
is in what intestinal casing.
Bratwurst?
Sauerbraten?
Donderblitzen?
Oh, Mom, isn't there
anything vegetarian?
Homer, I see
your daughter is one
of those whale-kissing,
Dukakis-hugging moon maidens.
Yeah,
one time she...
She's looking
at us. Be cool.
What are you doing?
Oh, I gotcha.
One, two, three, four,
I declare a thumb war!
One, two, three!
Hey, that was
a fast count!
Remember when I said
I would eat you last?
I lied.
Hi, Bart.
Whazzup!
Oh! You brought someone.
Yeah, this is Milhouse.
He's my best friend because...
Well, geographical
convenience, really.
I'm wearing
my bathing suit
under my pants.
Um... You want
to go swimming?
Okay, but you have
to watch me dive.
Fine.
Do you promise?
Just go!
He'll sleep tonight!
Hello, gentlemen.
Would you care to meet
my new best friend?
Rainier Wolfcastle?
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Hey, I've been
using that ab roller
you endorse,
but I haven't
gotten any results.
Right, because you've
been using it backward.
Are you really
Homer's friend?
After they shoot your movies,
who gets the leftover film?
Is it true
that if I kill you,
I become you?
This looks
like a job for my
authorized look-alike.
Hi, I'm Chuck.
I live in his trunk.
So how much you
look-alikes make?
'Cause some say
I look like
Macaulay Culkin.
These courtside
seats are great.
Thanks for the hookup,
Wolfie.
I just want my
daughter to be happy.
Plus, you eat the pretzels
I drop on the floor.
That I do, sir.
Bart, my school's
having a dance.
It's pretty lame,
but maybe you
can make it fun,
if we went together.
Yeah, I guess.
Defense!
Defense! Defense!
Defense! Defense! Defense!
Ouch! I sat on
something sharp!
Oh, that's just
Lara Flynn Boyle.
I have a Boyle on my ass!
Now, Willie, don't tell
anyone I'm trying my
stand-up comedy act tonight.
If the students find out
I'm performing at Floppy's,
I'll never live it down.
I won't tell if you
put me on the guest list.
All right. Plus one?
Nay.
Now, I'll give you
directions starting from
the Simpsons' house.
We are so there!
Aren't you supposed to
take Greta
to the dance tonight?
Oh, yeah.
Maybe I should
keep my promise.
I just hope
the audience is kind
because my material is weak,
and I have that
bladder thing.
That's it!
I'm blowing off the dance!
This is the biggest
thing that's happened
to me since chocolate milk!
They've got
chocolate milk now?
That was the prop comedy
of the sea captain.
More like
"thar he blows!"
Yarr, I'm so sorry.
All right.
Let's keep this
train wreck moving.
Principal Skinner?
I know him.
He's not funny. Well, enjoy.
So, it's standardized
testing time again.
Have you ever noticed
how the dumb kids
fill in the wrong circles?
Seymour! Seymour!
Lost my place.
Maybe, maybe, maybe, maybe
a little improv would
raise the roof here.
Would someone
name a profession?
Loser Principal!
Uh...
I think I heard
California surfer.
You suck, Seymour!
Oh, man. What a dork.
Greta called.
It seems you told
her you were sick.
Lisa, I only lied
because it was
the easiest way
to get what I wanted.
Bart, this girl
is in love with you!
Think about it!
Hey, I didn't lead her on.
I always played it
light and breezy.
Well, if you don't
feel the way Greta does,
you've got to tell her
before she gets hurt.
All right.
I know what to do.
I'll dump her
like she's never
been dumped before.
Then we'll go right
back to being friends.
Well, Bart, you really
understand women.
Lise, women are easy.
State capitals are hard!
And where were you?
Cockfight.
You're breaking up with me?
Don't worry. We get
that a lot here.
Lou, you can't
leave the force!
I can change!
I just think
there's more money
in private security.
All I'm hearing
is I'm too fat.
Aren't I?
I can't believe
he dumped me!
In my movies,
this is where
I would go berserk.
Dad, this isn't a movie.
No. Let my muscles hug you.
Greta, I'm sorry
I didn't handle
the breakup well,
but you're a sweet kid
and someday you'll
find someone who...
Whazzup!
Milhouse? Greta?
Well, no one has to
draw me a picture!
Oh! But I did.
Greta,
is this how it is?
Yes.
Except he kissed me
in the eye.
I was an idiot.
Now I'll be alone forever.
Why did I break up with her?
Oh, Bart,
it's human nature.
You only want her
because someone
else has her.
Prove it, using
examples from this room.
All right, look.
Maggie's not playing
with this ball right now,
but look what happens
when I take it.
See?
Give me the ball!
She use ta be
She use ta be my girl
I wouldn't lie about
a thing like that
She use ta be my girl
Well, well
Leave a message at the beep.
But don't be
a message monster
hogging all my tape!
Uh, Greta, it's me.
I think you left your pencil
over at my house, and...
He's there now, isn't he?
I knew it. You're there.
Just hear me out.
Bart, forget it.
I'm leaving in 10 minutes.
My dad's shooting
a movie in Toronto.
You're
going to Spain?
Goodbye, Bart.
So to win Greta back,
I have to go to Toronto.
Canada?
Why should we leave America
to visit America Junior?
This is for love, Dad.
Someday you'll feel
what I feel.
It's only fair.
We went to Europe
when Lisa lost her balloon.
Maggie, what do you think?
All right, Son.
We'll all go!
First class!
It's so clean
and bland. I'm home!
Wow! This bus station
is the birthplace
of Paul Shaffer.
Dad, no!
It says, "Don't walk!"
It doesn't matter.
They have free
health care.
Whoa! I'm rich!
Take off!
To the Great White North!
It's a beauty way to go!
Take off...
I'm a 10-year-old
boy in Toronto.
I should be the happiest
kid in the world.
But I can't stop
thinking about Greta!
You'll win her back, eh.
And B, we're closing
in five minutes.
Would a US dollar
change your mind?
American currency!
What time would you like
your breakfast, sir?
Take off!
To the Great White North!
Over there you can see
them shooting the film
Canadian Graffiti.
Oh, I see you drive
on the left up here.
No, Ma'am. I'm drunk.
There it is!
Wolfcastle's movie set!
Excuse me. Which way
to the chess club?
What's your name, nerd?
Melvin Eugene Puny-meyer.
Well, well, a big
muscle-bound nerd.
Ha! Just more
of you to pick on.
The geek shall
inherit the earth.
There she is, boy.
I don't know, Dad.
What if she's
still mad at me?
Listen to me, Son.
No one loves a quitter.
So you go over there
and you win her back.
But she might say no.
Oh, I quit.
There's no convincing you.
I'm
gonna take a nap.
You're not gonna win her back.
She's with the "House" now.
Milhouse, she's only dating
you to get back at me.
My therapist said that's
all I could ever hope for.
So take off, hoser!
I'm gonna knock you
into the next province!
Well, we've seen some
wild sweeping here today.
Yes. The broom handling
has been truly dazzling.
What's this?
Two young Yankee Doodles
have turned this match
into a dandy.
Both our viewers
must be thrilled.
Greta, I miss you
so much. Please
be my girlfriend again.
No.
Yes!
The "House" always wins!
Sorry, Milhouse.
I thought Canada would
save our relationship,
but it only made it worse.
You're breaking up
with me? Why?
I guess I was just looking
for someone more masculine.
I told you! I don't know
how that scrunchie
got in my hair!
Sorry, guys. But you two
have put me off dating
for at least four years.
I think I'll just buckle
down and co-produce
my dad's movies.
Need a unit production
manager?
It's too late, Bart.
Well, I guess
we're single again.
I can't believe
I have to give her
half my stuff!
But are we still friends?
Till the next one.
So, what do we do now?
Well, we're in Canada.
Let's find something fun!
I've got just
the ticket! Come on!
I can't believe we're
on the Canadian
Olympic Basketball team.
Yep. It's just that easy.
Wow, that was close.
You can be the center.
How come you always
run out of tardy slips
before you run out
of permission slips?
How come you suck?
Uh...
I lack confidence?
Whazzup!
English - US - PSDH