(SINGING) The Simpsons
(TIRES SCREECHING)
D'oh!
(SCREAMS)
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
MAN: Whoo-hoo!
(GULPING)
Hey, hey, hey!
No enjoying it!
Kent Brockman here
with Stormwatch 6.
Professor Frink,
what's the scientific
explanation for this
unusually severe
thunderstorm?
Well, Kent, we are, uh,
exploring two theories
at this point.
Um, A, either we have
a super cell of
high-pressure fronts,
or B, God is bowling!
With the balls
and the pins and
the rental shoes
and the very
bad cheese pizza
that comes in squares.
(CHUCKLING) Krusty, what's
your lighthearted take on
our recent bad weather?
Sorry, Kent. I sold
all my bad weatherjokes
to Jay Mohr.
But I can make
funny sounds
in your microphone.
Fine.
(BLABBERING)
A-ooga! (LAUGHS)
There you have it.
(SPUTTERING)
(GASPS)
Homer, do something
about this leak.
Don't worry, Marge.
Hot Wheels to the rescue!
Water flows down here,
through the straightaway,
a couple of wicked S-turns,
around the loop of death,
and out the mail slot.
Then it's the yard's problem.
LISA: My hamster!
(PANTING)
(SQUEAKING)
(SCREAMING)
You know, Homer,
I let a lot of things slide.
But when you can't keep a roof
over your family's head,
you're just not
much of a father.
I was gonna have
my classmates over
for a homework party.
But now
my refreshments
are ruined.
Goodbye, college!
He was supposed to be
in a show-and-tell this week!
(SNEEZES)
That's not gonna happen.
That teddy bear
survived three safety recalls,
but it couldn't
survive you!
Oh, that's it!
I'm going to Moe's!
Aw! It's raining outside!
It's raining inside!
(MEWLING)
Lousy cat!
(SLAMS)
Stupid Homer-hating family.
At least there's one place
I'm always welcome.
MEN: (SINGING) For he's
a jolly good fellow...
Oh, guys.
This is just
what I needed.
This ain't for you,
sweat stain.
It's a surprise party
for Lenny thrown by
his closest friends.
So what's Stephen Hawking
doing here?
(ON VOICE SYNTHESIZER)
I live here now.
You're looking
at the new owner
of the Little Caesars
down the street.
Pizza, pizza. Pizza, pizza.
Sorry, that button sticks.
So why didn't you
invite me?
We couldn't tell you
ahead of time because
you'd spill the beans.
I wouldn't ruin
a surprise for Lenny.
Surprise? What surprise?
(BLOWING HORNS)
(ALL GROAN)
Way to go, Homer.
Ugh! That's six years
planning down the drain!
I'm sorry.
I'll just sit
over here
until you stop
being mad at me.
Oh, great, Homer!
I bake a cake
shaped like Lenny's
favorite barstool,
and you wreck it!
Well, I can see
I'm not wanted here.
Wait, Homer.
Don't go.
Okay, beat it!
Who wants
ass frosting?
No, thanks.
I'm on Atkins.
My family hates me.
My stupid friends
kick me out
of their stupid party.
They'll all be sorry
when I invent
the world's best-tasting cola
And share it with no one!
(CHUCKLES)
(LAUGHING MANIACALLY)
Oh, man.
(GASPS) A sign!
Finally, a bar for men
who like to drink and
look at sexy women.
Welcome to Knockers, hon.
Let me know if you
see anything you like.
Read the sign, prevert!
HOMER: D'oh!
Hmm.
I'd like a beer and
a sympathetic ear.
I got my own problems.
I just lost
this eye last night.
How did it
ever come to this?
I'm the first man ever
to feel depressed in a bar.
I don't have a friend
in the world.
Look at the size
of that nacho plate!
I haven't seen
this much melted cheese
since I left
my Billy Joel albums
out in the sun.
(LAUGHING)
The sun.
Hey, you want to split this?
Wow. It's been
so long since
I've been with someone
who doesn't know
what a selfish pig I am.
Mine. Move your hand.
I get this.
Hey, my name's Ray.
Ray Magini.
Ray, you know me
better than anyone.
How can I
get my wife
to love me again?
Beats me.
I'm no marriage counselor.
Just a licensed
and bonded roofer.
(GASPS) Ray,
will you help me
fix my roof?
Sure, I'll help you.
Under one condition.
You gotta help me finish
this pitcher of beer.
Wait. Did I add
that right?
Now for my first act
as President...
(GRUNTS)
(SHATTERING)
(LAUGHING MANIACALLY)
Deal! To my new buddy!
Now all we need
is an awesome theme song.
Whatever plays
next on the jukebox.
Deal.
WOMAN: (SINGING)
Do that to me one more time
Once is never enough
with a man like you
Next song.
Uh,yeah,
that's what I meant.
Yeah, absolutely.
(HOMER SNORING)
Homer! I woke up
to find an owl
eating a mouse
on the pillow
next to me.
I think that means
six more weeks
of autumn.
It means you have
to fix the roof.
Don't worry, honey.
I found us a roofer
last night.
And you'll
never guess where.
Knockers on Route 98.
How did you know?
I'm psychic.
Look, I don't know
if I want a roofer
who hangs out in bars.
(SCOFFS) You're right, Marge.
I guess I should
look for roofers
at poetry slams
and yoga retreats.
High five!
Nah.
I got standards.
I don't hand out
high-fives like Chiclets.
Ray would
high five me.
Well, he'd better
high five our roof! Huh?
Yay, Mom!
Zing!
D'oh!
Come on, kids.
We're gonna
visit Grampa.
Then we're gonna
take the dog
to the V-E-T.
Huh?
Then take Bart
to get C-I-R-C-U-M-C-I-S-E-D.
Huh?
Uh, I'll tell you what
it means when it's over.
Hey, Homer.
Oh, Ray.
You came at
the agreed-upon time!
That's what I like
about you, Homer.
Everything impresses you.
"Impresses,"
what a big word.
I'm gonna
look that up.
Ah... This is gonna take
some work.
Tell me, was the roof
in good condition
when you bought the house?
I didn't really check.
I mainly bought this
house for the view.
Someday that bowl
will overflow,
and I'll be there.
Okay, kids.
We only have time
for a quick visit
to Grampa.
So as soon
as he feels loved,
we're out of there.
(BARKING)
Oh, he must smell leftovers.
Please. We call them
senior citizens.
Oh, look!
(ALL COOING)
A dog? What a nice surprise.
I'm gonna pet you raw!
(GRUNTS AFFECTIONATELY)
(ALL CHEERING)
Can we keep
your dog, please?
Keep my dog?
Till when?
Not too long.
Just till we die.
(CHUCKLES)
(LAUGHING)
Well, he does
seem happy here.
Also, gerontological studies
have demonstrated that
animal companions can slow
the inevitable decline of...
Yeah, okay, thank you.
Why don't you go
find a parade
and rain on it?
(THUDDING)
(YAWNS)
Huh?
(GROANS)
Oh! Sorry about that, pal.
Hey, no problem.
Accidents happen.
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
One, two, three, four!
I declare a nail war!
This is why
I got into roofing!
(BOTH LAUGHING)
NED: Hey, Homer!
Ned, are you okay?
Yeah. But my mower
can't get much lower.
(AIR HISSING)
I was wrong! (WHIMPERS)
(DOOR SLAMS)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Ah, that's Ned Flanders.
(CHUCKLES)
There's one
in every neighborhood.
(PAGER BEEPING)
Oh, sorry, man. I gotta go.
This says my kid
attempted something.
I hate the way
these things cut off.
Goodbye, Ray! Bye!
Oh, he turned a corner.
Ooh! Now I see him again!
(CRASHING)
(SCREAMS)
(SNORING)
Homer!
Huh? Huh?
You're drooling on
my Goodwill pile!
(GRUNTS)
And why is the hole
in the roof even bigger?
Don't worry.
Ray'll be back
any minute.
It's after 6:00!
He's not coming back!
He's a lousy roofer
and a flake!
Hey, watch
what you say
about him!
I think Ray
could be the one.
The one what?
My new best friend!
We think alike,
we act alike,
we finish
each other's sandwiches.
I don't want to hear
any more about Ray!
Tomorrow morning
you buy some shingles
and fix that roof yourself!
Ray's not gonna
like that.
You're not married
to Ray!
Well, if I was,
we'd have taller kids!
I'm sure everyone's happier
with Santa's Little
Helper here to love them.
Yeah. I bet the old people
will be acting
like young people,
like in those
cell phone ads
everyone hates.
(BARKS WEAKLY)
(GASPS)
He's become one of them!
Hey, boy.
Want a treat?
(GRUNTS)
Better get you home.
Come on, Lisa.
Right after Pat Sajak.
Oh! Jeez, Louise!
(BOTH WHINING)
You know, it's too bad.
We've had that dog
as long as I can remember.
What dog?
Who the hell
are you?
I wish I knew.
You know, son, my dad
used to take me down
to Johnson's Hardware.
Old man Johnson
knew everything
about fixing stuff.
When they built this place,
he hung himself.
(STRAINING)
Oh, sorry, son.
I wanted you
to bring me
the stack of tiles
from the top shelf.
Hey, Ray's here!
Hey, Homer!
Look, I just came down
with a case of shingles.
(LAUGHING)
What's in the box?
Hey, I'm real sorry
I never made it
back yesterday.
I hope
we're still friends.
Of course we are. Uh...
If you want to be?
Well, I want to be,
if you want to be.
I'll tell you what,
let me get a few
more supplies,
and I'll come
ﬂght over and
I'll finish your roof!
Hey, Dad.
Remember when you said
if l used
a chainsaw unsupervised,
I'd hurt myself?
Well, you were wrong.
I hurt someone else.
Oh! I have 45 minutes
to get ready for the prom!
What are you doing?
Why aren't you
fixing the roof?
I don't have to.
Ray's gonna be
here any minute.
(GRUNTS) I am so sick of
hearing about that
stupid, unreliable Ray,
who, by the way,
I have never even met!
All right.
Then you can just look
at the portrait
I painted of him.
Homer, how did you think
I'd feel when I saw that?
Something like that.
Uh! Uh! Oh...
Oh! Uh! Oh...
Oh! Oh...
Homer, come down
for dinner.
Did you make
enough for Ray?
Oh! Ray's not coming!
He is, too!
His truck's gonna
come around the corner
right now.
Right now! Right now! Now!
Now!
(MUTTERS)
(SHIVERING)
(SHAKILY) Now. Now.
Now.
Homer, I know
where Ray is.
Oh, thank God.
Where is he? Tell me!
Sweetheart, your friend,
Ray is in your head.
Ray wouldn't fit in my head.
He's a human man.
(SIGHS)
You have to understand.
Ray doesn't exist.
Yes, he does.
He's on his way.
And when he gets here,
we'll have ever so much fun.
You'll see. (LAUGHING)
We'll laugh! (SCREAMS)
(LAUGHING)
(GROANS)
(GASPS) Homer!
(LAUGHING WEAKLY)
(GASPS)
What? What's going on?
Where are my shoes?
(STRAINING)
(CHUCKLES)
Struggle all you want, Homer.
There's nothing
you can do.
(HOCKS AND SPITS)
Why... Excuse us
for a moment.
(GROANS)
What am I
doing here?
Let me go!
We'll let you go
when you admit
there is no Ray Magini.
Fine, I admit it.
Help me, Ray! Appear
and strike them down!
Homer, no one
has ever seen
Ray but you.
But that's not true.
Bart saw him at
the Builder's Barn.
No, l didn't, Dad.
I saw you
talking to yourself.
Flanders, you saw Ray
on the roof with me!
Sorry, Homer.
You'll have to
call me a "Ray-theist"
because I don't
believe I saw him.
Ned, are you okay?
There has to be
someone who saw him.
Someone who doesn't hate me,
like Flanders
and Bart. (GASPS)
Wait! The bartender
at Knockers!
I called that bosom bar.
The bartender said
you were there alone.
Ray's a figment
of your imagination, Homer.
You felt lonely
and unappreciated,
so you made him up.
And here's the clincher.
"Ray Magini" is
an anagram for "imaginary."
Wow. My subconscious
is a genius.
Well, that's all
very convincing and...
(THUDDING)
(BLABBERS)
He's right over there!
Hey, come on!
Can't anybody see him?
(BLABBERING)
You can only see
from my point of view.
I'm afraid this
calls for electroshock.
(GASPS) Electroshock?
Actually, the technical term
is electroconvulsive therapy.
Well, that's a world
of difference.
Light me up, Doc!
When you're getting juiced,
can you hold my turtle?
I want to bring
him back to life.
Aw... What did he die of?
I don't know.
He was dead
when I found him.
(WHIMPERING)
Homer, that's just
to bite on,
not to eat.
Sorry. Give me one that
doesn't taste so good.
That was rubber
covered in Vaseline!
Marge, write that down
so we can have it at home.
We can't begin
his treatment
soon enough.
(MACHINE WHIRS)
(ELECTRICAL CRACKLING)
(SCREAMS)
(HISSING)
(BLABBERING)
How you feeling, sweetie?
Much better.
Do you see anyone here
who isn't here?
Nope. Just you,
Marge, and Yogi Bear.
(CHUCKLES) Kidding!
(CHUCKLES)
Well, I see your sense
of humor's not affected.
That's a very bad sign.
(WHIRS)
(ELECTRICAL CRACKLING)
(SCREAMS)
Real.
Not real.
Real. Real.
Oh, sorry, Homer.
But recent historical evidence
indicates that Robin Hood
did not actually exist.
(ELECTRICAL CRACKLING)
(SCREAMS)
Fascinating.
You kids can relax.
Your father is fine now.
Fine and dandy?
Well, his dandiness
will slowly return with time.
BOTH: Dad!
Oh, kids,
I heart you, too.
Man, I'm glad to be off
that electroshock table.
Although, to be honest,
I did enjoy lying down.
Hello, Homer.
(GASPS) It's Ray!
I see him again!
Monster, you don't exist!
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
Hey, no one calls me
a monster and questions
my existence!
(GROANS)
The awesome power
of the human mind.
(GROANS)
I see Ray, too.
So do I.
Uh-oh.
Well, I'm not worried.
You've already agreed
not to sue me
for anything.
When did I
agree to that?
You did
when I validated
your parking.
You didn't validate
my parking.
Check and mate.
(CHUCKLES)
So Ray does exist?
That's right.
Now let's explore
the improbable
series of events
that led to this amusing
yet tragic farce.
On account of my eye patch,
I couldn't see Ray
sitting at the bar.
All I saw was
you eating and drinking
and talking to yourself.
And, Ned,
you didn't see me
because I was hiding
behind the chimney.
(CHUCKLES)
Gee, I thought
my vision was perfect,
and here I was
worshipping false eyeballs.
Wait, wait,
wait, wait.
How come at
Builder's Barn, I saw Homer
talking to thin air.
Well, that... Hmm.
HAWKING: I can answer that.
I've been tracking a tear
in the fabric of space-time,
which combined with airborne
pieces of metal
at Builder's Barn
to create
a miniature black hole.
This anomaly interposed itself
between Homer and Bart
causing a gravitational lens,
which absorbed the light
reflected from Ray the roofer.
That seems feasible.
(ALL CHEERING)
Wait. There's still
one last thing that
doesn't make sense.
Why did you start
fixing our roof and
then just disappear?
That's easy.
I'm a contractor.
(ALL LAUGHING)
That's right.
You're all crooks.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah,
we're all crooks.
It's true.
(LAUGHS)
Hey, wait a minute!
I went through a lot
of pain and suffering
because of this
"little misunderstanding."
Somebody owes me big.
Well, Homer,
I could make it
up to you.
Maybe a free
eye-scraping.
That's a given.
There's something else.
Something much more else.
Homer, can I
please knock off?
I've got surgery
in the morning.
Not if those gutters
aren't clean, you don't.
(MUTTERS)
So as I was
saying, Homer,
Mondays, 9:00, CBS.
They say everybody
loves that guy,
but I don't get it.
What are you
talking about?
Hey, I'm just saying,
catch it while
you still can.
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
HAWKING: Badda-bing,
badda-boom.
And we're done.