(crow squawks)
Oh, boy. Monday morning
chit-chat at the water cooler.
The only reason to have done
stuff over the weekend.
The only part of the
movie I didn't get is:
now Radioactive Man gets
his powers from his suit?
The suit is slowly killing him, but
if he doesn't wear it, he'll die.
Oh...
Wait, you guys saw the new
Radioactive Man sequel?
Uh, it's not a sequel,
it's a reboot.
Actually, this one
undoes the stuff
from the last one,
so it's a de-boot.
Stop talking!
I haven't seen it yet!
Radioactive Man Re-Rises
came out three days ago.
It is fair game.
Yeah, if you haven't seen it, then
you gotta leave the water cooler.
But what if I want
some cooled water?
You should have thought of that
when you were not
seeing the movie.
Fine.
I'll drink alone.
(grunts)
♪ The Simpsons 25x09 ♪
Steal This Episode
Original Air Date on January 5, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
It was so awesome
when Radioactive Man
had to erase his own memory.
Yeah, so he wouldn't be
tortured by his past
when he was born in the future.
Oh, they're talking
about the movie!
Hurry up, you idiot!
No, no, don't stop!
I'm sorry I got mad.
I'll do that thing you like.
I got Radioactive Man's
new villain...
the Collider.
I turn out to be a good guy.
I die, but come back
to life after the credits.
Oh!
Sometimes we feel there's
nowhere left to turn,
much like Radioactive Man,
when he had to kill his
own antimatter twin
- with a blast of time particles from
the Chrono-cube... - ♪ Amazing grace
- ♪ How loud I sing
- ...and in doing so, mortally wounding...
- ♪ To drown the spoilers out! - ...his
girlfriend, who was pregnant with his own...
♪ Shut up, shut up,
shut... ♪
(yells)
And stay out!
HOMER:
Okay.
I gotta go see the
Radioactive Man movie
before it gets
totally ruined for me.
Ooh, date night!
I'll go change my bra.
I want to see
Radioactive Man Re-Rises.
If Bart's going, I'm going!
If Grampa's going, I'm going!
If you all go, then I have
to pay for a babysitter.
We'll call that nice girl who's getting
her Masters in Child Development.
Emily-Beth? We can't
afford Emily-Beth!
She brings her own puppets!
(cooing)
Bye-bye, Maggie!
Bye-bye, money.
Two adults, two kids,
and one senior with the mind of
a baby so he should be free.
For the 3-D show,
that'll be $72.
- What?!
- Or, for ten dollars more,
you can see it in IMAX Hobbit Frame
Rate Virtual Reality Vision.
(moviegoers shuddering)
(vomits)
All right, movie, you
better be worth it.
(dramatic music plays)
(engines revving)
(dancers screaming)
HOMER:
The motorcycle dudes are chicks!
I wonder what else is chicks?
(women gasping)
♪
Don't ask.
Do smell.
ANNOUNCER: Also available
in "Arctic Slut,"
"Morning After Melon"
and "Elon Musk."
Hey... they tricked us!
That's a commercial!
If I wanted to pay for
commercials I can't skip,
I'd sign up for Hulu Plus!
Shh!
You're shushing me?
This guy's on his cell phone,
she's texting, he's sexting,
and that guy brought a
baby to a 9:00 movie!
(Spanish accent):
That's negative, man.
What happened to the movies?
First they got worse
than TV, and now this!
(all gasping)
(yelling)
And stay out!
(Homer moans)
Chins up, Homer. You don't need
a theater to watch the movie.
You just have to
illegally download it.
Illegally download it?
Is that legal?
Who knows?
But it sure is easy.
I'll walk you through it.
All you have to do is...
ANNOUNCER:
The FOX network forbids
the broadcast of
step-by-step instructions
for illegally downloading
copyrighted intellectual property.
In the meantime, please
enjoy this footage
from NASCAR's 2011
Martinsville Cup.
(engines roaring)
Wow, that was easy.
All I had to do was click on...
(engines roaring)
And play!
♪
Bless you, boy.
That was the greatest thing
I've seen on a computer
that I can talk about
with you in the room.
How did you know
how to do that?
I'm under 30.
Guys, guys, I saw the
Radioactive Man movie!
Here's my ten favorite
scenes from worst to best.
Number ten: when what's-his-name
did that stuff with those dudes.
- Number nine... - Uh, Homer,
that movie's been talked out.
We're discussing the
new James Bond flick.
I like that James
Bond is ugly now.
I like that he doesn't
have any gadgets.
I like that he's not
good at shooting,
doesn't say funny quips,
or do any James Bond stuff.
Shut up, shut up, shut up!
Homer, go to the theater
and see the movie.
(scoffs)
Theaters?
All I need to see this movie
is a laptop and a Web site
based in a country
that's really just
an offshore oil platform.
Care to join me?
♪
That was so much better
than the cinema.
It mixes the wonder of movie-going
with the rush of stealing.
All we want is brand-new,
big budget entertainment
in our homes for nothin'.
Why doesn't Hollywood get that?
Gentlemen, I am inspired to create
a theater for the people...
an experience free of
all the nuisances
and gouging of
modern-day moviegoing!
Yeah, no more jerks talking
on their cell phones!
No more jerks telling me not
to talk on my cell phone!
And best of all...
we'll never have to sit through
another annoying commercial again!
Welcome to
"Cinema Pirate-diso."
Tonight's movie is
Life is Funny,
directed by Judd Apatow.
It's based on his life, starring his
family and ad-libbed by his friends.
So for the next three
and a half hours, enjoy!
(frustrated groan)
Did you just pass gas while
we were making love?
You're the one who hired
the Korean taco truck
for our private
school fund-raiser.
(chuckles)
I live it, he writes it.
♪
Well, what did you think?
We may be going to Hell
for seeing "side bosom,"
but this backyard is
a little slice of Heaven,
all thanks to Homer Simpson!
(cheering)
This is fun!
And it was so nice of the movie
company to let you show their film.
Let me?
Uh, sweetheart,
I downloaded it off
the Internet...
illegally.
An illegal download?
But Hollywood says stealing
from Hollywood is wrong.
(scoffs)
Why should a regular guy like me
have to spend 15 bucks a ticket
so studios can pay
huge salaries
to the Air Buds and Ray
Liottas of the world?
Oh!
When I watched
that pirated movie,
I was stealing with my eyes.
So I'm repaying the good
people in Hollywood
for the ticket I
should have bought.
Now this money will end up in the
hands of the talented people
who make magic happen
on the silver screen.
(inhales)
Ah...
(startled gasp)
Karen, get me the FBI!
Karen!
You people joined this
squad for one reason:
to fight movie pirates.
I wanted to catch
serial killers.
(mocking, whiny tone): "I wanted
to catch serial killers."
From now on, you will
lay down your lives
to protect America's
chick flicks, buddy comedies
and steady stream
of animated misfires.
Sir, you have to see this.
"Took it off the Web...
"watched for free...
never pay for a movie again"?
Men, set your guns on "kill."
We're going after Homer Simpson.
I now present, direct from the
computer of an angry editor
at a special effects house,
Cosmic Wars Episode Seven.
(epic orchestral theme playing)
(audience cheering)
My childhood has been un-ruined!
Listen up, seat meat!
You are all in violation of Title
17 of the U.S. Copyright Code.
(all gasping)
Easy there, hotshot.
All the people are doing
is watching a movie.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
I'm not wearing an undershirt and
my badge is poking into my skin.
What's going on here?
Is there a fondler
in the neighborhood?
I'm here to arrest and hopefully
stage the prison suicide
of the mastermind of
this operation...
Homer Simpson!
Ooh, mastermind.
We got our man, thanks to a tip
from a heroic American snitch.
(gasps)
One of you turned me in?
Who was it?
You!
Superintendent Chalmers,
you never forgave
me for that time
we wore the same Hawaiian
shirt to that luau!
They're gonna take Dad!
- We gotta do something!
- I'm on it.
(screams)
Copyrighted material!
Don't look at it!
Someone sell me a ticket!
Ear plugs in!
Blinders on!
We trained for this!
(gunshot)
(grunting)
From now on, the only place
you'll be watching movies
without having to buy
a ticket is jail.
Oh... oh...
(whimpers)
Baby, promise me you'll
find out who turned me in.
(moans)
It's probably someone I
would never suspect.
Never suspect.
(moans)
Your moans of sympathy
are all I have.
Oh...
HOMER: Whoever did this to me will be
haunted by unbearable guilt forever!
Forever!
What are you guys in for?
Bank robbery.
Drug trafficking.
- What about you?
- Movie piracy.
- (all gasp)
- What?!
People in show business work
hard to make those movies.
My media stocks under-performed
because of people like you.
My brother lost his job
as a grip
on a movie set
because of piracy.
He had to sell his Jet Ski.
A grip without a Jet Ski
ain't no grip at all!
(yelling)
You're about to find out what
we do to copyright infringers.
(yelling)
(tires screech)
(all clamoring)
(train horn blowing in distance)
Uh... huh?
(horn blowing)
Huh...? (screams)
(men yelling)
(grunting)
(screams)
Whoo-hoo!
It's almost like
having Dad here.
Only with less growling
when I go near his food.
I just want to know who
dropped the dime on Dad.
Lousy rat.
Maybe the person that
turned your father in
thought they were doing
the right thing.
Homer just pirated a movie.
But it's not the worst thing
Dad ever did.
It's not even the worst kind
of pirate Dad's ever been.
Lisa, tell your brother that
stealing is wrong, no matter what.
I don't know. It wasn't like
Dad was stealing for himself.
He created this wonderful
experience for the whole town.
I just can't imagine
anyone turning him in.
(door creaking open)
- Dad, Dad, you're back, you're back!
- Hey! - Dad, you're back! Dad!
Homer, what are you
doing out of prison?
You have to go back
and give yourself up.
I can't go back to jail!
There's no shampoo, just soap!
Wait, I know one
place in Springfield
that doesn't care about
Internet piracy laws.
Thanks for taking us in.
Our family always
appreciates asylum.
This consulate is like
being on Swedish soil.
You're as safe here as you
would be in the Skatteskrapan.
(whistles)
Your country doesn't think illegally
downloading movies is wrong?
The people of Sweden believe all
movies should be shared freely.
How is that not stealing?
Bah, your Hollywood studios
are the real thieves,
claiming all their hit
movies have lost money.
I spit on their bookkeeping.
Yeah, and why don't they
make a sequel to Taken
where The Hangover
guys get taken
and the only ones that could
rescue them is Fast and Furious.
Aw, man, I would
love to pirate that.
As would the proud
people of Sweden.
(sirens blaring)
(tires screeching)
They've found us!
There's only one surefire way to get
fugitives out of a foreign building...
blasting death metal.
♪ Respecting the law,
respecting the law ♪
♪ Copyright law,
copyright law ♪
copyright law... ♪
You like this?
Oh-oh, Swedes love death metal.
It reminds us of death.
Damn those Peace
Prize-giving fish-smokers.
I'm so tired of being
trapped in this embassy.
Consulate.
Consulates are regional offices, which
serve the embassy in the capitol.
Thank you so much for sticking
with me through all this.
You're the greatest
wife in the world.
(moaning)
It was me!
I was the one who told the FBI.
You?
How could you?
You're my own flesh and blood.
I was just trying to
do the right thing.
Who would've thought
the authorities
would use a confession
against me?
Have you forgotten what you
promised at our wedding?
To love and cherish?
To aid and abet?
I never wanted to
say funny vows.
Well, you did!
And they got laughs.
Solid laughs!
I didn't mean for
this to happen,
but you were stealing.
All I ever had was you
looking out for me.
I got nothing now.
♪
All rise in the matter of
The People vs. Homer Simpson.
The people call Hollywood
ultra-producer, Judd Apatow.
Homer Simpson is
an enemy of art.
Art created by writers,
directors,
and the guy who uses a computer
to erase or enhance nipples.
And not just the people
who dream for a living,
but the people
who depend on us.
The spin class instructors,
the personal rabbis, Seth Rogen.
(laughing)
(crying):
It's true, I need him.
I saw a bootleg DVD of
The 40 Year Old Virgin
for sale at a car wash.
They left off my
director's commentary!
It didn't even have
a blooper reel!
(all groaning)
(gavel banging)
Homer Simpson, you
have been found guilty
of illegal reproduction and
distribution of copyrighted material.
Before sentencing, do you have
anything to say for yourself?
No.
Homer, tell them your
side of the story.
I know I hurt you, but
please trust me now.
It'll work.
You know what, Judge Apatow?
I do have something to say.
These movie people
may say I'm a pirate,
but I'm just a man.
A man who loved
Hollywood too much.
So I made my own rules
and fought the big guys
who tried to destroy
my way of life.
He doesn't sound like a villain.
- He sounds like a classic underdog.
- He's the unlikeliest of heroes!
But where's the love story?
At first my wife
didn't believe in me.
Maybe we forgot why we fell
in love in the first place.
But when times seemed
darkest, one minute ago,
she was there and gave me
the strength and courage
to fight for what I believe in.
He's a downloading David
versus a greedy Goliath.
An Erin Brockovich
but with more cleavage!
Two, three... Good Lord, he's
hitting all four quadrants!
One family, against all
odds, took on the system...
and lost.
(clamoring)
Mr. Simpson, I'd like to buy
the rights to make a movie
based on your true story.
I'm attached as
executive producer!
Attached! Attached!
One movie?
We envision a trilogy.
Will Smith's family wants
to play your family.
I'd be Jaden.
(all clamoring)
On behalf of Hollywood,
we are dropping all charges.
These people hate my dad.
How can they want to
make a movie about him?
Hollywood may be run
by big corporations
trying to squash people,
but they make movies
about people standing up
to big corporations
trying to squash
them and winning.
I'll sign with whoever can
convince Channing Tatum
to gain the most
weight to play me.
- Surprise! - Surprise!
- Surprise!
What the hell is all this?
We're so excited
about your movie
that we're having
a special screening.
But the movie isn't in
theaters till next week.
Yeah, we ripped a version off Bootleg
Bay just like you taught us.
It's still got timecode on it,
but, otherwise, it's a clean copy.
(chuckles)
You're pirating my movie?
The hell you are!
Piracy is stealing!
You're taking money out
of my family's mouths!
(gasping)
But the movie is... i-it's
about you pirating movies.
Oh, that's Hollywood fantasy.
We live in the real world, where
I have something called...
prof-it par-tic-i-pa-tion.
That's negative, man.
Oh, Homie...
Now all of you go see my movie
in the theater the day it opens!
No bargain matinees!
And tell your friends
it was great!
Buy the stuff they advertise
in the commercials before it!
Homer in the movie wears Ask
Body Spray and so should you!
Don't ask! Do smell!
Homie, do you really
think you should be...
Up-bup-bup-bup-bup!
What have we learned about not
blindly supporting our husband?
Ask Body Spray!
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
But then when times
seemed darkest,
she was there; she gave me
the strength and courage
to fight for what I believe in.
On behalf of Hollywood,
we're dropping all charges!
(cheering)
(laughing)
So what do you think, Lise?
Who are the good guys here,
the media companies or
the Internet freedom guys?
Well, both groups claim
their intentions are noble,
but at the end of the day,
they're both trying to steal
as much money as they can.
So... everyone's a pirate?
And the worst one of all is...
(Seth Rogen laughing)
Shh!