(theme music playing)
CHORUS: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
(whistle blows)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
(jazzy solo)
(chimes)
(tires screeching)
(honking horn)
D'oh!
(screaming)
(tires screeching)
And then,
the handsome prince realized
he had to go
to the bathroom really bad.
But the evil ogre, Barney,
had left the men's room
in the most wicked condition.
So, the prince went out back
to the enchanted alley...
That's not a fairy tale.
It's something
that happened to you at Moe's.
Shh! Anyway, the prince
passed out for a hundred years
until he was awakened
by the kiss of a noble raccoon.
And thank you, God
for the bad things adults do
which distract attention
from stuff I'm doing.
Amen.
He's also thankful
for your bounty, Lord.
Good save, Mom. 'Night.
Sweet dreams, honey.
Uh, Mom?
Will you help me
with my project?
I need to make a working model
of the digestive system.
Of course, honey.
Thanks. It's due tomorrow.
Tomorrow?!
Well, that's too bad, mister.
I'm not going to bail
you out this time.
You're right, Mom. I understand.
All right.
I'll get you the materials
but you're building it.
OK.
Oh, I'll make the whole thing.
OK, paper-mache mix,
pipe cleaners,
pig intestines and sparkle paint.
You're a lifesaver, Apu.
All the other stores are closed.
(gasps) At 11:30?
But this is the peak hour
for stoned teenagers
buying shiny things.
Whoa!
It's a living mirror!
Cool hat!
I'm glad you're always here.
But isn't it a little
rough on your marriage?
You know, Manjula understands.
I told her that endless toil
is the only true path
out of this jerkwater burg.
Well, when you have a free night,
we'd love to have you two
over for dinner.
Oh, please, do not be insane.
You hosted our wedding!
The least we can do
is have you over for dinner.
It is payback time, and this time...
it's personal.
(humming)
Wow! That looks great, Mom!
Some of your best work.
(gurgling)
Oh, it sounds so real!
I didn't turn it on yet.
(gurgling)
Uhh, oh, I'm never eating
chili again.
Ooh, chili!
Nelson, what are you doing?
I'm solving world hunger.
-(gurgling)
-BART: Hey, you're wrecking it.
What the-- look out!
It's gonna blow!
-(all screaming)
-(bursts)
ALL: Ew!
-I hope you're happy, Nelson.
-Very.
But I can't help wondering
where I go from here.
Stop worrying, Apu.
The Kwik-E-Mart is in good hands.
I'm not checking up on you, Sanjay.
I am simply asking you
how many pennies you have left.
(gasps)
Seven? I'll be right there.
No, he won't.
Apu's entertaining tonight.
If you need pennies,
take them from Jerry's jar.
-Oh!
-This is why I married you.
Ooh, what an outfit!
You are one hot mama!
You think so?
I can't let you in the store
like that
because you are smoking.
Oh! Apu.
(doorbell ringing)
Maybe we should not
-answer it, huh?
-(door creaks)
Door's unlocked.
Oh, Marge, Homer,
welcome!
Yes, welcome.
What a lovely home!
Oh, you are too kind, Marge.
I am sure you have noticed
the many small imperfections
that fill me with shame.
Oh, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no.
If anything, your home
makes me ashamed of my home.
Well, let us just say
we both feel bad.
Deal.
Who is your favorite
Indian pop singer?
Oh, don't make me choose.
Shankar, Shankar.
Oh, here we go.
(frenetic high-pitched wailing)
-Oh, sorry.
-(music slows down)
♪ You make me feel so young ♪
♪ You make me feel
so spring-sprung ♪
Good rice, good curry,
good Gandhi, let's hurry.
Mmm, this is delicious! What's in it?
Chickpeas, lentils and rice.
And what's in this?
-Chickpeas and lentils.
-Try it with rice.
I'm so glad we were able
to get together.
Well, you know how hard it is
to pry these two away from work.
(chuckling) Oh, yeah.
Homer's a real go-getter.
(laughing) Yeah.
I'm going right to the top.
(beeping)
Hmm, what's an "eltdown"?
Eh.
I don't understand, Marge.
Doesn't Homer work a standard
18-hour day?
Eighteen hours?
Nobody works that hard...
(clears throat) Mmm-mmm.
But he does work every day, right?
Well, pretty much.
Except weekends.
Wee... kends?
Uh, say, who's up
for a game of Ganesh-Gnop?
You told me it was
an American tradition
to work all the time
and never see your wife.
Yes, perhaps
I stretched the truth a bit,
but the Kwik-E-Mart
is a harsh mistress.
I think you just
don't want to see me!
Eh! Maybe we should just
close the door.
(arguing in Indian)
(arguing continues)
Maybe we should leave.
Uh-oh, no way.
I don't want to miss a word.
You don't know what they're saying.
I'm picking it up.
Sala seems to mean jerk,
and I think Manjula means
some kind of spaceship.
Uh, this could take a while, folks.
Thank you. Come again.
I hope we didn't get Apu
in too much trouble.
Aw, they're newlyweds.
They'll talk things out
and top it off with some loving.
-Oh, dear.
-Hmm!
(car honking)
MARGE: Either put the book down
or let me drive.
HOMER: Hey, they stole our idea.
-See? Look.
-MARGE: Ooh!
(tires screeching)
"I cherish you, my precious."
Uh... Nah.
"You're a heck
of a blacksmith."
Nah, I already got him one.
"You're a-peeling"
"Let's never split!"
(laughing)
That's funny
'cause they're monkeys.
So long, rejects.
(grunting)
Stupid cards.
Morning, Apu.
Still in hot water
with the squaw?
Worse than ever, I'm afraid.
My shameful neglect
has made her feel unloved.
Now I fear she will leave me.
Oh, she's not going to leave you
right before Valentine's Day.
That would be like going
to an air show
and leaving before the plane crash.
Oh, you are right.
There's still seven days
before Valentine's.
Ah! Seven chances to prove
my love for sweet Manjula.
(slurps)
Sweet mint julep...
I'll be at Moe's.
Hmm?
(growling and whimpering)
Come on, boy, come on.
Dad, the vet says
we shouldn't make him
fetch the Sunday paper.
(whimpering)
Good dog. Good doggie.
"Tax hike approved."
Bad dog. Bad, bad dog.
(whimpering)
Now to trim away the fat.
"Outlook." Ugh!
"Vista." No.
"Spotlight." Ugh! "Mosaic." Nah.
I'd love to look at "Scullery
Week" if you're through.
Oh! Sorry, Marge.
That's in my stockpile.
You can have this.
This is about investment opportunities
in Yemen.
Give me that!
All right, the personals.
Hmm... (humming)
"Successful mayor-type
seeks open-minded, discreet
cheerleader-type."
Oh, that's sweet.
Ah, here's one.
"Desperately seeking suction--"
Hey, look at this one!
(gasping) It's a poem.
(gasps) From Apu!
Well, don't just gasp. Read it.
"My darling bride, Manjula.
I hereby mend my ways.
I'll shower you with Valentines
for seven love-filled days."
Oh, how romantic!
I used to take out ads like that
when we were newlyweds.
The only ad you took out
was to sell our lawnmower.
We sold it, didn't we?
(both grunting)
Until last night, I never knew
Apu could be so romantic.
I can't believe it.
He covered your whole bed
with wildflowers!
Oh, I'm sure Homer has
done that for you.
Hmm. Sometimes I find pickle
slices in the sheets.
And he says I've got
six more surprises coming.
I feel like the luckiest
woman in Springfield.
-(squawking)
-(screams)
-Oh!
-(squawks)
♪ He loves the nightlife ♪
♪ He loves Manjula ♪
♪ The man they call Apu ♪
♪ Oh, yeah! ♪ (squawks)
He has trained a bird to sing to me.
Limo out front. Tickets to opera.
Front row loge. (squawks)
(groans)
Just once, I'd like a parrot
to say that to me.
Then the bird sang
"I Love the Nightlife"
with clever new lyrics.
Ugh! I hate that song.
I do, too, but it was sweet.
Women really like that
sort of thing, Homie.
Don't worry, honey.
I got something
really special planned
for Valentine's Day.
It's not that monkey card
I found in the car, is it?
Wouldn't you like to know?
(groans)
A chocolate husband!
Oh, how darling!
APU (muffled): Help! I can't breathe!
Oh, Apu!
Oh, you are the sweetest
filling of all.
(panting)
Air... I need air.
Oh, Apu!
Oh! My ears are filled with nougat.
Oh, dear!
There's a nut in my eye.
So then, the second salesman
says, "That's OK.
I just ate
all the hot buttered corn."
(laughing)
You like that one, baby?
-Hmm.
-Sarah, what's wrong?
Usually after two or three
truly tasteless jokes,
you're all over me.
Manjula got to see
La bohème.
Sarah, please.
Sarah, it's $10 a pill.
And so, with Valentine's Day
one day away,
all eyes are on the local romeo
whose seven-day gift-a-thon
has been delighting his wife
and introubulating the rest of us.
Reverend Timothy Lovejoy
says he's counseled
a number of disenchanted wives,
including Maude Flanders.
Everybody's marriage is falling
apart except ours.
See? The problem's communication.
Too much communication.
Homer, I've gone through
seven years of receipts
and you've spent less on gifts for me
than you have on temporary tattoos.
But Marge, it's worth it!
Look, the Taco Bell dog.
"Yo quiero ta..."
Hey, where'd it go?
Here, boy!
(whining)
You just don't get it!
(door slams)
This Valentine's crap
has gone too far.
(all agreeing)
Edna won't even let me clap
her erasers.
My Barbara
will no longer pleasure me
with the French arts.
The gal I'm stalking
had me bumped
back to 200 feet.
-MAN: Oh, Moe!
-That's too far.
HOMER: And ask yourselves, people,
who's to blame for all this?
Well, I guess we are.
I suppose I do take Maude
for granted.
I've done some of that myself.
Will you stop it?
It's easy to blame ourselves,
but it's even easier to blame Apu.
He's making us look bad.
(all agreeing)
-[horse neighing]
- What's going on out there?
(playing chamber music)
Aw, geez he's got everything
but the Shriners.
(beeps horn)
Hey, watch it!
You're all over the road.
We've got to stop that traitor Apu.
-ALL: Yeah!
-That's right!
Right after happy hour.
(all agreeing)
-BARNEY: I call side seat!
-MOE: Drinking will help us plan.
Come on, Apu. Make your move.
Maybe he's run out
of romantic ideas.
Naw, not our lover boy.
If I know his M.O.,
he's saved the biggest one
for today.
Ah gee, the man's just trying
to show his wife he cares for her.
How could we sabotage
his labor of love?
I don't know. Gasoline, axes--
I got some stuff in the trunk.
-Hey, there he goes.
-Let's roll.
Uh, Homer, you're driving.
Not yet, I'm not.
You'll know when I'm driving,
and it'll-- (shrieks)
Tiffany's, eh?
Yeah, looks like
Smoochy's going to seal the deal
with a diamond
the size of a doll's head.
Aw, man, he's making us look like
a bunch of cheapskates.
Whoa, whoa, my rope came loose.
WIGGUM: There he is...
behind that shopping bag.
A croissant? What the--
Ah, that's right!
They have breakfast
at Tiffany's now.
Only till 11:00.
So, that's it.
The crazy nut!
He went and bought her a sloop.
Well, this is one love boat
that won't delight and amuse.
Wait, chief,
he's not purchasing a boat.
Arr, it's kind of you
to deliver these copies of juggs.
They'll keep my men from resorting
to homosexuality...
for about ten minutes.
(all laughing)
Look who's talking.
Arr.
This is turning out to be
a total waste of time.
Not entirely.
Aw, geez we've been
following him for hours.
You know, with all the energy
we're putting
into this sabotage thing,
we could have written sonnets
for our wives
or learned to tango
or lovingly restored
one of those antique...
(yells) Ohh!
Whew! At least I got a hunk
of Moe's hair.
Man, that smarts!
Oh, baby, we got him now.
There's no escape from the airport.
Oh, nuts! We lost him.
I told you we shouldn't have
gone for long-term parking.
Hey, look! It's Elton John!
We had to make
an emergency landing.
It's that damned chandelier again.
Aah!
What's he doing in Springfield?
I got it. I got it.
Apu must have hired him
to sing for Manjula.
Not if I can help it.
And help it I might.
Mr. John, I'm your biggest fan.
I've tape-recorded
all your songs off the radio.
Oh, that's very sweet!
-Have a Grammy.
-Uh...
Sir Elton, my noble friends
and I would like
to dub you...
a Knight of the Grand Concourse.
Yeah. It's for all
your charity work and, um...
for, uh, you know,
teaching us, um, to love again.
Really? I did that?
How the hell should I know?
Just get in the cage.
What? Oh, hazing the new guy, eh?
You know, when I was dubbed
"Sir Elton,"
the Queen paddled me silly.
Hey, Apu's talking to a skywriter.
So, that was his plan all along.
If he writes a message
of love over Springfield,
we're all screwed.
ELTON: Hello? Lads?
Don't forget your old pal, Elton.
Can anyone hear me?
Skycap?
OK, here is the message,
and please don't skimp on the...
sarin?
Don't be frightened.
That tank's just
Peace Corps surplus.
HOMER: Not so fast, Apu!
Homer!
What a delightful coincidence!
We're putting an end to your
insane Valentine's rampage.
Never again will good, lazy men
have to-- What the...
Oh, no, you don't!
(panting)
Hey, you with the scarf!
Stop skywriting!
I have to deliver a message.
It's the skywriter's code.
I am so sick of that damned code!
If you won't stop, then I'll stop you!
(grunting)
What are you doing? Don't do that!
(plane whirring)
Oh, isn't that sweet?
(sighs)
That must be for Manjula.
Just once,
I'd like a love note in the sky.
(chuckles)
(grunting)
Lousy message!
You crazy fool, you'll kill us all!
Correction, kill us both!
(Homer grunting)
I love you... it's an angel!
Ooh, that's Neddy's pet name for me.
I love you, poppin' fresh.
Oh, Clancy! (laughs)
I love you, Edna K.
It's a little run together,
but that's what it says.
I love you... cactus?
Blobby? Upsilon?
Oh, who am I kidding?
Homer would never
surprise me like that.
(aircraft whizzing)
MAN: Doggone it!
You ruined my message!
What's the matter with you,
you crazy old buzzard!
-Get off me!
-You're making me mad!
-(both yelling)
-Oh, me!
My humble love note is turning
into a Valentine's Day massacre!
You think you've got problems.
I just chewed my way
out of a dog carrier.
Oh! Elton John?
That's my name.
Well, not really.
I hate to sound like
a screaming fan, but...
(screams)
That maniac nearly killed us.
Shall I... take you to the pilot?
Ha! You see,
because that is your song...
-I heard you.
-Yes, because...
someone saved your life tonight.
-(laughs)
-Cut it out!
Well, well, "The Bitch is Back."
(laughs)
(exasperated sigh)
Aah! Ow!
Durn'it! Why won't you die?
(yelling)
Oh, prickers! (screaming)
Huh? (gasps)
(whimpering)
(gasps)
What in the world?
(groaning) Roses...
So many roses.
Just when I think
I have you figured out,
you fall from the sky with roses.
Roses...
Oh, Homie!
Oh, they're beautiful!
Oh, I'm going to snuggle
your brains out.
Well, I think I have
a collapsed lung... but OK.
♪ If I was a sculptor, heh
But then again, no ♪
♪ Or a man who makes potions ♪
♪ In a traveling show ♪
♪ I know it's not much
but it's the best I can do ♪
♪ My gift is my song, yeah ♪
♪ And this one's from Apu ♪
Oh...
Oh, I can't believe it.
You closed the Kwik-E-Mart
just for me.
Well, you and the health inspector.
Champagne squishy?
Oh, thank you!
It should get you
pretty darned hammered.
(theme music playing)
-(murmuring)
-Shh!
Captioned by
Visual Data Media Services