♪ The Simpsons ♪
(chalk screeches)
(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(tires screeching)
(horn honks)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
(engine revving)
ANNOUNCER:
Hey, Lance Murdock,
you just jumped
16 blazing school buses.
What are you
going to do now?
(groaning)
I'm going to Duff Gardens.
Duff Gardens--
home of the whiplash.
To be completed in 1994.
(Lance groaning)
(screaming)
(all screaming)
And the washing machine.
(choking, gasping)
ALL: Wow!
See the happiest fish
in the world
at our fabulous
Beer-quarium.
(moaning)
(belches)
Bart, warm up the car.
We're going
to Duff Gardens.
BOTH: Yay!
Now, what do we say
when we get to
the ticket booth?
BOTH: We're under six.
And I'm a college student.
Kids, I have
some bad news.
Your Great-Aunt Gladys has...
passed on.
Gladys, Gladys...
about yea high, blue hair,
big dent in her forehead?
No, honey, Gladys looked
more like your Aunt Patty.
(shuddering)
Oh, yeah, there she is.
The funeral's
in Littleneck Falls.
Looks like we'll have to go
to Duff Gardens another time.
We understand.
No use complaining about
something you can't change.
But I want to go
to Duff Gardens right now!
Oh, Homer,
quit pouting.
(whines)
I'm not pouting.
I'm mourning.
Stupid dead woman.
♪ On top of spaghetti ♪
♪ All covered with cheese ♪
♪ I lost my poor meatball ♪
If you don't mind,
we're on our way to a funeral.
♪ Ding dong,
the witch is dead ♪
♪ Which old witch? ♪
♪ The wicked witch ♪
Homer!
Patty, Selma, I'm sorry.
He's hugging us.
What do we do?
Just close your eyes
and think of MacGyver.
(grunting)
Hey, Homer, this luggage
is crushing me.
Hey, you don't hear
Lisa complaining.
(muffled groan)
I can't believe
Auntie Gladys is really gone.
Her legend will live
forever.
Yeah, the legend
of the dog-faced woman.
(laughing)
Legend of
the dog-faced woman.
Oh, that's good.
Homer, that's
very rude of you.
What? D'ohhh!
Could we please
stop somewhere?
My butt's asleep.
(slurping and chewing)
All right, I'm almost there.
Ohhh!
Another place mat, sir?
Please.
While we're waiting for our pie,
let's take a minute
to remember Great-Aunt Gladys.
Hmm, wait a minute.
That was "Prince of Tides."
Five...
six...
seven...
eight...
What are you playing?
-Counting game.
-That's nice.
Nine...
ten...
MINISTER: He was a good man.
He was a kind man.
He gave to his community
and asked little in return.
He never--
(whispering)
That's a woman?
Dear Lord!
(laughs nervously)
Uh, well... I guess most
of what I said can be salvaged.
Take a seat, bozo.
And that eulogy better not
show up on the bill.
I'll keep this short.
Gladys lived alone, died alone.
I guess you could say she was
a role model for Selma and me.
She wasn't a rich woman...
(grumbling)
...but she was rich in spirit.
Forgot my hat.
Don't hassle the dead, boy.
They have eerie powers.
(snorts)
I thought this thing
was gonna be catered.
Boy, am I hungry.
I mean, I'm really,
really hungry.
It's just not fair, damn it!
(sobbing)
Oh...
Good-bye, Great-Aunt Gladys.
I wish I'd made
more of an effort
to get to know you
these last few years.
(raspy voice)
Don't worry about it.
(screaming)
(laughs malevolently)
I'm Lionel Hutz, executor
of Ms. Bouvier's estate.
She left a video will,
so I earn my fee simply by
pressing this "play" button.
Pretty sweet, eh?
I would like to start
by reading a passage
from Robert Frost.
"Two roads diverged
in a yellow wood, and..."
(tape fast forwarding)
Homer!
All in favor
of skipping the poem?
Thank you.
"...and that has made
all the difference."
Now, let's get down
to business.
LIONEL HUTZ'S VOICE:
To my executor, Lionel Hutz,
I leave $50,000.
Mr. Hutz!
You'd be surprised how often
that works, you really would.
To Marge, I leave
my collection of
potato chips that
resemble celebrities.
They're all here.
Otto von Bismarck,
Maurice Chevalier,
right up to Jay Leno.
These chips were
my children, Margery.
Take special care of them.
Uh-oh.
To my sister, Jackie,
I leave my pet iguana,
Jubjub.
Why didn't she just leave me
the bowel obstruction
that killed her?
To my dear childless nieces,
Patty and Selma,
I leave my grandfather clock
and these words:
Don't die lonely like me.
Raise a family,
and do it now.
Now!
Now!!!
Hey, a grandfather clock.
Not bad.
(clock tolling and ticking)
(snoring)
Aunt Gladys was right.
There's something missing
in our lives.
Don't worry.
We'll get that barking dog
record tomorrow.
Patty... I want a baby.
What do I do here?
Just tell us
about yourself.
Well... I want to have a baby
before it's too late.
You're looking
at a free lunch, boys.
Come and get it.
(amorous growling)
Ach! Back to the loch
with you, Nessie.
One drop of this love potion,
and you will have
any man you desire.
Really?
What are
the magical ingredients?
Mostly corn syrup,
a little rubbing alcohol.
You'll be lucky if it doesn't
make your hair fall out,
actually.
(grunting)
Paper or plastic?
You decide.
So, wearing a belt, are you?
Yep.
No suspenders for you.
I guess not.
Orange is really your color.
They make us
wear this.
Shall we continue
this conversation over dinner?
Uh... I'm not allowed
to date customers.
It's store policy.
No, it isn't.
-Ow!
-shut up, Arnold.
No, go for it, man.
"R,"
"Q,"
"J,"
question mark.
Smiley face.
SELMA: Next!
Wait a minute.
It says here
you're single.
Did I do wrong?
Combed, biscuits, chicken,
yellow, mailman...
You're reading
the wine list, sir.
Very good.
I don't know how to
thank you for dinner.
Use your imagination.
(childish chatter)
(child screaming)
(thudding)
Ehh!
Get out of my car.
This isn't my house.
Come to Duff Gardens
where roaming gangs aren't
a big problem anymore.
Now featuring
the clean-shaven sounds
of Hooray for Everything.
ALL: Hey, kids,
take a walk on
the wild side.
And all the races sing:
♪ Doo, doo, doo,
shoo-bee doobee doo ♪
♪ Doo, doo, doo ♪
♪ Shoo-bee doobee doo, yeah! ♪
Can we go to Duff Gardens
this weekend?
Sure...
unless another aunt dies.
(door closes)
Selma, your date's
over already?
Yeah.
I was so depressed,
I ate a jar
of expired olives.
(sighs)
I guess I'll never
have a baby.
Aunt Selma,
this may be presumptuous,
but have you ever considered
artificial insemination?
Boy, I don't know.
You've got to be
pretty desperate
to make it with a robot.
(whispering)
I knew that.
How do I know
I'm getting quality?
Don't worry.
Our donors have to pass
a rigorous screening process.
All done.
Thank you.
Always a pleasure.
What a beautiful
little girl.
(belches like Barney)
(babies belching like Barney)
(belching continues)
MARGE: "101 Frozen Pops."
A Nobel Prize winner.
An NBA all-star.
Ooh, one of the Sweathogs.
I checked.
It's not Horshack.
(groans)
Are you sure you want
to have a baby this way?
Yeah, you've had some
pretty bad experiences
ordering out of catalogs.
Remember that
mail-order husband?
(knock at door)
Ooh, you look just like
your picture.
Sorry, my mind's made up.
I want to have a kid,
and this is the only way
I can do it.
Why do you want
to have a baby so bad?
I got a lot of love to give,
and right now my only outlet
is my ham radio.
(man speaking
foreign language)
Are you sure you've
thought this through?
A child can really
change your life.
You'll have to
give up smoking.
-I'll chew.
-No man will want you.
All I got now
is sperm in a cup.
(both groaning)
BART/LISA: Get up! Get up!
Time to go
to Duff Gardens.
Mom! Mom!
We want to go
to Duff Gardens!
Oh, great.
Dad's dead.
(moaning)
Oh, have you been eating
that sandwich again?
Sand... wich.
Geez, we hardly made a dent
in that ten-foot hoagie.
I'll give it
a good home.
You've been eating that thing
for a week.
I think the mayonnaise
is starting to turn.
Two more feet,
and I can fit it in the fridge.
Homer, I found this
behind the radiator.
I really think
you should throw it away.
Suggestion noted.
Marge, I'd like to be alone
with the sandwich for a moment.
Are you going
to eat it?
Yes.
Aww!
You look terrible.
I don't care.
I'm going to Duff Gardens.
(thud)
S-s-so cold.
Your lips
are turning blue.
I think
you better stay home.
No!
Duff Gardens! Hurrah!
(horn blaring)
We really appreciate
you taking the children
on such short notice.
We'll have fun,
won't we, kids?
To get to Duff Gardens,
I'd ride with Satan himself.
That's the spirit.
See you tonight.
Good-bye, Dad.
Don't eat any solids.
But I love solids.
It won't be any fun
without you, Dad.
BOTH: Yayyy!
This is all your fault!
I-- Oh, how can I
stay mad at you?
Mmm!
Ooh...
There it is!
The Duff beeramid.
"The beeramid contains
so much aluminum
"it would take five men
to lift it.
22 immigrant laborers died
during its construction."
Ah, plenty more where that
came from.
♪♪ (theme park music)
Look! It's
the seven Duffs!
BART: There's Tipsy.
And there's Queasy.
LISA: There's Surly.
And Remorseful.
Hey.
Take a picture--
it'll last longer.
Get out of here.
Four score and seven years ago,
we took the finest hops
and barley
to brew a refreshing,
full-bodied lager.
Ahhh.
(beat boxing)
Well...
♪ I'm rappin' A.B.,
and I'm here to say ♪
♪ If you want to drink beer,
Duff's the only way ♪
♪ I said, the only way ♪
♪ Break down ♪
This is a disgrace.
Settle down.
Anything this bad
has to be educational.
Bart!
Let's see if they wore
underwear back then.
Yeah!
Do you feel any better?
No.
What are the odds
of getting sick on a Saturday?
A thousand to one.
To cheer you up, I rented
a couple of videos.
"Boxing's Greatest Weigh-Ins"
and "Yentl."
"Yentl"? What's that?
It deals with a bookish
young woman's efforts
to enter rabbinical school.
Sounds great!
Oh, my God,
you're delirious.
Hmm...
(Bart reading)
Wow!
You're charming the pants
off of me.
What did you say,
Aunt Selma?
I said take off
those damn glasses!
Ooh, this looks like fun.
A bench.
Kids, what do you say
you go get your Aunt Selma
a beer smoothie?
BOTH: No, come on, Aunt Selma,
we got to go.
Come on,
let's have fun!
(groaning)
Hey, man, if the line's
this long, it's got to be good.
Get bent.
MAN (on TV):
What's going on here?
Oh, Yentl.
I might have known.
That Yentl puts the "she"
in yeshiva.
Hmm, well,
you've cooled down.
That's what you think.
(growling)
(chuckling)
You know, I rented
another tape
in case you felt better.
"The Erotic Adventures
of Hercules."
With Norman Fell as Zeus.
Whoo-hoo!
♪ Duff beer for me ♪
♪ Duff beer for you ♪
♪ I'll have a Duff ♪
♪ You have one, too ♪
♪ Duff beer for me ♪
♪ Duff beer for you ♪
♪ I'll have a Duff ♪
♪ You have one, too ♪
♪ Duff beer for me ♪
♪ Duff beer for you... ♪
I want to get off.
You can't get off.
We have five more continents
to visit.
Hey, Lis, I dare you
to drink the water.
I'm not sure
that is water.
Chicken.
(clucking)
Quit it, Bart.
Quit it!
Quit it! Quit it!
Bart, be quiet.
Lisa, drink
the water.
(sighing)
(distorted)
♪ Duff beer for me ♪
♪ Duff beer for you ♪
♪ I'll have a Duff,
Duff, Duff, Duff... ♪
They're all around me.
No way out!
(insane laughter)
No way out, I tell you!
What's wrong?
Well, you just put your head
right here.
(snarling)
(maniacal scream)
Hercules, the Cyclops
tore off my clothes.
(laughing)
(giggling)
(snarling)
♪ I'll have a Duff ♪
♪ You have one, too... ♪
Bart! Lisa!
♪♪ (lively)
LISA: Ahh...
Oh...
(humming)
Ahh... I can see the music.
Mitch, you're doing
a bang-up job.
Thank you, sir.
(chuckling)
Whoa, that isn't good.
(screaming)
Stop the ride!!
I'll have to ask my supervisor.
Better stop it.
Can't you do something?
Hey. Surly only looks out
for one guy-- Surly.
-Sorry, Surly.
-Shut up.
SELMA:
Don't blame these kids.
It's not their fault.
I think their father
is missing a chromosome.
Miss Bouvier,
while we were rescuing this boy,
hoodlums made off
with three bumper cars!
(cars bumping)
(laughter)
And I don't think
George Washington
will ever be the same.
Ai yi, yi, yi, yi...
We found this one swimming
naked in the fermentarium.
I am the lizard queen!
Give her this,
and this,
and then these.
Thank you, doctor.
Oh, I'm not a doctor.
Come to Homercles.
(giggling)
I can't.
The beans will burn.
Homercles cares not for beans.
Hi, kids.
How was Duff Gardens?
Can't talk. Coming down.
Hmmm...
How do you do it, Homer?
You take an ordinary bed sheet,
fold it around like this--
No, I mean raising kids.
I just couldn't cut it today.
All I wanted was
a little version of me
that I could hold in my arms.
Oh, Jubjub.
When I went to pick him up,
Mom was trying to stab him
with a hat pin.
Shh.
♪ You make me feel ♪
♪ Like a natural woman ♪
♪ Oh, baby,
what you've done to me ♪
CHORUS:
♪ What you've done to me ♪
♪ You make me feel
so good inside ♪
CHORUS: ♪ Good inside ♪
♪ And I just want to be ♪
CHORUS: ♪ Want to be ♪
♪ Close to you ♪
♪ You make me feel
so alive ♪
♪ 'Cause you make me feel ♪
♪ You make me feel ♪
♪ Like a natural woman ♪
SELMA: Oh, yeah.
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.