CHORUS SINGS:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(exclaims)
(school bell ringing)
(belches)
(whistle blows)
(yells)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
(grunts)
Excellent.
(laughing)
(screams)
Don't worry.
I'll put out the flames.
-(thuds)
-(groans)
Oops! I used
the wrong end.
(muffled grumbling)
(groaning)
(laughing)
Hilarious!
I don't like this.
Real humor comes from people
being nice to each other.
Aw, come on, Marge.
There's nothing funnier than
a good old bonk on the head.
-I concur.
-D'oh!
-(giggling)
-Not funny.
Good night kids, and don't
forget, Krusty loves you!
MAN:
That's a wrap!
And you kids
in the studio audience,
please hand back all the hats,
toys, and savings bonds
I passed out during the taping.
(kids exclaiming sadly)
Great show, Krusty.
Terrific!
We've got to make changes.
Big changes.
These are your ratings
with young girls.
Hey, if my writers knew
how to appeal to girls,
they wouldn't
be writers.
First of all, we love being
in the Krusty business.
The subtitle:
"We don't trust you at all."
Anyway, we're giving you
a new female costar
-and she starts Monday.
-What?!
A new costar?!
Suppose I refuse to go along
with this?
Then we've got
an entire reality show
all set to pick
the new you.
Hey, hey!
I'm non-union!
Okay, okay. Change the show
however you want!
Make it exactly like the
other crap on your network,
but just let me stay!
(sobs):
Just don't fire me.
Now that's groveling.
Time to try out
my new deep fryer.
Who wants fresh doughnuts?
-Me! Me! Me-me-me!
And I even got
rainbow sprinkles.
Some rainbow--
there's no violet.
Then don't have any.
Hey, don't listen to me!
What do I know
about rainbows?
(smacking lips)
Mmm.
None for me, Marge.
I get free doughnuts at work.
I can see them now.
In the break room,
beside the fridge,
the pink cardboard box awaits.
Groaning with a "United Nations"
of doughnuts:
jellies rubbing elbows
with cream-filled,
the masculine contours
of the box juxtaposed
with the feminine curves
of the treats themselves.
Why didn't you
try to stop him?
I did, once.
(humming happily)
(exclaims)
No pink box?
Wha-What's going on?
I'm afraid your daily
doughnuts are no more.
You. Can't. Do. That.
Until Mr. Roosevelt's
New Deal starts working,
this country's still
in a depression.
I'm spending
a fortune on atoms,
and we have to cut costs.
But we have
way more expensive
unnecessaries
than doughnuts.
Yeah, like the ceiling
furniture.
Or all the joke ID badges
we order.
No doughnuts!
-No!
-D'oh!
Nuts!
Exactly.
Hey! Hey!
But seriously,
hey, hey, kids.
A word about today's show.
The network "geniuses"
with the ink still drying
on their MBAs...
(derisive laughter)
...think your old pal Krusty
should share his limelight
with an up-and-coming new star.
Let's give a respectful
welcome
to Princess Penelope.
(sparse applause)
♪♪
♪ Where do I keep
my princess-ness? ♪
♪ It's not in my jewels
or my crown ♪
♪ It's not in the smiles
of my handmaids three ♪
♪ Who hold up the train ♪
♪ Of my gown ♪
♪ It's the part of me
that wants to be ♪
♪ The girl whom
everyone flatters ♪
(groans)
♪ 'Cause in her heart ♪
♪ A princess knows ♪
♪ She's the only girl
who matters ♪
(trilling high note)
I can't keep
watching this dreck.
(relieved sigh)
Much better.
First, girls ruined
Sex and the City.
Now this.
I agree it's cliché,
but she does
have a certain...
(gasps) Unicorn!
(exclaims)
That is so fake.
You can see the strap
on the horn.
Just give me this!
Easy there,
Habitrail.
They took away
our doughnuts at work.
-All I've had are my meals.
-And the worst thing is,
there's nothing
we can do about it.
I think that's
the best thing
'cause then you
can say, "Well,
there's nothing
we can do about it."
Bartender, buy these men
a round on me.
You want to
"buy a round?"
I heard about that
in bartending school,
but I never seen it happen.
Oh, this is very good for me.
Very good indeed.
Gator McCall.
I'm a headhunter.
(screams)
(chuckles)
I'm a corporate recruiter
who specializes
in nuclear workers.
I guess these days,
headhunters can be anything.
You nuclear workers have no idea
how valuable you are.
Times have never been better
for your industry,
now that all the protesters
who marched in front
of nuclear power plants
are dying off
from radiation poisoning.
Are these business cards
or passports to a better future?
-Those are business cards.
-Nice.
Krusty, thanks
to Princess Penelope,
your studio audience is packed.
And we didn't need
any cardboard kids.
Yeah, but they're
all girls.
Girls don't laugh,
and they don't buy cigars.
Dutch Masters is gonna
drop us like a hot potato.
-(music plays, excited chatter)
-Hey, hey, kids!
Let's see what's in the news.
I see we reached a soft timber
agreement with Canada.
GIRLS (chanting):
We want the Princess!
Don't forget
the unicorn!
Did I hear the sound
of wishes being wished?
(girls clamoring):
Yes! Yes!
♪♪
♪ Glitter and sparkle,
one, two, three ♪
♪ You're all princesses
just like me. ♪
(sneezing)
Breathin' all this stuff
can't be good.
Poor Krusty.
He's become the lowest form
of life: a sidekick.
You said it, Bart.
Way to sum up the situation.
Take it easy, little buddy.
That's exactly
how I'll take it.
-Wanna come in
and get your sister with me?
-Hell, no.
Watch your language.
Now, why the hell not?
Ah, The Krusty Show
sucks now.
It's all pink and princessy.
Why are great things
always ruined by women?
The Army, the Fantastic Four.
Think how awesome
American Idol
would be with just
Simon and Randy.
(chuckles)
Oh, Bart, you say that now.
But when you're grown-up,
you'll just think it.
Now you stay here
and I'll get your sister.
(humming)
Princess Penelope,
sign mine, sign mine!
(gasps)
What the...?!
Where's all your Krusty stuff?
Right through
that magical door.
(gasps)
Ay carumba!
(groans)
Krusty?
Snap out of it!
You're Krusty the Clown.
One of Look magazine's
hundred most-promising clowns
of 1958.
A lot of suicides
in that group.
Funny suicides (chuckles),
but still.
My day is over, kid.
What are you talking about?
Whose name is on that sign?
D'oh!
-(Krusty doll laughing)
-Hey, how'd this one
get way over here?
That's it. I've hit rock-bottom.
Well, my comeback starts now.
I mean, now. Ow!
Let me start by getting
out of the Dumpster.
Oh, why do clown things
always happen to clowns?
Now other nuclear plants
let their employees
tape Gary Larson cartoons
on their workstations.
But here at Cap City Nuclear,
you can actually see...
Gary Larson.
Gary Larson?!
I thought you retired.
I was retired
until I got the call
from Capital City Nuclear,
offering me the chance to be
the in-house cartoonist
at a nuclear plant.
Gary, why don't you whip up
an instant classic
-for my friends here?
-You got it, Gator.
Man, a lion would not want
to see that on his X-ray.
(New York accent):
Where are you? Where?
You're not even in Nassau County
anymore. You're in Suffolk.
Look, look, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You're going the wrong way.
-(knocking)
-Hold on.
(lilting voice):
Coming!
Now see here,
Little Miss Scene Stealer,
I'm the star of this show.
You're just the reason
people tune in.
(New York accent):
Krusty, there's something
I have to tell you.
No, no! Let me finish:
I work like I drink: alone.
Or with a monkey watching me.
Krusty... I love you.
That way, if I pass out,
he turns me on my side so...
You what?!
I have loved you since
I was a 12-year-old girl,
in Mineola, Long Island,
watching your show.
WDQT?
They had this fat,
pathetic station manager.
-That was my father.
-Great guy.
I still have my
Krusty Klub ring.
I wasn't popular because I was
more beautiful and friendly
than everyone else,
but whenever I looked
at this ring,
I knew I had one friend.
You know those rings came
with a membership card.
That's the one.
Oh, my God.
Please don't tell me I died
on the operating table again.
You didn't.
This is real, Krusty.
(nervous chuckle)
Welcome to
the Krusty and Princess Penelope
Smoochie-Poo I Love You Hour.
No laughs, just
hugs and cuddles.
Don't worry.
Mr. Teeny's got
a flaming arrow.
Oh, yuck.
(to the tune of "This Old Man")
♪ This old clown, tee-hee-hee ♪
♪ He's as happy as can be ♪
♪ 'Cause I got a girlfriend
under 33... ♪
-Boo!
I walked 19 miles for this?
♪ Can't you kids be
glad for me? ♪
♪ I am her, she is me ♪
♪ I'm just like Penelope... ♪
♪ It's still on
in my head ♪
♪ It will be there
till I'm dead... ♪
(groans)
(humming tune)
Whether she was competing
in equestrian events
at the 1976 Olympics or spending
her summers at Holyrood Palace,
Princess Anne is truly
a world leader.
Okay, so far, for
"Inspirational Women Day"
we've had one Princess Anne,
15 Dianas,
two baby Princess
Ingrid Alexandras of Norway,
and one Princess Leia.
-I'm a Star Wars.
-(sighs)
(satisfied moan)
I don't care what anyone says.
Massages are relaxing.
Now if you boys sign up
with Cap City Nuclear,
you'll get weekly massages,
plus free sushi
right through the face hole.
Sir, I have some
unsettling news:
three of our workers
are being poached.
The heart
of our tug-of-war team.
No. No, this is our year.
How can this be happening?
Sir, I'm afraid your
doughnut-cutting measures,
while reasonable, were
perceived as draconian.
Comparing me to old Draco, eh?
I'll have to do
something about this.
(cracking)
(lush romantic music playing)
♪ I was a parched
little seedling ♪
♪ Until you were
watered with love ♪
♪ Love, love, love,
love, love. ♪
Stop the music!
Thank God.
I'm sick and tired
of this woman...
Yes!
...not being married to me.
Huh?
Penelope, will you be
my princess bride?
Oh, Krusty, yes! Yes!
(trilling high note)
That's it. Game over.
Is it, Bart? Is it?
What are you talking about?
A wedding is a
complex thing, Bart.
It's so easy for
something to go wrong.
(gasps)
Milhouse Van Houten,
will you do me the honor
of ruining Krusty's
wedding with me?
Oh, Bart, this is
all happening so fast.
Let's call my mom together.
Goodbye, power plant.
(sobbing)
I'd better get out of here
before I have a meltdown.
If I hadn't had to work in you,
we might've been friends.
So long.
Oh, right.
(all gasping)
Gentlemen.
Please don't leave me.
Sir, I'm afraid
it's too late.
Oh, I imagine Cap City's
been wooing you
with trips to the seashore,
a Christmas goose,
Spanish lemons,
folderol I can't
afford to match.
But please, accept this
little going-away present.
(scoffs)
You can't win us back
with mere doughnuts.
Oh, but these aren't
just any doughnuts.
These doughnuts were made
the old-fashioned way:
the dough is sweetened
with Cuban sugar
from pre-Batista plantations,
then it's deep-fried
in the tallow of three
different animals,
two of which are now extinct.
Hmm?
(Delibes' "The Flower Duet"
playing)
That is the most amazing
doughnut I've ever tasted.
Well, if you stay on at the
Springfield Nuclear Plant,
you could have one of these
tasty beauties every day.
(groans)
One of these every day
might kill us.
Can we get a health plan
to go with them?
Sure, you can have
a health plan...
or two doughnuts a day.
(moaning ecstatically)
Move over, Brangelina.
Take a backseat,
Queen Latifarod.
Because today belongs
to "Krustelope."
This is the 15th marriage
for Krusty,
and the first for
"Princess Penelope,"
who is not, in fact,
a real princess.
Her actual name is:
Penelope Mountbatten Hapsburg
Hohenzollern Mulan-Pocahontas.
(singing in Hebrew)
(clearing throat)
Well, let's do the ceremony.
("Bridal March" playing)
Friends, loved ones,
we are gathered here today
to marry a Jew and a...
Congregationalist--
is that even a thing?
And now, let's continue
with this mockery.
Hmm? Hmm?
You're not my ring bearer.
What happened to the monkey?
I locked him in the Torah room.
(chattering)
Kid, what's your angle?
I'm trying to seal
the deal over here.
Princess, before
you marry Krusty,
there's someone
you should meet.
Holly Hippie.
Krusty's sidekick in 1969
and his first wife.
He wouldn't let me watch
the moon landing.
I was jealous of
Neil Armstrong.
And his last wife,
Eartha Kitt,
recorded this before
her untimely death.
They were only married
for six hours,
but she still hated Krusty.
He was asleep for
five of those hours.
And the one he was awake,
was a cat-tastrophe.
(snarling)
Wow, wow, this is
such an eye-opener.
I am blown away by how little
this bothers me.
I really love this guy.
And you are the greatest thing
that's ever happened to me.
And that's why
I can't marry you.
This kid and his ugly
sister are right.
I won't be good
enough for ya.
You can never
disappoint me.
I know your past--
your mug shots,
your bowling alley shoe spray
addiction, your country album.
They don't bother me.
They don't?
Don't you love me?
Princess, you're the only
woman I care about enough
to ditch at the altar.
Okay, Krusty,
if that's how you feel.
We'll always have
Sideshow Mel's dressing room.
What?! Ew!
(lively music playing)
(laughing)
♪ We're after the same
rainbow's end ♪
♪ Waiting 'round the bend ♪
♪ My huckleberry friend ♪
♪ Moon river ♪
♪ And me... ♪
(applause)
Merci. Merci.
(gasps)
Oh...
Just my imagination.
KRUSTY:
No, it wasn't.
I came here looking for you,
and I fell off the boat.
(gurgling)
Krusty! My Borscht Belt baby!
You changed your mind.
Ah, I'd rather be a happy
schnook than a noble shlumpf.
♪♪
(trilling high note)
Enhanced by Fotokem