♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
D'oh!
(many bottles clinking)
Hmm?
ANNOUNCER (on TV): And now,
the thrilling conclusion of...
"Colonel Dracula
Joins the Navy!"
-Uh, Colonel?
-DRACULA: Blahh!
-(clinking continues)
-Hmm?
Lisa, what in the heck
are you doing?
Oh, it's for my junior
achievers club.
We're trying to earn money
by recycling.
Recycling is useless, Lise.
Once the sun burns out,
this planet is doomed.
You're just making sure
we spend our last days
using inferior products.
Well, I think it's a great idea.
Mom! Mom!
You're mixing polyethylene
with polyurethane.
-Marge!
-Well, I'm sorry.
And you have to cut
these up first.
Otherwise, animals
get caught in them.
Only the stupid ones.
I could still use more paper.
Hey, I know where there's
lots of paper.
(laughing)
Dad, you're not supposed
to have fun recycling.
This is serious.
Oh, okay.
(choked-up crying)
SKINNER:
What a load of garbage.
I'm ecstatic. With the money from this,
we're within striking distance
of our trip to Albany!
(cheering)
Super. Now, let's give
a big Junior Achievers'
welcome
to our guest speaker--
I know he can teach us
a lot about business--
Mr. C. Montgomery burns.
(scattered applause)
I'll keep it short and sweet.
Family, religion, friendship.
These are the three demons
you must slay
if you wish to succeed
in business.
When opportunity knocks,
you don't want to be driving
to the maternity hospital
or sitting in some
phony baloney church.
Or synagogue.
Questions?
Well, uh, I'm going
to take advantage
of this rare opportunity
even if you children
aren't interested.
Which do you think
is more important--
hard work
or stick-to-itiveness?
-Are there any real questions?
-Yes.
Um, does your plant
have a recycling program?
Re-cy-cling?
I'm afraid I'm not familiar
with that term,
you adorable little ragamuffin.
Hmm. You never heard
of recycling?
It means to reuse things
to conserve our natural
resources.
Oh, so Mother Nature
needs a favor.
Well, maybe she should
have thought of that
when she was besetting us with droughts
and floods and poison monkeys.
Nature started the fight
for survival,
and now she wants to quit
because she's losing.
Well, I say-- hard cheese.
But nature's not our enemy.
Well, surely, you agree
we can do without her.
No, I don't agree.
No?
How dare you question Mr. Burns?
I'll handle it, Smithers.
(chuckles)
Shut up, little girl.
If I had spent my life listening
to dismal Doras like you,
I wouldn't be worth
$200 million today.
But according to your
most recent biography,
you only have
$100 million today.
I... I...
(sputters)
Um...
Actually, sir, it's...
considerably less than that.
I, um... have to go.
(clapping alone)
Monty Burns, everybody.
I've called you all here
because I need
some honest answers.
What is my current
financial situation?
-Great.
-I hear great.
-All right, well,
let's have a look
at my stock portfolio.
Hmm. Confederated Slaveholdings.
How's that doing?
It's, uh... uh, steady.
I'm sure all your stocks
are doing well, sir.
-After all, you chose them.
-(murmuring approval)
Well, let's get out the old
stock ticker and have a look.
Here's where I stopped
checking it last time--
September, 1929...
Oh, no... Oh, no.
Oh, no.
Smithers, why didn't you tell me
about this market crash?
Um, well, sir, it happened
25 years before I was born.
Oh, that's your excuse
for everything.
I've got to do something
to get my money back quickly.
This calls for an aggressive
trading strategy.
ALL: Good idea, sir.
Take 50% of my money
and put it in the blue chips--
Trans-Atlantic Zeppelin,
Amalgamated Spats,
Congreves Inflammable Powders,
U.S. Hay--
and sink the rest
into that up-and-coming
Baltimore Opera Hat company.
That should set things
right again, eh, boys?
-Absolutely.
-Oh, yes, sir.
Genius. "A" all the way.
Can't go wrong with Congreves.
A half-ton of newspaper,
and all we get is 75 cents?
That won't even cover the gas
I use to go to the store
to buy the twine
to tie up the bundles.
It sounds like
you're working for your car.
Simplify, man.
(muttering)
Sorry, kids,
the trip to Albany is off,
-and there's to be no more recycling.
-(kids protesting)
But we didn't do that badly.
We collected enough paper
to save one whole tree.
(children crying)
CHILD:
Oh, Mommy, help.
Are you saying
my money's all gone?
-ALL: Mm-hmm.
-But...
I made all the right moves,
didn't I?
-Oh, yes, sir.
-Every move a right one.
I see it all now.
You're just a bunch
of yes men.
I was making the wrong moves,
and you were too gutless
to tell me.
Isn't that right?
-Oh, yes, sir.
-Dead on, sir.
Then I'll fix this myself.
Smithers, take out another
mortgage on the plant.
Well, the bank has already
foreclosed on the plant.
And your house, sir.
But... what will I do?
Well, the first thing
you'll have to do
is move out of the bank's house.
-I'll help you pack.
-(whimpers)
(faucet squeaks)
-Go on. Get out of here.
-(birds squawking)
And I'm sure a pro wrestler
such as yourself
will appreciate
all the closet space, Hit Man.
(sniffs)
Ooh...
this place has got
old-man stink.
-Ooh...
-Don't listen to him, sir.
You've got an enchanting musk.
And you wouldn't even be
the only wrestler
in the neighborhood.
The Shrieking Sheik lives
just three doors away.
(distant shrieking)
Hey-hey, I'll take it.
Uh, would it be all right
if I kept this portrait...
to remind me of better times?
Why would I want a picture of
a pitiful pencil-neck geek?
Yeah.
Why, indeed.
I'll make sure he forwards
your social security check, sir.
Mmm. Excellent.
Homer! You didn't tell me
Mr. Burns went broke and lost
the nuclear power plant.
Now, I can't remember
every little thing
that happens in my day.
You told me about that candy
bar you found three times.
You found a candy bar?
Oh, yes.
Gather 'round, my son,
and I shall tell you a tale...
I normally don't laugh
at other people's misfortunes,
but on behalf of
the recycling community...
Ha! It couldn't have happened
to anyone more deserving.
They're not going to close
the plant, are they?
No. The bank
put Lenny in charge.
Uh...
attention, everybody.
Uh... work harder. Bye.
-(groans)
-(knuckles crack)
Well, sir,
I have to get to work.
Lenny's a real bear
on tardiness.
Are there any chores I can do?
-(shattering)
-Uh, no, no.
Uh, you just stay here
and maintain your dignity.
(door closes)
(water dripping)
Ah. Here's a chance
to earn my keep.
I will go out
and get these items
from the food jobber.
Grocery store, please.
I am riding on the bus.
Hey, aren't you that
guy everybody hates?
Oh, my, no.
I'm Monty Burns.
I'm shopping.
Oh, my.
I wonder which is the cereal
for me?
Um, oh, excuse me.
Could you tell me where
I might find the "Burns O's"?
Sorry, pops,
they don't put nobodies
on cereal boxes.
Hmm...
well, I suppose
this one looks a bit like me.
Whoo. Thank you, shoppie.
I ventured
in to search for milk
when the door
snapped shut behind me.
Yeah, those dairy cases
are death traps.
Ketchup.
Catsup.
Huh. I'm in way over my head.
He's, uh, talking
to the ketchup now.
Burns is sure acting nutty.
Maybe going broke
and losing his plant
destroyed his brain.
Could you come
along with us, sir?
Are you here
to solve my ketchup problem?
Yes, that's right.
Where are you taking me?
What's happening?
Relax. You've gone off
your nut,
so we're stuffing you
into an old folks home.
Those, uh, store guys signed
the commitment papers.
But... I'm shopping.
(Homer glugging)
Here you go, honey.
That's about all
the recycling--
(hiccups)
...I can handle today.
Dad, if you just
drink one more,
I'll have a full bag.
Oh, but Daddy
doesn't feel so good.
Uh... there's got to be
more trash around
here somewhere.
Hey, why don't you try
the old folks home?
They practically live
in their own filth.
Thanks, Dad.
You're welcome, honey.
That's the activity room.
We're not allowed in there.
That's the library.
Not allowed in there either.
And don't even think about
going in the game room.
Egad, man, how are we
supposed to pass the time?
Best bet is to stake
yourself out a good spot
at the staring window.
(shudders)
♪ Don't tell my heart ♪
♪ My achy-breaky heart ♪
♪ I just don't think
it understands ♪
Come on, Mr. Burns,
join the fun!
That's the spirit.
So, this is how
the Monty Burns saga ends.
Oh, if I hadn't
surrounded myself
with those spineless yes men...
LISA: What do you mean
you don't have anything to recycle?
You must have some magazines
or newspapers.
That voice. That shrill,
disagreeable voice.
It's her!
Sorry, we're not allowed
to read newspapers.
They angry up the blood.
You! The troublemaking girl!
My name is Lisa, Mr. Burns.
Lisa Simpson.
It doesn't matter,
what your name is, you idiot.
What I want to know is, will you
help me get my money back?
Ha. I'd never help you.
You're the worst man in the world.
Yes. That's the kind of
moxie I'm looking for!
-You're hired!
-No, I'm not!
Sir, I'm so sorry
my grocer committed you.
We'll never shop
there again.
Not now, Smithers.
I've got an empire to rebuild.
And the person
who's going to help me is...
that girl.
("That Girl" theme playing)
-Please.
-No.
Please.
No.
-Please.
-No.
(doorbell ringing)
Sir, we've never met before,
but my name is Mr. Burns,
and I want your daughter
to help make me rich again.
You mean Maggie?
Ah, the baby who shot me.
No, I was referring
to your other daughter.
Lisa, you have a guest.
So, uh...
How's life in the gutter?
You again?
I've realized the error
of my ways, Lisa.
I need someone with
your integrity to help me.
Please?
Don't refuse this poor old man.
Uh...
well...
if I did agree to help you,
you could only earn money
by doing good,
socially responsible things.
-Nothing evil.
-"Nothing evil."
That's exactly the kind
of radical thinking I need.
It's a deal.
See that, boy?
Why aren't you making
any business deals?
(whining):
I'll do it this afternoon.
You mean there
are actually people
who will pay good
money for garbage?
Not good money, really.
Each can will get you a nickel.
Oh, don't pooh-pooh
a nickel, Lisa.
A nickel will buy you
a steak and kidney pie,
a cup of coffee,
a slice of cheesecake,
and a newsreel,
with enough change left over
to ride the trolley
from Battery Park
to the polo grounds.
There's a can.
You have to cut
these six-pack holders up.
Otherwise,
fish get trapped in them.
I see.
Ha-ha!
My first dollar.
Thanks to you, Lisa
and our hemp-smoking friend.
Shine on, you crazy diamond.
Sounds like somebody's living
in the past.
Contemporize, man.
Well, Lisa, as my advisor,
you're entitled to 10%.
Oh, I'm not doing this
for the money.
I'm just happy knowing
that future generations
will enjoy unspoiled
median strips
and pristine
highway embankments.
There's a can.
And from our "it's funny
when it happens to them" file,
remember millionaire
C. Montgomery Burns?
The man who blocked out
our sun, ran over a local boy,
and stole Christmas
from 1981 to 1985?
Well, guess who's flat broke
and picking up trash for a living?
Please be Flanders, please be Flanders
please be Flanders.
Excuse me, Mr. Burns.
Now that you're completely ruined,
-How do you feel?
-Excellent.
I'm on my way
back to the top.
I've turned these cans
into "can do."
Well, you smell terrible.
Good luck to you, sir.
Wow, he went
from stinking rich
to just plain stinking.
(laughing)
-Good one, Mom.
-Oh, you're so bad, honey.
You guys shouldn't
laugh at him.
Mr. Burns has changed.
He's different now.
-Yeah, he's broke.
-(laughing)
Two in a row.
(sighing)
Oh, you've really
turned my life around
these past few weeks, Lisa.
I've got my own business again,
my beloved employees.
Oh, consarn it...
Come on, let's pick up the pace,
you neglected old nincompoops.
Mr. Burns, if you want people
to do a good job,
you can't bully them.
You have to show them
they're appreciated.
Ooh, capital idea,
partner.
People, if we meet
this week's quota,
I'll take you
to the most duck-filled pond
you ever sat by.
Oh, hot diggity,
that's how they got me
to vote for Lyndon Larouche.
Wow, even I didn't know
he was so committed
to recycling.
See? I told you Mr. Burns
has changed. See?
Lisa, nobody likes a gloater.
-Right, Homey?
-Uh-huh.
See?
(applause)
Yes, thank you, everyone.
But 10% of your applause
should go to
my little partner,
Lisa Simpson.
For, if it were not for her
infectious moralizing,
we would not be here today
to witness the unveiling of--
the Li'l Lisa Recycling Plant.
(applause)
Oh, ain't that cute?
Makes Little Debbie
look like a pile of puke.
Would you like to be the first
to take a tour of the plant,
Li'l Lisa?
I'd love to, partner.
The whole plant
is environmentally sound.
It's powered by old newspapers.
The machinery is made entirely
of used cans, and the windows
are from the old liquor bottles
we collected.
Hey, I thought I told you
to stop licking my windows.
I know, you told me...
and when I woke up
this morning, I said,
"Barney, you're not going
to lick that man's..."
I'm so proud
of you, Mr. Burns.
You're getting
your fortune back,
and you're doing it
without endangering the planet
or cozying up
to the Aspen crowd.
Oh, hold your accolades
till the end of the tour.
You haven't seen
the best part.
I couldn't watch
your demonstration
of the fish caught
in the plastic rings
without getting an idea.
Look out over the water.
I figured if one six-pack holder
will catch one fish,
a million sewn together
will catch a million fish.
Watch.
What's going on?
Ah, I call it
the "Burns Omni-Net."
it sweeps the sea clean.
(gasps)
Oh, dear God.
BURNS:
I call our product
"Li'l Lisa's
Patented Animal Slurry."
it's a high-protein feed
for farm animals,
insulation
for low-income housing,
a powerful explosive,
and a top-notch
engine coolant.
And best of all,
it's made from 100 percent
recycled animals.
Oh, I think
I'm going to be sick.
Oh, a spoonful of slurry
will cure what ails you.
Ah! You haven't changed at all.
You're still evil,
and when you're trying
to be good,
you're even more evil.
I don't understand.
Pigs needs food,
engines need coolant,
dynamiters need dynamite.
I'm supplying it to them
at a tidy profit,
and not a single
sea creature was wasted.
You inspired it all,
Li'l Lisa.
Stop! Don't recycle!
It's murder!
You're helping Mr. Burns!
(robotic monotone)
But you told us to recycle.
You convinced us
it was good.
No, it's evil!
Please, stop recycling!
(robotic monotones) Stop.
You can't mix plastic with paper.
(gasps)
Oh! Oh!
(tires screech)
(sobbing)
Oh, I can't get the smell
of slurry out of my clothes.
I was a fool to help
that horrible old man.
I hope you learned
your lesson, Lisa.
Never help anyone.
(doorbell ringing)
Simpson, what are you
doing here?
-Why aren't you at work?
-I made a bad mistake,
and Lenny sent me home
to think about what I did.
But I don't remember what it was,
so I'm watching TV.
Well, Lenny's reign
of terror is over.
Mr. Burns bought
the plant back this morning.
-And--
-Enough chitchat. I need to see Lisa.
I don't want to talk to you,
Mr. Burns.
Oh, I think you will.
You see, I just sold
the Li'l Lisa Recycling Plant
for $120 million.
Congratulations.
Oh, don't congratulate me.
Congratulate
Bay State Fish Sticks.
As my advisor,
you're entitled
to 10% of the proceeds.
(gasping)
Lise, have I told you lately
that I love you?
Wow! I've never seen
so much money.
Oh, but I can't accept that,
knowing where it came from.
Can I, Mom?
(groaning)
Lisa, you do whatever
your conscience tells you.
(groans)
No...
Oh, you did the right thing,
sweetheart.
(chuckling)
Well, that's the first case
I've ever seen
of a man suffering four
simultaneous heart attacks.
I'm sorry, Dad.
It's all right.
I understand.
But we really could have used
that $12,000.
Um... Dad,
10% of $120 million
isn't 12,000, it's...
-(heart monitor races)
-WOMAN (on P.A.): Code blue! Code blue!
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.