(exclaiming)
(school bell ringing)
(Barney belches)
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
(grunts)
(groaning)
(laughs)
♪ The Simpsons 25x07 ♪
Yellow Subterfuge
Original Air Date on December 8, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
♪ Skinner! ♪
♪ Skinner
♪ He patrols the school halls
♪ Skinner! ♪
♪ When you spit,
he's got the balls ♪
♪ As you mosey through
the school ♪
♪ All the kids say
you're so cool ♪
♪ And you even made
♪ Bart Simpson spill his milk
♪ Skinner! ♪
♪ Skinner
♪ You're the master
♪ Of your fate...!
Skinner!
♪ Skinner
♪ You sure look good in chaps ♪
♪ Skinner...
Wake up. You're on!
(grunts)
Children, I have
some exciting news.
(kids murmuring)
I'm here to tell you about
a field trip so amazing,
we've put "sign here" stickers
on the permission slips.
As you recall, these stickers
came from last year's field trip
to the "sign here"
sticker factory.
But thanks to my
old navy buddy...
we both love to
shop at Old Navy...
the students of this school
will be taking a ride
on a nuclear-powered,
attack-class submarine,
the USS Tom Clancy!
(all gasp)
(chuckles) So you're
all excited, eh?
ALL:
Yay!
Well, that's too bad, because
many of you will not be going.
ALL:
Huh?!
There's limited room on the submarine,
so only the best-behaved students...
as determined by me...
will go on the trip.
- Whoo-hoo!
- Well, I get to go!
To increase the tension, everyone
starts with a clean slate.
But from this moment on...
I am the law.
I hold the red pen.
♪ Skinner! ♪
Pranks, inside use of outside
voice, off-color whistling,
and you're stricken
from the list.
And once crossed off,
you stay crossed off.
That's what pens do.
(gulps)
(bees buzzing)
Help! I'm trapped in space
with a man I don't like!
BART:
Aooga!
Submerge! Periscope!
Aooga! Aooga!
Die, Nazi octopus, die!
(makes explosion sound)
Sweetie, about the submarine...
what's your favorite food to eat
when you're disappointed?
I'm going shopping tomorrow.
Ice cream sandwiches. Why?
What your mother is trying to say is we
don't think you can be good that long.
Mom, is that true?
Well, that's sort of what
I was trying to say, but...
What your mother is
trying to say is...
No, you're wrong!
You're all wrong!
I didn't say anything.
- Were you thinking it?
- Yes.
Get real, ding-dong!
You've already done so much bad stuff,
Skinner's never gonna let you on that boat.
No, Skinner said I had a clean slate, so
right now, I'm as good as any other kid.
(Homer and Lisa laughing)
Good one, ding-dong.
Mom!
Don't listen to them.
They're the ding-dongs.
Wha...?!
Bart, sweetie, this is an opportunity for
you to turn things around yet again.
And I believe in you.
Yet again.
Thanks, Mom. I'll start by taking
my plate to the dishwasher.
Wherever that is.
(cupboards open, shut,
dish breaks)
Pfft. Marge, I love Bart as much
as you do, but actually not.
And that kid cannot go one week
without getting in trouble.
Now, if you'd be so kind as to start
my car for me, I'm going to Moe's.
(blowing air)
Ooh.
(engine starts)
Thank you.
(tires squeal)
Whoo-hoo!
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm!
What are you doing?
To avoid temptation,
I'm getting rid
of all the things that could get
me in trouble at school.
I buried all my whoopee
cushions in the backyard.
(flatulence sounds)
Hmm?
(groans)
- What the...?
- That's not where I buried them.
Come on!
Don't take my custom limo!
At least let me sniff my coke
out of the floor mats!
(grunts)
(sniffing)
(bicycle bell dings)
Oh, hi, little girl. What brings you
to see Uncle Krusty? (chuckles)
Krusty, are you broke?
Yeah. All it takes is some
bad luck at the ponies,
worse luck in
the Bitcoin market,
heavy investment in a
high-end bookmark company.
You could do what
Everybody Loves Raymond did.
Go off the air
while I'm still good?
That horse has left the stable,
gone to the glue factory
and has been used to
make art projects.
I mean, you could sell
foreign rights to your show.
Even SpongeBob did it.
Buon compleanno, Squiduardo!
No, no, no, Roberto!
E 'una mina della seconda
guerra mondiale,
che farà saltare in aria e...
Ah!
Calamari?!
No...! (sobbing)
No!
Uh... it's cute stuff, but
I'm still broke, girlie.
Not my Monet! I only
looked at it once!
What I'm saying is, you could produce
foreign versions of your TV show
with actors
from other countries.
Okay, I'll do it!
Not my Shetland dolphin!
Although I won't miss
the constant yapping.
Papa!
Not anymore, he ain't.
(booming thud)
Gum on the floor.
Off the list.
Unauthorized meat-a-pult.
Off the list!
Lips touching the fountain.
Off the list.
It's not my fault there's
no water pressure.
Excuses are like handkerchiefs;
everybody's got one.
- I don't have a handkerchief.
- Off the list!
Firm but fair, sir. Don't want any
troublemakers on our submarine.
Not bad, Simpson. Did
you wash your knees?
Front and back, sir.
You're like egg salad
at a picnic, Simpson.
Even when you look good,
we know you're going bad.
Principal Skinner?
I object to this arbitrary use of power
and request I be taken off the list.
- Off the list!
- Thank you.
Oh, man! Five days
without pranking?
I'm getting strange red marks.
But I'm gonna make it!
(engine backfiring)
Uh-oh.
(alarms buzzing)
Something's wrong with
my long yellow car.
(starter chugs)
Any of you kids got
a Triple A card?
What? No.
I'll be late.
Skinner will cross my name
off the list.
(grunts)
All fixed up!
(horn honks)
(tires screech, horn drones)
(school bell rings)
(laughs, hums triumphantly)
Off the list.
For what?
Muddy footprints on
the school floor.
- (gasps)
- I've broken a ten-year-old's spirit.
Time to celebrate with a
fruit-on-the-bottom yogurt.
Plain, plain, plain, plain...
Mmm! Fruit!
No, Mother, I did not
use any of your talc.
I don't know why the
bottle feels lighter.
Maybe you're just getting
stronger!
Some days I could just kill you.
(phone rings)
She heard me. Hello?
BART (nasally voice):
Hold for the president.
OBAMA (on spliced recording):
This is... Barack Obama!
Is this a prank?
- OBAMA: No.
- (gasps)
- That's offensive.
I want to... talk about...
submarines... and trips.
Simpson... has to go.
Simpson... has to go... on the...
submarine. On the... submarine.
Of course.
(tweeting)
This is... Barack Obama!
♪ So in love with you...
I like Ohio State...
You can put lipstick on a pig...
♪ So in love with you...
Welcome. Welcome,
foreign-market Krustys.
If you examine
your "Krusty Kit,"
you're gonna find
unremovable green hair dye,
a used red nose and a guidebook
on how to capture a monkey.
But now, the man they call
Mr. Monday Afternoon...
Krusty!
Hey-hey!
- Hai-hai! - Hu-hu! Heil-heil!
- Rodgrod med Flode!
Now, there are many words
for what I'm looking for...
rubles, renminbi, baht...
but they all mean money,
which rhymes with funny, which
you can be if you want.
I don't care.
Just do the Krusty show in your
country and send me ten percent.
Then send me another 60%.
Then five percent more,
and you're good.
Nice job, Simpson.
You even got my Suze Orman tape
unstuck from the cassette player.
She's the reason I was able
to purchase a new watch band.
Always bragging about
his watch band.
If only I could tell time.
Okay, I washed your car like you asked,
I did your paper route, and I'm sorry.
I really am.
This could be the
turning point of my life.
Where you, as a school
guy, made a difference.
What do you think? Can
I go on that sub?
Sorry, Simpson. Take her down.
KIDS:
Yay!
RALPH:
NELSON:
Yippee!
MILHOUSE:
Poor Bart.
Rasta hey-hey,
on the left-hand side.
(laughs) As my
mother used to say,
"Wanti wanti can't get it,
getti getti no want it."
Now here's Itchem
and Scratchem, mon.
(laughs)
(cheering)
♪ They smoke
♪ They toke
♪ They smoke and
toke and smoke ♪
♪ Ha!
♪ Smoke, smoke, smoke
♪ Toke, toke, toke
♪ The Itchem and Scratchem Blow. ♪
♪
Eye and eye say good-bye.
The blessings of
Jah upon you all.
Nice.
You're a hit all
over the world.
There's Chinese Krusty
with Sideshow Mao.
Even Irish Krusty.
Me ma, she had 12 children,
but only three lived.
Then they closed the mill.
(chuckles sadly)
Hey-hey.
(Irish flute plays
melancholy tune)
And it's all thanks
to you, kid.
To show my appreciation,
I'm gonna bring you with me next
time I entertain the troops.
Warning: they're not
American troops.
(slurps)
Hello, boy. At times like this,
there's not much you can say,
especially if you don't
know what happened.
(sobs)
Skinner didn't let me go.
Really? Hey, I bet that
submarine isn't so fun anyway.
(sniffs)
You think so?
- Fire that torpedo, Milhouse.
- Aye, aye.
- Where'd it go?
- It was just imaginary.
I know a kid should never turn to his
father for help, but I got screwed.
Is there anything you can do?
As I always say, don't
get mad; get dinner.
Then get even.
With Skinner.
You'll really
help me get revenge?
Yes.
What's Skinner's weakness?
- Everything.
- Good.
We can use that.
♪ Skinner! ♪
♪ Skinner ♪
♪ You are feeling pretty smug ♪
♪ Skinner! ♪
♪ Sipping cocoa from a mug ♪
♪ When you've reached
the mountaintop ♪
♪ Your next step is a drop. ♪
No, no, no, no, no!
♪ Skinner! ♪
(knocking)
I'll be right there. Just
saying good-bye to Mother.
(imitates Mother): Seymour,
I'm going out for a walk.
Uh-huh, see you in several
months at the soonest.
(knocking continues)
We have a problem, Seymour.
I did everything for you and
you stabbed me in the back.
Wait a minute, I knew you
were a neat freak, Skinner,
but you beat your
rug till it bleeds?
(gasps)
All right, I'll come clean.
I woke up and, surprisingly,
Mother wasn't there beside me.
She was dead.
Still, I can't be
sure I killed her.
Well, I'm sure our town's police
force will handle this competently.
Now, I could investigate further, but you
don't want to sit in a jail all weekend.
Chief, that was
awfully arbitrary.
Not compared to this.
(groans)
Let me handle this. Just go
upstairs and shut the door.
There are some things
only a boy should see.
(door closes)
(both laugh)
(cackles)
Now do you want to dispose
of this jelly-soaked pillow?
Just call me The Cleaner.
(slurps)
- Um, where's the body?
- She's in a better place.
(chain saw rumbling)
The deed is done.
Oh, I wish you'd asked
me before you...
Look, you kill them, I get rid of them.
That's always been our deal.
But I do have one question:
Do you want the head?
No, no, God, no.
Well, if you change your mind, it'll
be in my freezer. But only for a week.
Got a lot of ice
cream coming in.
Ugh, if this were a movie,
Mother wouldn't let me watch it.
Now, I'm afraid it's time
to start your new life.
You'll be hunted, on the run, searching
for the man who killed your mother,
which is you.
So avoid mirrors.
(Krusty humming)
Krusty, I have
some very bad news.
The foreign Krustys are
all hotter than you.
Irish Krusty's got a
show on Broadway.
Oi, where's your monkey?
There never was a monkey.
I was just tellin' stories
to forget me consumption.
(coughs)
(applause)
Well, you see there, they need
to hit the word "monkey" harder
if they want to get a laugh.
Don't you get what I'm
trying to tell you?
You are now the least popular
Krusty in the world.
What about Romanian Krusty?
What, you mean
President-for-Life Krusty?
(low groan)
I still get a piece, right?
Putz. You're the least successful
version of you there is.
A piece.
Now, let's see where this goes.
Irish Krusty, this is your baby.
The only thing working
round here is your libido.
Now I know why Ma walked into the sea with
her pockets full of rocks, on Christmas.
Why doesn't this
material work for me?
Seymour, the cops
are on their way.
(siren wails)
Here's a bus ticket to
Juarez and your fake I.D.
SKINNER: Oh, come on, I don't look
anything like this "Dick Fiddler."
No, you don't... yet.
I don't want to sound ungrateful, but
could I eat one of the potatoes?
Sorry, but Dick Fiddler
is allergic to potatoes.
I understand.
(both giggling)
Dad? Thanks for
sticking up for me.
(laughs)
Someday I may have
to fake my own death.
And maybe you can
help me with that.
- Sure, Dad.
- Someday soon.
As in, what are you
doing this Friday?
Aah! Dick Fiddler!
Gentlemen, I can't
run away from what I've done.
I accept that I
killed my mother.
My whole life,
she's belittled me.
Maybe deep down, I'm glad.
This has gone far enough.
I'm starting to think this "school
project" is more than meets the eye.
Mother?
You're alive?
Seymour, when this
fat guy and his kid
asked me to fake my
death to punish you,
I said, "Sure, that's
something to do."
You know, when you glare like
that, you look really beautiful.
(grumbles):
Mm-hmm.
But when I just heard you say
you were glad to see me dead...
I thought, "Now I'm gonna be
meaner to you than ever."
How is that possible?
I've stopped taking those
pills that keep me nice.
(gasps)
♪ Fiddler! ♪
♪ Fiddler, you look stupid ♪
♪ In that beard ♪
♪ Fiddler! ♪
♪ This dream is getting weird. ♪
KRUSTY: So I heard many of you are
dissatisfied with my 75% cut of your take.
Well, we did consider
letting you keep more.
(cheering)
But instead, we're giving
you something even better.
I will do a guest shot
on each of your shows.
Huh? Eh?
(jeering, shouting)
- Twist him like a balloon.
- Cut off his hey-heys.
Let's slice him up and cook him
in our traditional dishes.
Krusty, can't you
think of something?
I'm very bad in a crisis.
I also can't ad-lib, memorize
anything, improv or tell a joke.
Uh, you know, why did you
even become a clown?
Well, I was supposed to
be one of the sad ones.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
♪ They smoke, they toke
♪ They smoke and
toke and smoke ♪
♪ Ha!
♪ Smoke, smoke, smoke
♪ Toke, toke, toke
♪ The Itchem and
Scratchem Blow ♪
♪ Ha!
Shh!