CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(Ned whimpering)
(exclaiming)
(school bell ringing)
(Barney belches)
(whistle blows)
(yells)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
D'oh!
(tires screeching)
(grunts)
♪♪
D'oh!
So what are we doing here?
What, is it the thing where
the family runs in and sits down?
That's it?
We flew you in
and put you up for that?
I, I think we're done here.
Paul.
(playing The Simpsons
theme song)
(song ends)
Lisa Simpson, your actions
have brought devastation
upon this town,
and all because
of your selfish desire
to be accepted by others.
(gallery murmuring hostilely)
Leave her alone.
That's my only
talking daughter.
Lethal inject her
on the electric chair.
Bart, it's okay to say that
at home but not in court.
-Take it back.
-Withdrawn.
Now, Lisa, tell your side of
the story, and use your big voice.
Well, it all started
a couple of months ago.
Your Honor,
I'd like to request
that everyone in the court
picture in their minds
what the witness
is describing.
I'll allow it,
but no flights of fancy.
LISA:
Like all too many stories
about my family, it began with
somebody watching television.
Well, McBain,
you certainly picked
a bad time to come
out of retirement.
I hope you have
a COBRA plan.
(hisses)
You are suffering from
a reptile dysfunction.
HOMER:
(groaning) Down in front.
Damn it,
why do kids have heads?
Homie, stop watching the movie
in the other people's car.
Oh, but I'm invested
in the characters.
You'll miss the turnoff
to the fancy new mall.
I make my own turnoffs.
(tires screeching)
And that, kids,
is how you stick it
to the Towne Centre Real Estate
Investment Trust.
No, no, no.
Whoo-hoo!
(tires screech)
Someone thinks we're leaving.
I'll wave them off.
No, no, no, no, let's see how
long we can keep 'em waiting.
Everyone act like
we're buckling up to go home.
-(laughs)
-Homie.
Marge, if you were
married to Da Vinci,
you wouldn't tell him
not to Da Vinch.
(groans)
Damn it,
are you leaving or not?!
Leaving?
Why on earth
would you think that?
(roars)
(all laughing)
We totally wasted his time.
And ours.
(laughs)
This place is so great.
When the trolley hits you,
it doesn't even hurt.
(bell ringing, Homer giggling)
You try it, Maggie.
(bell ringing, Maggie giggling)
Ooh, condos.
Lenny, do you live here?
Yeah, I just moved in.
I have a Drippin' Dots
for breakfast every morning;
at lunch, I get a massage
in front of strangers;
and then I spend the afternoon
browsing cell phone skins.
Ever get tired
of those dancing waters?
(Strauss' "The Blue Danube" playing)
The day I moved in.
So what are we all going
to do together?
Actually, we just came to do
some shopping as a family.
Oh, no worries.
Mr. Mall can make
his own excitement.
Give me one doll
from every time period,
and set me up for a tea party
in a private room.
Lenny, you asked me to stop you
from coming back in here.
Let me help you.
You can help me by giving me
Ellis Island Emily.
Hi, dear, I'm your Uncle Lenny.
I'm going to buy you
an all-new wardrobe,
fix your teeth,
send you to the best schools,
and you're going to hate
and resent me for it
'cause you're an American now.
I was hanging on to these
gift cards as investments,
but then half the companies
went out of business.
Better sort those out.
(applause)
CROWD:
Aw...
(loud applause)
CROWD:
Aw...
(grunts nervously)
D'oh!
Do-over.
Hmm.
Whoo-hoo!
Unspool it into my mouth
till that card
is at zero.
Draw the curtain.
(Bart humming)
Sir, as a complexion
scientist,
I must advise you
against using any more.
This is the most powerful
hydrator we sell.
Less blathering, more slathering.
(grunts happily)
(laughs)
-(laughing)
-Hey!
Watch it!
Yo, Bart dude.
Can I get a ride
to the food court?
Hop on.
(laughing)
Ho-ho!
(grunts)
Hmm.
I kind of want to
create my own thing.
Do you sell
any just plain sets?
No.
We do all the imagining for you.
(sighs)
Well, I'll just buy one of these
and build something
different.
You do and you'd better
build yourself a lawyer.
LAWYER: Miss Simpson,
does the court really need to hear
everything that happened
in every store
your family visited?
Trust me, I've left a lot out
and cleaned up the swears.
Anyway,
I ran into some schoolmates
and thought they
might be friendly.
That's what kids do, right,
hang out at the mall together?
But when I went over...
Hi, guys,
what are you doing?
Duh, having feathers
woven into our hair.
LISA'S BRAIN: Those girls
are snotty and shallow.
Tell them off.
Can I join you?
(Lisa's brain groans)
Lisa, how can we put this?
You're the reason no one wears
Silly Bandz anymore.
Wha...?
They, they don't?
(gasps)
(grunts)
What the...?
(sighs sadly)
(moans)
Enough.
I don't trust this place.
Where are the cashiers?
Huh? Oh.
Huh?
Oh.
Yeah, the lightest,
most desirable computer
in the world for the next
three weeks: the Mapple Void.
I'll take it,
provided you charge me
for services
that Google offers for free.
-I already have.
-Sweet.
This computer is so great.
I'm watching the latest
Sofia Coppola movie
at 20x speed to make it seem
like a normal movie.
I think it just froze.
Oh, no, no,
that bird just moved.
Uh-oh, a draggy backpack.
I have no friends.
Aw, sweetie, hey,
why don't you make friends
with my new computer?
-Okay.
-Let me just finish downloading
the complete works
of Shakespeare.
(humming)
(sneaky chuckle)
Now who's the greatest writer
of all time?
I'd have more friends
if I knew what people liked,
but I won't know what people like
unless I'm their friend.
It's a conundrum.
Helpful hint:
If you want friends,
don't use words like "conundrum."
(phone rings)
-JIMBO: Co-what-drum?
-Jimbo heard me say it.
I'm dead.
Hmm.
It's easier to be friends
with lots of people online
than one person in person.
What if I started
an online meeting place
where all are equal
and I am the undisputed center?
(both grunting)
How's this for a conundrum?
It's not really a conundrum.
Sit at my feet,
and I will elaborate.
So, to summarize, Your Honor,
Lisa Simpson created
this "social network"
because she had no friends.
No, that is not true. I...
May I remind you
you're under oath?
All right already.
I had no friends.
With a attitude like that,
I wouldn't be her friend.
Life is too dang short.
So, since I had no friends,
I assembled a motley crew
of the friendless to help me
construct my social network.
Did we become friends?
No.
(overlapping chatter)
As the CEO of SpringFace,
I want you all to have fun
as you write source code
until you fall asleep
at your consoles.
-(all agreeing)
-Delightful.
Here's my favorite
computer game: Angry Nerds.
(squawks)
(all snorting like pigs)
Nelson, is there any way
I could be your friend?
The only way
I would be your friend
is if I could click a box
under your picture saying
"Accept friendship request from."
Nelson, you've just given us
the template for our site.
I don't care.
(grunts)
(clatter like bowling pins)
(groans)
If we don't move,
his odds of getting us both
are 374 to one.
Ooh-oo-ooh, ooh.
(grunts)
Bye.
(keyboards clatter)
Now, to skip ahead,
your diabolical plan
was an instant success.
I never said it was diabolical.
Withdrawn.
This social network
quickly unified
the disparate children
of Springfield Unified.
Oh, I just got invited
to make out with Shauna.
See?
That went out to 200 guys.
(groans)
And seven girls.
(brightly)
Oh...
Santa's Little Helper's friends
with Snowball Two?
Now I've seen everything.
Ha, all my friends
have birthdays this year.
(typing)
(click)
(chuckles)
I just un-friended Skinner
Doggone it.
I'm less popular
than the hornet's nest
in the gym.
You said you were
getting rid of that nest.
We trade the honey
for chalk and yardsticks.
Hornets make honey?
Better than wasp honey,
not as good as bee.
Is this how
you talk on dates?
I wish my dates
were this interesting.
Hit refresh.
-(click)
-Hit refresh.
(gasps)
I have a thousand friends.
And only eight
of them are Milhouse.
A thousand kids?
If you could get each of them
to send you a dollar,
you'd be a millionaire.
Well, it's not just
kids using SpringFace,
it's moms like me, Marge.
Wait a minute,
grown-ups are on this?
Yeah, look.
We've got to thank you, kiddo.
We've gotten so much more
action since we signed up
and used this picture
of ourselves.
(raspy chuckling)
-That's not you.
-You can see
our reflection
in the sunglasses.
(chuckling)
Wow, I've created something
incredibly popular.
And I've created something
that created something
incredibly popular.
And I created
an alcoholic hippo.
You never showed it to me.
A stupid alcoholic hippo.
-I still want to see it.
-There is no hippo.
Then why did you say it?
'Cause you're the hippo.
Are you just saying that
'cause you don't want me
to see the hippo?
I don't have a hippo!
And so, this so-called
"SpringFace"
spread from the world
of children to adults.
Man, this Web site
makes talking drunk
to my wife so much safer.
I am sitting here...
zero sheets to the wind...
(sneaky chuckle)
HOMER: ...counting the moments
to closing time
when I can stumble home to you.
Another round, Moe.
Uh-oh, did I type that?
Delete! Delete!
Hmm, typing "delete"
does not delete.
(puzzled groan)
It is gratifying to see
all of you bowing in prayer,
the light of God
shining on your faces.
Uh-oh, Bernice Hibbert keeps
"liking" Bumblebee Man's posts.
That's how it starts.
Tsk-tsk-tsk-tsk-tsk.
Why did I make this church
a Wi-Fi hotspot?
(groans)
If you can't beat 'em, join 'em.
Let's see, which Muppet am I?
Beaker?
Hm, I guess that's fair.
Friend, friend,
awaiting reply, friend...
Sherri? Terri?
Hopscotch?
Double Dutch?
Ringolivio?
Anyone?
Oh, I have a thousand friends,
and I feel more alone than ever.
Whee!
I am trying
to set a mood here.
(somberly)
Whee.
So, to sum up,
Lisa's social network
turned into the biggest
Internet failure since...
(chuckles)
Well, there've been so many.
"Ask Jeeves," anyone?
(raucous laughter)
(horse neighs)
And so SpringFace became
too big to control,
just like the 60-foot baby
in my self-published novel,
The 60 Ft. Baby.
Order it online now,
while you can still cheat
the government on sales tax.
(clears throat)
As I was saying,
SpringFace was used
in ways I never expected.
(typing)
(video game gunfire)
Thanks for SpringFacing me
your head cleaver, Bart.
(screaming)
(magazine reloading)
(gunfire)
(screaming)
Check this out: I'm hiding
a bomb in this pile of corpses,
so when Kearney
loots their ammo,
he gets a face full
of ass shrapnel.
(explosion)
Damn, I got ass-shrapped!
(groans)
(tires squealing)
What the...?!
That idiot cut me off.
(camera clicks)
I'm gonna run his plates,
find out who he is, then change
his SpringFace profile picture
to a shot of a monkey.
(chuckles)
Get that, Marge?
A monkey!
-Homer, watch the road.
-Right.
Status update: Homer...
is... watching... the...
(shrieks)
(tires screeching, thud)
(tires squealing, crashing)
(metal crunching)
(trolley bell dings)
Dislike! Dislike!
-(thud)
-(sirens wail)
(sirens wailing,
tires squealing)
(tires screeching,
cars crashing, glass shattering)
Somebody call 911!
I don't know how to use
the phone on my phone.
Hey, did you guys get
my picture of the fire?
Yeah, I did;
nice grab.
-I didn't get it yet.
-Yeah, funny how that works.
Lisa Simpson,
can you give us any reason
why the city should not force
you to shut down your site?
I know it's awful and insular
and caused 35 deaths,
but I had friends.
Four digits of friends!
I had a friend in common
with Malcolm Gladwell.
He friends everybody.
Fine.
I'll shut down the site.
♪ When you were here before ♪
♪ Couldn't look you in the eye ♪
Time to get a life.
♪ You're just like an angel ♪
♪ Your skin makes me cry ♪
(imitating guns firing)
We don't need your
crummy website.
We can make
anything into guns.
(imitating guns shooting)
JANEY:
Lisa. Lisa!
Want to play Marco Polo
with us?
We just realized you don't
have to play in a pool.
You really want me?
(sarcastically)
No. We want your Dad.
Marco.
Come on, Lisa.
-Polo!
-Fish out of water.
(laughter)
♪ When you were here before ♪
♪ Couldn't look you in the eye ♪
♪ You're just like an angel ♪
Hey, Winklevosses.
You're gonna lose yet again.
You should see
the expression on your faces.
Oh, wait, you can.
They're fat, they smoke,
they started
training a week ago.
Why can't we pull away?
Because we can't
stop concentrating
on that $65 million
Facebook settlement,
which somehow wasn't
enough for us.
Even though we were rich
in the first place.
(grunts)
So long, you big babies!
Hope you like
the taste of silver!
Help us, Larry Summers!
Come on, Wonder twin!
Pull!
NARRATOR: And now, for a Simpsons
"Show's Too Short" story.
(thunderclap, bat screeching)
Once there was
a young rascal named Bart.
This lad was trouble
from the very start.
When it came to mischief,
he had a black thumb.
It didn't hurt
that his daddy was dumb.
And when it came
to best friends,
it was Milhouse who picked him.
Sometimes the sidekick,
sometimes the victim.
Then one day
at school engulfed in ennui,
Bart dreamed of wrapping
the place in T.P.
So off to the discount store
they did skulk.
With the evil intent
of buying in bulk.
They went to the school
and put up a ladder.
Only to wait
for Milhouse's bladder.
All that evening
they unfurled with delight.
And soon the school
was covered in white.
The mischievous boys
had done their best.
When an eagle approached,
needing a nest.
They tried to escape
with struggles and squirms.
But all they got
was a diet of worms.
There they remained
to this very day.
So now you know,
pranks do not pay.
Simpson!
(The Simpsons theme
performed by The Tiger Lillies)
-(song ends)
-Shh!
Subtitled by A. Vandelay