♪ The Simpsons ♪
(chalk screeches)
(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(tires screeching)
(horn honks)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
Live from Hawaii's
beautiful Molokai Island--
we're not just for lepers
anymore--
it's...
I'm your host, Troy McClure.
You may remember me
from such films
as "The Erotic Adventures
of Hercules,"
and "Dial "M" For
Murderousness."
Tonight we'll see
Angela Lansbury
walk on hot coals.
Excitement, she wrote!
(painful groaning)
How could someone
abuse their body that way?
Moe, don't throw out
that brine.
But first, a man
whose inspiring battle
with Percodan addiction
is soon to be
a movie of the week:
Krusty the Clown!
I'll be played
by Jimmy Smits.
(laughing)
Now he faces
his toughest audience--
three Siberian tigers.
Simba, on the ball!
(screaming)
Eh, they'll be chewing
on him for a while.
Ay-yi-yi, la policia!
(laughing)
Hey, Homer, phone call.
Hi, Homie.
It's really starting to snow.
I think you should
come home.
But, Marge, Alan Thicke
is throwing knives
at Ricardo Montalban.
-Ow!
-Sorry, Ricardo.
BILL: Take it easy folks,
it's snow picnic out there.
MARTY: (chuckles)
I snow what you mean.
BILL: You're dead weight,
Marty.
(screams)
(groans)
D'oh!
Well, I got him
as good as he got me.
D'oh!
Now, before
I give you the check
one more question:
this place "Moe's"
you left
just before
the accident--
this is a business
of some kind?
Don't tell him
you were at a bar.
But what else is open
at night?
It's a pornography store.
I was buying pornography.
Heh, heh, heh.
I would have never
thought of that.
(grunts)
'Fraid old Zeke,
he rides up here with me.
Can't trust a pig
with watermelons, you know.
(loud slurping)
She'll go 300 hectares
on a single tank
of kerosene.
What country
is this car from?
It no longer exists
but take her
for a test drive
and you'll agree,
zagreb ebnom zlotdik diev.
Put it in "H."
HOMER:
Kids, if we buy a new car
we get our parking
validated for free.
Do you come
with the car?
Oh, you.
(giggles)
Do you come
with the car?
Oh, you.
(giggles)
(imitating gun fire
and grenade explosions)
Bart, that car belonged
to Bonnie and Clyde.
Show a little respect.
Mm-hmm!
Our tireless
safety engineers
crash-test
over 1,000 cars a year.
Hey, wait.
That's not a dummy.
This exhibit is closed.
(gasps)
The Batmobile!
Adam west!
Hey, kids-- Batman!
Dad, that's not
the real Batman.
Of course I'm Batman.
See, here's a picture
of me with Robin.
Who the hell's Robin?
I guess you're only familiar
with the new Batman movies.
Michelle Pfeiffer, hah.
The only true Catwoman
is Julie Newmar
Lee Meriwether,
or Eartha Kitt.
And I didn't need molded plastic
to improve my physique.
Pure West.
And how come Batman
doesn't dance anymore?
Remember the Batusi?
Nice meeting you.
Just keep moving.
Don't make eye contact.
(gasps)
Wow!
Just think what I could do
with that plow.
Homer, I've got to sneak
these valuable art works
out of the white house,
but I can't get out
of my driveway
because
of these protesters.
Mr. President,
those young people
are about to get
a dose of reality.
(people screaming)
(chuckling)
Oh, I can't
afford it.
Pally, this doesn't cost money,
it makes money.
You make the payments by
plowing driveways on the side.
Well, I really should
discuss this with my wife.
Your wife?
(imitates whip cracking)
Wait, you think
I'm gonna buy a $20,000 truck
just because you make
that noise?
(cracking whip)
I'll take it!
I can't believe
you bought that plow.
We can't afford it.
If you're gonna
get mad at me
every time
I do something stupid
then I guess I'll just have
to stop doing stupid things.
-Good.
-Fine.
I'll never, ever do
another stupid thing.
Good night.
Oh, Homie,
didn't that hurt?
No.
HOMER: Marge didn't reckon
with these flyers
and this flashy jacket.
Uh! Oh!
Oh! Ah!
Ohh!
BARNEY:
Forget it, Homer.
People don't read
these things.
Watch.
20% off at Lullabuys.
Just tell them
Big Baby sent you.
I know you can hear me.
I'm talking to you.
You sicken me.
I guess guys like us
just can't get a break.
Well, at least
I can't sink any lower.
Come back, diaper!
Come back!
Hi, Ma.
And now to read from
the Epistles of St. Paul...
Homer Simpson.
(clearing throat)
Dear Lord,
in your infinite wisdom
you know the number to call
when you need a plow
is Klondike 5-3226.
Homer,
this is really low.
Not as low
as my low, low prices.
(snaps fingers)
-(organ plays)
-HOMER: Ooh! Ung! That's Mr. Plow--
Oh, I'm gonna lose my plow.
Dad, have you considered
buying cheap commercial time
on channel 92?
Check it out.
Arrr!
90 "Sea Chanteys"
on three compact discs.
♪ Blow the man down,
mateys, blow the man down ♪
♪ Row, row, row your boat ♪
♪ In the navy, come on
and join your fellow man ♪
Act now and get a bonus CD--
"Hornpipe Fever."
Arrr!
Hmm...
Almost time
for our commercial.
Dad, who's watching TV
at 3:17 a.m.?
Alcoholics, the unemployable,
angry loners.
Look, there we are.
It may be on a lousy channel,
but the Simpsons are on TV.
Our driveway's snowed in.
ALL:
Old man winter!
(laughing)
That's right.
I fill your driveways
with ice and snow.
What are you
gonna do about it?
Nothing, that's what.
(grunting)
-Stop!
-ALL: Mr. Plow!
Get out,
you lousy... season.
All right,
I'm going.
My head hurts. I have to
lie down for a while.
Yay!
Hello. I'm Mr. Plow.
Are you tired of having
your hands cut off
by snow blowers,
and the inevitable
heart attacks
that come with
shoveling snow?
BOTH: Uh-huh.
Then call Klondike 5-3226.
Call now and receive
a free T-shirt.
He could still surprise you.
But I'm a real tightwad.
Can I afford
this remarkable system?
Absolutely.
My prices are so low
you'll think I've suffered
brain damage.
You are fully bonded
and licensed by the city,
aren't you, Mr. Plow?
Shut up, boy.
(growls)
So remember...
♪ Call Mr. Plow ♪
♪ That's my name ♪
♪ That name again
is Mr. Plow ♪
HOMER: Well, John Q. Driveway
has our number.
Now we play
the waiting game.
Aw, the waiting game sucks.
Let's play
Hungry, Hungry Hippos.
Oh, thank you, Mr. Plow.
Now my store can remain open.
Let's do it.
We're not
prisoners anymore.
We're free.
We can go
anywhere we want.
I'm cold and frightened.
Mm...
Hm...
-Mm--
-(grunts)
I'm afraid classes
may be cancelled today.
Look!
♪♪ (triumphant music)
We won't miss
a minute of school
thanks to your father.
Say your prayers, plow boy.
Mr. Plow,
for making it possible
for people to get
where they're going
without resorting to public
transportation or car pooling
I give you
the key to the city.
MOE: Here you go, Mr. Plow--
a beer on the house.
Wow, Moe.
You didn't even give a beer
to those freed Iranian hostages.
They shouldn't have been there
in the first place,
but Homer is a real hero.
I wish I was a hero.
Well,
wishing won't make it so.
You got to pull up your diaper,
get out there
and be the best damn Barney
you can be.
Here I come, world!
(screaming)
Whoa!
(clattering)
How do you think
he'll do, Moe?
I think
he'll do just fine.
I was wrong about
you buying that truck.
I'm very proud of you...
Mr. Plow.
(giggling)
This might sound silly
but just for a change,
would you mind...
Cutting my nails?
Brushing my teeth?
No, no.
Could you wear
the Mr. Plow jacket?
Just, uh, for fun.
Ohh...
♪ Call Mr. Plow ♪
♪ That's my name ♪
♪ That name again
is Mr. Plow ♪
(alarm ringing)
Ah, white gold.
(gasps)
What the--
Why, that--
Uh!
(horn honks)
Hiya, Homer.
Say hello to the Plow King.
Barney, you stole my idea.
Don't worry, Homer.
There's nothing wrong with
a little healthy competition.
-(gunshots)
-(air hissing)
(laughing loudly)
(moaning)
Well, well.
If it isn't Mr. Plow.
(grunting)
Hey, Plow King,
save some for me.
Wow! Linda Ronstadt!
(grunting)
Linda Ronstadt?
How did you get her?
We've been looking
for a project
to do together for awhile.
♪♪ (Country)
♪ When the snow
starts a-fallin' ♪
♪ There's a man
you should be callin' ♪
♪ That's KL-5-4796 ♪
♪ Let it ring ♪
♪ Mr. Plow is a loser ♪
♪ And I think
he is a boozer ♪
♪ So you better
make that call ♪
♪ To the Plow King ♪
(belching)
How could you, Barney?
After all
I've done for you.
"Lachrymose is to dyspeptic
as ebullient is to..."
Effervescent.
All right!
-Harvard, here I come.
-Psst!
Barney, my dad's asleep.
Want a beer?
I dunno.
The S.A.T.'s are tomorrow.
I've got two words for you:
Mellow out, man.
Hmm? Hmm?
All right, just one
if it'll get you off my back.
Hey! Where have-- (belches)
you been all my life?
(groaning)
Thank you,
Plow King leaving.
Flanders, I thought
I was your plow man.
Homer, why don't you
plow it again.
Forget it, pal.
I don't need your
phoney-baloney job.
I'll take your money
but I'm not gonna plow
your driveway.
Mr. West, you said there was
a job for me.
There was, when I called you,
45 minutes ago.
So long, Superman.
Your secret identity
is safe with me.
HOMER:
Ring, damn you. Ring.
-(phone rings)
-Mr. Plow.
That name again
is Mr. Plow.
MAN: Hello. I'm calling
from delinquent accounts
at Kumatsu Motors.
Oh, you want the Mr. Plow
who plows driveways.
This is Tony Plow, you know--
from
"Leave It To Beaver."
Yeah, they were gay.
Oh, what am I gonna do?
I think you should
do a new ad--
one that's
fresh and original.
I know. I'll do a rap.
♪ Boom, che-che, boom,
che-che, boom-che-boom ♪
♪ I'm Mr. Plow
and I'm here to say ♪
♪ I'm the plowingest guy
in the U.S.A. ♪
-(cat howls, Bart and Lisa complaining)
-♪ I got a big plow ♪
♪ And I'll move
a lot of things... ♪
-BART: Stop. Please.
-♪ ...if you have one ♪
Stop it right now.
Promise you'll never
do that again.
All right.
Mr. Simpson
I guarantee you
we'll come up with a commercial
that can save your business.
You know those radio ads
where two people with
annoying voices yammer
back and forth?
I invented those.
-(grunts)
-Ow!
Happens all the time.
♪♪ (opera)
Dad, was that your commercial?
I don't know.
The torch has been passed
to a new generation of, uh...
snow plow people.
Come on,
give me the key.
These look like teeth marks.
I thought there was
chocolate inside.
Well, why was it
wrapped in foil?
It was never
wrapped in foil.
Hardest hit by the blizzard
is Springfield's forbidding
Widow's Peak.
Our own Arnie Pie
is on the scene.
Everything's snowed in.
All I can see is white.
Arnie, please,
the ski conditions.
Mayday! Mayday!
I think I'm flying into a mountain.
Tell my wife I love--
(chuckles)
That's great, Arnie.
Hmm.
Hello, Plow King?
I was wondering if you could
plow my driveway
on top of forbidding
Widow's Peak.
I don't know.
I'd be up there all day.
I wouldn't be able to
plow any other driveways.
There's a $10,000 bill in it
for you.
Oh, yeah?
Which president's on it?
Uh, all of them.
They're having a party.
Jimmy Carter's passed out
on the couch.
Wow! I'll be right there.
Barney,
I'd like to put
a Spanish version
of your jingle
on my next album.
♪ Señor plow no es macho ♪
♪ Es solamente
un boracho... ♪
Yeah, you do that.
Well, I guess
you can plow my driveway
but I wonder what happened
to the Plow King.
Oh, I guess he just doesn't
respect his customers.
Oh, could you make sure
not to scrape my asphalt?
Kiss my asphalt.
(chuckles) So I said,
"Kiss my asphalt."
Hmm? Hmm?
Springfield's
beloved Plow King
is trapped.
-(gasping)
-Barney Gumble,
shown here
donating $50,000
to the Shelbyville
Dance Theater,
was caught in
a sudden avalanche
on Widow's Peak
earlier today.
It was captured on film
by a camera crew
making the upcoming
Fox special
"In Search of Bigfoot."
MAN:
Hold it, Bob.
We can see
your wristwatch.
Oh, damn it.
MAN: Hey, what's that?
(belches)
(rumbling)
(Barney screaming)
This is all my fault.
I've got to save him!
Homie, please,
don't go.
Hey, this old girl
is as surefooted
as a mountain goat.
(bleating)
(thudding and bleating)
(thudding)
(bleating and thudding)
(weak bleating)
D'oh!
Oh-ho!
(screams)
Easy...
easy.
(sighing with relief)
Ah, dying's not so bad.
I'll be reunited
with my loved ones--
my dad, and that plant
I never watered.
(rumbling)
Barney!
Homer,
you saved my life
and I'm not gonna
forget it.
From now on,
we'll be partners.
Barney, that's great.
When two best friends
work together
not even God himself
can stop them.
GOD: Oh, no?
The snow's melted!
We can go outside again!
I don't like the looks
of those teenagers.
Could this
record breaking heat wave
be the result of the dreaded
greenhouse effect?
Well, if 70 degree days
in the middle of winter
are the price of
car pollution,
you'll forgive me
if I keep my old Pontiac.
(laughing)
-(phone rings)
-Hello.
MAN: Hello.
This is the Repo Depot.
I'm just calling
to distract you
while we repossess
your plow.
Oh, yeah
how dumb do you think I--
Oh...
Oh, now, Homie,
you have your health,
you have
your best friend back,
and you do have
that certain
special something.
You mean...
Mm-hmm.
♪ Mr. Plow,
that's my name ♪
♪ That name again
is Mr. Plow ♪
Our forecast calls
for flurries of passion
followed by
extended periods
of gettin' it on.
(Marge giggling)
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.