(SINGING) The Simpsons
(TIRES SCREECHING)
D'oh!
(EXCLAIMING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
You know, we should visit
Shelbyville more often.
They have a store
that just sells shoes.
I feel like I'm in Paris!
Oh! The famous
Shelbyville Theater District!
Can we see a play?
A play?
All plays suck,
all the time,
and always will,
and everyone knows it.
Look, we'll compromise.
We'll go see a play
that Lisa doesn't
want to see.
Huh?
Let's see...
There's Equus
starring Sideshow Mel,
the 3 Dollar Bills
in Gay, Gay, Gay!
Ooh! Song of Shelbyville.
(SINGING) From the schoolhouse
where our grandparents learnt
To the bad zoo
where all the animals burnt
We're home to Christian,
Muslim and Jew
Although not
many of the last two
There's a girl for every guy
Birthplace of the button fly
In good old Shelbyville!
Say, fellow Shelbyvillian,
enjoying our famous
low humidity?
I'll say. The only thing
lower than our humidity
are the greens fees
on our public golf course.
Which one?
All three!
(ALL CHEERING)
Yes. Yes.
Why' look,
it's Springfield Billy!
(ALL HOOTING)
What are you doing
here in Shelbyville?
I came here for
the legalized gambling.
But Springfield Billy,
we don't have
legalized gambling here.
Sure you do.
I saw a bumper sticker
that said "Free Tibet."
(ALL LAUGHING)
(GASPS) They're saying
Springfielders are
stupid hicks.
It's like
looking in a mirror.
What's a mirror?
It's a big city word
for reversifying glass.
Oh!
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATION)
That show
was hilarious.
That Springfield
Billy cracks me up.
For your information,
Springfielders can be
intelligent and articulate.
I happen to know
because we're
from Springfield.
Springfielders?
Oh! (THUDS)
(ALL HOOTING)
MARGE:
This is the worst crisis
the Springfield Cultural
Activities Board
has ever faced.
Those Shelbyvillians
are maligning us all.
I've never heard such
mean-spirited hate-hoots.
We've got to upgrade
Springfield's image,
show them
we're more than
just a town
that's still
afraid of eclipses.
Hey, how 'bout we open
a fancy restaurant,
and when people check
their hats and coats,
we steal them?
Why do you come
to these meetings?
Free water.
There must be
something else.
Think, Marge, think.
Culture... Vulture...
Birds of prey...
Pray in a church...
The Father, Son
and Holy Ghost...
Ghosts are scary...
Scary rhymes with Gehry!
That's it!
Architect Frank Gehry!
He could build us
a concert hall like
he did in Los Angeles.
Well, we could use
a new HQ for
the Springfield Philharmonic.
They're playing
Gustav Mahler
in abject squalor.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
Little help?
(SCOFFS) Next time
we're keeping it.
Then ifs agreed.
We ask Frank Gehry
to build us a concert hall.
Bill, bill,
Bilbao, bill...
Snoopy stationery!
MARGE: Dear Mr. Gehry,
would you please build
a concert hall for our town?
We may not be
the biggest city,
or the prettiest,
but we were the first city
in America to abandon
the metric system.
(MARGE LAUGHING)
(GROANS)
(GASPS)
Frank Gehry,
you're a genius!
Behold the new
Springfield Concert Hall.
ALL: Ooh!
And none of this
would have happened
if not for a letter
I received from
one little girl.
I wrote that letter.
You wrote I was
"the bestest architect
in the world"?
Well, aren't you?
All in favor of building
a $30 million "screw you"
to Shelbyville?
ALL: Aye!
(CLAMORING)
Get off
my masterpiece,
you punks!
I'll call your mothers!
Yo, Frank Gehry!
Like curvilinear forms much?
(GRUNTS)
(HUMMING) Huh?
(SNORING)
Hey, cat, get your own pants!
(GRUNTS)
Kids! Why's the cat
so fat?
Dad, Snowball's not fat.
She's just got
winter fur.
(GRUNTS)
Okay, she's fat.
(CHOKES) Can't breathe...
Someone dangle
some string.
(MEOWING)
(MUSIC PLAYS)
I'm so excited.
It's like giving
birth to a child
of steel and iron.
(BEETHOVEN'S FIFTH
SYMPHONY PLAYING)
Where is everybody going?
The symphony,
she has just started!
So? We already
heard the
Dum, dum, dum, dum
The rest is just filler.
I thought this was gonna
be the soundtrack
to the movie Beethoven.
Was I sadly mistaken.
It sounds better
on my cell phone.
(BEETHOVEN'S FIFTH
SYMPHONY PLAYING)
Don't leave now!
The next piece
is an atonal medley
by Philip Glass.
(ALL SCREAM)
QUIMBY: You stupid hicks!
Why didn't you tell me
you hated classical music?
We didn't have time.
The concert hall
was designed and
built so quickly.
We're broke,
but I have a plan.
We change
the name of the town
to escape our creditors.
I need names, people!
Lima, Peru!
Gotham City!
Wiggumville!
Burger King!
MR. BURNS: Perhaps I can
be of assistance.
Smithers, tear me
a new drape hole.
If you hand over
the concert hall to me,
I'll assume the debt
and all of your
problems will disappear.
(SNAPS)
The building is yours.
Excellent!
MARGE: (GASPS)
He's turned it into a prison!
(GRUNTS)
(ALL HOOTING)
(CLAMORING)
Let's see now.
Barely finished
high school.
You've challenged me
to fight six times since
the interview began...
Make it seven!
Mr. Simpson, I like the way
you go nuts over nothing.
Now all you have to do
is pass this drug test.
Hmm.
(HUMMING)
Hmm?
(MUSIC PLAYING)
Cool, but I'll never
pass with this.
I better switch samples.
(CHUCKLES)
(HUMMING)
MR. BURNS: Simpson,
I haven't seen so many
drugs in a wang
since I ran
a Chinese opium den!
"Crack, smack, uppers,
downers, cutters, inners,
"horse tranquilizers,
cow paralyzers, blue bombers,
"Green goofers,
yellow submarines,
"LSD Mach 3,
and trace amounts
of...(GRUNTS)
"Human urine"?
Well, there must
have been a mistake.
My body is a temple.
Guards, remove this
coked-out man-balloon
from my sight!
But he misread my pee!
He misread my pee! (CRYING)
(STRETCHING)
We're not
overfeeding her.
We've been giving her
this low-fat cat food!
I'll bet
she's sneaking food
from someplace else.
Let's follow her!
I'd rather follow the dog.
I think he's up to something.
(ZOOMING)
One thing at a time, Bart.
(MEOWING)
There you are, Smokey!
Snowball ll has
another family!
This is worse than
when we thought
Mom was having an affair.
Turned out
she was just going
to the library to cry.
Now she just
bottles up her misery
like a normal mom.
Gentlemen, my prison
is losing money.
We need more convicts
in the dungeonarium.
Dungeonarium.
That's catchy.
Well, I could
beef up arrests
by enforcing
some of these
old forgotten laws.
(GRUNTS)
(THUDS)
Okeydokey.
Let's see here.
Here's one from 1834.
"It's unlawful for a man
to be hatless during
daylight hours."
Hmm. Hmm?
Smithers, if I didn't
arrest you that night
in the park,
I'm not going to
arrest you now.
Stupid prison guard
jobs thinks
it's so big. (CLATTERS)
Everyone gets
a prison job but me.
All my best
friends are guards.
They think they're so cruel
and corrupt, but they're not.
Okay, boys,
here's a loony law
from 1911.
"Five kicks
of the same can
"shall be
considered illegally
transporting litter."
(GRUNTS)
(CLUTTERS)
That's a hard five.
All units move in.
(SIREN WAILS)
We're putting you away,
Kicky Mantle.
And give that can
the whole CS! treatment.
You know,
lab tests,
weird lights,
Shots from
the can's point of view.
Yeah, that's it.
Lots of flash and no meaning.
(LAUGHS) Okay,
new meat, you're clean.
(GURGLING)
I'm not supposed
to be new meat.
I'm supposed to have your job.
I'm sick of you
positing an alternate reality!
(GURGLING)
(CLANKING)
No Frank Gehry
designed prison
can hold me! Ha-ha!
(GRUNTS)
Oh, my God,
that man might be hurt!
Guards, there's a prisoner
in there!
Nice nab, Simpson.
You did the right thing
squealing on that guy.
Squealing? No.
I just wanted to help him.
Whatever. How'd you
like to be
a full-time rat?
Really?
You mean eat cheese,
gnaw through electrical cords,
things like that?
(MUNCHING LOUDLY)
Not exactly.
Mr. Burns,
I've thought about it,
and I don't want
to be a snitch.
It's not an honorable life.
Now, now,
there are perks.
A private cell, extra dessert,
and this adorable little hat.
Well, I am
a sucker for
a little hat.
So, we have
an agreement?
Well... I don't know.
But it's the only way
you'll survive in here.
Well, I would like
to survive long enough
to see the effects
of global warming.
(WHISPERS) I've got
an inside tip that
it's all a bunch of crap.
Okay, you've found
your snitch.
Excellent! Now,
what have you
got for me?
(WHISPERS) Homer Simpson
has become a snitch.
(GRUNTS) Tell me
something I don't know.
Sometimes I go
to the movies alone.
Say, is that
a gang tattoo?
I thought
those weren't allowed.
Yeah, it's a gang
I was in as a kid.
GMS.
"Galactic Mystery Solvers“.
(SIGHS) The only mystery
we couldn't solve
was how not to grow up.
Hmm?
That's right,
an unauthorized tattoo.
I came here right away.
Very good.
Here you go!
42-inch plasma TV
as a thank you from your...
Your, mother.
Oh, that "my mother."
Tell him thanks.
Okay, Tattoo Man.
It's a month in
the hole for you.
Solitary confinement?
But without my
weekly canasta, I'll die.
(STUTTERS)
It's my raison d'être.
(SNIFFS) Ew!
Smokey, you've got
that awful smell
on you again.
That's the smell
of her real family,
the Simpsons!
And for your information,
our walls have a bunch
of dead raccoons
in them,
but we are saving up
the money to find them.
Well, whatever.
Smokey's our cat.
(MEOWS)
Smokey, stay!
Now back.
Heel.
Snowball does tricks?
Sure. Come on, Smokey,
do your Smokey shuffle.
(BOTH CLAPPING)
Well, I don't care
what you say.
She still loves us more.
Don't you, Snowball?
(HISSING)
(MEOWING)
You toyed with my heart
like it was a toy heart.
Gentlemen, we must determine
which of our fellow inmates
has become
me rodentus incarcerarium.
You heard the boss.
Find the rat.
I found the rat,
and he's right here.
I ain't the rat,
I'm the pigeon.
I thought
you was the mole.
No, you're thinking
of that guy who
was the canary.
But we can
all agree,
we work in
a business with
a very rich lexicon.
Rich lexicon,
very rich.
(ALL AGREE)
Ooh! A Tiffany's box!
And the thing inside
is from Tiffany's!
Homie, you've never
done this before.
How'd you afford it?
Well, if you really must know,
(WHISPERS) I'm
a prison snitch.
(GASPS) Haven't you seen
what happens to people
who rat in prison movies?
Sure, they're on top
of the world.
Then there's a big
riot scene.
Then... I don't know.
I usually doze off.
The prison snitch is killed!
And that could be you.
Because you're
the prison snitch!
(ALL GASP)
(ALL GROWL)
What are you
dupes looking at?
You've never seen
bling-bling before?
What is it they have
that keeps Snowball
coming back to their house?
Only one way to find out.
(BELL RINGS)
My baby turtle
crawled into your
basement window.
0h, you poor boy.
What's your turtle's name?
Uh...
Apron Boobs-face?
Really? Well,
let's go find it.
And what's your name?
Uh...
Shoes... Butt-back?
HOMER: Uh-huh.
Hmm.
Psst. (WHISPERS)
There's a jailbreak tonight
How come nobody
told me before?
I sent you an e-vite.
You never responded.
Nice netiquette, jerk.
(WHISPERS) There's gonna be
a breakout tonight.
Very good. Now,
I'd like a little
more information.
Are biographies
arranged by author
or subject?
What is Bart
still doing in there?
You forgot to take
some brownies.
Thanks, Mother Dexter!
I'll be back tomorrow.
Bart, why were you
in there so long?
Lis, that place is great!
They have a jukebox
in the basement.
And look at the trick
they taught me!
(HUMMING)
Are you watching?
(MOANS)
When they come
busting out,
we'll be ready.
Every single guard
is outside waiting
for them.
Something
don't feel right.
Usually when
there's a jailbreak,
there's electricity
in the air,
like the calm
before a summer storm.
Or right before
a heavyweight fight.
Mine's more poetic.
(GROANS)
Now, where the hell are they?
PRISONERS: Kill the rat!
Kill the rat!
What happened to the guards?
PRISONERS: Kill the rat!
Okay, okay. Don't panic.
Maybe they'll tire
themselves outwith
their chant.
(GASPS)
I call the balls of his feet!
(ALL SHOUTING ANGRILY)
Marge, they're gonna kill me!
Oh.
I only did what
I had to do to survive
in a style befitting
a French monarch. (SCREAMS)
(ALL SHOUTING ANGRILY)
Flaw. Segway, fly!
(SCREAMS)
We've all heard
of a laugh riot,
but a prison riot'?
Kent Brockman high above
Montgomery Burns
State Penitentiary,
where our expensive
Thermocam 3000
is finally being
used for something.
This red glow is the heat
from a pack of inmates
who are desperately
looking for prison snitch,
Homer Simpson,
This massive blob over here,
who is attempting to hide
in the kitchen area.
Good luck, blobby.
(PRISONERS CHANTING)
Kill the rat! Then have snack!
Kill the rat!
Homer.
Homer, where are you?
(GRUNTS) Marge!
How did you get in here?
As president of
the cultural board,
I was given a key
to the concert hall.
(SLAMS DOOR)
There's the filthy rat
we're gonna kill.
And his wife,
who sometimes
drives my son home
from school.
Oh, you must be
Michael's dad!
Marge, come on! (GRUNTS)
We'll be safe
in the gas chamber.
(GRUNTS)
(SCREECHING)
I want you to look
into the faces of
those poor men.
Each one is a life
you made worse
with your ratting.
(ALL STRAINING)
Oh. Marge, I'm sorry
I got you into this mess.
Can I snitch
on my heart and
say I love you?
Oh, Homie...
(ALL STRAINING)
(EXPLOSION)
(GAS HISSING)
(PRISONERS COUGHING)
Tear gas, my one weakness.
(ALL GROANING)
You can come in, Governor.
Well, I'll make
these rioters
regret their folly.
This prison will make
Abu Ghraib look like
the Four Seasons.
Smithers, we'll need
electrical wire, a hood
and someone
who can really
point at genitalia.
Done and done, sir.
(GRUNTS)
Hold on a minute.
Governor, I've been
using my powers of
snitching for evil,
But now I want
to tattle for good.
This prison
is a hellhole.
They feed us horse meat,
with traces of jockey meat!
I'll have you know
I buy the finest cuts of beef.
(MILITARY TRUMPET PLAYING)
The guards
are sadistic
and cruel.
I can't help
the way I am.
When I was a boy,
I saw my father
murdered before my eyes.
By me.
Governor, I think
the only fair solution
is to pardon
all these thugs
and murderers.
Well, since there's no room
in the prisons you came from,
I'm releasing you all
to a garbage barge,
where you will
bare-knuckle box
till one of you
emerges as king
of your floating hell.
(ALL CHEER)
You know
what I missed
in the joint?
Just lying here
watching you
sleeping sweetly.
Sleeping sweetly.
Sleeping sweetly...
I won't tell
if you don't tell.
Listen to me!
This whole building
is unsafe.
They cut corners
everywhere.
People! It's a deathtrap.
No, Dad,
you fell asleep
in front of the TV
watching
The Towering Inferno.
How do you know
the title of my
prophetic vision?