(SlNGlNG) The Simpsons
(TlRES SCREECHlNG)
D'oh !
(SCREAMlNG)
(TlRES SCREECHlNG)
(GlGGLlNG)
Wait till he puts
his unsuspecting butt
on that toilet seat!
(GlGGLlNG)
(TOlLET FLUSHlNG)
Huh? Where's the Ee-yow?
All yours, Homer.
You didn't sit on the toilet.
l didn't have to.
l'm a dude.
(GRUNTS)
Butt on bowl, little man !
(BOTH STRUGGLlNG)
Hey, my pants aren't down !
lt doesn't matter!
Ee-yow!
(LAUGHlNG)
Why you little. . .
(CHOKlNG)
Joke's on me, is it?
Ah !
(WHlRRlNG)
(GAGGlNG)
(HOMER GROANlNG)
(CHOKlNG)
MARGE:
What's all that racket?
lt's old lady Simpson !
Run !
What's going on?
Uh, l'll tell you
what's going on.
l'm taking you all
out for pancakes.
ALL: Yay!
Yeah !
BART: This place
looks familiar.
lt used to be
The Leaning Tower of Pizza.
They just painted
the tower brown.
Either way,
everyone who works in
the kitchen speaks Spanish.
(lNDlSTlNCT TALKlNG)
Hey, Apu.
What's with the line?
lt's application day
at Miss Wickerbottom's
Pre-Nursery School.
Pre-nursery school?
The fast track
begins at birth.
That's it!
Claw and bite for position !
We have only enough
tuition money for two.
For the rest of you,
better luck next life.
That's a lot of pressure
to put on a baby.
All they should
be worried about is
the Raspberry Monster!
(MARGE BLOWlNG RASPBERRlES)
(MAGGlE GlGGLlNG)
You know,
Marge makes a good point.
Competitive schools
aren't for every baby.
(LAUGHlNG)
Are you saying
my daughter can't cut it
just because
l owe you $1 4,000?
l'll show you !
Come on, Maggie.
You're getting
into that school.
l will hire
a collection agency.
Which one? Tri-City,
Omni-Pay, lnsta-Threat?
l've beaten 'em all !
The pig says "oink."
The chicken. . .
HENRY:
Look, stop right there.
l could go to any
Chuck E. Cheese in America
and hear what animals say.
Do you know what l say?
l say, "Next."
You're a poopie!
You nurse with that mouth?
And what's your name?
Maggie.
l'm sorry, but why
are you answering for her?
Maggie doesn't talk yet.
Not a word?
Oh, no, no.
She says lots of words.
Like when
she wants something,
she says. . . (GRUNTlNG)
Maggie, we're not
a mime school,
so we can't take
a non-talker.
But here's some good news.
The Gap will always
need sweater folders.
l'm sorry we wasted
your time, your lordship.
(MARGE GRUMBLlNG)
My baby has no future.
Oh, Maggie will do just fine.
She'll have plenty of money,
because she'll
marry a grocer. . .
Grocers don't
make that much.
. . .who steals from the till.
Would ya let me finish? Jeez!
Maggie, you're as smart
as any one of those kids.
Come on.
Did we ever turn off
that shower nozzle?
(ALL GRUNTlNG)
l'm taking you
all out for tacos!
BOTH: Yay!
Okay, for Malibu Stacy's
beach party,
we've got pita,
hummus, tempeh, tofu.
What other fun foods
do we need?
lce? Did you do that?
(GlGGLlNG)
Okay.
What's a good side dish?
Rice. Why not caviar?
Oh, my God !
You're not just smart,
you're brilliant!
Mom !
Well, look who's back.
Pippi Non-talking.
Just because
Maggie can't talk,
doesn't mean she's dumb.
Einstein didn't
speak till he was three.
And even then,
he could only speak German.
Fine. l'll give her
an lQ test if only to
extinguish all hope.
All right, my quiet American,
how many eyes do you have?
Go on, Maggie.
You can do it.
Well, congratulations.
You're now as intelligent
as a pig.
Let's see if you can
move up to dolphin.
How many people
in your family?
(GASPS)
Woo-hoo!
l got that one right, too.
(LAUGHlNG ENTHUSlASTlCALLY)
Okay, last question.
Arrange these
four arrows
to make five arrows.
l remind you,
you only have 1 5. . . Oh.
ALL: Ooh !
Yeah !
Philippa, l think
you should come in here.
Your baby is brilliant.
Why, she could already
teach at Florida State.
Oh, my God !
Yay!
Go, Maggie!
Go, Seminoles!
This better
be important, Henry.
l was choking on something.
Meet Maggie Simpson, lQ 1 67.
One sixty-seven !
That's amazing
for a Christian.
But my lQ is only 1 59.
Maggie's more
intelligent than me?
That's right, because 1 67
is a bigger number than 1 59.
Do you see how that works?
Yes, thank you.
So our kids keep
getting smarter.
lf we have another one,
it could build
a time machine,
which we could use
to go back in time
and not have any kids!
All our children are smart.
Some are just
smarter than the others.
Welcome to the others.
(SCREAMS)
MARGE: Maggie, look at
all the stuff your
new school sent over.
Look at these
courses you'll be taking.
Advanced Peekaboo.
(MAGGlE GlGGLlNG)
Got Your Nose and Other Lies.
(READlNG)
(LAUGHlNG)
l'm slapping this
sucker right over
"Support Our Troops."
Look, Lisa.
There's something
in here for you !
Really?
(GROANS)
And Maggie
gets a shirt, too.
(SCOFFS)
Sweetie, you seem so blue.
Did the last of
something die?
No, Mom. lt's just that
l used to be the smart one.
Now, l don't know who l am.
Well, l know who you are.
And here's something
to help you never forget.
l already have one of those.
Well then,
find a new identity.
Hmm.
Your mother's right, honey.
Katie Couric didn't just
become the world's
most famous dwarf.
She escaped from the circus
and went for it!
All right.
lf l'm second-rate
as the smart kid,
l'll find
a new raison d'etre.
That still sounds
like the smart kid.
Right, right.
Time to show them
the new me.
No one's happier
and more well-adjusted
than a stand-up comedian.
How about these entrees?
Stuffed cabbage?
Can you believe
they found a way to
make cabbage worse?
(LAUGHlNG)
All right.
So what else is going on?
Let's see.
Hey, why do they
call them "field trips"?
We never go to a field.
Oh, untrue. Last Thursday,
we visited a battlefield.
Uh, well, l. . .
l'm bem-barrassed for you.
The following
"ha-ha" is not from
amusement but
an expression of contempt.
Ha-ha!
(GROANlNG)
Okay, okay,
don't get discouraged.
Every me they reject
gets me closer to
the me they'll like.
(HEAVY METAL MUSlC PLAYlNG)
What are you now, Lisa?
An Oakland Raiders fan?
lt's called goth,
eternally clueless one.
My new name is
Ravencrow Never Smiles.
Cool. We can be
goth together.
We'll go to
the cemetery and summon
the dark lord
by kissing and junk.
(LAUGHS)
Okay. But first,
you must apprentice
by kissing
the goddess lronica,
uh, who lives in this rock.
Do it for an hour,
hour and a half.
Yes, my mistress.
(KlSSlNG)
Who's that girI
running around with you
TeII me who's that girI
Oh, none of these
feel right. Wait, wait.
Did l try soccer player?
Tried and failed.
(GROANlNG)
l'm a mess. l can't believe
l'm jealous of a baby.
Hey, l'm jealous of her, too.
When you're a baby,
you spend all day just
rolling around on the floor.
Boy, l miss that. Ow!
Fine. Roll around
on the floor, baby.
(GRUMBLlNG)
Floor baby! Floor baby!
You're making fun
of him for something
you made him do!
Yeah? Well, you're gay.
People who accuse others
of being gay
are often
covering up their own
latent homosexuality.
Um, uh. . . (GRUNTS)
Bullies rule!
The school sent this
dealie over for Maggie.
His name is Phonic Frog.
PHONlC FROG:
Aw. Buh. Kkk.
Huh-Oh-Muh-Eh-Er.
(LAUGHlNG) That's me.
This is
Huh-Oh-Muh-Eh-Er's doctor.
He's too sick to work today.
(CHUCKLlNG)
l'll be right back.
(WHlNlNG)
Fine. l'll help you
with your stupid flashcards.
(CHUCKLlNG)
Aren't you smart?
Let's try another one.
A little harder this time.
Hmm?
(SNORlNG)
(HESlTANTLY)
No, that's wrong.
That's right!
This spells "dog."
MARGE: Lisa!
(SCREAMS)
You are purposely teaching
her the wrong word !
Lisa, l'm surprised.
Your sister just wants to
learn and be like you !
Well, maybe she needs
a better role model.
PHONlC FROG:
I agree with your mother.
You are a disappointment
to Huh-Oh-Muh-Eh-Er.
(SOBBlNG)
(MUTTERlNG)
l used to be the smart one.
(BELL RlNGlNG)
PHONlC FROG:
Where is my dinner?
Maggie, you're such
a quick learner.
Why don't you
learn how to fly?
But I Iove you.
(LAUGHlNG EVlLLY)
(GASPlNG)
(SNORlNG)
Z-Z-Z-Z-Z-Z-Z...
Goodbye, Maggie.
l'm smart enough
to know you're
better off without me.
(SlGHlNG)
Two cents.
l'm sure a lot of
great people have
started with less.
Nope. Never under a dollar.
(SlGHS)
MARGE: Lisa's gone!
You have to find her!
Why can't you just
accept the fact that
Lisa is old enough to
take care of herself?
Back off and let
her live her life.
But she's only eight.
Oh, l thought you said 80.
Well, we'll get right on it.
Now, this may not
be the best time,
but l'm supposed to
give you this survey
rating the effectiveness
of the Springfield Police
Department.
"Somewhat satisfied." l see.
Well, maybe l'll just
somewhat find
your daughter, huh?
Fine. "Extremely satisfied."
Looking good, boys.
Now, let's go get
some smoothies.
Oh, l'm tired. l'm hungry.
Red plastic sandals are not
great running away shoes.
(GASPlNG)
Air conditioning,
water fountains, dioramas!
And l'll never run
into my family here!
lt's the perfect place
to start a new life!
(ATTENDANT MUTTERlNG)
(GlGGLlNG)
No food allowed.
You can't hide it
in your clothes.
Would you please step
out of the line, sir?
Go ahead and search.
You will never find it all.
l'm baking muffins
as l speak.
MAN: Some trees are big.
Some trees are small.
But all trees have bark.
Except for popIar,
ash and mapIe.
(PEOPLE EXCLAlMlNG)
(GlGGLlNG)
(LlSA PLAYlNG SAXOPHONE)
Lousy Maggie.
Thinks she's so great.
Thinks she knows. . .
Oh.
l miss them all so much.
(SOBBlNG)
l hope this typeface
catches people's eye.
lt sure didn't move
our old fondue set.
Why do you always take
the children and
not the fondue sets?
Why, Santa? Why?
Good news, Simpsons.
We found your
daughter's belongings.
Where'd you find these?
Giant tongue.
Oh ! l knew it!
We also discovered something
very unusual at that museum.
Oh, my God ! What?
Well, if you drop a feather
and a bowling ball
in a vacuum,
they'll fall at
the same rate. (CHUCKLES)
You think you've
seen it all in this job,
and then something
like that comes along.
Come on. Come on.
CLANCY:
That's where we found
your daughter's things.
LlSA: Huh?
You look around there
while Eddie, Lou and l go
ask a few questions.
Like how does
a helicopter fly?
And what causes thunder?
l say it's angels bowling.
Lisa?
HOMER: Lisa?
MARGE: Lisa?
BOTH: Lisa?
(ClRCUS MUSlC PLAYlNG)
(LAUGHlNG)
(SCREAMlNG)
Oh, no!
The giant is waking up!
(ALL SCREAMlNG)
Oh, God.
We're in a belly.
Everyone, take off
your shoes.
(YELLlNG) How do we get out?
Your baby has
to press the red
"evacuate" button.
Yo, Chief,
we got a problem here.
l see a vase, but Eddie
sees two people in profile.
Now, this may shock you,
but you're both right.
MARGE: Maggie!
HOMER: Come on, Maggie!
Come on !
BART: The red button !
ALL: Hit the red button !
Hit the red button !
HOMER: Hit the red button !
(ALL EXCLAlMlNG)
HOMER: Ew!
Maggie, press the red button !
l know, we'll use
reverse psychology.
Maggie, don't press
the red button.
Damn it!
(ALL SHOUTlNG)
Marge, l've always
loved you.
Bart, you were a worthy foe.
(CRYlNG)
(PANTlNG) Mom ! Dad !
l'm so sorry
l got you into this!
Lisa, you're all right!
Oh, good. She's here
in time to see us die.
Maggie, l'm sorry l was
jealous of your special gift.
From now on,
l'm gonna
nurture and cherish. . .
Just tell her which
friggin' button to push !
Maggie, push the red button.
You can do it! Red !
(COOS)
(ALL EXCLAlMlNG)
Wooo!
Now, Marge, you can't say
l never take you anywhere.
(GRUMBLlNG)
(GROANlNG)
(ALL GRUNTlNG)
Well, l think we all
learned a lesson today.
Don't try to be something
you're not, namely food.
Chief, now l can't see
either one.
Well, we're all pretty tired.
Let's try a different one.
Which figure is bigger?
The answer will
knock your socks off!
l'm sorry l ran off.
Being second to Maggie's
not so bad.
But why didn't Maggie
press the right button
until l told her to?
PHlLlPPA: l believe
l can answer that.
How'd you get in here?
Your butler let us in.
Play along.
l'll explain later.
l'm afraid your daughter's
no longer welcome
at our school.
She's as common
as an angry woman
in an lbsen play.
(LAUGHS) Zing !
Let's just watch the tape,
monkey man.
Whenever Maggie
is asked a question,
she looks over at Lisa.
How many eyes do you have?
Go on, Maggie.
You can do it.
(TAPE REWlNDlNG)
PHlLlPPA:
Now, rotate and magnify.
(GASPlNG) l don't
remember doing that!
l would never cheat!
Perhaps. But subconsciously,
you wanted her
to succeed. Watch.
PHlLlPPA:
Here, you're telling her
the answer is no.
Here, the solution
is a square.
Here, you're telling her
the answer is
California Condor.
So Maggie's not a genius?
She could be at
sweeping up hair. (CHUCKLES)
That's my baby, jerk!
Ow!
You call that a punch?
l felt it,
but it was like,
"So what?"
Oh ! Again with the nose.
l have a chin, you know?
(GRUNTS)
Don't worry, sir.
The maid and l will
take him out to the curb.
Come on. Come on.
You promised me
no one would get hurt!
l don't care
what they say, Maggie.
To me, you're brilliant.
(PLAYlNG SAXOPHONE)
Not for babies.
HENRY: Do we reaIIy need
three of these peopIe?
Too ethnic, change it.
More like "Cart-wrong."
Worst voicing ever.
FinaIIy, a reaI ceIebrity.
Oh, good. More producers.
Just what they need.
Him, l like.
Yes, but what's
he done IateIy?
Very originaI.
Simon Cowell as Simon Cowell.
Well done.
(SlGHS) I reaIIy
don't care anymore.
All useless.
The credits reaIIy
have to go this Iong?
Oh, shush yourself.
English - US - PSDH