Gather round, me buckos
A story I will tell
Of a woman named Lily
Who cast quite a spell
It started back in Britain
It started in a pub...
- She's mine.
- It's my birthday.
She's mine.
I can't be the cause of this.
- I'm leaving.
- Your fault!
We were fighting over Lily,
using knife, fork and club
That's all I got.
The rest will be spoken word.
Lily gets why we're here.
Life is supposed to be fun.
I loved her. We all loved her.
The way gophers love
that sweet, sweet poison.
Every man wanted her for
the greatest reason there is.
Lily could make life fun.
Now everyone,
hold hands with a stranger.
Oh, pleased to meet you.
How delightful.
Lily!
Good one, Lily.
Thanks, Lily!
Pub's back open!
But like The Beatles
and balmy weather,
she was too hot
for England to handle.
I find you far too alluring
for the average Englishman
and banish you to Britain's
penal colony, America.
This is your captain speaking.
- Will you date me?
- Sorry. No.
Okay. I'm experiencing
some emotional turbulence.
My life is pathetic.
Going back and forth,
back and forth.
I don't want to live anymore.
Even the most glamorous movie
stars of Hollywood bored her.
Oh, farewell, Leo.
You're a lovely boy,
but my heart isn't some CGI bear
for you to conquer.
But I've completely opened
myself up to you.
I even admitted I play
the same guy in every role.
Marry me!
Oh, maybe I should
go back to England.
No. Give this country a chance.
Don't judge us by Hollywood.
All right,
but I'm leaving now, dear.
You'll have to content yourself
with generic supermodels,
I'm afraid.
Nothing ever works out for me.
She needed to get away.
Somewhere. Anywhere.
So she threw a dart.
What's next?
So she headed to Springfield,
little knowing that its men
had the lowest testosterone,
not counting the Columbia
University football team.
Lily wanted peace,
but the best‐laid plans...
Can't understand me?
Too bad.
I'm your narrator.
Do not tell me...
The only thing worse
than when you guys yap
is you sitting here
all quiet and sullen.
I ain't sullen, I'm lachrymose.
Oh, why did I give him
that stupid word‐a‐day calendar?
Impulsinicity?
Excuse me, there, lady,
but this is a man's bar.
And I'd like a man's drink.
Bourbon, neat, in a dirty glass.
You got it.
Just got to look up
what neat means.
I just don't understand.
Understand what?
What's a pub without a song?
At the pub at the crossroads,
there's whiskey and beer...
There are songs about drinking?
There's brandy, strong cognac
that's aging for years
But for killing the thirst
and for easing the gout
There's nothing at all
beats a pint of good stout
Pint of good stout
Oh, what's that
I hear you asking?
Where are the Simpsons?
Haven't you heard enough
about the bloody Simpsons
to last a thousand lifetimes?
Well, I guess not.
So, Homer is about to receive
an unpleasant surprise.
What a great day.
I've never been so happy.
Nothing can ruin it. Nothing.
What? Where you going?
On our vacation, remember?
My aunt's letting us
use her home at the Vineyard
for three weeks, rent‐free.
How come I'm not coming?
Well, that was
her one condition.
I'm gonna
miss you all so much.
Well, at least
I'll have the dog.
Sorry, Dad. We put the pets
with Mr. Flanders
because, well,
we knew he'd take care of them.
Come to papa.
Good, good.
Make‐believe you love him.
Flanders, I love you!
We're staying at my Aunt Edith's
house at Hyannibunkport.
It's south of Squibagansett,
east of Codtucket,
next to Little Crabkill Bog.
Those are great names.
You'll never want to leave.
I'm gonna keep you in my sight
as long as I can.
We love you! Stop following!
Okay.
Drink it up,
then throw me out the door
I've traveled in England
I've traveled in France
At a hint of good music,
I'll sing or I'll dance
So hear me then, mister,
and pour me one more...
Gentlemen...
If I can't drink it up,
then throw me out the door
You have to seize life
and relish every minute.
Eliminate all sorrow.
Open a bloody window.
Hallelujah
Okay, okay,
that's enough of that.
Hallelujah
Ha...
Hey, Lily, you like suspenders?
'Cause I got them.
Well, I hope you don't mind
if I give them a wee snap.
Intimacy.
Lily, you've transformed this
dump into a joint. Bless you.
Who are you?
- Homer Simpson.
- You know, Homer,
I've never met a man who didn't
offer me his chair or his beer.
- You have now.
- So, tell me,
what's wrong with you?
It's personal.
Tell me. Maybe I can
lighten your load.
- My family left me for three weeks.
- No.
The dog and cat
are with Flanders.
I'm alone.
I don't know what to do.
You have to have a good time
for their sake,
because if you don't,
they'll feel guilty
and never forgive you.
And you'll never forgive them,
because they're causing you
the misery.
And you'll all be buried
in dirty laundry
with squealing kids
for the rest of your days.
You're the smartest woman
I've ever met in my life.
Except one.
Shut the window!
But then everything
smells like you.
Take that.
Anticipation
is making me late...
Welcome to our tour
of the Vineyard.
This is where Steven Spielberg
shot Jaws.
That's the end of our tour.
Now, my aunt's house
is only eight miles away.
But we just have
to make it before sundown.
Mom, I think
you've gone off the road.
Watch out for that deer!
- That was close.
- More deer!
We're here.
Your turn, Lily.
I miss them. I miss them.
It's been so long.
No one to comfort me.
Put your mobile away, because
I'm gonna sing in German.
Vor der Kaserne
Vor dem grossen Tor
Stand eine Laterne
Und steht sie noch davor...
This is like that beautiful
scene in Sound of Music
when all the Nazis
sang good night.
Wie einst Lili Marleen
Wie einst
Lili Marleen
If you're done singing,
can we turn up the game?
What's wrong, lady?
We miss you inside.
A good bloke
who never had a break,
and now has a broken spirit.
He's lost and lonely,
and really doesn't
give a fig about me.
- I'm in love.
- I love him too.
Okay. The sun is shining.
I can finally read my book.
Hello, nature.
Time to meet your death.
Bart, those are tick bites!
You'll get Lyme disease.
Why didn't somebody warn me?
Get me a priest.
Mom, I always liked you.
Oh, honey, try to relax.
Watch Itchy & Scratchy!
I am itchy and scratchy.
Meanwhile,
Homer little dreamed that...
Willie! Do you think it would
kill you to rake and talk?
Would you rather
I tell the story
about what's under
these leaves and dirt?
Oh. No. No, no, no, no,
no, no, no. Carry on.
Getting back,
Lily continued to light up
all the men's lives,
except Homer's.
Lily!
Gentlemen.
I made you all picnic lunches.
Yeah!
It's British food.
Post‐1990 British food.
Yes!
Smithers,
that woman has captivated me,
which, if memory serves,
is an early state
of physical arousal.
Sir, we've been
through this before
with several women
and one very shapely tree.
I feel a tingle I haven't felt
since they took the cocaine
out of Coca‐Cola.
I must woo her.
And Simpson's my way in.
Have him ask her
on a date on my boat
which will actually be
a date with me.
But, sir, why not have me
ask her directly?
As if I could trust you
to keep your hands off a lady.
How well you know me, sir.
Very good, Maggie!
Now we can cook them.
Who are all those people?
It's the weekenders
from Falmouth.
It's almost here.
And raise the prices...
Now!
Clam strips and beer!
Black Dog mousepads!
- Over here!
- T‐shirts!
CDs by James Taylor's brother!
That's it! We're going home.
Everyone was innocently falling
into Burns's trap.
And trouble brewed as
Lily offered a perverse prayer.
Forgive me, Lord.
I must have Homer.
Please let me win him,
even briefly.
It would be like having
a lover and a child
at the same time.
Hey, Lily. How you doin'?
Homer! I'm so glad
you asked me to meet you here.
Thanks, I'm glad
you feel that way.
But there's something
I didn't tell you.
You're on a date
with my boss.
That's my boat.
My name is Montgomery Burns.
I'm the richest and therefore
most attractive man in town.
Okay, see ya.
Wait, wait, wait, Mr. Burns!
Surely a venerable gentleman
such as yourself
would know that
I need a chaperone.
Of course.
Simpson, join us.
Smithers, cue my weapon of woo.
I know a shortcut.
Why am I staring at her?
I'll make my eyes
look at something else.
Oh, my God.
I'm smiling back.
I hope you enjoyed
your dinner.
And just wait till we get
to dessert.
You make me feel like
I'm having dinner
with a James Bond villain.
She gets me.
Now, wink for me, Smithers.
What am I doing here?
What have I done
to this wonderful woman?
How can I make it up to her?
I'm sorry.
Why did you bring me here?
Fear of unemployment.
Let's just stay
through dessert.
Look at me!
I'm Gypsy Rose Lee!
You and me and
my cardiologist make three!
Sorry, I have to leave
right now.
But why?
I just spilled
a glass of wine on myself.
Also, this bottle.
Homer, let's go.
That was awful.
There's some people
that make you feel
being lonely isn't so bad.
And there are people
that make you
never want to be lonely again.
I hear ya.
And I almost understand ya.
Thank God
you were there to save me.
That's what I'm best at.
Saving people from things
I get them into.
You've got a little cake
on the corner of your mouth.
Oh, I do? Where?
- Just here.
- There?
- Just there.
- Where?
- Right there?
- Just... You're missing it.
- There?
- Just to the...
- Oh, just let me do it.
- Okay.
You can stop now.
I meant go slow.
Wait a minute, wait.
While you're there,
could you get the upper lip?
Oh, my God,
what am I going to do with you?
Please, nothing.
I'm taking you home now.
Well, aren't you going
to walk me in?
Look, Lily.
You're the most...
Finish that thought.
You're the most anything
of any woman
I've ever known
except for my wife.
Who I loved, I mean love!
I said love!
Oh, that's beautiful.
Thank you.
But give me one damn
proper kiss goodbye.
No.
No. No!
This is good,
but is it worth
burning in hell forever?
We'll see each other
in our dreams,
whether you like it or not.
You stay out of my dreams!
All my stuff's in there!
Gotta stay awake. If I dream
of Lily, it's all over.
Gotta stay awake.
Must not dream.
Oh, no.
You've got a little cake
on the corner of your mouth.
- Homer? Homer?
- She's here.
She's here and God help me,
- I'm glad.
- Homer.
- Marge!
- Surprise!
We came back early.
Oh, thank God.
Oh, thank God!
I'll never let you go a...
Who's calling you so late?
Telemarketer.
Gotta take it.
Those people are so sensitive.
- Hello?
- Wrong number!
- Homer?
- Damn it!
I need to see you now, Homer.
You know the address.
Lovers Lane,
just off Fidelity Avenue.
Listen.
I have to tell you right now
I can never see you again.
Can you tell me in person?
Great idea.
Keep me on the line.
I'll guide you here.
You realize
nothing's gonna happen.
Of course.
I promise you chocolate
and kisses
Martinis with lemon drops...
No, feet! No!
I just woke up
And made you pork chops...
Pork chops!
You're home.
Yes, I am.
And I'll never leave you.
There might be frequent
interruptions.
I may stop at Moe's,
I may be watching
the hot dogs spin
at the movie theater,
or I may be picking
a flower for you...
but I will never,
ever leave you.
Homie.
Now boarding, non‐stop
Springfield to London.
Sorry, lady.
How was America, dear?
There's nothing there for me.
It's big, full of fried food,
and heartbreaking...
and that's just one man.
There'll never be another
like him.
Buy you a drink, sweetheart?
No.
Fancy a drink?
No, thank you.
Would you get... No.
No. No thanks.
Get off.
Buy you a corndog?
Yes!
But first, are you married?
And would you shave off
the mustache?
Yes, and immediately.