(SlNGlNG) The Simpsons
(TlRES SCREECHlNG)
D'oh !
(SCREAMlNG)
(BRAKES SCREECHlNG)
l don't understand
this game, Bart.
How come we have
to rake your lawn
while you just
get to sit there?
Because l'm "it."
Now whoever finishes
first gets lemonade.
BOTH: Yay!
For me.
Later when we wash his bike,
l'm not gonna do a good job.
l'm telling Mr. Bart!
Shh !
Hey, guys.
(GlGGLlNG)
Uh-oh. Girls.
You guys need
your cootie shots.
(BOTH CRYlNG OUT lN PAlN)
Well, l hate this job,
but l love the health plan.
Okay, ladies.
Don't you have
a poodle to dress up?
Fine, we'll go.
We'll find some other way
to entertain our
boy-crazy cousin
who thinks you're cute.
Oh, l wouldn't mind
pushing that in the mud.
(MUMBLlNG)
Homer drunk? But how?
Hmm.
Round and round
the bottle twirls,
l hope it stops
on one of the girls.
(GASPlNG)
l hope you like
the taste of
ringworm medicine.
Ew!
Ugh !
Ew! l kissed
that sad weird kid !
My beer!
You never had a chance
to become my urine.
(SOBBlNG)
Why you little. . .
(CHOKlNG)
My first kiss.
Stop it, Homer!
There's only one way
to settle this.
ln Simpson Family Court.
What the hell's that?
l got the idea from
a now discredited book
on raising children.
(GAVEL BANGS)
Now up, the case of
Simpson v. Simpson.
Mr. Simpson, do you
think it's appropriate
for a 1 0-year-old boy
to steal a beer
with intent to kiss?
Do you think it was
appropriate to bet
against your son's
little league team?
What? Permission to treat
this witness as hostile.
Homer,
l'll bet when you were 1 0,
you were stealing beers,
kissing girls,
and tipping dinosaurs.
Your father's first kiss
was in high school,
with me.
Actually, Marge,
there was someone
before you.
(GASPlNG)
lt was years ago
when l was 1 0, back in
the '60s or '50s.
Or maybe it was
the early '70s.
Underprivileged?
You pretended
we were poor just to
get me into camp?
Uh, yeah, pretended.
Hey, you must be Homer!
l'm Lenny and this is Carl.
Wow, a Negro.
We prefer the term "black."
So cool.
Heya, fellas. l'm Moe.
l'm your junior counselor.
(CHUCKLlNG)
Moe's not really
a counselor.
His parents
dropped him off here,
like, two years ago
and they never
came back for him.
l sleep under
upside-down canoes.
(CHUCKLlNG NERVOUSLY)
(UPBEAT MUSlC PLAYlNG)
(CARL AND LENNY GROANlNG)
(ALL LAUGHlNG)
D'oh !
ln the summertime
when the weather is high
(ALL YELLlNG)
That's the girls' camp
right over there.
(COY GlGGLlNG)
Hi.
Oh ! l can't wait
to meet the girls!
ALL: Wha. . .
That's right.
You're working
in the kitchen.
That's how our
camp pays the bills.
What bills?
We got no water, no heat.
We catch our own breakfast.
Twelve kids died at our camp.
We need the money
to pay lawyers.
l thought
we were gonna play
fun games at camp.
Oh, here's one!
lt's called
"Stay out of my way." ldiot.
YOUNG MARGE:
Oh, no. My retainer.
l got it!
Ooh la la!
A girl with teeth ! Me like.
YOUNG MARGE: Oh, thank you.
You sound so sweet.
(CHUCKLlNG)
That's 'cause
l've eaten 1 6 pieces of pie.
(BOTH GlGGLlNG)
You know,
doing dishes has been
the best part of camp.
YOUNG MARGE: Really? Why?
Because l talked to you.
YOUNG MARGE: Aw!
l couldn't see her
through the flaps,
but she's my kind of girl.
Tell us more about the flaps.
To me, they were
the rubbery gates of heaven
because behind them
was the girl of my dreams.
Oh, man. Someday love'll come
sliding down my chute.
Well, l can ask if
she has any friends
because she wants
to meet me tonight.
Way to go!
Out of sight!
Now, Homer,
if you're gonna go,
you better take
some protection.
Oh, a switchblade!
l see the switch,
but where's the blade?
(CLlCKlNG)
D'oh ! Found it.
An eye patch?
But l've got a date tonight.
Oh, don't worry.
Chicks love
that kind of thing.
Patches, scars, stumps.
Everything but zits.
All right,
how should l get there?
Hmm.
l guess it's row versus wade.
And it's my right to choose!
Are you looking
to cross the lake
which separates ye from she?
Who are you?
The sailing instructor.
And on movie night,
l run the projector.
Only PG. Nothing R.
Yarrr.
HOMER:
I couIdn't beIieve my eye.
She was the prettiest
girl l'd ever seen.
(CHUCKLlNG NERVOUSLY)
Until l met your mother,
who made that girl look like
a Godzilla made of garbage!
Homer, that girl was me!
(ALL GASPlNG)
How romantic.
You and Dad were drawn
to each other as kids
and you didn't
even realize it!
Yes. And then your
father broke my heart.
And if l'd known
it was you, l never would
have married you.
Oh, this is so confusing !
l'd like a brief recess.
Granted.
(BANGS GAVEL)
Whee! Recess!
(DOOR SLAMS SHUT)
(GlGGLlNG)
Whee!
Let me get this straight.
When you were my age,
you had the hots for Mom
and didn't even know it?
Oh, that's cool
or is it lame?
l guess l'll go with lame.
You were lame!
Why? Because
l only kissed one girl
in my whole life?
That's still
one more than you.
l've kissed three girls.
(SOBBlNG)
l'm so lame!
You're not gonna
be kissing anybody
for a while!
Well, that stinks!
But l still get
to kiss you, right?
(GRUMBLES)
Mom, why are you so mad?
l'll start from
the beginning.
The girls' camp
was focused on teaching
etiquette and deportment.
Now that l've
captured your interest,
let me continue.
By summer's end,
l promise you will
all walk like ladies,
talk like ladies,
and hold your
liquor like ladies.
Now chin up, head back,
legs together. Excellent.
Girls, see how
Marge's legs are slanted?
You make Jackie O
look like a splay-legged
milk-horse.
Now stand and walk.
(STRUGGLlNG)
Well done.
l'd be proud
if you grew up to be
my husband's mistress.
Thank you.
l used to walk
like this all the time
until my tendons snapped.
They heard it in Shelbyville.
Anyhoo, one night
we had a special dinner.
We were Iearning
to use all 33 forks.
Young lady,
that is not an olive fork!
Here's a simple trick
to help you remember.
Ow!
Hmm. Mmm-hmm.
Knife and fork together,
denied yourself dessert.
Nice work, Marge. Really.
Oh, no! My retainer!
YOUNG HOMER: l got it!
Oh !
l'd thank you,
but l don't even
know your name.
l bet it's something
low-rent like Billy Bob.
Or Homer.
Big ugly Homer!
(GlGGLlNG SPlTEFULLY)
Oh, l'm sure
it's a much nicer name
than Homer.
Er. . .
Think, Homer. Think.
YOUNG MARGE:
What did you say?
l'm Elvis!
Elvis Jagger.
Elvis Jagger Abdul-Jabbar.
(LAUGHlNG HEARTlLY)
l told my friends
l had a date.
What should l wear?
Should l paint my toes?
And what should
l do with my hair?
You could iron it.
lron my hair?
That's what
Leslie Uggams does!
BART: LesIie who?
MARGE: Uggams!
Oh, it's really
straightening out.
(CRlES OUT) Hmm.
l guess
l'm going to have to be
a brunette tonight.
Oh, dear me.
One day as
a straight-haired brunette.
l feel so bad for you.
Stupid girl !
Please don't be a freak.
SEA CAPTAlN:
l met her on the mountain
There l took her life
Met her on the mountain
Stabbed her with my knife
(WHlMPERlNG)
Hi.
Oh. He's cute.
And he's got an eye patch.
l've never seen
a boy so mysterious.
You must be Elvis.
Elvis? What the hell
kind of name is. . .
Oh, yeah. Right.
We've heard the same story
two times now.
Whose side are
we gonna hear next?
The Sea Captain's?
No, no. l'd best
be on me way.
l'll just take
some Teddy Grahams
for the road.
There goes a good friend.
Now l'm gonna warn you kids,
the next part of
the story gets a little WB.
Oh, man. l want to kiss her.
Wait. I just thought of
the greatest move ever!
(EXAGGERATED YAWNlNG)
Oh, no. He yawned.
I'm boring him.
Do you like music? l do.
l like Bobby Goldsboro,
Gilbert O'Sullivan,
Terry Jacks, Parliament,
but not Funkadelic.
How am I supposed
to kiss those things?
Interrupt her
with something witty.
Er. . .
Um. . .
Yes?
Kiss her aIready.
What are you, chicken?
(CLUCKlNG)
Is he making chicken noises?
Imagine me and you, I do
l think about
you day and night
It's onIy right
To think about
the girI you Iove
and hoId her tight
So happy together
If I shouId caII you up,
invest a dime
And you say
you beIong to me
and ease my mind
Imagine how
the world could be
so very fine
So happy together
Ahhh !
l can't see me
Iovin' nobody but you
For aII my Iife
When you're with me, baby
the skies'll be blue
For aII my Iife
Me and you and you and me
No matter how
they toss the dice
it had to be
The onIy one for me
is you, and you for me
So happy together
Way to go, Dad !
The perfect kiss!
lt was pretty delicious.
lt was as satisfying
as a million Hallmark cards
with all
the right sized envelopes.
(SlGHlNG)
lt felt like
a cluster bomb wiping out
a graveyard full of zombies.
(SlGHlNG)
But then your father
showed his true colors.
Uh-oh !
Will l see you
again tomorrow?
Absolutely.
Or my name isn't. . .
Whatever l told you it was.
MARGE:
So we arranged to meet again
at Second Date Rock.
(HUMMlNG)
(SlGHlNG)
l guess he's not coming.
lt was years before
l could trust a boy again.
(SOBBlNG)
That's horrible.
How could you, Dad?
Because he's the kind
who kisses and leaves you !
(SOBBlNG)
l can't believe
you stood Mom up.
Face it, Lise. Men are dogs.
The worse we treat you,
the more you want us.
That's not what dogs do.
(LAUGHlNG)
You said "dog doo!"
(CHUCKLlNG)
She sure did.
Now if Lisa's finished
with her shenanigans,
l'll tell you why
l didn't show up.
We had just finished
our first smooch.
And I feIt a feeIing
l had never felt before.
l found this stone earlier.
l was gonna use it
as a nerd smasher.
But l want you to have it.
Ooh, it looks like a heart.
Hey, you're right!
Give it back!
Oh, no,
l still want you to have it.
But every time you
smash a nerd with it,
think of me.
l will.
See you tomorrow night, okay?
(SlGHlNG)
What a kiss.
lf l died now,
l'd die happy.
(SCREAMlNG)
Oh, what a view!
Good ol' patch !
You saved my life!
Ahhh !
So you thought you could make
a break for it, did you?
Well, no one ever
escapes from Fat Camp.
Because the only way out
is up a gentle slope.
What the. . . Fat Camp?
(WHlSTLE BLOWlNG)
(GROANlNG)
(PANTlNG)
l don't belong here!
Heh ! Your boy bosoms
tell a different tale.
(GRUNTlNG)
Okay. Take a break, ladies.
No eating the grass!
Hey, he didn't say nothing
about this poison oak!
Sweet, sweet poison.
Uh-oh ! (GROANlNG)
(VlBRATlNG)
Ohhh. . .
l've gotta go.
l've got a date.
Yeah, you've got a date
with a skinless
chicken breast.
(LAUGHlNG)
Somewhere out there,
she's waiting for me.
Hello. l'd like to speak
to Elvis Jagger Abdul-Jabbar.
Hey, don't you try
and prank me
with a fake name!
l will out your intestines
and use them to
make a lanyard !
Hello? Hello?
(GRUNTS ANGRlLY)
And that's the origin
of that.
(SOBBlNG)
That boy l kissed
wouldn't even tell
me his real name.
Typical. All boys want
the same thing,
to kiss until
they're hot and heavy,
then vamoose.
Trust us.
We know everything about boys
except what they look
like below the waist.
l have some theories
based on a G. l. Joe
l bought.
Well, l. . . l never
want to date a boy again !
(SOBBlNG)
Are you leaving camp
because of that boy?
Because that's what l've been
telling everybody.
You're also pregnant.
l just can't stay here.
Everything reminds me of him.
Oh !
(GRUNTlNG)
Oh, the pain !
(GROANlNG)
Man was not meant
to sit up! Oh !
We've got an emergency here.
We need 1 0 cc's pronto.
And by cc's, l mean cupcakes.
MAN: I know
what you mean, BiII.
l've worked here
Ionger than you.
Now's my chance!
(PANTlNG)
Love conquers all !
Snake!
Bye-bye!
Thank God they're gone.
l can't believe
l went five minutes
without one of
these dream sticks.
Hey, have you
two longshoremen
seen a pretty girl?
lf you are
who l think you are,
that girl is gone.
And she never
wants to see you again.
She wouldn't do that.
We shared something special.
What? Just 'cause
she smooched you?
Was that special?
(SOBBlNG) No!
(SOBBlNG)
l just blew my
first chance at true love.
And now that my special girl
has heard the truth,
l know she'll forgive me.
Earth to special girl,
you'll forgive me, right?
l guess so.
Uh, l think
we'll go to bed now.
What are you doing?
lf they fight in front of us,
we might get new bikes.
Homer, when you nurse
a hurt for 30 years,
it doesn't go away
in an instant.
What about now?
(FRUSTRATED NOlSE)
No, Homer.
What about now?
Marge, l'm really sorry
l hurt you.
But l've done way
worse stuff since then.
There was
the gun l hid from you.
The time l sued the church.
Ruining Lisa's wedding
in the future.
Remember that?
Homie, l know this
shouldn't bother me,
but a girl only
has one first love.
(SlGHlNG)
l guess it didn't
mean that much to you.
That's not true!
l thought about
that girl every day
of my life until l met you.
l wish there was some way
l could believe that.
All right.
This is my memory box.
l haven't opened
it in 30 years.
Ooh ! A letter
from my old pen pal.
Someday l'll write
you back, Osama.
Ah ! Here's what
l'm looking for.
Oh, Homie! You did care!
l sure did.
l kept it right next
to my lBM stocking.
l kept my heart, too.
Because somehow you realized
l was a good guy after all?
No. As a reminder of
the hurtful things
men can do.
(GULPlNG)
But now it can
have a second meaning.
MARGE: Oh, Elvis.
HOMER: Oh,
anonymous girl who turned out
to be Marge!
(KlSSlNG)
English - US - PSDH