♪ The Simpsons ♪
D'oh!
-Ahh!
-(tires screech)
(honking)
SMITHERS: Testing.
Testing for Mr. Burns.
Here you go, Sir.
I've warmed up the crowd for you.
Welcome, employees!
Come in.
The whole night's
entertainment is on me.
Monty Burns!
(cheering)
ANNOUNCER (on PA):
Welcome, welcome, welcome
to an evening of
exciting quarter-mile
action, action, action.
Our first race is a benefit
for daredevil Lance Murdock
Murdock, Murdock,
who's hospitalized
with cirrhosis
of the liver, liver, liver.
CROWD: Yay!
All right, liver!
Boy, it sure
would be fun
to car-pool in one
of those, huh, kids?
I'd be a real
hot-rod mama, wouldn't I?
Huh? Huh?
You missed
the race, Mama.
Hmm. I wish
I'd pay more attention.
Smithers, this beer
isn't working.
I don't feel
any younger or funkier.
I'll switch
to the tablespoon, Sir.
ANNOUNCER (on PA):
Coming up next
our feature race:
The Nuclear Power Plant
Championship!
Plant, plant.
Ah, at last!
Smithers, fetch the bi-oculars.
Ooh, damnation!
Tell them to go slower.
Yes, Sir.
Hi, guys, can we keep
it in first gear
for a couple laps?
Go! Go!
Slow down.
BURNS: Excellent.
Oh, this novelty foam hand
is ludicrously oversized.
Go swap it
for a smaller one.
It is a bit
ostentatious, Sir.
I'll be right back.
Hey, Burnsie!
Ha! This was some
swell shindig.
Thank you very much.
Smithers,
what's happening?!
I had a great time.
I just want
to shake your hand.
(mumbling)
You're the greatest.
Smithers, help!
Doesn't seem as funny to me,
but what do I know?
BURNS: Smithers!
Oh, my God!
Yah.
(yelling)
You should have seen
the murderous glint
in his eye, Smithers,
and his breath reeked
of beer and pretzeled bread.
I'm so sorry, Mr. Burns.
This was all my fault.
Don't concern yourself.
If things had turned ugly,
I always had my mace.
Don't let me off the hook
that easily, Sir.
I failed you and I'll
never forgive myself.
Never! Never! Never!
Never! Never!
(phone ringing)
SMITHERS:
Never! Never! Never!
Good morning, Sir.
To make up for my
failure last night
I've alphabetized
your breakfast.
You can start
with the waffles
and work your way
up to the Zwieback,
and to prevent
newsprint
from rubbing off
on your hands
I've laminated
today's newspaper.
I appreciate the thought
but my pen
won't write on this.
How am I supposed to do
the Junior Jumble?
Oh! I can't
even grovel properly.
I'm a buffoon!
I don't deserve to live
on your planet anymore!
(crashing)
(gurgling)
(gasps)
Pull yourself
together, man.
I daresay you're in need
of a long vacation.
No! Don't make me
take a vacation!
Without you,
I'll wither and die!
That's a risk
I'm willing to take.
But what would you
do without me, Sir?
(scoffs)
I'm not a baby
who needs a nursemaid
to burp me.
(burps)
You see?
Now, I insist
you take a vacation
just as soon as
a temporary substitute
can be found.
Yeesh!
I've got to find a replacement
who won't outshine me.
Perhaps if I search
the employee evaluations
for the word "incompetent."
-(beeps)
-714 names?
Better be more specific.
"Lazy," "clumsy,"
"dim-witted,"
"monstrously ugly."
Aw, nuts to this.
I'll just go
get Homer Simpson.
HOMER:
I think Smithers picked me
because of
my motivational skills.
Everyone always says
they have to work a lot
harder when I'm around.
You know, Dad,
assisting Mr. Burns
could give your career
a real shot in the arm.
You know, Homer,
assisting Mr. Burns
could give your career
a real shot in the arm.
Mom, I just
said that.
Sor-ry!
Next time, get
your own darned corn.
Um, is this the chair
I'll be sitting on?
Yeah.
Now, I realize
caring for Mr. Burns
seems like a big job
but actually,
it's 2,800 small jobs.
Uh-huh, but this is
the chair, right?
Your new duties will include
answering Mr. Burns' phone
preparing his tax return,
moistening his eyeballs,
assisting with his chewing
and swallowing,
lying to congress
and some light typing.
(phone ringing)
Montgomery Burns'
office.
Oh, hello, Mrs. Burns.
I'll see if your son
is available.
Mr. Burns
has a mother?!
She must be a hundred
million years old!
She has limited
capacities.
All she can do
is dial and yell.
I'm sorry.
Monty can't come
to the phone right now.
He's in a very
important meeting
and can't be disturbed.
Uh-huh.
Okay, I'll give him
the message.
Mr. Burns can't stand
talking to his mother.
He never forgave her
for having that affair
with President Taft.
(chuckling)
Taft, you old dog.
Really, Smithers.
I'll be fine.
I'm sure your replacement
will be able
to handle everything.
Who is he anyway?
Uh, Homer Simpson, Sir.
One of your organ banks
from sector 7G.
All the recent events
of your life
have revolved
around him in some way.
Simpson, eh?
HOMER: Uh, Mr. Smithers?
I don't understand
2,700 of my new duties.
Well, the van's leaving.
Which one duty is giving you
the most trouble?
Um...
What do I do in case of fire?
(muffled)
Sorry. Can't hear you. Bye!
(crackling)
Aw. Just my luck.
(panting)
(gasping)
Good Lord, Smithers,
you look atrocious!
I thought I told you
to take a vacation.
Uh, Smithers
already left, Sir.
I'm his replacement,
Homer Simpson.
Ah, yes, Simpson.
I'll have my lunch now.
A single pillow
of shredded wheat
some steamed toast,
and a dodo egg.
But I think
the dodo went extinct.
Get going!
And answer those phones,
install the computer system,
and rotate my office
so the window
faces the hills.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Okay.
Um, can you repeat
the part of the stuff
where you said
all about the things?
Uh, the things?
(quiet snarl)
(alarm buzzes)
(grunting)
Lousy two-legged pants.
Homie, it's 4:30
in the morning.
Little Rascals
isn't on till 6:00.
I know.
I'm taping it.
I want to get to
Mr. Burns' house
bright and early
to make his breakfast.
Mm, poor Homie.
Poor, poor...
(snoring)
Hmm...
One of these must be
a breakfast-maker.
Well, it's my job
to cook him breakfast
and I'm gonna cook
the best damn breakfast
he ever ate.
Hmm...
(groans)
Doughnuts?
I told you
I don't like ethnic food!
Here. Tell me
how my stocks did yesterday.
Uh...
They all won.
Hm?
What about my options?
Well, you can either get up
or go back to sleep.
I believe I'll get up.
(brush scrubbing)
BURNS: Scrub harder.
Got to get that layer
of dead skin off.
HOMER: Ugh.
I think...
the fangs today.
BURNS: Simpson?
Simpson?
Did you get
that report
on the accounting
department?
Yes Sir, I did.
"The accounting department
is located on the third floor.
"Its hours are 9:00 a.m.
to 5:00 p.m.
The head of this department
is a Mr. Johnson or Johnstone."
Here are your messages.
"You have 30 minutes
to move your car."
"You have ten minutes."
"Your car
has been impounded."
"Your car has been
crushed into a cube."
"You have 30 minutes
to move your cube."
(phone rings)
Yeah-lo,
Mr. Burns' office.
Is it about my cube?
It's Mr. Smithers.
He's calling for you.
How's everything going there,
Sir?
I have a lot of free time
on my hands.
If you Fed-Ex me your mail,
I'd be happy to open it
and return it to you.
Everything's fine, Smithers.
This Simpson fellow seems to be
getting dumber by the minute.
I've never seen anything
quite like it.
Anyhoo, you just
enjoy your vacation.
(groans)
(snoring)
Look alive,
Simpson!
I'm not paying you
to goldbrick!
Yes! Yes, Sir...
Now get cracking
on my long division
and don't forget to
show your work, Simpson.
I'll have it on your desk
in the morning, Sir.
Bart, leave
Simpson alone.
(whispering)
Simpson, I need a ride to the library.
Kids, stop exploiting
your father.
Homie, why don't you
lie down and relax?
No time, Marge.
I think Mr. Burns wants me
to do some long division.
Simpson! Lie down!
Sorry, but you need
a good night's rest.
(sighing)
(bell clanging)
BURNS: Simpson!
(bell tinkling)
(panting)
The telephone's been ringing
for some time.
Answer it.
Yello?
It's for you.
♪ Relax... ♪
Mr. Burns-- 48 rings.
Are you all right?
What did Simpson do to you?
Oh, nothing other than drive me
to distraction
with his incompetent boobery.
Terrible at everything.
A complete moron!
(whispering)
But I'm not really free
to talk right now.
Now look, stop calling me and
start enjoying your vacation.
Remember, I want to see
lots of pictures
when you get back.
Actually, sir, picture-taking
is not allowed
at this particular resort.
Oop. I got to go now.
There's a line
forming behind me.
(shuddering)
(yelps)
60 watts!
What do you think this is?
A tanning salon?
I asked for light starch
on my night cap.
(yelling)
You call this Postum?
You call this
a tax return?
a super computer?
-(grunting)
-D'oh! Ow!
(yelling) You're a travesty
of a joke of an assistant!
(whimpering)
(yelling)
(clock ticking)
(whimpering)
(shrieks)
(gasping)
Is there something
wrong, Homie?
No.
Except?
Except...
I killed Mr. Burns!
What happened, Dad?
I punched Burns right in his
104-year-old face.
Are you sure he's dead?
Maybe you just really,
really hurt him.
Okay. Maybe
everything's all right.
Maybe if you go apologize,
he won't even fire you.
If he's alive.
Mr. Burns?
(raspy breathing)
-(gasps)
-(screams)
I'm really sorry I hit you,
Mr. Burns.
Here-- let me put some salt
on that eye.
No, please!
I can't bear another thrashing.
Just leave me be.
Y-Yes, Sir.
Must call Smithers.
He'll protect me
from this beast.
I've seen people activate
this machine a thousand times.
Doesn't seem to be
any trick to it.
Let's see-- Smithers.
S-m-i-t-h-e-r-s.
(ringing)
Success! It's ringing!
Moe's Tavern.
I'm looking for
a Mr. Smithers.
First name, Waylon.
Oh, so you're looking
for a Mr. Smithers, eh?
First name, Waylon, is it?
Listen to me, you!
When I catch you
I'm gonna pull out your eyes
and shove them down your pants
so you can watch me kick
the crap out of you. Okay?!
Then I'm going to use
your tongue to paint my boat.
Oh, Smithers if only
you could hear me.
(gasps)
Something tells me
Mr. Burns needs me.
(shouting)
Praise God.
I think the thug
has finally gone home
for the day.
Now I can make my escape.
(yelps)
Hi, Mr. Burns.
You want your coffee now?
Uh, no, I'm, uh...
making it myself.
(rattling)
Hear that?
The percolations are imminent.
No need to come in.
Cease your ingress.
(nervous laugh)
(sighs)
(knocking)
Stay back, Homer.
Approach no further.
Coffee's already made.
I stomped the beans myself.
Well, can I at least
drive you home, Mr. Burns?
-It's 5:00.
-No! I thought, uh--
I thought I'd chauffeur
myself this evening.
Yes, that's what I thought.
How difficult could it be?
I'm sure the manual
will indicate
which lever is the velocitator
and which the deceleratrix, hmm?
I can't believe it.
All my life I've avoided
doing things for myself...
but I'm actually enjoying this.
Plus, I'm making
incredible time.
(honking)
Beep beep!
Out of my way!
I'm a motorist.
(screeching)
That's some nice
reckless driving, Mr. B.
Would you like me to shred
those environmental reports
for you, Sir?
Already taken care of.
(chuckling)
Cappuccino, Simpson?
(phone rings)
Ahoy-hoy?
No. You have the wrong number.
This is 5-2-4-6.
I suspect you need more practice
working your telephone machine.
Not at all. Ahoy.
Mr. Burns, is there anything
at all I can do for you?
No, Homer.
You've already done
more for me than any man.
Your brutal attack forced me
to fend for myself.
I realize now that being
waited on hand and foot
is okay for your average Joe,
but it's not for me.
I want to thank you.
Thank you.
Oh, my God.
I knew I shouldn't have left.
Ah, welcome back,
Smithers.
Say, do you know
Homer Simpson?
He pitched in
around the office
while you were away.
Bang-up job, Simpson,
but I guess it's back
to your trusty post
in sector 7G.
(sighs)
You heard the man, Simpson.
Ahh.
And my dear, dear Smithers
You're no longer needed at all.
You're fired. Ta!
You shouldn't have
gone away on vacation.
(gobbling)
Cheer up, Homie.
I just feel terrible about
getting Mr. Smithers fired.
That job was all he had.
Imagine how
you'd feel, Marge
if you got fired
from the...
those things
that... you do.
Quick, Mom, whip up a cake
before Dad fires you.
Don't worry, Dad.
Mr. Smithers
is a resilient man.
I'm sure he can get a great job
at any corporation he wants.
SMITHERS:
Meet your new piano mover.
(groaning)
Now, we're gonna have to put
a steel rod
where your spine was.
Will I ever move
a piano again?
(laughing)
Oh, my goodness
gracious, no.
SMITHERS (on PA):
Get ready for exciting quarter-mile action
at the Springfield Dragstrip.
It'll be motorized mayhem,
mayhem, mayhem...
(lowers voice) Do we need
all those "mayhems"?
We do?
All right, fair enough.
I suppose
you know your business.
(loudly) Get ready for
fun, fun, fun!
(softly)
The people are already here.
We don't need to keep
hustling them like this, do we?
Let go of me!
Where are you throwing me?!
Uh... hello,
is that a "help wanted" sign
in the window?
Uh, yeah. I need someone
to help me
with the midnight
beer delivery.
Your job is
to distract Barney
until it's safely
off the truck.
I'll just wait out back
until then.
I look forward
to working with you.
Mr. Smithers, wait.
You can't let yourself end up
in a place like this.
You've got two choices.
You can give up on yourself
and take the Barney-guarding job
like so many of us
have contemplated
in our darkest moments,
or you can admit to yourself
there's only one person
that can make you happy
and do whatever it takes
to get them back!
You're right.
But I'm gonna need
your help.
(clock strikes)
Oh, my God!
TRUCK DRIVER:
Beer delivery. Just sign here.
Oh, no! It's you!
(loud crashing)
(Barney laughing)
-DRIVER: Hey!
-BARNEY: Oh, boy!
DRIVER: Give me that!
(metal clattering)
(loud burp)
Okay, I got you covered.
Mr. Burns may have mastered
2,799 of my 2,800 duties,
but I'll wager dollars
to doughnuts
he still can't handle
a call from his mother.
You're on.
(phone ringing)
What?
Hello, Mrs. Burns?
This is Waylon Smithers.
I have your son
Montgomery on the line.
That improvident lackwit.
Always too busy striding
about his atom mill
to call his own mother.
I'll give him what-fors
till he cries brassafrax!
(chuckling) Perfect.
When I give the signal
you transfer the call
to Mr. Burns.
After she tears into him,
I'll rush in and save the day.
Got it.
I'm transferring a call
in to you, Mr. Burns.
BURNS: No problemo.
Uh...
ooh.
Um...
-(dial tone)
-Uh-oh.
BURNS:
Ahoy-hoy?
Hoy?
(in falsetto)
Hello, Mr. Burns.
This is your mother.
(whispering) No!
Ugh...
Oh, hello, mater.
Um... sorry about pulling
the plug on you and all.
Who could have known
you'd pull through and...
live for another five decades?
Ooh, is my face red.
(whispering)
Mrs. Burns is 122 years old
so try to sound more desiccated.
And she doesn't call
her son "Mr. Burns."
(cracking falsetto)
Son, this is Mrs. Burns.
I just called to say
I don't love you.
You are a bad son, Mon... tel.
So...
(screams)
Impersonate my mother,
will you?
And you, Smithers, you must
have put him up to it.
I'm glad I fired you.
You really blew it
this time, Smithers.
(yells)
Stop that!
Stop that at once!
You're fighting!
Stop fighting
like a girl, Simpson.
(grunting)
Okay.
Heh-heh-heh.
(screams)
Stop it! Stop it, I say!
I'll teach you
how to use a phone, you boob!
D'oh! D'oh! D'oh!
It's for you.
D'oh!
I'll show you!
(growling)
(chortling)
Ow!
(screaming)
(thudding)
Oh, my...
Here comes the endangered condor
into the power lines.
Mmm. Mmm, mmm.
I've got Bobo
hot from the dryer.
Careful not to burn yourself
on his eye.
I don't need you
to do any of this.
I'm totally
self-reliant now.
What I would like, though,
is a Spanish peanut.
Skin?
Mmm. Mmm.
It's a remarkable thing.
In the short time
you were gone
I learned to be
completely self-reli...
...ant.
Oh, and as for that
brutish fellow
who knocked me
out the window,
see that he gets
what's coming to him.
I already have, Sir.
What'd you
get that for?
For knocking Mr. Burns out
of a third-story window.
Makes sense to me.
Did he die?
What am I, a doctor?
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.