(SINGING) The Simpsons
D'oh!
(SCREAMS)
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
ALL: Surprise!
(SHOCKED GASPS)
I don't see
why I need a new
driving license.
My old one's
just fine.
Hmm, I have serious
doubts about your
skill behind the wheel.
You drove in
with three people
on your grill.
(GROANING)
At least
I'm out doing things.
Do you know this baby
once outraced
the Flying Finn,
Paavo Nurmi?
(GRUNTS)
Turn the heater off.
It's boiling in here.
What are you
talking about?
This car is cooler
than Guy Lombardo.
(GASPS)
What's wrong with me?
(SOBBING)
(LAUGHING)
Good heavens.
She's some sort
of female madman.
(GASPING) Hot. So hot.
(MECHANICAL HUMMING)
Stop that,
you want-wit!
I might get stung
by a bumbled bee!
(SCREAMING)
Van Houten blows
past Simpson!
He's got all
the right moves!
(GRUNTS)
And a fight
breaks out!
(GRUNTING)
(SOBS)
(TIRES SQUEALING)
(SCREAMING)
Car!
Car what?
Car is the subject,
but I don't know
the verb.
SELMA: Wha...
(SIZZLING)
(PANTING)
I still feel hot!
Sir, thank God
the airbags activated!
Those are my lungs.
(SLURPING)
Ugh!
Selma, what you
experienced was
a hot flash.
An early symptom
of menopause.
What the hell's
menopause?
Son, menopause is
when the stork
that brings babies
gets shot by
drunken hunters.
It's a natural process
that women of
a certain age
go through.
And it's something
to be feared.
Right, Doctor?
(CHUCKLES)
Far from it.
Maybe we
should all take
a look at this.
(CLUCKING)
What do you know?
She's out of eggs.
And if you're
watching this,
so are you.
Hello, I'm Robert Wagner,
actor,
smooth customer,
and women's
health advocate.
Just as the end
of the day can
bring great beauty,
So too can the
end of menstruation
be a time of radiance
and celebration.
Sure, you may
experience
mood swings,
loss of desire,
and private dryness.
But don't worry.
You can still do
everything that
you did before.
Everything?
Including
having children?
Ma'am, we're
trying to make
a video here.
Menopause means
you can't have
any more children,
but it also marks
a wonderful new plateau
in a woman's life.
So let's all give
menopause a round
of "mena-plause."
"Mena-plause"?
I'm not saying that.
So that's it.
The end of the line.
I'm never gonna
have children.
(SIGHS)
Selma, I never
realized you wanted
a child so badly.
I didn't want
to get pregnant
and lose my looks.
(SNORTING)
But now I'm afraid
I'll grow old alone.
What about your
pet iguana, Jub-Jub?
Jub-Jub can't take
care of me when
I'm old and sick.
All he can do
is eat me when
I'm dead.
Don't cry,
sweetie.
Everything's
gonna be all right.
Come on, kids.
We should go.
Goodbye, Selma.
I'm not dead,
idiot.
I know.
That was for the
other patients.
Ow! Ow!
MY thingies!
(ORGAN MUSIC ON TV)
We now return to
Son of Satan!
Everyone has
a child but me.
Cheer up, sis.
There's a dented
can sale down
at Tregman's.
(GROANS) This is one
problem damaged
food can't solve.
Wow. You really
are down.
Hey, you ever
think of adoption?
The adoption process!
That'll end the heartbreak!
Hey, hey, hey!
That foot's not dead,
it's just asleep.
Ooh! He's perfect.
For this
little guy,
I'm gonna
give up smoking.
From now on,
we're a Skoal family.
(CHOMPING)
Um. Is this the
baby pound, where
I gived up my kid?
Because I needs
to get him back.
Oh, no!
The birth father!
I shouldn't have
given him away.
Seems I misheard my wife.
What she said was,
she's tired
of having rabies.
Give me back
my belly fruit!
If you want,
I'll call you after
Brandine's next litter.
Yeah, pass.
(SIGHS)
Don't give up,
Aunt Selma.
China has
thousands of baby girls
who need adoption.
Great. Another job
lost to a foreigner.
Madam,
your adoption application
is in perfect order,
except for one thing.
(GULPS)
You forgot to fill out
the name of your husband.
Husband.
Of course.
The Chinese government
only allows wholesome,
married couples to adopt.
No "hen without cock."
I apologize if that
is a double entendre
in your language.
It is not in ours.
Don't worry.
I'll just write
my husband's name
on this form.
Have you ever
heard of MacGyver?
Yes. Big star. Big star.
We know he's not
married to you.
Right, right, right.
And don't forget,
your husband must go
with you to China
to pick up the baby.
All right.
Here I go.
Writing the name.
(GRUNTING)
Excellent.
You are
Mrs. Homer Simpson.
He is your soul
mate and lover.
Yes. Homer Simpson
is my whole world.
I love him.
(SHUDDERS) Oh!
I just felt
a chill go through
my very soul.
Yeah.
Those Sloppy
Joes'll do that.
How about that Selma,
flying all of us
to China for no
apparent reason?
And how about me
getting off work
by saying I'm
teaching math skills
to inner-city youths?
Yes, there are
many kinds of heroes.
Marge, when are
we gonna tell Homer
he has to pretend
to be my husband?
Wait till the
Drambuie and sleeping
pills kick in.
(GULPING)
Hey, look. A dragon.
Hello, Homer.
Give me your peanuts,
and you can fly on my back.
I'll give you... One!
Oh, you are
a very greedy man.
The other dragons
shall hear of this.
HOMER: Hey, dragon,
you fly like a girl!
Go, go, go!
(SIGHS)
(NERVOUS MURMUR)
Homer, I'm gonna
need you to do
something for me
when we get to China.
You name it,
O wise mountain ape.
You have to pretend
to be my husband.
HOMER: No!
That's him.
The man who broke
a dragon's heart.
(CHINESE-STYLE SINGING)
The man who broke
a dragon's heart
Homer, if you do
this one small favor,
it could transform
Selma's life.
(WHINY) But, Marge,
I don't want her
to be happy.
Okay. Don't do
it for her.
Deal!
Do it for me.
(MOANS)
Okay, I'll do it
because your sweet
love is the one thing
that saved my life
from being an
unmitigated disaster.
Ha-ha!
Now we're even!
This is your captain.
We have started our descent
and will soon be
landing in Beijing.
CO-PILOT: If you look out
the left side of the aircraft,
you will see our
monument to warrior
and spicy chicken pioneer,
General Gao.
HOMER: Wow. It makes
the Lincoln Memorial
look like crap.
Very good. You have
passport, husband...
All we need now
is the sack of
10,000 happinesses.
When do I get my baby?
In a few days.
(GROANS)
This will give you
a chance to explore our
nation's ancient culture.
(GROANS)
And it will
give me a chance
to closely observe
the intimate details
of your married life.
(BOTH GROANING)
Madam Wu, these are
(CHUCKLES) our children,
Bart and Lisa.
Yes.
And this is Marge,
our surprisingly
hot nanny.
Hmm. Thank you,
Mr. Simpson.
Don't mention it,
Miss... October.
Butdon%look
at her passport!
It's different!
MADAM WU:
These are the famous
Shaolin Temple monks.
They pursue spiritual
peace through mastery
of bare-fisted murder.
I've heard
of these guys.
You can wave your
arms at 'em and
make funny faces,
and they just
have to stand
there and take it.
(JIBBERING)
Homer, no! Stop!
You're thinking of
Buckingham Palace!
What?
(GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
(HEART BEATING)
I hope you washed
your hands first.
Oh, look at
him sleeping.
He's like a little
angel that killed
50 million people.
Yes, you are!
The Great Wall
of China was begun
nearly 2,000 years ago
in order to repel
barbarian invaders.
With these
pogo sticks,
we'll finally
make it over.
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
All right,
everyone
take a break
and come back
Monday with five
fresh ideas.
Can't make it Monday.
My kid has a thing.
When I was 17,
I walked into
the jungle.
And by 21,
I walked out.
And by God,
I was rich.
(WOMEN SINGING IN CHINESE)
Boys, you see
what I was
talking about?
The greatest
things can happen!
(WOMEN CONTINUES SINGING)
I finally
get this play.
MADAM WU:
So, Mr. Simpson,
what do you do for a living?
I'm a nuclear...
HOMER'S BRAIN: Wait a minute.
These guys don't know me.
I can be
whatever I want.
(GRUNTS)
I'm a Chinese acrobat.
(ALL GASPING)
You shall be
back in the land
you love soon.
Tomorrow we
will give you
your baby.
Oh, my God, really?
My life
begins at last.
That is quite
an insult to your
other children.
We understand,
ma'am.
We're pretty
lousy kids.
Lisa, soon you
will have a Chinese
baby sister
who will surpass
you academically.
I don't know
about that.
I'm considered
pretty smart.
Well, Tibet was
considered pretty
independent
How'd that
work out?
(GASPS)
How dare you make
light of that brutal...
Mind your
manners, Lisa.
Such loving
discipline.
Maybe someday
someone will love you,
too, childless servant.
(ANNOYED MURMUR)
I regret to inform you
that our final stunt
will not be performed.
Our star acrobat
had an onset of
outspokenness
and suffered
a bullet-related death.
This is most
disillusioning.
It seems our leaders
are not all-knowing.
Now I will
question everything!
Why doesn't Pearl
Jam ever come here?
(ALL PROTESTING)
Homer, we need
your acrobatic skills.
Only you can
prevent this riot
and save our beloved
communist dictatorship.
You guys are commies?
Then why am I seeing
rudimentary free markets?
Just go perform
that stunt!
Unless you
are not who
you claim to be.
(NERVOUS LAUGH)
It's showtime!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
I give you the great
American acrobat,
Homer Simpson,
to attempt our
most popular stunt,
Chairman Wow!
Hup! Nice chair toss.
Good one, skinny.
You guys get
these chairs
from Regal Rents?
Boy, you're
a great stacker.
Hi, Lisa.
Now that's precarious!
Boy, this is easy.
Maybe I am
the world's
greatest acrobat.
(ALL GASPING)
(SCREAMING)
(APPLAUDING)
USA! USA! US...
(BONE CRACKING)
A-
(EKG BEEPING)
(HOMER MURMURING)
Ooh. You're curing me
with acupuncture.
No. A porcupine
snuck in while
you were asleep.
Go on! Shoo! Come back
in Year of Porcupine,
which is never!
I'd like you all
to meet someone.
Introducing
Ling Bouvier!
(GASPS) Selma,
she's beautiful.
(GURGLING)
This is Homer,
your daddy.
Without him,
I wouldn't
have you.
(LAUGHING)
Aw. She likes my eyes. Ow.
Homer,
I do appreciate
what you did.
How'd you like
a little time
with Miss October?
I would,
but Marge
would kill me.
I mean, oh, right.
Ow, ow, ow!
Homer, of all
the sneaky,
dishonest things
you've ever done,
playing Selma's
husband was by
far the sweetest.
It wasn't easy, Marge.
I missed you so much.
Hmm. (GIGGLES)
Okay, one
quick snuggle.
Is there any other kind?
Fool me once,
shame on you.
Fool me twice,
shame on Wu!
Ling, you're gonna
be very happy in America.
Unlike everyone
else there.
(GIGGLING)
Selma Bouvier,
this man is not
your husband.
And for that,
no adoption!
Mama!
They took my baby.
(SOBBING)
Wow, the fortune
cookies here really
are more accurate.
(SOBBING)
I am so sorry
about what
happened.
But at least
you saw what
it was like
to be married
to me for
a little while.
(SOBS HARDER)
Listen, I've got
a plan to get
Ling back.
But we must be discreet.
You never know
where there might
be a spy.
Yes, tell me your
plan in detail,
American sister.
Don't have
a cattle, dude.
(GRUNTS)
Let's talk about
this outside.
(SPRAYING)
Hold still, Homie.
Yeah, Dad.
If you don't
look perfect,
you'll never be
able to sneak in
and steal Ling back.
You look just
like a Buddha statue.
Now all you need is
an expression of
utter serenity.
Just think about
the day you found
that Junior Mint in
your belly button.
(CONTENTED MURMURS)
(DOORBELL RINGING)
A Buddha statue?
We cannot
leave it outside.
It is bad feng shui.
Feng shui?
I thought that
was just a trick
to sell crappy end
tables to the West.
Just put this hook in
his nostril and pull.
(SCREAMING)
(MOANING)
l never
moved a Buddha
this heavy.
Let's cut him in
chunks and worship
the chunks.
Ooh!
Now let's see.
Which one is Ling?
Ling? Ling?
(GURGLING)
Ling!
(GIGGLING)
If we can just get to
the Delta Airlines
Gold Medallion Lounge,
they can't get in
without spending
frequent flyer miles.
Plus, we get
free apple, orange,
and grape fruit juice.
MADAM WU: I am afraid
that juice is not
on your tongue just yet.
(ALL GASPING)
Give the baby back!
I cannot allow
her to be raised
by an unmarried woman!
Madam Wu, I too
work for a cruel
and faceless empire...
The Department
of Motor Vehicles.
May I talk to you,
bureaucrat to bureaucrat?
Yes. But you first
must sign this form.
And initial here.
And here.
Now we must
find a notary.
(CHUCKLES)
This is Wang Pu's
time to shine!
Proceed.
Madam Wu, we both love
the enforcement
of pointless rules.
But there's
a greater joy in
bending the rules
to help someone
who thinks all
hope is gone.
I was this woman's
husband for a few days,
in name only,
and beer will soon
obliterate that memory,
but I don't think
this baby could find
Any greater love
on your planet
or ours.
You may not
believe this,
but I once was
a baby myself.
My father
was a Ping-Pong
champion.
He died when
the ball got stuck
in his throat.
The Heimlich maneuver
was invented
the very next day.
My mother raised me alone,
so I know it can be done.
You may keep
your baby.
But, you!
Drop the panda!
But he loves me. Ow!
Ow! Why you little...
I'll endanger you...
(GROWLING)
(GRUNTING)
Goodbye, Simpsons.
You'll be back
someday, Ling,
as a spoiled
American teenager.
(LAUGHING)
(LAUGHS LIKE SELMA)
Something's
wrong with Bart.
He's acting weird.
(IMITATES BART)
Feast on my shorts,
stupid father man.
Wait, you're
not Bart.
Close enough.
(LAUGHING)
(CHINESE-STYLE SINGING)
American jerks are going home
Now we sleep for
a thousand years
When we wake,
the world will end
David Silverman here,
supervising director
of The Simpsons.
And tonight,
I'm gonna show you
how to draw Bart.
Now we start off with
a tin can, like this.
And a little tuna
fish can for the bottom
part of his head.
A little hinge
of an ear.
And a big sausage
for a nose.
Two giant golf
balls for eyes.
Now here's
a trick about the hair.
It's one, two, three,
four, five, six, seven,
eight, nine points.
And there you go.
Perfect Barts every time.
Now once you've
mastered how
to draw Bart,
you can put him
in all sorts
of costumes.
Some that he likes,
some that he hates.
Well, that's it,
my friends.
Thank you very much.
Keep watching.