♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Ahh!
-(tires screech)
(popping)
SKINNER (on PA):
And finally,
the bake sale to raise money
for the car wash
has been canceled
due to confusion.
Well, that concludes
this morning's announcements.
I'm Seymour Skinner,
and stand by to resume learning
in five, four, three...
Oh! It's hard enough
to keep the kids awake
without you, Seymour.
(all gasping)
Mrs. Krabappel,
I also have
an announcement to make.
Can't it wait
till I retire?
(clears throat)
I want one and all
to join me in celebrating
the anniversary
of my portentous birth.
Here you are, Nelson.
A birthday party?
(blows raspberry)
Here you are, Nelson.
I said...
(blows raspberry)
(engine revving)
All right, men.
Get ready to blast off.
Whoo!
We're in orbit now.
What's that?
A call from the president?
Hello?
(imitating Nixon):
Ah, yes.
Let me just say this
about that.
Okay, Mr. President.
Bart, this is boring.
I guess we could go
to Martin's party.
I don't know.
If we're seen there,
it'll definitely take
our social standing
down a notch.
We're at what now?
Three?
Three and a half.
We get beat up,
but we get an explanation.
(continues imitating Nixon)
Beautiful colors. Never has--
Mayday! Mayday!
♪♪
Hmm.
Bart!
Uh, Mrs. K.
Hey, it's Saturday.
Your powers are useless
against me.
Relax. I'm just here to have
fun like everybody else.
Don't think of me
as a teacher.
Okay.
So...
Mm-hmm.
(nervous laughter)
(sighing)
Excuse me.
(pitiful whimpering)
(crying)
Mama!
Hey, Houdini, why don't you
saw Martin in half?
Oh, I'm not the kind of magician
who does tricks.
I'm a math-e-magician.
(all groaning)
Oh, man.
Now, prepare to marvel
at the mysteries of the universe
as I make this remainder
disappear.
(chuckling)
But seven goes
into 28 four times.
Uh-- this is a magic seven!
(children chattering)
Edna!
Seymour.
Mind if I sit down?
Hmph! It's a free country.
I...
I don't follow you.
Oh, just sit down,
Seymour.
It might be nice to talk
to a grownup for a change.
Well, this party is certainly
a break in my routine.
You know, normally
I spend my Saturdays
carefully laying out my clothes
for the following week.
Then I stroll down to the car wash
to see if Gus is there.
Oh, yeah. You've got
to keep busy.
I collect matchbooks
from glamorous nightclubs.
It's amazing.
It you just write to them
and ask them nicely...
Is this...
How you imagined
your life, Edna?
Well, yes, but then,
I was a very depressed child.
To poor decisions.
Hear, hear.
WOMAN:
Seymour! I told you
not to play
in the neighbor's yard.
It's a party,
Mother.
I was invited.
Well...
Then I must've been
invited, too.
Help me, Edna.
I know where we can hole up
for a while.
(crying)
That's it.
Looking good.
Getting warm.
Uh... I feel queasy.
Don't stop, Milhouse.
You're so close.
I got to barf.
Where's the bathroom?
(kids screaming)
(all moaning and groaning)
Oh, my tummy!
I told you we should've served
cake instead of oysters.
I'm ruined!
Ha-ha!
(groaning)
(siren wails)
(Lisa groaning)
Bart, how come
you're not sick?
Eh! I gave my oysters
to the cat.
(retching)
Hey, why'd you eat them?
I thought
you were a vegetarian.
I didn't. I just
wanted to leave.
(fake groaning)
More tea, Edna?
What kind of little boy
has a tea set?
Hmm! I think we both
know the answer to that.
A lucky boy.
You know, Seymour,
there's an innocence about you
that can be quite charming.
Oh! Well, I've always admired
your tart honesty
and ability to be personally offended
by broad social trends.
Oh, really?
Mm-hmm. Very much.
And your laugh.
You mean, "Ha"?
Mm-hmm. That's the one
that makes me feel...
(breathing heavily)
Oh, boy.
(clears throat)
You have a breath mint
I could borrow?
I've got
some menthol cigarettes.
Oh, the heck with it.
BART: You are never going to guess
what I saw at Martin's party
after you guys left.
You know that playhouse?
Well, I--
-Good gravy!
-Oh, thank you.
It's just brown and water.
So I looked in the window
and there it was.
The grossest sight
I have ever...
SKINNER (on PA):
Bart Simpson, report to
the principal's office
immediately.
Now, Bart... son...
I don't know
what you think you saw
but, let me assure you...
What Seymour... Oh...
What Principal Skinner
means to say, Bart,
is that sometimes
a little boy's imagination
can run away with him.
That's the best
you can do?
You could have at least said
you were giving her C.P.R.
or rehearsing a play.
Is it too late
to say that?
Mm-hmm.
(clears throat)
We're just a little concerned.
If people were to find out
the principal
was dating a teacher,
they might see it as
a conflict of interest.
(laughs)
And...
There are those
who might try to use it
against us
for their own advantage.
Like me, for one.
Like you, for...
Bart, if life has taught me
one lesson repeatedly,
it's to know
when I'm beaten.
Let's talk deal.
(grunts)
As you know, Bart,
your permanent record
will one day disqualify you
from all but the hottest
and noisiest jobs.
What do you say, son?
You keep our secret,
and some other student
can inherit your gloomy
windblown future.
Deal.
This is a great day
for forbidden love.
Mmm. This dessert
is exquisite.
What do you call it?
Applesauce.
(chuckles)
Oh, of course.
I'm sorry. I don't get out
to restaurants much.
That's okay.
I don't entertain much.
Usually it's just soup
for one, salad for one,
wine for three.
(laughs) You know,
I always thought
I'd fall for a woman
just like Mother...
even though
I didn't want to.
And now that I haven't,
I've discovered what
true happiness can be, Edna.
Seymour, swallow
that applesauce
and kiss me.
I'm afraid I already swallowed
it while you were talking.
Mmm...
(Edna giggling)
Good morning, students.
Way to go there, Wendell.
There's Ralph--
He knows the score.
Jimbo,
how's that hat today?
Janie, Janie, bo-phaney!
The only way to survive
a deadly blaze is...
Oh, heck, life's too short
for fire safety.
Let's go outside
and pick wild flowers.
(cheering)
SKINNER (on PA): Bart Simpson to
the principal's office.
Post haste.
(Skinner humming
"Eine kleine nacht musik")
Bart, so good to see you.
I have a little favor
to ask you.
I'd like you
to give this note
to Edna when you
get back to class.
I don't think
I have to tell you
it's for her eyes only.
"Dear Edna"--
(mumbling)
(sing-song)
I hear reading.
Do you think
anyone saw us?
No. It went
just as we planned.
Except they confiscated
my thermos of cola at the door.
Ohh--
Skinner, Krabappel,
what are you two doing here?
Superintendent Chalmers!
Uh, why, we're--
We're, uh, on a, uh--
-a-- what do you call-- field trip.
-Uh, with a student.
-Yes! He's, uh...
-He's purchasing refreshments
-in the lobby.
-I'll go get him right now.
(whispering)
Car keys, car keys, car keys.
(sleepily) Stop pushing me.
What's going on?
Just enjoy the movie.
It has Tom Berenger.
You think they actually
filmed this in Atlanta?
I don't know.
I don't think
it's important.
Yeah.
(honking)
Mother doesn't approve
of me dating,
so I need you to keep
her busy for a few hours
while Edna and I sneak out.
(door slams)
Oh, I can't take
much more of this.
I collect
pictures of cakes
that I clip out
of the magazines.
It all started in 1941
when Good Housekeeping featured
a photo of a lovely cake.
You wouldn't happen to have any
real cakes around here, would you?
Oh, my no.
I don't care for cake. Too sweet.
Now, this is called
a Lady Baltimore cake.
At my age, I don't have
much saliva left
so you'll have
to lick my thumb
before
I can turn the page.
Oh, can't I just turn
the page for you?
No!
But you can pick out
any picture
you want to take home
with you.
Okay.
That one.
-No!
-Ow!
You can't have that one!
That's a coconut cake!
(pencils scratching paper)
Bart Simpson!
How many times do I have
to tell you no talking!
Report
to the principal's office!
But-but I wasn't...
-And here, take this with you.
-(groans)
Mrs. Krabappel,
Bart has something
he wants to say to you.
-I won't say it!
-Bart!
(groans)
Oh...
I love you,
Edna Krabappel.
(children laughing)
(chanting)
Bart's going to marry the teacher.
Where are you
registered, Simpson?
(groans)
Thank you, Bart.
That was very sweet.
You may sit down now.
They're not going
to get away with this.
I'm going to step out
for a few minutes, class.
Martin,
you're in charge.
Now, Bart, uh...
(coughs)
You must promise not
to fall in love with me.
(children laughing)
Now, Martin's scoring
off me.
Oh, that is it.
Listen up, everybody!
Follow me!
What's going on, huh?
What's happening,
Simpson?
Where are we going,
anyway?
Okay, crew...
Set your faces to stunned.
(all gasp)
Um...
School dismissed.
And then Bart
opened the door
and Principal Skinner
and Mrs. Krabappel
were kissing!
-(gasps)
-And swearing.
Father, Uncle Apu,
a teacher was in the closet
with the principal
and he had as many arms
as Vishnu
and they were
all very busy.
-(gasps)
-Wow.
I was in the library,
at the time,
but Janie told me
that Principal Skinner
and Bart's teacher, Mrs...
What's her name?
Krabappel?
Yeah, Krabappel.
They were naked
in the closet together.
Oh, my goodness!
Wait a minute.
Bart's teacher
is named "Krabappel"?
I've been calling her
"Crandall."
Why didn't someone tell me?
Oh, I've been making
an idiot out of myself!
Mrs. Krabappel
and Principal Skinner
were in the closet
making babies,
and I saw one of the babies,
and the baby looked at me.
Baby looked at you?
Sara, get me
Superintendent Chalmers.
-Thank you, Sara.
-Hmm.
-Skinner!
-Uh, Superintendent Chalmers.
The whole town's in an uproar
about your sleazy shenanigans.
Now, I'm going to
give you a choice.
You can give up this tawdry
fulfilling relationship
or you two will be
out of here so fast
your mortarboards
will spin.
And where is
your mortarboard anyway?
Uh... Right here, sir.
So, what'll it be, Seymour?
Well...
I'm sorry, but, uh, I can't
give up the woman I love.
Well, then I'm afraid
you leave me no choice.
I want you out
of the building by 3:00.
-You're fired. Edna, too.
-(gasps)
Well, it's going to be hard
to say good-bye to all of you.
We've had a lot
of fun together.
Nelson, Nelson, Nelson.
How many kids
have you beaten up this year?
I don't know-- 50.
Ah, 50.
Where does the time go?
You, uh, you wanted to see me,
Principal Skinner?
Mm-mm.
It's Mr. Skinner now.
I'm just a man.
Bart, I want to apologize
for the awkward position
Edna and I put you in.
Your-- Your help made
our love possible.
I don't know
what we'll do without you.
Well, so long.
Wait a second!
You don't have to leave
just because
Superintendent Chalmers
told you to.
What are you getting at?
You spent your whole life
following orders--
from your mother
the army,
Superintendent Chalmers...
Just this once, man,
stand up for yourself.
Okay, Bart.
Let's go, Seymour.
Okay, Edna.
Uh... No, wait!
We're not going anywhere.
I'm going to do what Bart
should have told me to do
a long time ago.
Attention, Springfield.
We have barricaded ourselves
in the school
and are not coming down
until our demands are met.
Willie hears you.
Willie don't care.
Obviously, you two
have no experience
causing a scene.
I'll be right there.
All right people,
we've got
an escaped octopus
on the roof
of Springfield Elementary.
Let's roll.
Two cameras.
So, once again,
I've been had.
But an even more
interesting story
has developed high atop
this two-story school:
A love story.
Skinner,
get off of my school.
No.
You get off of my school.
Homer,
Bart's up there!
Give me that!
Bart,
this is your father!
Do you know
where the remote is?
I looked
all over the house.
Did you check
your pocket?
It was--
It was in my pocket.
Fine.
Stay in the school.
We don't want you
to come out.
BART: You got it.
Damn.
All right, boys,
roll up the sound truck.
We'll blast them out
with music.
(feeedback squeals)
(melodic acoustic piano
playing "Embraceable you")
♪ Embrace me, my sweet... ♪
Oh, Edna, I hope
this siege never ends.
Seymour, you're heaven
in hush puppies.
Oh...
Turn the music off!
Ha! It's working
like a charm, boys.
Now cut the power
and hit them with the lights.
♪ ...Irreplaceable you ♪
♪ Just one look at you ♪
♪ My heart grew tipsy... ♪
Ugh!
-(ringing)
-I'll get it.
-Talk to me.
-You have got to end this thing, Seymour.
We're not coming down
until our jobs are reinstated
and you acknowledge
and celebrate our love.
No one would like to celebrate
your love more than I
but I'm a public servant
and not permitted to use
my own judgment in any way.
Then let us take our case
directly to the towns people.
Oh, yeah, that'll be
real productive.
Who do you want
to talk to first?
The guy in the bumblebee suit
or the one with the bone
through his hair?
My opinions
are as valid
as the next man's!
Yeah, all right.
Just come on down.
Well... This is it.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to go out there
and tell every man,
woman and child
that I love
Edna krabappel.
Well, that's nice,
but first you got to grab
their attention.
And I think I know how.
I have a bomb.
ALL:
(gasping and murmuring)
Hey, wait a minute.
Those are hot dogs.
Armour hot dogs.
What kind of man wears
Armour hot dogs?
It was a good idea, Bart,
but it's just not working.
Just speak
from the heart, Seymour.
Tell them how we brought
a little happiness
into each other's lives.
Ask them why they're forcing
two dedicated people
to choose between their
careers and their hearts.
Excuse me, Edna.
I don't think we're talking
about love here.
We're talking about s-e-x
in front
of the c-h-i-l-d-r-e-n.
Sex Cauldron?
I thought they closed
that place down.
What are you people
talking about?
My child told me
you two were having sex
in the school janitor's
closet.
You know, "Making babies"?
Yes, illicit sex.
Doing it! It! It!
Sordid public sexual
congress!
This is absurd.
I did not have relations
in that closet,
and the fact is,
I haven't...
Uh...
(crickets chirping)
Yes?
Seymour, I think
you'd better tell them.
It's the only way
to clear our names.
(sighs)
Well, everyone,
the fact is
I haven't ever
had relations.
I am a virgin.
Ha-ha!
(all murmuring)
Hey, does this mean
that Mrs. Krabappel
is a virgin, too?
KRABAPPEL:
Ha!
Well, Seymour,
it's clear
you've been falsely accused
because no one...
anywhere... ever...
Would pretend to be
a 44-year-old virgin.
Oh, that's for sure.
I'm, I'm inclined to agree.
Ugh! I'll never look
at him the same again.
That was more than
I wanted to know.
(clears throat)
Okay, well, um,
Edna, Seymour,
in light of these, uh...
uh... revelations
I, uh, suppose we,
uh... overreacted.
Do we have our jobs back?
What?
Oh, yes, yes, yes. Sure.
Just, uh, you know,
keep the lewdness to a minimum.
I'm out of here.
Skinny, Krabby,
catch you later.
Uh, hold on, Bart.
May we have
a word with you?
We want to thank you
for helping us
through
a difficult period.
Oh, no problemo.
So, I guess now
you'll be getting married
or something, huh?
Well, actually, Seymour and I
have decided to break up.
Huh?
We can't continue on like this,
trying to build a private
relationship in public--
The whole town
watching our every move
with a fine-tooth comb.
Mm-hmm. I'm used
to humiliation
but not in front
of a crowd that size.
But you seemed
like such a good couple.
Bart, when you get
a little older
you're going to learn
that, sometimes, romances
don't turn out exactly
the way you'd like them to.
Hmm...
That's why I love
elementary school, Edna:
The children believe
anything you tell them.
(chuckling)
(both laughing)
(cork popping)
KRABAPPEL:
Whoo! Oh, Seymour...
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.