(electrical buzzing)
(snoring)
Oh, for the
love of...
-Huh?
-(cocks gun)
(groans)
(sighs)
Ah, Halloween:
the one night when we can walk
the streets undetected.
Hey, lame-os.
Turner Classic
Movies called.
They want
their costumes back.
(taunting laughter)
We lame-os?
I have a remedy
for our predicament.
Into this costumery.
(sinister laugh)
-Yeah?
-Oh.
(party music playing)
(doorbell rings)
(grunting)
Friends of Homer’s?
They’re not my friends.
We brought a bottle of booze.
Boooooze!
Come in! Come in!
(grunts)
(owl hooting)
(chuckling)
Mmm.
Good!
Beer good.
You good.
(both moan)
(doorbell rings)
(gasps)
(all scream)
You said you were going out
to kill children tonight.
We were,
then we bumped into
our old friend, the-the-the--
my man here!
You’ll be sucking
your own blood tonight.
Let’s get ’em, girls!
(monsters groaning)
-Bad Wolf!
-(whining)
Bad!
Lighten up, ladies.
It’s not cheating
when you’re wearing a costume!
(screams): Not the face!
It’s time to announce my choice
to represent our class
at the National Reading Roundup.
(chuckling): Here it comes.
My choice is...
Hubert Wong!
-(applause)
-Wha...?
Hooray for Different-Face!
Congratulations,
Hubert.
Or should I congratulate
your tutor:
Amelia,
at the Homework Factory!
Your victory is tainted!
-Asterisk! Asterisk!
-Lisa,
don’t take it personally.
I barely spent any time
on this decision.
Asterisk! Asterisk!
Asterisk!
Lisa Simpson
in detention?!
My horoscope told me I’d see
something interesting today,
but I thought that meant
the horoscope itself!
Stupid Miss Hoover.
(grumbling)
I heard about your run-in
with Hoover.
Aren’t teachers
the worst?
I don’t want to
talk about it.
Listen, you’re
a smart kid.
I bet you like ideas.
I do.
Well, I just had a whopper!
What if you got revenge
on Krabappel for me,
and I got revenge
on Hoover for you?
Crisscross!
Interesting.
With no obvious motive,
no one would suspect us.
Exactly! Crisscross!
-Do we have a deal?
-Thanks,
but I’ll pass.
If I say "crisscross"
one more time,
-will that change your mind?
-Listen,
you’re a persistent
fellow, but I...
-Crisscross!
-I’m in.
♪♪
Bart, have you established
your alibi?
Yep. I’m at the tennis match.
And people will remember
you were there?
I’m pretty sure they will.
Mm-hmm.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
(doorbell rings)
Hello?
Hello? Oh!
I’ve been ding-dong-ditched!
(sinister chuckle)
Crisscross.
(cackles)
You should’ve seen the look
on Krabappel’s face!
And you should’ve seen
the look on Hoover’s face.
In fact,
here it is.
(gasps)
You killed her?
Right. Like we agreed.
I never said "kill"!
Yeah, ’cause you’re smart.
You don’t say "kill,"
you say "prank."
Like Mom and Dad
say "snuggle"
when what they
really mean is
"let’s lock the
door and hug."
Well, I didn’t kill
Mrs. Krabappel!
So, all you did was ring
her doorbell and run?
Yeah, ding-dong-ditch!
"Ding-dong-ditch"
means you kill her,
then you throw
into a ditch.
Geez, pick up a book.
You’re a monster!
A deal’s a deal,
little sister.
Tomorrow after school,
go to her house and T.P. her.
That’s it?
Just T.P. her?
Yeah, torture and pulverize her.
Then ding-dong-ditch the body
and we’re even.
I think I’m gonna
be sick.
(rhythmic chopping)
Oh, Lisa!
Come hold this blade so it
doesn’t slice through my neck.
Come on.
I trust you completely.
Slice her like a bagel!
Ah, got it!
Thanks, Lisa.
Last thing I want is
to be sliced in two--
you know, like a bagel.
(water running)
(gasps)
Bart?
I’ve been waiting
for you...
and trying to figure out
how girls pee.
Sorry, Bart, I couldn’t do it!
There’s got to be another way.
What if I gave you
homework help?
I won’t give you
the answers,
but I’ll give you the tools
to find the answers yourself.
No dice.
Either take care of Krabappel,
or Groundskeeper Willie will say
he saw you kill Miss Hoover.
Why would Willie do that?
Let’s just say...
he owes me a favor.
(screams)
Crisscross!
Like the plaid
on me kilt!
You’re not wearing
a kilt.
Uh-oh.
All right, Bart.
I guess I have
no choice.
I have to kill...
-you!
-(screams)
♪♪
-(bells ringing)
-KIDS: Ice cream!
(kids cheering)
(merry-go-round squeaking)
-(growling)
-(screams)
Go ahead, do it.
You’re no different from me.
We’re made from the same dinna.
It’s pronounced D-N-A,
you idiot.
And we are not the same.
I am not a murderer,
and I never will be!
(groans)
-(gasping)
-(applause)
Well done, Lisa!
It was an accident,
I swear!
Sure. An accident.
Ha!
Ay caramba, you little snot.
I’m here at Krustyburger
for the launch
of the highly anticipated
"Burger Squared."
Krusty, what
can you tell us
about this fantastic
new sandwich?
I’m glad you
asked, Kent.
We start
with Grade A beef,
feed that to other cows,
then kill them
and serve the unholy results
on a seven-grain bun.
Burger Squared!
The math checks out!
Cows eating cows?!
That’s an abomination!
Now, Lisa,
you’re a vegetarian,
but these cows have made
a different choice.
And now, this lucky reporter
will be the first human
to sample this delicious crime
against nature.
Mmm.
Juicy, flavorful,
with just a hint of...
(angry zombie snarl)
Hey!
That’s my check-cashing
arm, you stupid...
(enraged zombie roar)
(screaming)
(roaring)
(people screaming)
(all roaring)
A little tip: you might want
to wash me before you eat me.
-(roaring)
-Thank you.
The munchers got Moe!
Well, we’re not going
out to help him.
We have no idea what hideous
creatures might be out there!
-(pounding window)
-Please, let me in!
How do I know
you’re not a muncher?
I’m your father
and I need your help!
I can’t make sense
of that muncher talk!
-(ferocious snarls)
-(Grampa screaming)
-(munching)
-(body thuds, screaming stops)
(dog howling)
Hungry.
So hungry.
There’s nothing to eat.
Except this.
There’s gotta be something yummy
out there.
(electrical buzzing)
(roaring)
(gasps)
A hamburger!
(grunting)
(humming)
(munching)
(chomping, belching)
(gasps)
Bart ate
a tainted burger!
I’ll bash him
with this book!
-(grunts)
-(screams)
Dad!
No! That’s the last book
in the world!
Really?
Yes! It’s-- oh.
Go ahead.
Wait!
The burger didn’t change me!
I’m not a muncher!
Oh, my God.
If Bart could eat the burger
and survive,
then maybe he can yield the key
to an anti-muncher vaccine!
(gagging)
Then we must keep this boy
safe from harm!
Better call Dr. Hibbert.
-(grunting)
-(groaning)
(sighing)
Well, I suppose
Bart could be immune--
-(roaring)
-a genetic "chosen one,"
if you will.
(chuckles)
If so, secrets locked
within his blood could
be the key to saving humanity.
You must get him immediately
to the safe zone,
just outside of town.
If you see my wife,
tell her I love her.
You mean tell her
I love her?
Or I meaning you?
(screaming)
(dial tone droning)
Mm, I’ll just
high-five her.
(door creaking)
(whispering):
Now remember, no loud noises.
(door squeaks open)
Oh, man, that
breeze feels good!
(munchers growling,
Homer and Bart scream)
(whimpering)
To the panic room!
We don’t have
a panic room!
To the panic room store!
(munchers growling)
(muncher Grampa growling)
(two gunshots)
(à la Terminator): Come with me
if you want to live.
(growling)
Another politician
who can’t keep his promises.
APU:
Psst!
This way.
Well, this day can’t
get any crazier.
(munchers clamoring, growling)
(engine revving)
Apu, how did you survive?
Well, as a vegetarian,
I did not consume
any tainted burgers,
and as a convenience store
owner, I am armed to the teeth.
We need windows, too!
-(tires squealing)
-(growling)
-(glass shattering)
Shoot her!
(gun cocking)
I can’t shoot her.
She’s Lisa’s godmother.
You can apologize in hell!
I guess I could.
(gunshot, groans)
(engine revving)
(yelling)
-(crash)
-Hmm?
What the...?
(sighs)
I will get
out and push.
No matter what, Bart must
make it to the safe zone.
(growling)
(grunting)
(engine revving)
That was so noble of Apu
to give his life for us.
Where are you going?!
You were supposed to stop
at the bottom and wait for me!
(munchers growling)
(truck sputtering)
I don’t see the
safe zone anywhere.
Let’s play a game.
Who gets to carry
the chosen one?
Ow!
Aw, did the chosen one hurt
his chosen little noggin?
Ow! Ow! Ow!
Ow! Quit it. Ow!
-Quit it!
-(flies buzzing)
Well, well, well.
Who’s an unproductive
worker now?
Got your nose.
(laughs)
(shrieks)
Why you...
(grunts)
(growls)
(growling)
Homie, where
have you been?
(jabbering)
Dad, are you becoming a muncher?
I think the better brains is,
are you brains a brains?
(growling)
Where do you want it,
the mouth or the eyes?
-Ooh, mouth.
-Eyes it is.
No! When we get you
to the safe zone,
we can cure your father!
Safe zone?
You really think
there’s a safe zone?
(cackling)
Well, you’re right.
It’s right over there.
-(all clamoring)
-Let us in!
(shotgun blast)
Let us in.
We have the chosen one!
CROWD:
Oh...!
Welcome, son.
To survive, all we must
do is eat your flesh.
MARGE:
Hold it right there, bub.
What kind of civilized people
eat the body
and blood of their savior?
(uneasy murmur)
There must be another way.
Hmm...
(kids shouting playfully)
LISA:
Time has passed.
Children play in the streets.
At night,
there is music and laughter.
And all we had to do was let
Bart take a bath in our food.
Hey, Lis,
want some soup?
(sneaky chuckle)
(sighs)
Mm-hmm.
(moaning)
♪ Oh, why can’t no girl love
a guy with this mug ♪
♪ Whose mother declared
you’re too ugly to hug? ♪
How’s about pouring
me a beer, ugly?
How about some
of my new microbrew?
Must be another mouse
in the pipe.
Let’s see
if this cobra solves it.
(hissing)
Nothing.
Huh.
♪ Just once I wish cupid
would draw back his bow ♪
♪ And shoot me a cutie
whose standards are low... ♪
(whoops)
An unattended tap!
Like taking beer
from a baby!
♪ I’m unlucky in love,
I’m unlucky in luck... ♪
(Homer screams)
Oh!
Oh, my God, Homer!
Just try to relax.
Okay, don’t relax!
Don’t relax!
Oh, Marge, the most
awful thing just happened!
What is it, Moe?
Um...
She’s so beautiful,
it makes my heart take wing!
Look at me!
I can fl... Ow! Ow! Aah!
(groans)
(sighs)
(grunts)
Um, Marge, Homer,
uh, just ran out
saying he don’t love you,
and he never did.
He what?!
HOMER:
Help me!
That, uh... that’s me.
I’ve been taking
ventriloquism lessons.
(laughs)
HOMER:
Help me or kill me!
Huh? Huh!
Now, let Dr. Moe cure
what ails you.
There’s something odd
about this beer.
-(gasps)
-♪ It tastes
like cuddling ♪
♪ It tastes like clean clothes ♪
♪ It tastes like hot steaming
cocoa mixed with rainbows... ♪
-It does?
-♪ Full-bodied ♪
♪ Full-blooded ♪
♪ It’s such a lovely blend ♪
♪ It’s jolly, it’s loyal, like
drinking your best friend! ♪
♪ I stopped my crying ♪
♪ Why, I don’t know ♪
♪ But this rosy, cozy,
bubbles-in-my-nose-y ♪
♪ Makes me wanna have... Mo’! ♪
(applause, cheering
and whistling)
This is the best
musical in light years.
Light years measure
distance, not time.
You know
what I meant.
(orchestra plays)
So, Marge, uh, Homer’s been gone
a whole week, huh?
Ooh, in an unrelated matter,
I just put on cologne
and shaved my knuckles.
I’m still hoping
Homie will come back.
Marge, I’ve got some
bad news to give you.
It’s a letter from Homer
on my stationery
in my handwriting,
using my idioms
and speech patterns.
And it begins, "Dear Midge:
you probably hate me by now,
and if you don’t,
what’s wrong which youse?
But don’t give up on men.
Bart, Linda and the other one
there need a dad."
That does sound like Homer.
"The reason
I left you is simple."
"I’m gay."?!
Yeah, read on. It gets gayer.
(talk-sings):
♪ While turning gay
the other day ♪
♪ A thought occurred to me ♪
♪ I’d like to try most every guy
from here to Timbuk-tee ♪
(singing):
♪ Oh, there’s so many men
around the world ♪
♪ Of every shape and size ♪
♪ I want to nibble on Jamaican
jerks and teriyaki thighs ♪
♪ I want
to French-kiss a Frenchman ♪
♪ And spoon an English duke ♪
♪ ’Cause frankly, dear ♪
♪ To not be queer
just makes me want to puke ♪
♪ So find yourself a man
who’ll want you in the sack ♪
♪ I recommend
our dear old friend ♪
♪ Bartender Moe Szyslak! ♪
♪ Letters don’t lie! ♪
So, what do think, Marge?
Will you give Moe a throw?
Hmm, well...
Maybe you need a little more
milk of amnesia.
Dang, I’m missing
the secret ingredient.
Uh, let me squeeze some more out
of the secret ingredient bag.
(laughs)
Uh-oh.
Looks like I got to wing it
a little bit here.
The other day,
I ran into an Irishman.
(with Irish accent):
Oh, really?
No, O’Reilly.
(laughs, clears throat)
Oh, uh, I see we’re,
uh, back in business.
(groaning)
Now, a little more hemoglobin,
and your wife will be disrobin’.
-(grunts)
-(groans)
(phone ringing)
I can’t talk now.
I’m watching a play.
You want how much
for a radiator?
Is that new or rebuilt?
(laughs)
There.
Oh. Oh. Oh, my God,
I’ve never felt so...
uncreeped-out by you!
Marge, I loves youse.
Will youse be mines?
I guess it is time to move on.
MOE: Before you do, I just
got to warn you, Marge.
♪ My taste for romance
is kinda perverse ♪
♪ I can only make love
in the back of a hearse ♪
♪ Plus I gotta be dressed
as a Civil War nurse ♪
♪ And then when I’m finished,
I’ll go through your purse ♪
♪ But you could do worse ♪
♪ I could do worse ♪
♪ We’re proof that you ♪
-MOE: ♪ You could do worse ♪
-MARGE: ♪ I could do worse ♪
♪ She couldn’t possibly
do worse! ♪
(grunting)
Homer, does this mean
you still love me?
Of course I do, Marge.
Can you still love a man
who’s half-beer?
I always have.
To love!
(both sigh)
(to Simpsons theme):
♪ We hope you enjoyed
this year’s Halloween show ♪
♪ Treehouse of Horror,
number XX! ♪
Shh!
(snoring)
(snoring, mumbling)
(screams)
Enhanced by Fotokem