(SINGING) The Simpsons
(TIRES SCREECHING)
D'oh!
(EXCLAIMING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(HUMMING)
ls there anything
more fun than
a nice Sunday drive?
Oh, yeah,
it's great.
Why don't we top it off
by reading to old people?
Well, I think
in these days
of petro-terrorists
and ozone depletion,
a Sunday drive
reeks of bio-hubris.
Hey, hey!
It's Krusty
the Clown!
What do you say, Krusty?
What?
Can't I get
a cup of coffee
without doing
a monkey dance
for you freaks?
The fishing hat
means leave me alone!
Always nice
to see him.
How did Dad
get out of this
snooze cruise?
He's cleaning out
the garage.
I can picture it now.
I cleaned out the garage
and lost 50 pounds.
(LAUGHS)
(SIGHS)
Ah! Hmm.
It seems a shame to chuck out
these cross-country skis.
Mmm.
I'll keep one.
Let's see, now.
"Kill spiders"?
We don't have spiders.
(SCREAMS)
(STRAINS)
Stupid spider!
Afraid of dying?
(GRUNTS) Ah-ha!
Huh?
(SCREAMING)
(SCREAMS)
(CLANKIING)
What?
Spider poison
is people poison?
(CRIES)
Bart! (G RU NTS)
Hmm. Where's the pain?
(GROANS) Ow!
There it is! (CRYING)
A spider?
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMING)
Ow!
HOMER: Ow! Ow! Ow!
(THUDDING)
(GASPS) Homie!
Time to open
the envelope
I gave you.
(STRAINS)
Out of the way!
I learned CPR
while waiting
for other kids
to finish
their math tests.
(BLOWS)
(GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
Compress his chest!
I'm on it.
(BOTH GRUNT)
(COUGHS)
Hey! What...
What happened?
Where am I?
Who put
those spiders
in my mouth?
Oh, thank God!
He's alive!
You wouldn't believe
what happened to me!
I tried to do
what you told me to,
but I don't even
know what happened.
(CLUTTERING)
I don't even know
what happened.
Honey?
I'm trying to remember...
Oh, uh...
Near-fatal booboo
today really scared me.
What would the kids and I do
if something happened to you?
Don't worry,
if I croak,
you'll marry
Lenny or Moe.
The winner
will be determined
by a card game
I invented.
I got all the rules
written down up here.
You keep
almost dying.
Just look at
our vacation photos.
(SINGING) Vacation
All I ever wanted
Vacation
Had to get away
Meant to be spent alone
(MUSIC STOPPED)
Homie, if you die,
I'm gonna have three
kids to take care of.
I want you
to buy some
life insurance.
Please?
Sure. If it'll give
you peace of mind.
But I'm not gonna die
for many, many years.
I know. I just want to...
(SCREAMS)
(CHOKING)
(BUZZING)
Mr. Simpson,
before we can
insure you,
we need
to ask you
some questions.
Have you ever had
a heart attack?
Haven't we all?
Strokes?
None.
No, wait,
three. (LAUGHS)
Since the last one,
I don't remember so good.
Are you a smoker?
Yes, I am.
You don't smoke!
(SHUSHING)
I want her
to think I'm cool!
If I sign it,
it still counts!
(SCREAMS)
My hemophilia!
Oh, uninsurable?
Oh.
(SIGHS)
I'm not gonna worry
just because
Homer doesn't
have insurance.
A lot of people don't.
(ANNOUNCER SPEAKING)
(MURMURS)
Oh, Roger,
I just love
our present lifestyle.
Don't thank me.
Thank our many
debts and obligations.
(SCREAMS)
(GAGGING)
Honey!
Stop kidding around!
Honey?
(SCREAMS)
Brenda, I'm afraid
your husband
had no insurance.
Well, how will I
feed my family?
You should have
thought of that
before you had children
with a dead man.
Oh!
Oh, this is only
based on a story.
A true story!
Brenda! Where's your wealth?
Gone! Along with
my sanity!
(CACKLES)
But I'm still pretty,
right? Right?
(ANNOUNCER SPEAKING)
Mmm. We need
to start saving.
Go easy on that!
It's got to last
till you're five.
Budget-Os'?
That's right.
It's much less expensive
than the leading
clown-based cereal.
You just have
to assemble it yourself.
We saved 50 cents
on that purchase.
Mom, why are you
so worried about money?
Oh, we're just saving
for a very rainy day.
You mean when
the big tuna
goes belly-up?
Huh?
Well, I just think we should
be building a nest egg.
Way ahead
of you, Marge.
I just ordered
a series of tapes
on saving money.
They should
get here soon.
I paid a bundle for
overnight delivery.
I have a book
from the library
with the same
information.
Okay, I'll just hire
a haulage firm
to cart them away
at my expense!
Directory assistance?
No more
directory assistance!
It's not free.
Well, I'll get
a lawyer on that.
No, a whole team
of lawyers,
who will dine on mustard
flown in from the Orient.
No more
Oriental mustard!
(GRUNTING)
It's so embarrassing.
Mom is making us
wear clothes from Goodwill.
(GROANS)
Ha-ha! People died
in those shirts.
(BOTH GROAN)
Hey, hey, hey!
No outside suds!
I'm sorry, Moe.
Marge won't let me
spend any money,
even counterfeit money!
(LAUGHS)
It's my money.
I'm the one
who earns it.
Drinking beer
out of a thermos
like an animal.
Can you help me unload
this soup from the car?
There was a sale,
so I bought 400 cans.
Marge, your penny-pinching
rampage has gone too far.
Oh, honey,
I know it's not easy,
but we've got
to put money away.
You can't enjoy money
when you're dead,
so why not
have fun now?
Don't you think
you've had enough "fun"?
Last year
you spent $5,000
on donuts,
$2,000 on
scalp massages,
$500 on
body glitter...
Hey, I earned
that money.
While you lounge
around here,
Doing laundry and
putting up drywall,
I'm at work
busting my hump.
Oh, please!
From what I hear,
you waltz in there at 10:30,
take a nap
on the toilet,
then sit around
googling your own
name until lunch.
(GASPS) Who told you that?
You shouted it
while we were
making love!
Now, look here,
mister.
I pay the bills,
I do the budget,
and I'm in charge
of the money.
Hmm!
Are you going to let her
push you around?
Yeah, show that skirt
who's boss, see?
Give us
our independence, Homer.
Yes, President Franklin.
I was never president.
I invented some kind of stove.
Well, I invented a Popsicle
made of Mountain Dew.
Sweet.
Yeah, yeah,
that's swell.
(GASPS)
My scrimpings!
(GRUNTS)
You banged?
Did you spend
our savings
on a motor home?
No. I spent our savings
on the down payment
for a motor home.
I need a castle
where I can be king!
VVell, I hope
you enjoy it,
Your Majesty,
'cause I'm not
speaking to you.
(GRUNTS)
Damn it!
Kids, your mother
and I have decided
to take
a little break
from each other.
While we deal
with our issues,
I plan to go on
Motor Home Makeover
and trick this thing
out like a palace,
not like that dump
you live in.
All I need is for
someone to start
a show called
Motor Home Makeover!
I see. You were mad enough
to leave our house,
but not mad enough
to leave our property.
That's my
half-assed dad.
Hey, I couldn't leave
you kids.
You're like
my own family.
Now check
this place out.
Neat! When I sleep
at Dad's, I call this bed.
You can have it.
This one's way better.
That's a bread compartment.
You're a bread
compartment!
Kids! Come back
in the house!
Oh, do we have to?
I melted string cheese
over some corn chips.
BOTH: Oh, boy!
I've got Gameboys
and caramel apples!
MARGE: I'll let you
sass me!
HOMER: I'll let you
punch me!
MARGE: You can wear swimsuits
instead of underwear!
HOMER: We'll have
Christmas tomorrow!
BOTH: Yeah!
(SINGING)
Welcome to the jungle
We've got fun and games
We got everything
you want, honey
We know the names
We are the people
that can find
whatever you may need
(GROWLS)
(BEEPS)
Whoo-hoo!
Free gas!
Well, it's a pleasure
to meet another sultan
of the slow lane.
That's my rig
over there.
She's a Roam Away
Silver Coach.
34 feet of
walnut-burled freedom.
(WHISTLES)
Boy, I wouldn't mind
driving that
to the Holland,
Michigan Tulip Festival.
I'm looking
for a place
to dock the beast.
I don't mean you, Martha.
I've never loved you either.
We use jokes
to mask our pain
at the death of our son.
Really.
Hmm. A place to dock?
I got room.
I have a backyard
that makes my front yard
look like an idiot.
Can I bring the rest
of the convoy?
(ALL HONKING)
Are you crazy?
Let 12 complete strangers
live on my lawn?
Well, we'll give you
regional beers.
It's a deal! Whoo-hoo!
And there you have it.
Ah!
Welcome, welcome.
If my wife asks,
you're here for
a Boz Scaggs concert.
MARGE: Homer!
What are all these
recreational vehicles
doing here?
These are my new friends.
They like me for me
and my plumbing
and gas hookups.
Young lady,
I like what
you're driving.
Is that one of them
two-level Wander-Kings?
This is a house!
(GROWLS)
Hey, boys,
let's play her
the RV national anthem.
(STARTS ENGINE)
(ENGINES REV)
Daddy, all the fumes
are making me dizzy.
Well, now, Rodney,
the Lord wouldn't
let us die this way.
That's right, Ned.
Now, you three
take a little nap
while I make
some hot chocolate.
BOTH: Yay!
(SINGING)
I've been everywhere, man
I've been everywhere
Travel, I've done
my share, man
I've been everywhere
I've been to Springfield,
Shelbyville, Ogdenville
Cap City, Ogdenberg,
Shelbytown, Spring City
Capfield, West Springfield,
Paris, Rome
And Shelbyville adjacent...
Sing it, baby!
That's a lot of places.
Whoo-ee!
Oh, yeah!
I know another
place you can go!
To sleep.
Sorry, Marge.
We've got the power now,
and you can't turn us off!
Can't turn off the power, eh?
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(SINGING) Sashay this
and fancy that
Watch the dog
dance with the cat
(SIZZLING)
(ANGRY MURMUR)
Lights out, weirdos!
(GROWLS)
I was making
a Monte Cristo sandwich
when my crisper cut out.
It's not golden brown,
it's not brown,
it's not nothing.
Dang!
Oh!
You don't belong
on the lawn.
You belong
in your bed
with your wife.
That's no marriage bed.
It's a loveless slab
of bossiness!
(GASPS) Well,
you're not perfect either!
Name one way I'm not.
MARGE:
You hide food in my hair.
You think brushing
your teeth is foreplay...
I'll have you know
I could have married
Sideshow Mel!
Boy, they're really
going at it.
Do you think
they're gonna
get divorced?
No. I don't see
Dad doing all
that paperwork.
HOMER: What?
I seem to recall you
asked me to get this fat!
Oh, boy.
Let's get out of here
before Dad does
a bad impression of Mom.
HOMER: (MOCKING)
Ooh! I'm Marge Simpson.
Don't eat
off the floor. Ooh!
MARGE:
lam so sick of that story
about finding an onion ring
in your French fries.
It was 20 years ago.
HOMER: That was my Woodstock!
Oh!
You know
what started
all this trouble?
This motor home.
How can a vehicle this cool
destroy a marriage
that crappy?
Hey, I know
this is a crazy idea,
but hear me out.
What if We. .. (GASPS)
Take this back
to the dealer?
Well, I was gonna say,
"Call Reverend Lovejoy,"
but l guess
this could work.
HOMER: Oh, yeah, Marge?
What about my womanly needs?
(HOMER WAILING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(HONKING)
Slowly, slowly.
The RV dealer
is across town
under that gorilla blimp.
How do you know
that's their blimp?
Duh! It's Kamper Kong.
(ROARS)
Bob, word on the street
is there's two kids
trying to return an RV.
Return an RV?
(GRUNTS)
Tie me to the Kong
and cut its tethers.
MARGE: You don't take
anything seriously.
Not even your
bankruptcy hearing!
Hey, that judge
thought I rocked.
Case closed!
Although my case
is still open.
If you need me,
I'll be in my trailer!
(GASPS)
My RV is gone!
It was more than a motor home.
It was a car
I could go
to the bathroom in.
(WAILING)
Hey, a note.
MARGE: (READING)
"Dear Mom and Dad,
"we don't want
you guys to split up,
"so we're driving the RV
back to the dealer."
(GASPS) We've got
to stop them.
Oh! This is a parent's
worst nightmare!
They've stolen a car
and they're home alone.
Let's see,
the RV dealership is
Across the freeway
on the corner of...
Hey! This is
a Flintstones Fun Map.
Look, Dad wrote something.
"'Dino.' Short for dinosaur?
"Remember to ask Jeeves."
(BOTH SCREAM)
We're on the freeway!
Would you look at
those Simpson kids?
Last year
it was Razor scooters,
this year
they're driving RVs.
When I was a kid,
my mom would give me
an empty egg carton
and I'd pretend it was
a spaceship to the moon.
You'll never guess
what I used
for astronauts.
I'm going to say eggs.
Shut up.
Oh, my God,
there they are!
(GRUNTS) Oh!
I've lost them!
I can't see past all the SUVs!
Don't worry about the SUVs.
There's a gentle
curve up ahead.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
Bart! Pull over!
We'll stop fighting,
we promise!
Prove it!
Yeah, kiss and make up!
We're not
quite there yet,
but we've opened up
a dialogue!
Not good enough! Kiss!
Oh!
French it up,
lover boyl
I'm not a machine.
I can't just turn it on!
Oh! Come here.
(MOANS)
(GROANS)
Now pull over!
First, raise
my allowance.
Why, you little...
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(CHOKING)
We're going downhill
and I can't reach the brakes!
(BOTH SCREAM)
Look! "Runaway Truck Lane!"
We're saved!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Oh, rats.
(BOTH SCREAM)
LISA: Ooh!
(SIREN BLOWING)
Oh! Thank God
for that Turkish freighter.
Now we'll just
go get them and...
(SIREN BLOWING)
My kids
are on your boat.
Turn back!
I see no kids.
And we must get
these Season One
Northern Exposure DVDs
to Kahramanmaras.
(BOTH PANTING)
Help us!
Bring back our children,
you Cyprus-splitting jerks!
Just for that,
we keep your children.
Will you raise them Christian?
Coptic Christian.
No! (CRYING)
Captain, wait!
I have something here
that might change your mind!
What are you showing me? Soup?
300 cans of Budget
Club mushroom soup!
If you have some
noodles and tuna fish,
you can make a casserole
that's small on price,
but big on flavor.
You are a wise woman.
It is a shame
you dress like
a Lebanese prostitute.
Return to the docks!
Well, if he thinks
he's getting a corner piece,
forget it.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
Wow, Marge,
once again, your mom-ly
wisdom averted disaster.
And I promise
I will return this RV
first thing in the morning.
HOMER: Easy... Easy...
Easy... Easy...
D'oh!
Water damage?
Can't be returned.
I win again!
(CACKLES)
Aw, hey.
It's only money.
And it did make
a cool splash. (GIGGLES)
Marge,
you're taking this
pretty well.
Dude, she seemed tense,
so we put a little
hashish in her meal.
Cool.
Which came first,
turkey the bird or
Turkey the you guys?
If you don't want
to say it, just think it.
(SINGING)
Istanbul was Constantinople
Now it's Istanbul
not Constantinople
Been a long time gone
Constantinople
Now it's Turkish delight
on a moonlit night
Istanbul
(SINGING)
I've been everywhere, man
Crossed the deserts bare, man
I've breathed
the mountain air, man
Of travel I've had
my share, man
I've been everywhere
I've been to Reno,
Chicago, Fargo, Minnesota
Buffalo, Toronto,
Winslow, Sarasota
Wichita, Tulsa,
Ottawa, Oklahoma
Tampa, Panama,
Mattawa, La Paloma
Bangor, Baltimore,
Salvador, Amarillo
Tocaplllo, Barranquilla,
and Perdilla, I'm a killer
I've been everywhere, man
Crossed the deserts bare, man
I've breathed
the mountain air, man
Of travel I've had
my share, man
I've been everywhere