The Simpsons
D'oh!
All right, family.
Who can guess
what's different
about dinner tonight?
Same old garbage.
This guy's always on!
Oh, you two.
We're eating
genetically modified
vegetables.
Look how big they are!
This corn doesn't
look so big.
That's baby corn.
What?
American corporations
should stop playing God
with nature.
There's nothing
to be afraid of.
They're all grown by
the vegetable division
of Union Carbide.
Mom, my potato
is eating a carrot!
That's it. From now on,
I'm growing all our
vegetables myself.
Go away! Go away!
What you doing, Mom?
I've tried heckling them.
I've tried jeckling them.
It's time I made
myself a scarecrow.
Go away! Go away!
"... in God,
the Father Almighty
"Creator of
heaven and earth... "
Shoo! Shoo!
"Heaven and earth... "
Where were we?
Now I'm lost.
Yeah, I did it!
Marge is in the house!
I will be soon.
Because it needs
some cleaning!
Huh?
I'll regroup
at Red Lobster.
You ain't pretty no more!
Look.
I've made some friends.
Now, go do my bidding!
Uh...
Whatever it may be.
So, Lisa says
by killing their enemy
I became the alpha crow.
I got to admit.
I'm kind of nervous here.
We haven't seen Barney
since they enveloped him.
I'm sure he'll turn up.
Look, here's one
of his buttons.
All right, that's it.
Get them out of here!
This ain't no crow bar!
This is a crow bar! See?
They got the little
stools and everything.
That's Russell Crow,
Cameron Crow,
Crow Diddley,
Hume Crow-nyn,
Gregory Peck.
Homer, I'm very
uncomfortable having
a gang of crows
in our bedroom.
It's a murder, honey.
A group of crows
is called a murder.
I'm sleeping
on the couch.
Drop it in!
Don't cram it in!
Forget it! I'll do it myself.
Aw, look.
Maggie wants to fly, too.
Hey!
Cut it out!
Put her down!
Thank God you're okay.
Okay, that was not cool.
We need to lay down
some ground rules.
We'll get to that!
Right now, I think we
need some time apart!
All right, that's it!
Shoo, you stupid crows!
Shoo! Shoo! Shoo!
That is not a worm!
Ow! Ow! I hate getting
stitches in my eyes!
Stupid crows!
Don't be mad at the crows,
Homer.
They weren't
trying to blind you.
They were just trying
to drink your sweet,
sweet eye juices.
Mmm. Fascinating.
Say, Doctor,
can you do something
about my searing pain?
Well, there is
a medication. Although,
it's a little controversial.
Does it go in the butt?
I'm talking about
medicinal marijuana.
Prescription pot.
Texas THC.
Look, man,
I don't do drugs!
Homer, for your eyes,
the best tonic is chronic.
You're not afraid,
are you?
I had a bad experience
with drugs.
It was that
golden weekend between
summer school
and regular school.
Hey, Homer, want to
smoke some marijuana?
They say
it's a gateway drug.
Well, well.
If it isn't the
Doobie Brothers.
Uh-oh.
Crotch the weed, man.
Smell any drugs,
Sergeant Scraps?
For me, the '60s ended
that day in 1978.
But, Homer, you can't let
a single bad experience
scare you away
from drugs.
But isn't marijuana,
or "dope," illegal?
Only for those
who enjoy it.
Medical use of
marijuana is legal
in this state.
We'll also provide you
with a prescription bong.
Do you want the wizard
or the skull?
Occasions,
persuasions clutter your mind
Incense and peppermints,
the color of time
Okay, let's see.
"Toke as needed.
"Caution, objects
may appear more edible
than they actually are. "
Incense, peppermints
What's that billowing
down the stairs?
It's smoke!
It smells like
the art teacher's office.
Smoke on the water
Da-da-da-da-da-da-da!
Uh-oh.
Da-da-da-da-da!
They burned down
the gambling house
It died with an awful sound
I am hungry for a candy bar
I think I'll eat a Mounds
Homer!
You're doing drugs!
And now
I'm guilty of possession!
I could go to prison
unless I testify
against you.
Marge,
it's making my eyes better.
And it's legal.
I could walk up to
the president
and blow smoke in his
stupid, monkey face!
And he'd just
have to sit there
grooving on it.
Color sky Havana lake
Color sky rose carmethene
Alizarian crimson
Wear your love like heaven
Hello?
Marge, I just realized
I am the "ow"
in the word "now. "
And if you
tell anyone...
Honey, I like it
when you call.
But we just talked
five minutes ago.
Hang on,
I've got call waiting.
Hello?
Hey, it's me.
I've got Marge
on the other line
and she is totally
bumming me out.
Dad,
I thought you didn't
like her saxophone.
I didn't. But now,
Daddy's special medicine,
which you must never use
because it will
ruin your life,
lets Daddy see
and hear magical things
you will never experience.
Ever!
Dad, it's 1:00 a. m.
and I'm out of saliva!
Wow.
That saxophone would
make a great pipe.
Hi-diddily-hey, Homer!
Oh, my God!
This dude does
the best Flanders!
You got the mustache
and the "diddily!"
Okay, now do Wiggum!
Homer, it's me. Ned.
Right.
The God dude.
Hey,
I got a question for you.
"Could Jesus microwave
a burrito so hot
"that he himself
could not eat it?"
Well, sir,
of course he could.
But then again,
wow, as melon-scratchers go,
that's a honey-doodle.
Now you know what
I've been going through.
Well, luckily,
I've got a book right here
that's jam-packed
with answers.
Mmm.
Oh, man, this is long.
Could you read it to me?
I guess that
could be arranged.
"The grace of the Lord Jesus
be with God's people.
The end. "
Wow. Wow.
God does so much for me
and he doesn't ask
anything in return.
Well, I know he's wishing
you'd sign his petition
to re-criminalize
medicinal marijuana.
Done and done!
Now do Wiggum!
Well, okay.
I guess it would go
something like this.
All right, Simpson,
you're under arrest, see?
I said Wiggum!
"And so, potential investors,
I hope you don't think
our IPO is an IPU."
Then I hold my nose thusly.
What do you think, Smithers?
Bit of a downer, sir.
Well, I hope
the investors like it.
I have to raise $60 million
or we're out of business!
Why is that, sir?
I told you,
I pissed it away!
Don't make that face.
Yes, that's the one.
Smithers, I need someone
who laughs at all my jokes.
You know, honest feedback.
Oops! I thought
this was the can, man.
Well, you're a happy Homer.
What's your name, young man?
You just said it!
Well, if you like that,
listen to this.
Working hard or
hardly working?
Smithers, you could
learn a thing or two
from this braying moron.
Young man,
I'm making you my
executive vice president.
Sir, I believe
that position was
informally promised to me.
No, Smithers.
I would've said anything
to get your stem cells.
Now, welcome aboard!
You're covered with
a very fine fuzz.
"Hardly working. "
Where did you
get that suit?
Whoa, whoa!
One question at a time!
Yes, you?
Look, I'm really
starting to worry.
There's half-eaten
cupcakes everywhere.
We're all out of paper clips.
And the curtains
smell like doob.
Oh, yeah?
Well, I got news for you!
I just got promoted,
and it's all thanks
to "Yes-I-cannabis!"
We have a kitchen?
Now,
where are those three
chandelier-hangers I hired?
You mutton heads!
This is why we can
never hold down a job.
Look at Shemp.
He is so high!
Hey, "Shemp" is "hemp"
spelled backwards.
And "Otto" is
"Otto" backwards!
Now, I'm scared.
Homie, I don't mean
to nag, but what does
this have to do
with healing your eyes?
As soon as I graduate,
I am so out of here!
This just in.
The Marijuana
Re-Criminalization Initiative
took another
step forward today
as supporters collected
the final signatures
required to place it
on the ballot
for next Tuesday's election.
We got to get out and
stop that initiative!
Marge, I'm gonna need
10,000 veggie burritos!
No guac in mine.
Good night, Homer.
Dude, your mom is hot.
Don't encroach on our roach!
You've got to
run like an antelope
out of control
Okay, okay.
Hold on. Hold on.
I smell marijuana smoke.
That better be medicinal!
If Phish don't see
a prescription slip,
we are out of here!
We can wait all night,
people.
Here we go.
Whoa!
This guy is seriously ill.
My doctor never told me that.
I had to hear it from Phish.
A one, a-two,
a you-know-what-to-do
Run, run, run, run,
run, run, run, run,
run, run, run, run
You've got to run
like an antelope
out of control
Thank you.
And now, a man
who's a real pothead.
I'm sorry. "Pothead. "
Homer Simpson!
Good afternoon.
I want to thank you all
for coming down here,
taking time off
from your jobs.
Jobs? What?
Jobs...
Because we need to keep
medical marijuana legal!
Whether you suffer
from glaucoma
or you just
rented The Matrix,
medical marijuana
can make things
fabulous, medically.
So, my mellow
fellow citizens,
when you go into
that voting booth
on Tuesday,
the seventh...
Uh, Homer,
that was yesterday.
Oh, man!
They already voted!
And we lost!
Oh, man!
I can't believe we
spaced on the date!
What are we gonna do?
Well,
we can't just stand here
staring at our hands,
although... Wow!
That's right!
I married that chick.
They call them fingers,
but I never see them fing.
Oh, there they go.
There we go. Dump all that
medical marijuana on there.
Actually, that smoke is
a little too inviting.
Throw on that
sack of barber hair.
I could've smoked that pot
and worn that hair.
Homie, you don't
need drugs anymore.
Your eyes are all better.
Eyes? What the hell
are you talking about?
I want my old dad back.
The one who was yelling
all the time and...
You know, I'm not
really sure what I want.
Homer, it's over.
I want you to look
at your children
and promise them
you will never
do drugs again.
All right,
I'll do it for my kids.
As long as you're
doing things for me,
would you tie
up your bathrobe
when you walk
around the house?
Never!
Yeah, I can still
crash here, right?
Get out.
Remember when I
dropped my keys
and you thought
the phone was ringing?
Yeah.
Get out.
What's the matter, Homer?
You're drunk.
But you're not
like sloppy drunk.
Going cold turkey
isn't as delicious
as it sounds.
Look, I'm really glad
you're off the wacky-tobacky.
Yeah.
You were getting all
spacey and everything.
We were gonna
have an intervention.
Yeah.
But at the planning party,
I got alcohol poisoning.
I nearly died.
I was already
making excuses not to
go to your funeral.
It's been three days,
and my mind is clearer.
My sperm count is up,
and I'm able to
recognize simple
shapes and patterns.
Dad, you just said that
three minutes ago.
Unregardless,
I will no longer
be a slave to this!
Why are you
keeping that thing?
As a reminder, Marge.
Yello.
Ahoy-hoy, Executive V. P.
I'm putting the final touches
on my speech to the investors.
And I need your
generous guffaws.
But I can't find
you funny anymore.
I'll either tickle your ribs
or feed them to my dogs!
Now, we're ordering out.
What would you like
on your pizza pie?
Extra cheese?
What do you take me for?
Lorenzo de' Medici?
See you soon.
Don't worry, Homie.
You don't need Mary Jane
to laugh at Mr. Burns' jokes.
Just picture him naked.
Or... With a funny hat on!
"So, profit margins
will be thinner
"than Louise Brooks'
negligee. "
You know, Louise Brooks,
the silent star of Lulu.
One of us has
got to start laughing.
If Mr. Burns gets
flop sweat, he'll die
of dehydration.
I'm drenched with sweat.
I'm going to
take a bathiola.
When I come back,
you'd better be laughing.
This stuff can
make anything funny,
even that show
that follows Friends.
But I promised my family
I wouldn't smoke it anymore.
Well,
I've got to do something.
Start inhaling, Waylon.
This suit used to
belong to Judy Garland.
We could sing a song
if you don't mind
being Mickey Rooney.
You mean that
guy on 60 Minutes
who yells all the time?
Sixty minutes? Oh, my God!
Mr. Burns has been in
the tub for an hour!
Oh, Mr. Burns!
You were too beautiful
for this world.
Oh, man. Oh, man.
We killed Mr. Burns!
Mr. Burns is
gonna be so mad!
The investors meeting
is in 20 minutes!
So what?
Mr. Burns is dead!
We can carry on.
Michael Eisner's been
dead for five years.
Ted Turner's just a hologram.
Now, we got to think.
So, when somebody says
I was an embarrassment
to the country,
I say, "It depends on
what the meaning
of 'was' is, jerk!"
You owe me $200,000.
Good night, everybody!
Bill Clinton, everyone!
He's Jimmy Carter
with a Fox attitude!
And now,
a man you will see
is definitely not dead,
Mr. Montgomery Burns!
Mr. Burns,
as we're running long,
may we skip your speech
and go directly
to the questions?
Mr. Burns,
a two-part question.
One, when will you
see a profit again?
And two,
what's that red stuff
coming out of your ear?
Mr. Burns,
may I field that one?
It's true
we're losing money.
But there's no reason
we can't dance, dance,
dance the night away!
Mr. Burns has
left the building!
We are mollified!
Brilliant.
We lost $60 million
and they're
cheering for more.
Mr. Burns,
you're alive!
Yes.
I regained consciousness
during my big dance number.
Those strings pulling me
every which way
jostled my heart
from its slumber.
And you wanted to
take him to the hospital!
Oh, and you didn't?
Well, the worm has
finally shown its fangs!
Smithers,
make me slap him!
You call that a slap?
Make me slap you.
Now, both.
Now, just you.
Now, give me a taste.
Now, both again.
Now, all three.
Excellent.
ENGLISH - US - PSDH