CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screeching)
D’oh!
(shrieks)
SKINNER:
Next item on the agenda,
I’m afraid that
due to funding cuts,
we’ve had to sell
the science department skeleton
and replace it with
this Halloween costume.
Thank you, Willie.
Now, please return it
to its plastic snap case.
(clears throat)
Moving on--
our class trip to Italy
is now spaghetti night
at Papa John’s,
and your $1,500 deposits
will not be refunded.
Ooh, Papa John’s!
We will conclude by
passing around a sheet
on which I would like
everyone’s e-mail address.
(groaning)
What’s wrong?
I can’t fill out
that clipboard.
I don’t have e-mail.
(crowd gasps)
Oh, Marge, you got
to get on the Net.
It’s got all the best
conspiracy theories.
Did you know that Hezbollah
owns Little Dolly Snack Cakes?
This stuff will
rock your world!
Fine, I’ll log onto
Wahoo or Yippy
or A-O-K or Pooka-dooka
or whatever it’s called.
Can we move this
meeting along?
I pay my taxes,
I expect my orange drink!
Ambrosia!
And this Web site
will tell you the weather.
Sunny?
I never have to look out
the window again.
♪ Let’s go surfing now,
everybody’s learning how ♪
♪ Come on and safari with me ♪
Paper towels
for 69 cents.
68 cents.
66 cents!
Kids, get
in the car!
We’re going
to Pennsylvania!
Ooh.
629,000 results?!
Wow.
And all this time,
I thought "Googling yourself"
meant the other thing.
It’s our house!
But what’s that thing?
(gasps)
Everyone can see you!
Get inside!
Never!
MARGE:
Just put on a towel!
HOMER: Why don’t I just
put on a dress?
(Homer grunting, panting)
(door opens)
FLANDERS: Homer,
you’ve met my parents.
HOMER: Not naked,
I haven’t.
That Internet
has it all.
Today, I found I had the same
birthday as Randy Quaid,
I MapQuested a great new
route to the armory,
and I got a list
of local houses
where I’m not letting you kids
trick or treat anymore.
I’m proud of you, Mom.
You’re like
Christopher Columbus.
You discovered
something
millions of people
knew about before you.
Hmm!
(crickets chirping)
(mouse clicks, Marge groans)
I sent everyone I know an e-card
for St. Patrick’s Day,
but not one person
wrote me back.
Hmm. Maybe
if I hit "Refresh."
(groans)
Still nothing.
But maybe now.
Or now.
(groans)
The only thing that changes
is the banner ad.
Hmm?
(groans)
Ooh.
Earthland Realms?
(tinny fanfare playing)
Earthland Realms
is a multiplayer
online role-playing game.
Do you agree to the following
terms and conditions?
"For amusement only.
Credit card information may be
sold to Korean gangsters."
(sighs)
Just click "Agree."
Step one,
create your character.
Let’s see.
What kind of
goofy goobly
should I be?
Whoa.
Look at those
bazooms.
Who designed
this character?
Probably a man.
Hmm! I can make her look
any way I want.
Let’s see.
Hair: blue.
Shoes: sensible.
Body type: Olive Oyl.
Face: other.
That’s better.
Now, let’s role... play.
Wow, it’s like
a Renaissance fair,
but without all
the chubby couples.
This is really annoying.
You’re telling me.
Greetings, Cleric.
Will you undertake
a quest on my behalf?
Eh, maybe I should run this
by my husband first.
Things are more fun
if you just answer "yes."
Then, yes.
Hither me forth
on mine arduous quest.
Once again,
just "yes."
Yes.
First, you must find
the Armandahl of Nuxinor.
All I see
is that rock.
You have found it!
Oh!
(typing)
Okay, activate
my level seven power stones.
Wield the orb
of oblivion.
And zap!
Hmm, needs
more goat soul.
BART: Mom?!
What are you kids
doing up so late?
We just got up.
It’s 7:00 a.m.
(gasps)
I was on the computer
all night!
Actually,
it’s Saturday.
(gasps)
I played a day
and a night.
Bart,
it’s not Saturday.
Shh.
I should
get some sleep.
(yawns)
I better check
on my elf-self.
(tinny fanfare playing)
(growls)
Thank you.
Come again.
Apu?
Mrs. Homer.
How nice to see
you in the Realms.
How did you
get in my game?
Are you a virus?
Oh, no.
I, too, am
online playing.
That cobra king
over there
is actually Snake.
The prison guards think I’m
getting my online law degree.
Ha, ha!
And that beguiling enchantress
is Mrs. Krabappel.
This game is a great way
to meet eligible men
who can afford
a computer.
(panting)
Or have access to one
at the school library.
It’s amazing how you can be
a turkey in every reality.
What’s important
is we’re talking.
I’m Moe.
I’m playing this
while I’m on the can.
Wow, Moe!
You’re a troll.
What? No.
My character’s supposed
to look like me.
Why does everyone keep
thinking I’m a troll?!
(muttering angrily)
(horse neighing)
(neighing)
(gasps)
Who are
we hiding from?
The Shadow Knight.
Where he rides, death
is sure to follow.
The Shadow Knight?
He’s the most evil,
destructive player in this game.
He once beat me to death
with my own life bar.
Mmm... mmm.
(booming voice): Who dares
battle with the Shadow Knight?
(sinister laugh)
(groaning)
Oh...
He was a good man.
A good, moist man.
Eww.
I can’t watch this.
BART: Another senseless
killing by...
the Shadow Knight!
Hmm?
(sinister laugh)
(gasps)
My son is
an evil knight!
The most successful evil knight
in all the Earthland Realms!
Not bad.
(booming voice):
Ay caramba, what a day!
Brave sir knight?
(normal voice): What
is it, Lady Milhouse?
I’m not a lady,
it’s a spell.
A spell you said
you’d reverse.
Yeah, yeah,
it’s on my list.
Anyway, someone’s here
to see you.
Hi, Bart!
It’s your mom!
I’m in your videogame
with you!
What?
(groans)
Why Milhouse,
don’t you look pretty!
It’s a spell!
And thank you.
Mom, what are you
doing in my game?!
How would you like it
if I suddenly started
going shopping with you?
I’d like that
very much.
(grunting)
Uh, wh-what can I get ya,
Mr. Shadow Knight, sir?
A grog? Grog light?
Uh, diet grog
with lemon?
Just wring the blood
from this pixie head.
Yes, sir.
Hi, everybody!
How do you play this game?
(moaning)
Ow!
(groaning)
Now flog yourself
with this mace
while reciting
the Goblin’s Code!
Goblin’s Code,
yes, sir!
All goblins must be free
of visible worms.
Oooh!
In the presence
of a lady,
a goblin must remove
his hat and ears.
(grunts)
(laughing)
Bart, are you
drinking?
Mom!
(laughing)
You’re making me
look bad
in front
of my minions!
If they think less of you
because of me,
then they’re not really
your minions.
(grunts)
I’m going off to explore
the Crevices of Lagrimmar.
Great, I’ll come
with you.
Shouldn’t you bundle up?
Here, let me enchant
your pants.
(grunts)
Hey, Lisa,
self-conscious
about your shins?
In my day, girls were worried
about their boobs.
Dad, I’m going
to play soccer.
I fell in love
with the game
when I saw
Bend It Like Beckham.
(Indian music plays)
Father, I am proud
of my cultural heritage,
but I also love soccer!
(cheering)
You tell him,
Jesminder!
I forbid you to bend
it like Beckham.
Plus, you must marry
this complete stranger.
His father is an important
business acquaintance of mine.
Love counts
for nothing!
You tell her,
Mr. Dhanabhai!
Business contacts are more
important than love!
(girls grunting)
Wait, that’s soccer?
I always called it
"human foosball."
Would you like me
to take you to your game?
You already promised
you would.
Aw, do I have to?
(girls grunting)
Uh-huh.
Okay, Morty,
I’ll tell them.
Sorry, ladies.
We got no referee,
so the game’s
been canceled.
(laughing)
I’m sorry.
I’m sure you’re
very disappointed.
(laughing)
What happened
to the ref?
He quit!
Being a ref is
a thankless job...
the parents hate ya...
the only upside is the kids
share their snack with you.
HOMER: Did someone
say "snack"?
I’ll be your ref!
(girls cheering)
Dad, where’d you get
that outfit?
I got fired from
Foot Locker.
♪ Kicks just keep getting harder
to find... ♪
What’s the
matter, buddy?
The American flag not
good enough for ya?
(grunts)
That was my father.
I’m your father now.
I’m open! I’m open!
♪ No, but not with kicks ♪
♪ You just need help, girl... ♪
(panting)
So... tired.
(vomiting)
Could someone bring me
another barf cone?
So... I thought
it went real well.
Until I swallowed
the whistle.
You don’t even
know the rules!
This could be
my new thing,
and you’re turning
it into a joke!
Hilarious joke?
Sadly, no.
I’m disappointed with the way
you acted today...
but I’m not
surprised.
(sighs)
(whistle blowing)
Oh, let’s see.
Should I take the Trail of
Death, or the Path of Doom?
Maybe I should
just go back.
(shrieks)
(gasps)
Is this Wall Street
Journal online?
(screams and groans)
Oof.
Well, well,
looks like
something’s finally about
to happen in this game.
Just in time.
I was about to go
to the Pottery Barn site
to get design ideas.
(metal clanging)
It’s the Shadow Knight!
Run!
I forget how to do that.
Control-shift-R...
(Dolph screaming)
Thank you, Bart.
This frame grab’s going
on my coffee cup.
You guys wanna meet
at the Kwik-E-Mart?
I’m in the tub right now.
I’m in Denmark!
GIRL: Let’s go,
come on!
(girls cheering)
Ow.
(whistle blowing)
Hand ball!
Direct kick!
Dad, I’m impressed!
You’ve become
a much better referee.
Thanks, honey.
After what you
said to me,
I watched hours
and hours of soccer.
I almost saw a goal!
But there were so many ads
for Spanish cell phones.
(panting)
Do it, sweetie!
Save our troubled
marriage!
(grunting)
(whistle blowing)
Foul on 23!
That’s crazy.
Your daughter
just tripped
on her own
clumsy feet!
Come on, Lisa.
Admit it!
Um, uh...
I’m a spectator addressing
a player-- answer me!
I said foul
on 23!
You are so blind,
even Jesus couldn’t
heal you!
Helen, please.
Don’t drop
the J bomb.
Well, I’m throwing you
both out of the game!
(both gasp)
(Lisa gasps)
Ow!
She tripped me.
Ow! Oh!
Ow!
(blows whistle)
Foul on the other girl.
Lisa gets
a penalty kick,
and every other kid has
to pay her a dollar.
That is an outrage!
Your daughter’s been
floppin’ all day!
She has not.
Your daughter’s a dirty player.
Sir, I have sired
a dum-dum, a mush-head,
a what’s-it, a dog boy,
and somethin’ with
a human face and fish body,
what we called Kevin,
but my young’uns is
not dirty players.
I don’t need a soccer lecture
from a hillbilly.
That’s hill-William
to you, sir.
How about
a lecture from me,
Ronaldo?
(gasps)
Ronaldo?!
Winner of two
World Cups
and three FIFA Player
of the Year awards?
Yes, I am
what you said.
Now I travel the world
exposing floppers,
and your daughter
is a flopper.
Now, Ronaldo away!
You heard
Geraldo.
What’s it
gonna be?
(sighs)
Yellow card!
You can’t give me
a yellow card.
You’re my father.
When I put on these shorts,
I’m not your father anymore,
and judging by how
tight they are,
I’m never going to be
anyone else’s, either.
(grunts)
This is what I think
of your yellow card!
Unsportsmanlike
conduct.
That’s a red card.
You’re out
of the game!
But... But...
Oh!
Another family broken
up by Ronaldo.
Yes!
What a fun quest!
Aren’t you glad I made you
take that nap in the middle?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let me just put this holy
grail in my trophy room.
Whoa!
Where’s all my stuff?!
I thought all the swords
and severed heads were kind
of gory, so I redecorated
using the Hello Kitty
expansion pack.
No!
Mom?
Mom?!
I was killed
by my own son.
How could you kill
your own mother?
It was just a game.
A game I used to enjoy
before you mommed all over it.
Lisa, sweetie,
I was just
following the rules.
Great.
The one time you actually
do something right,
you ruin my life.
(sobbing)
I think
I’ll go to bed.
It’s 5:00
in the afternoon.
Who cares? I’m dead.
Jumpin’ Johnnycakes!
Those dames
are cheesed.
Son, I’ll never understand
women if I live to be 40.
Big if.
You said it.
Enjoy me
while I last.
(both laughing)
(chuckles)
Want to go slam
a few beers?
Want to watch me?
You know it.
(glass squeaking)
What’s the matter,
Homer and Bart?
Lisa’s mad at me,
and Marge is mad at him.
Well, I’m just
the bartender here,
but it seems to me,
you could win Lisa back
by appealing to her
sense of reason,
and you can win
your mom back
by appealing
to her feelings.
Gee, Moe,
you give great advice.
Yeah. What have you done
with the real Moe?
(all laugh)
(grunting)
Lisa, honey,
I bought you something.
A DVD!
Not interested.
It’s a documentary
by the BBC,
in cooperation
with Canal Plus.
(gasps)
Give me, give me, give me.
(Homer laughs)
(whirring)
ANNOUNCER:
Brighton, England, 1985.
Manchester United plays
Sussexton Hamptonshire-on-Leith
when a deadly riot
breaks out in the stands.
Oi, your boy’s
a flopper, he is!
No, he isn’t,
he isn’t!
Your mother can
kiss me bum!
(grunting and clamoring)
(loud chatter
and blows hitting)
(poignant music plays)
ANNOUNCER:
22 years later,
this riot is still going on.
(clamoring voices)
(Lisa gasps)
ANNOUNCER:
Last year in Brazil,
an on-field scuffle
turned so violent,
locals say a statue
of the Virgin Mary came alive...
and beat the holy snot out
of everyone.
("Adagio For Strings" plays)
Oh.
Mom, I’m going
to give you life
the way I imagine
you gave me life--
by pressing
alt-F-5 repeatedly.
(electrical humming and popping)
(theme from X-Men plays)
(electrical humming continues)
(moaning)
(thudding)
Bart, you brought me
back to life!
As best you could.
Ha-ha!
(roller squeaking)
Sweetie, are you
here to forgive me?
No.
Oh! But to
get that DVD,
I had to become
a PBS subscriber.
Now I’m paying for crap
like American Masters.
(sobbing)
Dad, I can’t
forgive you,
because there’s
nothing to forgive.
Huh?!
You were right
to kick me out of that game.
Soccer was
making me insane,
just as it did the continents
of Europe and South America.
Those places
are pretty terrible.
So from now on,
I’ll play soccer
for the same reason
I study chemistry--
for fun.
Do you want
to play a little?
I sure do.
Wait till I tell
the other moms
you gave
two-thirds
of your life
force to save me.
What a good boy.
(pounding on door)
This way.
Slay him and take
his experience points!
(all grunting)
Wait. Stop!
If you kill me, I’ll egg
your houses in real life!
It’s still
worth it.
(grunts)
I live in a loft!
Ow!
My jewels!
All right! I got
his flame sword!
(laughs)
(grunts)
Aw, come on.
Ew!
(pastoral music plays)
♪ The Shadow Knight
shall rule no more ♪
♪ We’ve spilt his blood
upon the floor ♪
♪ With a hi and a ho
and a trolly lolly lay ♪
♪ It’s the jolly merry
month of May! ♪
(sighs)
Don’t worry, honey.
I’ll hunt down our friends
who murdered you...
one by one.
Whatever.
I’m gonna go
play outside.
(laughter)
(blows whistle)
Look what I can do!
(grunts)
(laughs)
I have taught you well.
(echoing):
Too well.
Mom, are you sure you
don’t want to play?
No, no. I’m fine.
(grunting)
Why am I paying
$14.95 a month for this?
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Shh!
Enhanced by Fotokem