(theme music playing)
CHORUS: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
(screams)
Ugh! Salisbury soup again?
My joe isn't sloppy enough.
And talk about weak coffee.
I'll take that.
What are they doing with our 45 cents?
(groans)
I bought my lunch at the gas station.
It's the kind John Glenn eats
when he's not in space.
(hissing)
Wow! Just like the commercial.
There's a brainteaser on the back.
"Professor Provolone's Picto-Puzzle!"
MARTIN: That's a tough one.
-Got it!
-Is this it?
Excellent, Milhouse.
How 'bout this?
Nice work, Bart.
How 'bout you, Lisa?
I'll get it in a second. Don't worry.
Oh! Of course.
It's-- (whispering)
Yeah! Champion of the world!
Answer this, Professor.
(grunting)
Hey! Some of us
are still trying to solve it.
Just you.
Maybe I can't concentrate
because of all your cooties!
It's called lice. And it's nothing
to be ashamed of.
(scratching)
-(school bell rings)
-(cheering)
LISA: OK, let's see. It's not Egyptian.
-It's not Prince's names.
-(foot steps)
Uh--
-Want a hint?
-I don't need a hint, Ralph.
But you're suffering.
(Lisa groans)
So, Lisa. Did you get
that brainteaser yet?
For your information,
none of your business.
You look tired. Are ya tired, Lisa?
(sighs) If you're suggesting
I stayed up all night
trying to solve that childish puzzle,
you're right.
-(clatter)
-Ah. Now I can't remember my combination.
Look at my "aggie-culture" project.
It's a piece of a cow.
(gasps) The project.
I forgot all about it.
Very nice, Janie.
Good use of pipe cleaners, Becky.
(buzzing)
Don't open it, Ralph.
I'll just give you a C-minus.
Yay!
-Not finished, Lisa?
-I'm finished. I just got to--
(grunts) There. It's a pig!
It's an eraser with pushpins.
And a spring for his curly tail.
(laughs) Oink, oink, oink.
This is terrible at best.
I'm surprised at you, Lisa.
Me too.
Oh, it looks like somebody's
"hogging Dazs" ice cream.
(laughs) I should write this down.
-More coming.
-(door dings)
Um, I'm looking for something
in an after-dinner burrito.
You'll have it in 45 seconds, sir.
(beeping)
To pass the time,
please enjoy this novelty pen.
Why would I want to
look at a pen with a-- (gasps)
Oh, no! Her clothes are coming off!
(chuckles) Hey, you know
who would love this?
Men.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Liftoff!
(moans)
Look at this mess.
Where is that elderly old man?
Old man! Old m--
(screams)
Hey, look. A freezer man!
-Wait a minute. There is a note.
-Oh.
"I have frozen myself so I may live to see
the wonders of the future.
Thaw me out when robot wives
are cheap and effective.
P.S. Please alter my pants
as fashion dictates."
(saxophone playing)
(off-key)
Now you're swinging, honey.
(scatting off-key)
Darn it!
Oh, no! No, no!
The George Raft look is dead.
I wanted Audie Murphy!
If you would just apologize to Louie,
you could get your hair cut
the way you want.
No apology! Not until he admits
he's a jerk!
Mom, I think something's wrong with me.
I can't do anything right lately.
You're just having a bad day.
I had one last week.
I burned the roast. My cake fell.
And I ran out of butter, so I had to spray
the English muffins with PAM.
Maybe you're just a lousy cook. Ow!
MARGE: I'll go get the Bactine.
It can't just be a bad day.
I feel like I'm getting
dumber by the minute.
Oh, ain't no big deal.
All Simpsons start to lose
their smarts around your age.
-What are you talking about?
-Well, I'll show ya.
Follow me.
Wow! Dad was a good speller?
Oh, your dad used to be smart as a monkey.
Then his mind started getting lazy
and now he's dumb as a chimp.
-Grampa!
-Hey, I am, too.
Your brother's coming along nicely.
Look at Bart's homework.
Back when he was your age,
he was smart as a chimp.
(gasps) This is just two years ago!
That's right. Then the Simpson genes
kicked in.
This is crazy. Just because you and Dad
and Bart went downill
doesn't mean it's gonna happen to me.
-Does it?
-Sure!
But it doesn't mean you can't live a long
and pointless life.
(groans)
Dear Log, can it be true?
Do all Simpsons go through
a process of "dumbening"?
Wait. That's not how
you spell "dumbening."
Wait. "Dumbening" isn't even a word!
Ugh.
(groans) I've got to find out more.
(voices shouting)
(grunting, laughing)
That makes 22 to 16.
Time is running out.
(Dr. Hibbert laughing) So you're worried
about your genes, huh?
Well, does it hurt when you go like this?
-No.
-Then will you turn
this projector on for me?
I think the film should answer
all your questions.
(introductory music plays)
MCCLURE (narrating): Have you ever
wondered why fat parents have fat children
or why Chinese parents
have Chinese children?
It's no coincidence. It's because of
D.N.A.
Hi. I'm Troy McClure.
-(alarm blares)
-(men shouting)
You may remember me from such medical
films as Alice Doesn't Live Anymore
and Mommy, What's Wrong
with that Man's Face?
But, Mr. McClure, what is D.N.A.?
What the-- Oh, hi, Billy.
Let's find out together.
D.N.A. is God's recipe for making you.
(soundtrack music stuttering)
You take a dash of Dad, a pinch of Mom...
then we bake for nine months, and--
Mmm. That's good Billy.
Mr. McClure, what does D.N.A. stand for?
(stuttering)
That didn't answer anything.
-I need more information.
-Would you like to see it again?
Isn't there any way I can change my D.N.A.
like sitting on the microwave?
Hmm. Not according to any movie
I've ever seen.
I'm afraid you're stuck
with your genes, Lisa.
(chuckling)
-(door dings)
-Hi, frozen body.
-(thumps)
-Hmm. He's got a lob...
but I don't hear a dob.
-(thumps)
-Oh. Uh, there it is.
You're lucky he's still alive.
This freezer is an attractive nuisance.
Just look at all that ice cream.
It's damn near irresistible.
Well, we better leave him in there.
Moving him now could kill him
and tire us out.
NELSON: Check it out!
-A freezer geezer.
-Please, young customers,
ignore the frozen gentleman,
and return to your impulse buying.
Aw, but we wanna stare at the ice dude.
-We'll give ya a buck.
-No. This is a convenience store...
not a freak show.
$1.20?
-(carnival music playing)
-Come one, come all.
See the amazing frozen man.
Also gaze at the Frito
found in a bag of Doritos.
Marvel at the floor
that just won't come clean!
(thinking) Dear Log, my worst fears
have been confirmed.
I've hit my mental and creative peak
at the tender age of eight.
What will my life be like after I descend
into mediocrity?
-(clank)
-(laughing)
Oh.
-(clank)
-(laughing)
(thinking) Well, Ralph seems happy enough.
Maybe I should just give up now
and settle into a mindless, happy stupor.
ANNOUNCER 1 (on TV): We now return to
When Buildings Collapse on Nonstop Fox.
-(building collapses)
-(Homer and Bart laughing)
(cheering)
-(Bart and Homer whooping)
-(groans)
Hey, Lise, wanna join us?
Room for one more.
We're watching the TV.
NARRATOR (on TV): Man has always loved
his buildings.
But what happens when the buildings say,
"No more"?
(triumphant music plays)
HOMER: Yes! (laughs)
-(both laughing)
-HOMER: Oh! Ooh!
Yeah! (laughing)
(cheering)
HOMER: I didn't think
it was gonna fall over.
-Yeah!
-Whoo! Whoo! Whoo!
(show ends)
The best part was
when the buildings fell down.
Yeah. Ha. Maybe people got hurt.
Hey, yeah. (chortling)
ANNOUNCER 2 (on TV): And now,
a Channel 6 editorial reply.
(singsong) Boring!
ANNOUNCER 3 (on TV): And now,
When Surgery Goes Wrong.
All right. Sounds good.
(carnival music playing)
-Behold the can of mystery!
-(crowd murmurs)
The label vanished many years ago.
What strange wonders lie inside?
Treasure, dog food?
Whoa! Some things man
is not meant to know.
ROD AND TODD (reading): "Show me your"--
-Hey!
It says, "Show me your tie."
It's cute. Come on. Let's go.
Me and Frostillicus go back a long way.
I used to share a bathroom
with Frostillicus.
In fact, I got
a real funny story about that.
Actually, it's not
so much funny as it is long.
It seems that there was this...
Whoo! What a gold mine!
(gasps) Oh, my goodness!
(whistling)
Boy, seeing that
stomach surgery made me hungry.
Marge, we need
5,000 c.c.'s of snacks, stat!
No snacks. Dinner will be ready
in three minutes.
(all three groaning)
If she started dinner three minutes
earlier, we wouldn't be in this mess.
BART: Relax, Lise.
Dad and I always have a plan "B."
(gulping, chewing)
Pretty neat, huh?
But those candy bars
are all squished and melted.
-Wha--
(muffled) Come on, Lisa. Join your family.
(whimpering)
-(kids crying)
-Quit it!
-Quit it.
-(dog barking)
(in Southern accent)
Quit-- You kids knock it off.
Mama's watching her stories.
(fly buzzing)
Hi, honey. It's me, your husband, Ralph.
Hey, angel pie. Can you drive me down
to the libarry?
I wanna rent us up some movies.
(groaning)
Wesley, get mama's pryirng bar.
Easy does it now. Easy. Little more.
Yeah... right... that's the spot.
-(grunts)
-I'll get your coat.
-(normal accent) No!
-No what?
-I don't wanna turn out that way.
-What way, angel pie?
Like you!
Lisa, come on.
Your tomato soup is getting a skin on top.
Fine. She doesn't get her skin.
Lisa insulted us, Mom.
She thinks she is so great.
I'll dance on her grave.
-Bart!
-What? Oh, napkin. Right.
(thinking) Dear Log, it won't be long now
before my mind melts
into a soft, Simpsony sludge.
Soon, the arts and literature
I love will be replaced
by talk radio and vulgar mud flaps.
It's time to give my brain its last meal.
Oh, Kenny. Look at the interplay
of light and shadow.
It's so luminous and vibrant!
(laughs) Thanks, Lisa. I painted that one.
(lowers voice)
The real one's in my garage.
(violin plays)
Hmm. Sounds like she's hitting a baby
with a cat.
You have to listen
to the notes she's not playing.
(scoffs) I can do that at home.
(door dings)
Son, I represent a group of oil tycoons
who make foolish purchases.
We already bought us
a stained glass bathrobe
and the world's fattest racehorse.
Now we need your Ice Man.
Oh, no. I could never sell him.
He's like a frozen father to me.
-How much for just the head?
-(cracking)
(Jasper moans)
By gum, it worked.
I've awakened in the future.
"Moon Pie."
What a time to be alive.
Hey, who unplugged my freezer?
Return to your state
of living death at once, sir.
Is that you, Apu?
Whoa! Time has ravaged
your once-youthful looks.
-(door dings)
-(grunts)
Ah, well, Sanjay. That is the end
of our freak show.
We must relinquish the giddy glamour
of show business
and return to the humble pleasures
of the neighborhood shopkeeper.
-Hmm.
♪ That's the way,
uh-huh, uh-huh, I like it ♪
Time traveler discount?
Come on in!
-Great set.
-Oh, thanks.
But the crowd kept looking at me like
I was using too many augmented ninths.
Aw, they just came for the buffalo wings.
But you really got through to me.
Oh, good. I figure if you've got
something special to say,
you have to share it with the world.
Yeah. While you still can. Thanks.
(running footsteps)
Damn. That felt like a sale.
I'm sorry, little girl.
We don't just put people on TV.
Unless, of course, they're replying
to an editorial.
Uh, I am! I'm strongly opposed to...
Proposition, uh, 305!
You're against discount
bus fares for war widows?
-Uh, you bet I am.
-OK. Makeup.
I'm getting worried about Lisa.
She's been gone for hours.
If I were her, I'd be buying me
a great big chocolate apology cake.
Authorities believe
the wave of towel snappings will get worse
before it gets better.
And now, with an editorial reply,
here's a small girl.
Hello. My name is Lisa Simpson.
(gasps)
I'm supposed to talk to you
about Proposition 305.
Mooching war widows.
But I have something
more important to say.
For reasons beyond my control,
I will soon become
vapid, sluggish and slow-witted.
So before that happens,
I want to share some things
with you that have meant a lot to me.
What is she doir out there?
I'll cut off her mike.
No, no, no. Let her speak.
I'm trying to get fired.
And please don't deprive yourself
of wonderful books like
To Kill a Mockingbird, Harriet the Spy
and Yertle the Turtle,
possibly the best book ever written
on the subject of turtle stacking.
She's got that right.
Beauty is all around us, and not just
in pageants and parlors.
You can find it in the swirl of galaxies
or the swirl in the center of a sunflower.
That's a good idea. Let's go out
for some frosty swirls.
Homer, your daughter
is pouring her heart out.
-We'll tape it.
-Why's she saying all this? Is she dying?
Oh, she's just upset 'cause I told her
her brains turning to mush.
You know, on account of the Simpson gene.
Simpson gene? That's just foolishness!
No. Baldness, too.
So please, I beg you,
don't take your brain for granted.
It's the best friend you'll ever have.
(clears throat)
Little girl... likes her brain.
What's your opinion?
(scoffs) Simpson gene.
Somebody's gotta set that girl straight
and I know how to do it.
Marge, get me your address book,
four beers and my conversation hat.
-(snoring)
-Lisa. Lisa, honey, wake up.
(yawns) Why bother?
Because your father
has a big surprise for you.
-I'm adopted?
-Better. Come look.
Lisa, it's me, Daddy. Your father.
I rounded up every Simpson
in the tri-city area
so I can prove to you there's nothing
wrong with the Simpson genes.
This is your great-uncle Chet.
Go ahead, Chet. Tell her what you do.
I run an unsuccessful shrimp company.
Oh. But... you run it, right?
-Oh, yeah.
-OK.
Uh, this is your second-cousin Stanley.
Um, I shoot birds at the airport.
Everybody hates birds, right?
(whimpers) Well,
you look pretty successful.
Thanks. I play a millionaire at parties.
At least I'd like to.
You probably should have
researched this first, eh, Dad?
What about you?
Well, sir, I step in front of cars
and sue the drivers.
I beg celebrities for money.
-I'm a prison snitch.
-Jug band manager.
-My legs hurt.
-(groans)
Oh, Lisa's right. We're nothing
but a big bunch of losers.
Show's over, folks. Go home!
What about our five bucks?
You get it after you leave.
Now get outta here.
(voices mumbling)
Wait a minute, Homer.
You didn't ask everybody.
What about the women?
Fine, fine.
What do you do, "Dr. Simpson"?
-Doctor?
-That's right.
I'm Chief of Complicated Surgery
at the InvasiCare Clinic.
That means you went to college, right?
You have to
if you want to be an architect.
Or an environmental lawyer.
Or Regional Sales Coordinator
for the third largest distributor...
of bunk and trundle beds.
Oh! Did you hear that, Lisa?
So all the Simpson women turn out OK.
That's right, sweetie.
The defective Simpson gene
is on the "Y" chromosome,
so only men are affected.
(both growling)
-Yeah!
So I'm not doomed!
Oh, Dad, I've never been happier
to be your daughter!
Oh, thanks, honey. Remember...
there's nothing that says you can't be
a Simpson and a success.
Unless you're a man.
So wait a minute.
This means I'm gonna be a failure?
Yes, son. A spectacular failure.
(grunts)
(Lisa thinking)
Dearest Log, I am me again!
And I feel like
there's nothing I can't do.
Except this stupid braintea--
(gasps)
I got it! Whoo-hoo!
I mean, splendid.
(theme music playing)
-(murmuring)
-Shh!
Captioned by
Visual Data Media Services