♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
(music repeats)
-Here we go!
-Come on, come on!
All right,
everybody got their ticket?
Then get ready for today's
super-Barto jackpot drawing.
Come on, cantaloupe.
And 'round
and 'round she...
Uh-oh.
(buzzing)
(screaming)
No refunds.
Force majeure.
Read the back of your ticket.
(groaning)
Oh... $900?
Well, we'll have to dip into
the retirement fund again.
(grunting)
(clattering)
Aw, nuts.
Hello?
China?
A little help?
Well, I never thought
it would come to this,
but I guess
we'll have to sell
Grandma's Civil War doll.
Mom, are you sure
you want to sell
a family heirloom
to pay the gas bill?
I mean, what would
your grandma say?
I'm sure
she'd be proud
that her descendants
had piping hot tap water
and plenty of warm,
dry underwear.
That is so true.
Hmm, these campaign buttons
are all partisan.
Don't you have
any neutral ones?
"May the better man win"?
"Let's have a good,
clean election"?
That sort of thing?
No, but we do have
some old shirt buttons.
They're kind of kooky
and fun.
Missy, you just
talked yourself
right out of a sale.
Hey, Lise, check it out,
pogo stilts.
These were banned
in all 50 states.
HOMER: Ow! Ohh!
What happened?
Wow, an actual robot
from the movie
"Clank, Clank,
You're Dead."
Think of how awful
it would be
for the poor
midget inside.
Oh, boo-hoo.
That's what they
get paid for.
(gasps)
Oh, Homer, look!
A TV guide
owned by Jackie O!
Oh, you should see
the crossword puzzle.
She thought that Mindy
lived with "Mark."
Give her a break.
Her husband was killed.
Oh, I know.
Wasn't that awful?
Hi, I'm John.
Can I help you with anything?
Yes, I have something
that I'd like to sell.
Please tell me
it's your hair.
(giggling)
No. It's an heirloom
my grandmother
passed down to me,
a very rare old figurine
from the Civil War.
Please don't construe
our ownership of this
as an endorsement
of slavery.
Hmm.
Well, see,
here's the thing on this.
It's a Johnny Reb bottle,
early 1970s.
One of the J&R Whiskey
"Liquor Lads."
Two books of green stamps,
if I'm not mistaken.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, no,
no, no, no.
It's a very,
very old figurine.
No, it's a liquor bottle.
See?
Ah, that will make
your bull run.
(murmuring sadly)
Well, I guess it'll
always be a monument
to Grandma's secret
drinking problem.
Okay, so maybe that thing's
a hunk of junk,
but look at what
you're selling.
50 bucks for a toy?
No kid is worth that.
Oh, but this is the Rex Mars
Atomic Discombobulator.
Don't you just love
the graphics on this box?
No.
How you can you love a box
or a toy or graphics?
You're a grown man.
It's camp.
The tragically ludicrous?
The ludicrously tragic?
Oh, yeah.
Like when a clown dies.
Well, sort of...
But I mean more like
inflatable furniture
or "Last Supper" TV trays,
or even this bowling shirt.
Can you believe somebody
gave this to Goodwill?
(murmuring sheepishly)
And that kind of stuff
is worth money?
Boy, howdy.
Man, you should come over
to our place.
It's full of valuable,
worthless crap.
Well, if you're
inviting me over...
I practically insist.
Shall we say 5:00?
The snacking hour?
My heart is palpitating.
Woo-hoo!
Pimento nose and voila.
Mommy's patented
happy-cracker snack platter.
(doorbell rings)
Ding-dong.
Classic.
I mean, that says
it all, doesn't it?
Oh, man, you weren't kidding
about this place.
Well,
I just love it.
Do I know you?
Oh, the color scheme
and the rabbit ears.
And the 2.3 children.
I mean, where's the Hi-C?
Hi-C
and fluffernutters.
Oh!
And pearls
on a little girl.
It's a fairy tale.
Oh.
Oh, I've got the exact
same curtains,
only in my bathroom.
Didn't you just die
when you found these?
Not really.
They just had corn on them.
Kitchen? Corn?
Oh!
(giggles)
(chuckles)
Oww!
Why you little--
Aaah! Dad! Dad!
Company! Company!
Oh. I'll just be
another minute, John.
Have a seat.
(choking)
So do those records
have camp value?
Everything here does.
You yourself are worth
a bundle, Homer.
Why, I could wrap a bow
around you
and slap on a price tag.
♪ I love the night life
I love to boogie ♪
Come on, Homer,
join the party.
♪ On the disco... ♪
Mom, John loves Itchy
and Scratchy
as much as we do--
Maybe more.
Yeah, and he collects
toy robots.
He is quite a charmer.
Your father's certainly
taken a shine to him.
Oh, Homer,
you are the living end.
(both laughing)
Oh!
That John is the greatest guy
in the world.
We've got to have him
and his wife over
for drinks sometime.
Mmm, I don't think
he's married, Homer.
Oh, a swinging bachelor, eh?
Well, there's lots
of foxy ladies out there.
Homer, didn't John
seem a little...
festive to you?
Couldn't agree more.
Happy as a clam.
He prefers
the company of men.
Who doesn't?
Homer,
listen carefully--
John is a ho-mo--
Right.
...sexual.
(screams)
Oh my God, Oh my God,
Oh my God,
Oh, my God!
I danced with a gay.
Marge, Lisa, promise me
you won't tell anyone.
Promise me!
You're being ridiculous.
Am I, Marge? Am I?
Think of the property values.
Now we can never say
only straight people
have been in this house.
I'm very sorry
you feel that way,
because John invited us
all out for a drive today,
and we're going.
Whoa-ho-ho. Not me.
And not because John's gay,
but because he's a sneak.
He should have the good taste
to mince around
and let everyone know
that he's that way.
What on earth are
you talking about?
You know me, Marge.
I like my beer cold,
my TV loud,
and my homosexuals
fa-laming.
(horn honking
"Over the Rainbow")
Zzzapp!
(gasps)
Homer, at least come out
and say hello.
-No. Nuh-uh. No.
-Oh, come on.
-Oh, no.
-You liked John this morning.
No! I am not setting
foot outside this house
until that man is gone.
Oh! Dad,
you are the living end.
Hey, where'd that cool,
creepy Santa come from?
Japan. Except over there,
they call him
"Annual Gift-man"
and he lives on the moon.
JOHN:
And that's where Kent Brockman
was caught cheating
in the Springfield marathon.
-Whoa.
-Ooh. Oh.
And there's where
Lupe Velez
bought the toilet
she drowned in.
ALL: Oh! Oh!
BART:
That was a killer tour, man.
I never realized
how many celebrities
humiliated themselves
right in our own backyard.
This is a sordid little burg,
isn't it?
Makes me sick
in a wonderful, wonderful way.
-John.
-Oh... Waylon.
I'd like you
to meet the Simpsons.
I know the Simpsons.
So this is your
sick mother?
Don't do this
to me, Waylon.
(laughing)
How'd it go?
Tell me everything
that happened.
He didn't give you gay,
did he? Did he?
Oh, jeez, Louise!
You don't even know
what you're worried about anymore.
John's a witty,
urbane person.
Oh, and I'm not.
Hey, Dad, look
what I got.
Zzzapp. Zzzapp.
Zzzapp... Zzzapp...
Bart! Where'd you
get that shirt?
I don't know.
Came out of the closet.
Uh... huh.
I hope
you all saved room,
because I made
your favorite dessert.
Store-bought snack cakes--
Both kinds.
Hmm, hmm.
Hmm...
(gasps)
(Homer mumbling)
Homie, I can hear you
chewing on your pillow.
What's wrong?
Marge, the boy was wearing
a Hawaiian shirt.
So?
There's only two kinds of guys
who wear those shirts:
gay guys and big,
fat party animals.
And Bart doesn't look like
a big, fat party animal to me.
So if you wore a Hawaiian shirt
it wouldn't be gay?
Right.
Thank you.
I hope you realize
this is all your fault.
I mean, do you have to be
so effeminate around the boy?
Homer, I don't think
there's a problem with Bart
but if there is,
it's probably because
you're not spending
any time with him.
Good night.
("It's In His Kiss" playing)
All right, boy, come on.
Today we're going to--
-(screams)
-♪ Or is it in his face? ♪
♪ Oh, no,
it's just his charm ♪
Gonna what, Homer?
♪ Oh, no that's... ♪
(record scratches)
And Helen Lovejoy,
sure, she looks blonde,
but I've heard cuffs
and collar don't match,
if you get my drift.
I don't,
but I loved hearing it.
You!
I should have known.
Well, good morning,
sunshine.
Homer, John brought us
cactus candy.
Look, John, you seem like
a perfectly nice guy and all.
Just stay the hell away
from my family.
Well, now you don't
get any candy.
-No, that's cruel. Take a teensy piece.
-No.
Homer, what have you
got against gays?
You know. It's...
It's not... usual.
If there was a law,
it would be against it.
Oh, Homer, please--
You're embarrassing yourself.
No, I'm not, Marge!
They're embarrassing me.
They're embarrassing America.
They turned the navy
into a floating joke.
They ruined all our best names,
like Bruce and Lance and Julian.
Those were the toughest
names we had.
Now they're just... uh...
-Queer?
-Yeah, and that's another thing.
I resent you people
using that word.
That's our word
for making fun of you.
We need it.
Well, I'm taking back our word,
and I'm taking back my son.
Don't worry, boy.
We're going to
set you straight.
By tomorrow morning,
you'll be a regular
Burt Reynolds.
What are you talking about,
Homer? Where are we going?
Just a couple of good,
old-fashioned manly places...
Father and son.
HOMER'S BRAIN: You're leaving
the arm there too long.
You want
to make it worse?
No! No! He'll know
you're onto him.
Quick, shake his hand.
Just remember, son,
whatever happens
I'll always love you.
As? As?
As a father. A father.
Regular father.
Whew.
What am I supposed
to do here?
Nothing.
Just sit. I'll be back.
Well, it's been two hours.
How do you feel?
I don't know.
I kind of want a cigarette.
That's a good start.
Let's get you a pack.
What's your brand?
Anything slim.
Okay, that didn't work.
But I know
something that will.
(machinery clanking)
Bart, I want you
to shake hands with--
What's your name, fellow?
-Roscoe.
-Roscoe, here, runs this mill.
He's going to show us around
and let you get
a first-hand look
at real, all-American Joes
doing what they do best.
Why the hell would
I want to see that?
You'll thank me
on your wedding night.
Hey! Listen up!
I want all of youse to say
hello to the Simpsons.
TOGETHER:
♪ Hell-o-o ♪
(gasps)
Has the whole world
gone insane?
(lisping) Stand still.
There's a spark in your hair.
Get it, get it!
(whimpering)
Hot stuff
coming through.
Dad, why did you bring me
to a gay steel mill?
I don't know.
This is a nightmare!
You're all sick!
Oh, be nice.
Oh... My son doesn't stand
a chance.
The whole world's gone gay!
(factory whistle)
Oh, my God,
what's happening now?
We work hard,
we play hard.
(dance music playing)
♪ Everybody dance now ♪
(moaning)
♪ Everybody dance now! ♪
And the entire steel mill
was gay.
Where you been,
Homer?
Entire
steel industry's gay.
Aerospace, too,
and the railroads.
And you know what else?
Broadway.
I always thought
Bart would grow up
to be just like us.
What happened?
Oh, it ain't
no mystery.
Whole modern world's got
a swishifying effect on kids today,
and their MTVs
and their diet sodas
ain't going to set them
straight neither.
You got to do it yourself,
Homer and you gotta do it fast.
What would turn Bart
into a man fast?
You have to think for me.
Well,
let's see now...
Time was, you'd send
a boy off to war.
Shooting a man
would fix him right up,
but there's not even
any wars no more
thank you very much,
Warren Christopher.
Better yet,
Bart could shoot a deer.
That's like shooting
a beautiful man.
Hey, he's right,
Homer.
After the boy
bags a deer,
all the diet sodas in the world
won't turn him back.
Then you just
sit back
and watch the grandkids
roll in.
Hunting, eh?
(laughter)
(growling)
Stand aside, Marge.
I'm taking the boy
deer hunting.
He's going to grow up
straight for once.
What?
You never went hunting before,
and you're
perfectly straight.
Oh, yeah? How long
since you've had a baby?
But, Dad,
it's barbaric.
How does killing a deer
make you more of a man?
It just does.
Name me one gay Indian.
Uh-oh. Something's
going to die.
Butt out, buttinsky.
What would you know
about hunting?
I know this much.
I wouldn't wear that hideous hat.
Here. Take this one.
It was worn
by Yale Summers in "Daktari."
Hang on to it, toy-boy
you might need it
when it starts
raining naked ladies.
Today you're going
to be a man, Bart.
You guys going
to teach me to drive?
Oh, yeah. Let a twinkle-toes
drive Betsy. Right.
(nervous laughing)
No, boy.
You can't drive.
You're only ten.
You're going hunting.
You ever been hunting
before, there, Barty?
Nope. Something
about a bunch of guys
alone together
in the woods...
Seems kind of gay.
That is a very immature
attitude, young man.
Remember, guys, the truck
only holds six carcasses,
so don't shoot nothing
but trophy bucks, huh?
Aw, we should have
just stayed at the bar
and shot some rats.
Hey, those ain't
your rats, Barn.
Well, Homie, you ready
to call it quits?
Oh, but... Wait a minute.
Bart's not fixed yet.
He hasn't even...
Homer...
Ohh...
Come on, don't take
it so hard, Homer.
You still got
that other kid--
Uh... Lisa.
Let's, uh, take her out
hunting tomorrow,
make her into a man.
Aw, she'd never go.
She's a vegetarian.
Oh, jeez! Homer, jeez!
You and Marge ain't
cousins, are you?
No. This whole thing
is my fault.
I've been a lousy Dad.
(gasps)
Cheer up, Homer.
Christmas is coming
early this year.
JOHN: Did he say
where were they going?
No. They were just going
to find a deer
and make Bart
shoot it.
Deer? Ha!
Not around here.
They all migrated north
when the state park
converted to astroturf.
But if there's
no deer out there
then what are they hunting?
The only thing around here
that's even close to deer is...
Hey, boy, wake up.
Your old man
found some deer.
Huh? You did?
Wait, man,
those are reindeer.
-(gun cocks)
-Yeah. And it's your shot, son.
What? I'm not going to shoot
a reindeer in a pen.
Come on, Bart.
Be a sport
and kill Blitzen, okay?
Dad!
Aw, criminy,
here come the waterworks.
Bart, I'm going
to turn my back,
and when I turn around,
I want to see
a whole pile
of dead reindeer!
(loud bang)
That a way, son!
You made your old man proud.
I didn't do anything.
(bang)
Hey, they're going nuts
like in those nature films!
Ah, must be mating season.
(all screaming)
Dad, I'm scared.
Me, too, son.
No, don't.
You have to protect
yourself!
Son, there comes a time
in every father's life
when he must...
(grunting)
Dad, are you hurt?
Just my bones and organs.
-(snorts)
-(grunting)
D'oh!
("Jingle bells" playing)
MECHANICAL VOICE:
Ho, ho, ho!
What the--
Bart, look!
It's Santa Claus!
Whoa! It's Santa,
all right,
and he is kicking ass!
MECHANICAL VOICE:
Ho, ho, ho! Ho, ho, ho!
It's a miracle!
JOHN: No-- Ultrasuede
is a miracle.
This is just good timing.
(groaning)
Oh, Homie, I'm so glad
you're safe.
Hmm, you feel softer
than before.
I've been tenderized.
How'd you know
that thing would work?
Well, the sound
is just brutal,
and I figured reindeer
would naturally be afraid
of their cruel master,
Santa Claus.
I mean,
wouldn't you be? Ha!
Is it okay to come out now,
Mr. Gay Man, sir?
I'll do anything
you say. Anything.
Aw, Moe, we were saved
by a sissy.
Yeah, yeah.
We'll never live it down.
Oh, boy, it looks like
it's suicide again for me.
Hey! We owe this guy,
and I don't want you
calling him a sissy.
This guy's a fruit,
and a...
No, wait, wait, wait.
Queer, queer, queer.
That's what you like
to be called, right?
Well, that or John.
This is about
as tolerant as Dad gets,
so you should be flattered.
Great!
Well, Homer,
I won your respect
and all I had to do
was save your life.
Now, if every gay man
could just do the same,
you'd be set.
Amen to that.
You know, Bart,
maybe it's just
the concussion talking,
but any way you choose
to live your life
is okay with me.
Huh?
(whispering)
He thinks you're gay.
He thinks I'm gay?
♪♪
♪ Everybody dance now ♪
♪ Here is the dome
back with the bass ♪
♪ The jam is live in effect
and I don't waste time ♪
♪ On the mike
with a dope rhyme ♪
♪ Jump to the rhythm, jump,
Jump to the rhythm, jump ♪
♪ And I'm here to combine
beats and lyrics ♪
♪ To make you shake your pants,
take a chance ♪
♪ Come on and dance,
guys, grab a girl ♪
♪ Don't wait,
make her twirl ♪
♪ It's your world
and I'm just a squirrel ♪
♪ Trying to get a nut
to move your butt ♪
♪ To the dance floor
so yo, what's up? ♪
♪ Hands in the air,
come on, say yeah ♪
♪ Everybody over here,
everybody over there ♪
♪ The crowd is live
and I pursue this groove ♪
♪ Party people in the house,
move! ♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.