CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
(whistle blows)
(playing blues)
(tires screeching)
D’oh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
Hey!
(machine whirring)
(squeaking)
(humming)
Ooh, the new issue
of Smothering Mother Magazine.
Hmm...
"Are Bees Building Hives
in your Diaper Genie?
The Deadly Truth about Oxygen."
(gasps)
"Is your Baby a Suckaholic?
Experts see new links
between pacifier overuse and...
(gasps)
...low achievement."
(sucking)
Maggie, honey, this
is for your own good.
Growing up means giving up
everything that
makes you happy.
It’s true. I’ve given up
everything but raisins.
And the doctor says
they’re killing me.
Sweet, plump coffin nails
is what they are.
(groans)
(loud crash, meowing)
(whimpering)
(crashing continues)
(toy clicking)
Maggie, I’m sorry
you miss your pacifier.
But when a mother
makes a decision,
she has to stick by it.
(gasping)
Okay, okay,
you can have it back!
(groans)
(doll groans)
Oh!
(banging)
I can’t believe you
listened to this magazine.
It’s a Larry Flynt
publication!
Lisa, stop reading mastheads.
I can’t. I won’t!
(growling)
Where’s your father
with those pacifiers?
I couldn’t find Maggie’s brand,
but I got every other
kind I could find.
How about Syntho-Nip?
Kiddy Cork?
Thumbstitute?
AccuTeat?
Bink 182?
Want to suck
on the receipt?
(crying continues)
Make her stop!
You make her stop!
I’ve had her all day!
-I can’t take it anymore!
-Larry Flynt?
Larry Flynt? Larry Flynt?
Larry Flynt,
Larry Flynt, Larry Flynt?!
(crying stops, dog pants)
(toy squeaking)
ALL:
Ooh!
(panting)
Good work, boy.
Just for that, we’re going
to treat your heart murmur,
not just "see how it goes."
(toy squeaking)
(squeaking continues)
(muttering):
Oh, stupid baby.
Growing her brain on my dime.
(squeaking)
ANNOUNCER (on TV):
Are you counting sheep
all night long?
(bleats)
Mhmm.
He needs help!
(baaing):
Help from a drug!
ANNOUNCER:
That help is here. Meet Nappien
(chimes, angelic harp playing)
Nappien activates your brain’s
napping centers,
and attacks
your body’s awake-agens.
And unlike Sleepia,
it won’t cause
foot fattening or elbow stink.
Ooh!
Okay, Nappien,
do your stuff.
Hmm, it’s not working.
You lousy,
worthless piece of...
(snoring)
(Homer yawns)
What a wonderful night’s sleep.
Thank you,
methasorbizone tartrate,
also known as Nappien.
(groans)
Last night, someone ate
all the food in our fridge.
Maybe it was
the same person
who tied each of the dog’s feet
to a toy car.
And someone used
our videotapes as dominoes.
Homer, I think
you dominoed this.
That’s ridiculous.
If I had set up those dominoes,
I’d be wearing my special
domino-setting-up kneepads.
(all gasping)
It was you.
How is that possible?
I’ve read that people do
strange things in their sleep
when they’ve taken Ambien--
I mean Nappien.
See? "May cause dry mouth,
mood swings,
and nighttime kookiness."
Mood swings?!
Mood swings.
(sobbing):
Mood swings!
Mood swings? Mood swings!
♪ Mood swings! ♪
Mood swings,
mood swings!
Mood swings!
(snoring)
(yawning)
Nappien, you did it again.
And everything is
as it should be.
(screams):
John Lennon?!
Yoko?
So you’re the one
behind all these hijinks
at the Rock ’N’ Roll Wax Museum.
ELVIS’S VOICE:
Thank you. Thank you.
Oh!
Mr. Simpson, why did you hurt
the dollies?
Well, son, your Uncle Homer
is like 80% of America--
wacked out
on prescription drugs.
But users
are losers.
You’re confusing
drugs with...
drugs.
(Rod and Todd scream)
Okay, here’s the solution.
I want you kids to lock
the bedroom from the outside,
so I can’t get out
and perpetrate
my nocturnal mischief.
Why don’t you just quit
taking the pills, you hophead?
Because I’m filled
with stress!
Oh! I have three kids
and no money!
Why can’t I have no kids
and three money?
(footsteps running, thudding)
(mumbling unintelligibly)
(grunts)
(thudding, items crashing)
Why am I sleeping
when right next door
is every boy’s dream:
a fat, suggestible zombie dad?
(muttering)
(gulping)
(mumbling)
BART (whispers):
Hey, zombie?
Huh?
Want to come
out and play?
Zombie kill.
No, play!
Zombie file grievance.
(Homer mumbling)
Whoa! Your dad’s
a zombie?
Let’s make him
give us haircuts.
(Homer grunting)
How does it look?
Ooh.
( mumbling)
And that’s only one
of the cool things
we’re going
to do with him.
Zombie montage.
♪ ♪
(whistling)
Oh! My stomach is groaning
with walnut meat.
Come on.
Just one more.
(groans)
(mumbling)
What the...?! My car?!
Milhouse?! Nutmeat?!
(screams)
(tires squealing)
(all screaming)
(screaming continues)
(screams, grunts)
(screams)
(firehouse alarm bell ringing)
(grunting)
(growling)
(men screaming,
dogs growling)
Oh, my God, what have I done?!
You’ve horribly injured
the whole fire department!
What are you,
a travel agent?
’Cause you’re sending me
on a guilt trip.
Sorry.
BROCKMAN:
While our brave firemen
recuperate,
Springfield is a town
without a fire department,
which is bad news
for people like this man.
Sir, how does
it feel knowing
that no one is
coming to save you?
Oh, not as bad as knowing
that somewhere,
gays are marrying each other.
That’s the real
emergency, Kent.
Once again, crisis has
brought out the best in us.
I feel kind of
responsible.
Maybe I should volunteer
to be a fireman.
Volunteer fireman?
Count me in.
Just call me
Fireman Skinner.
You know, I think
I’ll volunteer, too.
Why did you
say too?
Well, I assume
I’m not the first one.
MAYOR QUIMBY:
It is with great pride
that I turn over the safety
of this city
-to the first four people
who showed up.
-Mm-hmm.
Your sense of civic duty
and this pamphlet that came
with the fire extinguisher
are all the training
you need or shall receive.
-Mm-hmm.
-Yeah!
We’re here to join
the volunteer fire department.
You’re too late.
Beat it!
Lousy civilians.
I wish I could
burn ’em all.
Easy there,
Fire Chief Moe.
(Homer giggling)
Oh, I can’t wait
for my first fire.
(gasps)
Is that one?
That’s just someone
barbecuing.
Oh!
(gasps)
Is that one?
That’s a guy
with red hair.
D’oh!
Sweetheart, come to dinner.
I can’t!
That fire siren could sound
at any moment.
Any moment.
♪ ♪
Did I say any moment?
Any moment.
(firehouse alarm bell ringing)
What the hell is that?
That’s the
fire siren!
(whooping)
Marge, when you
see me next,
I’ll be a soggy,
smoky hero.
Mmm.
Soggy, smoky hero.
(guttural utterance)
Just come back
alive, okay?
Don’t tell me
how to do my job!
You save-a Luigi’s place!
Mwah! Mwah!
Luigi give you
all the food you want!
On the house!
(all slurping and moaning)
Hey, this is sweet, huh?
Almost makes up
for not gettin’ paid.
We don’t get what?
(slurping)
(metal creaking)
(grunting)
Oh, thank you.
Your jaws of life are superior
to my movie Jaws of Life.
You guys are the real deal,
as opposed to my movie
The Real Deal,
which was not
the real deal.
Well, uh, your thanks
makes it all worth it.
No, I must thank you properly
with crew jackets
from my less successful films.
Total Explosion,
Father of the Presi-bot,
I Shoot Your Face,
I Shoot Your Face Again,
Frankenberry the Movie 2:
The Frankenberry Wears Prada.
Ooh, leather arms!
People just give you
this stuff?
Hey, it’s the least
they can do
after we saved them
from being melty-faced weirdoes.
We are entitled to some
sort of compensation.
After all,
we’re volunteers.
That’s right, ’Pu.
People owe us
because we’re heroes.
It’s even on my
business card.
I printed them on the back
of my old business cards.
See? It’s different.
Mr. Burns, jump
into this net!
What’s in it for me?
Just jump!
(whimpering)
(wind whistling)
(groaning)
So, I see by your tie
you’re a Yale man, too.
Let’s croon, shall we?
♪ Boola, boola,
boola, boola... ♪
Well done, gentlemen.
Too bad Smithers didn’t make it.
I’m right here, sir.
Excellent.
But since I thought
you were dead,
you won’t get paid
this week.
Make a note of it.
Well, that doesn’t
quite seem fair.
(mutters)
But you four,
you’re the real heroes.
Oh, we don’t need...
It was nothing,
really.
Just doing our job.
What do you think
he will give us?
Fine art, I bet.
No, no, no, the complete
Munsters on DVD!
I hope it’s
spaghetti.
(clears throat)
Thank you, and good-bye.
-Wha...?
-Huh?
Ta-ta,
toodle-loo.
Go back to
your tenements,
where the O’Briens
live next to the Goldbergs,
who rub elbows with Antonellis,
and the only thing
you have in common
is the squalor
of your chamber pot!
Oh, how I hate you!
Bye-bye.
Of all the nerve.
Burns stiffed us!
I can’t believe he acted
completely in character.
Lousy Burns,
so ungrateful.
I hate him
so much.
Hold on a second,
fellas.
I don’t like the looks
of that flaming ember.
I’d better blow it out.
Ha, ha, ha.
(blowing)
-Hmm.
-Hmm?
(Moe continues blowing)
Oh, the fire has spread
to this room full of valuables.
And it’s our duty
to follow it.
Well, the fire’s out,
but, uh
I think some of these valuables
are smoke-damaged.
He’s not gonna want ’em.
Heh-heh-heh.
Moe, are you suggesting
that we should steal?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
It ain’t stealing
if you take it fast.
(screams)
Gentlemen,
I’d like to thank you.
You’ve saved
my store.
Well, most of it.
What do you mean?
Uh, well, your building
will be fine, but unfortunately,
a lot of your merchandise
was completely vaporized:
high-end stereo equipment,
size 10 men’s shoes...
And some stuff I wanted.
Oh, my.
I didn’t think
the damage was that bad.
But you must be
telling the truth.
You’re firemen, after all.
Yeah, we’re awesome.
This’ll make a great
toilet seat.
Uh... hmm.
Uh, gentleman,
I’m, uh...
(chuckles)
I’m starting to wonder
if we’ve crossed a line here.
Just what are you
getting at?
Yeah, Hall Pass.
You better not be thinking
of ratting us out.
It would be a shame if the next
fire you fought was in hell!
Okay, okay.
I’ll just look the other way.
(grunts)
You guys sure aren’t
making this easy.
(fire alarm ringing)
Oh, thank God
there’s a fire.
Marge’s birthday’s
coming up.
I think what she would
treasure most
is a gift bought through
-honest effort because...
-(siren blaring)
...integrity...
...trust...
-...exploitation...
-(siren blaring louder)
...the golden rule...
...role models...
...serious crime...
...zero tolerance...
...the Ten Commandments...
(siren blaring louder,
alarm sounding)
Next time Maggie
does that in a pool,
tell me quietly;
don’t announce it.
But, Mom, the lifeguards
have to know.
Just let the chemicals
deal with it.
(siren approaching)
Look at me! I’m a fireman!
Hey, Mom, can we go see
Dad put out the fire?
Well, I guess every boy
should see his father as a hero.
Hey, guys, check out
the radical-free air
generated by
my stolen Ionic Breeze.
Oh, bogus gizmo,
grant me eternal life.
Mom, is Dad stealing from people
he’s supposed to help?
(groans)
BOTH:
King of thieves,
we worship you.
(chuckles)
(gasps)
He is stealing!
Oh... uh...
HOMER:
Look at me, guys!
I’m stealing
five Segways at once!
And speaking of segues,
I’m off to my next
morally questionable activity!
(grumbles)
You’re nothing but a
diabolical master thief!
The kind that haunts
the slopes of Saint Moritz
or the casinos
of Monte Carlo!
We’re not thieves;
we’re scavengers,
like the beautiful vulture
or the heroic tapeworm,
or America’s sweetheart,
the maggot.
You should’ve seen
the faces of your children
when they caught you stealing.
Kids, get in here
and show your father the faces!
(gasps)
(sobbing)
Make them stop!
You make them stop
by doing the right thing.
("Sad Eyes"
by Robert John playing)
♪ Sad eyes ♪
♪ Turn the other way ♪
♪ I don’t want to see you cry ♪
♪ Sad eyes ♪
♪ You knew there’d come a day ♪
♪ When we would
have to say goodbye ♪
♪ Sad eyes. ♪
(music stops, alarm sounding)
(all grunting)
(coughing)
Moe, can we talk?
Are you crazy?
It’s 500 degrees in here!
Oh, no, wait, it’s only 495.
What’s on your mind?
Moe, I think
-we may have perverted...
-Go on.
...our duties as firemen.
(groans):
Oh.
(both scream)
First Skinner, now you.
Well, maybe you got a point.
Maybe we...
A solid gold grandfather clock!
(sizzling)
Oh! This thing’s hotter
than Ellen Barkin!
(floorboards creaking)
Moe, I can save you, but you
have to let go of the clock!
But it’s been in my family
for over 40 seconds!
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait!
What about Nabu?
Apu is dead.
I was reincarnated
as this cat.
(both gasp)
(chuckles)
Oh, you have
just been Apu’d!
(groans)
♪♪
My baby!
Could do worse than
grow up to be like you, sir.
Let’s hear it for Homer!
(cheering)
So Daddy saved Apu and Moe.
And believe me,
we learned our lesson.
What’d you do
with all the loot?
We sent it to skid row,
where it would do the most good.
Look at me.
I’m the bum of the future!
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Shh!
Enhanced by Fotokem