(SINGING) The Simpsons
(SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
(HORN BELLOWING)
(BEEPING)
(INSTRUMENTS PLAYING)
(PLAYING DIFFERENT TUNE)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
D'oh!
(SCREAMS)
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
Come on, boy.
Take your pill.
(GAGS AND SPITS)
Mom, the dog won't
take his medicine.
It helps if you wrap
it in a slice of cheese.
Woo-hoo!
Free cheese!
Homer, that was
for the dog.
What happened to us, Marge?
We used to feed
each other cheese
and laugh all night.
Then came
the heart attacks.
(RUMBLING)
(GASPING)
What's that rumble?
LISA: It's a media circus.
Woo-hoo! The circus!
A media circus.
Woo-hoo! I don't know
the difference.
LISA: ABC, CBS.
Uh-oh. The Christian Science
Monitor has a flat tire.
I'll get the spare.
No. We must wait
for God to jack us.
In Springfield today,
a sex scandal has
brought in reporters
from around the world.
Why, here's Fox News.
We are the champions
My friend
The cause of all
this commotion is mayor
and suspected
illegal immigrant
Joe Quimby,
named today in paternity suits
by 27 different women.
(EXCITED CHATTER)
Joe, why won't you
acknowledge our love child?
Er, uh,
that is not my baby.
(QUIMBY-LIKE) Er, uh,
Waa...
Raise this as your own.
This is the most
exciting scandal
since the Juice
was on the loose!
The Juice is
still on the loose.
(SCREAMS)
Mr. Mayor, just how
many illegitimate children
are you hiding?
Kent, I'm hiding nothing.
Except this puppy.
ALL: Aw.
Look into his eyes
and tell me I'm lying.
Well, I'm placated.
And so are all my friends
in the local media.
(CHUCKLES)
I have a question.
Chloe Talbot,
Global News Network.
Oh, it seems
a big-shot reporter from
Some major news
outlet isn't satisfied.
Well, if it isn't local news
legend Kent Brockman.
Hey, Kent, run over
any more pedestrians?
Those records are sealed.
She's from Springfield.
I knew her in high school.
I didn't think
anyone successful
came from Springfield.
What about that
two-headed goat?
Technically, he was born
in Shelbyville.
Yes. But he came
here to die.
HOMER:
One of you ate tin cans.
One of you ate health food.
How you solved crimes,
I'll never know.
Mr. Mayor, you
claim to be faithful
to your wife.
But I have obtained
this exclusive videotape.
(NERVOUS GROAN)
Come on, baby,
read my sash.
You're the "major"?
That's "mayor,"
you fertile moron!
Two things are certain.
The mayor is
in deep trouble.
And the local
newsmen in this
town are idiots.
Channel 6 News rocks!
A car chase every night
or the weather
girl wears a tube top!
And if she doesn't,
you win a pizza!
(WISTFUL MURMUR) Chloe sure
turned out successful.
You're successful,
too, Mom.
You made a chore wheel
that's both fair and wise.
(EXCLAIMS)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Marge, I figured out a way
we can get in on
this Quimby lawsuit.
Bart, go ahead.
(QUIMBY-LIKE) Mayor Quimby
is my, er, father.
Give me $1 million.
Huh? Huh?
(SIGHS)
(CHANTING)
Diamond Joe's gotta go.
Diamond Joe's
gotta go.
Mr. Mayor, will you
answer one question?
Only if it's
submitted in writing.
Checkmate.
Marge? Marge Simpson?
Chloe! Hi!
Marge! Oh... Where
are you living now?
Evergreen Terrace.
Paris! Just like
you always dreamed.
Terrace. Evergreen
Terrace. The street
that smells like pee.
This is my
daughter, Lisa.
Chloe, I really
admire how you got out
of Springfield and
became such a success.
Hey, only the
lame-o's stay.
And your mother,
super lady.
(GROANING)
Well, it is good
to see you, Chloe.
Would you like to come over
for dinner tomorrow?
Oh, I'd love to.
I'm getting so sick
of these greasy
catered meals.
You insult me,
you insult Italy!
Which is shaped
like a boot.
Who knew?
(DOORBELL RINGS)
Homer Simpson.
I saw you
on the television.
I remember you
from high school.
You barfed in my tuba.
I believe it was
the school's tuba.
(MUNCHING)
Chloe, these kebabs
you made
are as good or
better than anything
I've ever had at this table.
Homer!
Oh, Marge,
I'm just being polite.
(MUNCHING)
Mmm.
My back pain's
completely cured!
That was one too many.
I got the recipe
for these in Istanbul.
More.
I was writing a story
for Harper's Magazine.
Harper's Magazine!
I have a picture
of Lewis Lapham
on my binder.
(GROWLS)
Oh, but I've been
yapping about
myself all night.
Marge, what's exciting
in your life lately?
Well...
Uh... Oh, we finally
found out why the dog
was scooting around
on his butt all day.
Turns out he had
an impacted
anal gland.
The excitement
never stops.
Chloe, would you
like to see slides
of our trip to Athens...
Boulevard
Recreational Center?
Pdloveto.
Oh, my show's on.
Mind if we watch a little?
I guess.
ANNOUNCER: "The Talbot Report"
with Chloe Talbot.
Tonight Chloe
interviews Bob Dylan.
So, Bob, what religion are
you converting to now?
Hey, I'll tell you
one thing...
(UNINTELLIGIBLE GIBBERISH)
No war. Shalom.
ANNOUNCER: Followed by
Chloe's triumphant return
to her depressing
little hometown,
Springfield.
Hello, Ned.
Hey, Comic Book Guy.
Krusty the Clown,
I thought he was dead.
Yeah. I guess you ain't
been to too many
supermarket openings lately.
(GROANS)
You know, Chloe,
some of us stayed
in this town and
made it a better place.
Oh, come on, Marge.
The only reason
we don't move out
of this dunghill
is because
of my court-ordered
ankle bracelet.
(BEEPING)
I'm here. I'm here.
Quit bugging me.
Why do you always have
to show that to company?
It's a conversation starter.
(GROANS)
This is the dance
the Chinese government
makes dissidents perform
before they shoot them.
(VOCALIZING)
Homer, what are you doing?
I swallowed a chicken bone.
(GAGGING)
(SIGHS)
Chloe, you've lived
so many fascinating places.
Yes, but down
deep in my heart,
I'll always be the girl
who wanted to
leave Springfield.
Gee, with all that travel,
you probably
haven't had much time
to find that special someone.
Oh, I've had a few flings.
(COUGHING NAMES) Bill Clinton.
Schwarzenegger. Oh, excuse me.
But not all of us
can be as lucky
as you, Marge.
Homer's a wonderful man.
(CONTINUES VOCALIZING)
Did you just
swallow another bone?
Same one!
Chloe is amazing.
Even her serving
bowl smells glamorous.
(INHALES)
That's ridiculous!
No one's bowl smells...
(INHALES)
It's like Christmas in Aspen.
(SIGHS)
Did you know
back in high school
that she'd be such a star?
Back then
we were both stars
in the thrill-a-minute world
of high school journalism.
MARGE: Together,
we broke the biggest story
of the semester.
One of the cafeteria workers
was spitting in the soup.
I'll teach you to give me
my first job out of prison.
(SPITS)
When we published the story,
we received
the school's highest award.
Ladies,
it is my great pleasure
to award you these
certificates of merit.
In this box marked "honoree,"
fill in your names.
And over here,
write in what you did.
I'll be back.
You ain't tasted
the last of my spit.
Oh, that Moe.
But good for you, Mom.
Why didn't you follow Chloe
into journalism?
Well, we both faced
a tough decision.
Go off to journalism school,
or stay in Springfield
with our sweethearts?
(MOANING)
Stay with me, Marge.
And I promise
we'll travel the world
and perhaps outer space.
(IMITATES STAR SHIPS)
(IMITATES LASER GUNS)
(MOANING)
Barney...
I love you, Chloe.
And I love you,
too, brake fluid.
(BELCH)
Chloe left town
as soon as Barney proposed.
I would've followed her,
but my plans changed
when God brought me
a wonderful little boy.
Bart, stop that!
This isn't what
it looks like.
(GRUNTING)
Why would Homer
write his name in grime?
(GRUNTING)
Ah, that's better.
Mom, Chloe just won
the Peabody Award.
Well, I just made
the bathroom floor
smell like lemons.
Where's the
award for that?
Oh, Mom, don't feel bad.
Everybody
appreciates your...
Uh-oh. I'm late for my
dinner with Chloe.
(GIGGLES)
HOMER: Good news, Marge.
I've learned to
walk naked on stilts.
(GROANS)
Whoa, whoa.
(GASPS)
There's Dan Rather
and Tom Brokaw
hanging out
with Kent Brockman!
You want your mike back,
local anchor?
This just in.
I'm pissed off.
Hi, fellas.
Chloe, you want
to feel my muscle?
(CHUCKLES)
Chloe has such
an amazing life.
(SIGHS)
I wonder what
would've happened
if I'd stuck with journalism?
Oh, honey, her life
can't compare to yours.
You've got three kids,
a TV tray from Expo 67,
and you're
married to King Stink!
Yeah, I guess.
Marge, listen to me.
Chloe may have
a flashy job, but you're
the backbone of this family.
You're like the electrical
tape that holds
the two halves of
my car together.
That's a sweet
thought, Homie.
I just hate to see
you upset, honey.
(GASPS) You know what would
be a good name for Maggie?
Chloe!
Oh!
That was such
an exciting night.
Morley Safer has
the biggest head
I've ever seen.
I really had fun.
(SIGHS) It's gonna be
a letdown going
to school tomorrow.
We have to make
a pilgrim out of felt.
Hey, I'm covering
the UN Women's
Conference in
Capital City tomorrow.
You want to come
with me?
Oh, that'd be wonderful!
Oh, I'd have
to ask my mom.
You can ask her right now.
She's glaring at us
from the front lawn.
Marge, it's my fault
we're a little late.
How dare you show my daughter
a life of fun and possibility?
Hey!
Keep your dishwashing
hands off the Armani.
For your information,
our electric dishwasher
is on the fritz.
Not that you care about
the ups and downs
of my appliances.
Do you? Do you?
Oh! That's it!
I'm going to
show you some moves
I learned from
G. Gordon Liddy!
I'm so sick of names!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
CHLOE: Oh! My hair!
Ladies, (CHUCKLE) there's no
need to fight over me.
No one's fighting over you!
Oh. Well, then carry on.
CHLOE: You don't know
when to quit.
"Shiner Be Gone."
Tura-Iura-Iura
Tura-lura-li...
Hmm.
Lisa, honey,
let me explain
what happened tonight.
Sometimes when your mom
has half a glass of wine,
she goes cuckoo bananas.
Hmm. So, is it okay
if I go to the Women's
Conference with Chloe?
Let me think
about it. No.
(GIGGLES)
Oh, I've never
disobeyed Mom before.
Is this a step I'm
really willing to take?
I don't know. The more
I think about it, the...
(GRUNTS)
Thinking is for losers.
Bart!
Thanks for helping
me make up my mind!
Thanks for cushioning my fall.
I didn't cushion your...
(GRUNTS)
Chloe, I saw your
report on Kuala Lumpur.
Truly hard-hitting.
Thanks, Tom.
I really appreciate that.
(CHUCKLES) So I...
You know, I was wondering...
Yes?
Would you like
to come to my celebrity
racquetball tournament?
I'll have to
check my schedule.
(GRUNTS)
(LISA GRUNTS)
I'll give you
a first-round bye.
Gotta go, Tom.
I'll think about it.
Lisa, breakfast.
I know you're mad at me.
But I hope you're not mad
at Cap'n Crunch...
(GASPING)
(CHOKING)
(GRUNTING)
Homer, we've
gotta get Lisa!
All right. While I'm gone,
boy, you think about
what you did.
(GRUNTS) What did I do?
You... Why, you little...
(CHOKING)
You need a reason for
strangling, do you...
I'll fix your wagon...
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
Hello?
Chloe, forget about
the Women's Conference.
I need you to get over
to Mount Springfield!
It's about to erupt.
Don't we have a reporter
who specializes in
natural disasters?
Yeah. He's busy covering
Julia Roberts' last haircut.
(CHUCKLES)
But seriously, he's dead.
Now, get going.
Hey there! My name's Chet.
I'm the cameraman
for this here 'cano story.
Let's see.
I've been to Afghanistan,
Serbia, Lebanon...
(LOUD ERUPTION)
Okay, okay, I lied!
I shoot wedding videos
in Dallas, Fort Worth...
Okay, okay, just Fort Worth!
Ah!
Hello, UN Women's
Conference!
(EXCLAIMS)
We're trapped!
Lisa, we may not make it.
But at least we can
go out as the great
journalists we are.
I'm not a journalist.
You are now.
Remember to keep my
boobs in the shot.
And we're on in five,
four, three...
I don't see Lisa in
any of the seminars.
And I'm growing
ashamed of my penis.
(GASPS) Homer, look!
I'm here at the long-dormant
Springfield Volcano,
which is now spewing
noxious debris into the air.
How male.
ALL: Mmm-hmm.
With me is my
8-year-old camera girl,
Lisa Simpson.
She's taken my daughter
to an erupting volcano?
That's it! She is off
the Christmas card list!
Marge, that's
crazy talk!
Now, look, I'll save Lisa.
Your place is
here with the women.
WOMEN: Boo!
Okay, you go save Lisa.
I'll stay here with the women.
WOMEN: Boo!
What do women want?
(FRIGHTENED CRIES)
(GASPS)
We've gotta go now!
Okay. I'll run
as fast as I can,
but I'm full of potato salad.
(GROANS)
I'm sorry, folks. You're not
allowed to go up there.
In fact, I don't
even know why I'm here.
This lava is not a criminal.
It hasn't hurt anybody...
(SCREAMING)
Anybody I know.
Chief, my daughter's up there.
You're a father, too!
Yeah. But I'm a cop first,
then a boat enthusiast,
amateur historian,
yo-yo dieter,
then I'm a cop again...
LISA: Help!
Help! So much sulfur dioxide!
I'm coming, sweetheart!
I'll save you, Lisa!
(RUMBLING)
Oh, my God!
Oh!
Ooh.
Be careful, Mom!
There's hot lava
under the ground!
Actually,
when it's underground,
lava is called magma!
You're so smart, Chloe!
Walter Cronkite
told me the same thing!
Shut up!
Mom, that was incredible.
Oh, nothing's more powerful
than a mother's love.
Mom, your hair!
Don't worry.
We've got two hours
before it burns
down to my head.
Our top story tonight...
I'm about to die.
Oh...
Barney, you
saved my life.
Chloe, when you left me,
I was devastated.
But I sobered up
long enough to
become a pilot.
With you beside me,
I think I could
make it work.
How about a half-hour
of pity sex?
Is there any
other kind?
(BURPS)
In the wake of
the devastating eruption,
one Springfielder
proved herself a hero,
Marge Simpson!
She's won herself
a free hero sandwich
at Springfield Sub Shops.
Extra charge
for warm-ups.
Mom, I want to be
just like you.
I mean the lava part,
not saving Lisa.
Pretend to care!
(GRUNTING)
(CHOKING)
Well, looking
at you kids, I know I made
the right choice in life.
I'm sure you did.
But still, don't you
ever wonder what
might've happened
if things had
gone differently?
Well...
This is Marge Simpson
reporting from Lake Placid
where the "Miracle on
Ice" never happened.
No!
(GRUNTS)
Lisa, what are you
doing in there?
Praying to Buddha,
Jesus, SpongeBob.
There's no time to be picky.
Perhaps we should help.
Screw her!
(LAUGHS)