CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screeching)
D’oh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
Ah.
(chewing noisily)
Bart, what are you doing?
I only eat the clown heads.
That’s so wasteful.
I’ve always done it.
Just like I only eat
the eyes off a lobster.
(Marge groans)
Oh, you should
be ashamed!
Your father works very hard
to put lobsters on our table.
Every night, he comes
home exhausted,
with his voice
too hoarse to talk.
(screaming)
(grunting)
I’m the king of goofing off!
(grunts loudly)
Ow! Unnecessary roughness!
So what? That’s legal
in Rolo-Polo.
I thought we were playing
Cincinnati Time Waste.
Oh, in that case...
(screams)
(sobbing)
What did I do?
When you pass
the coffee machine,
you’re supposed to yell "hot
pot" and eat a sugar cube.
He’s right, Homer.
That’s a two-minute penalty.
(giggling)
MEN:
Penalty, penalty, penalty!
Penalty, penalty,
penalty...
(laughing)
On your feet, you sniggering
oran-gu-tan.
(laughing)
(suppressed laughter)
My fat friend,
you are hanging
by a very thin thread.
("Pop Goes The Weasel"
playing)
If you want to keep your job,
then you better start...
(humming "Pop Goes
the Weasel")
You’re thinking about
that ice cream truck,
aren’t you?
Well, you can just
forget about...
Come and lick me, big boy.
I said lick me!
(groaning)
(screams)
Ew!
(spits)
You’re not ice cream!
Faker.
("Pop Goes the Weasel"
playing)
Ice cream man, wait!
You’re fired!
As for the rest of you,
you’re supposed to be
a chair-hockey team!
All I see is five showboaters.
Now sit down
and give me 50 twirls.
That’s more like it.
Ice cream man!
(tires screeching)
(panting)
Homer, there you are.
What does my best customer
want today?
One butter-crusted
choco-rocket, please.
I wish I had more
customers like you.
Oh, I’m barely
scraping by.
Yeah, this economy
is tough on everyone.
Change a hundred?
Sure. That’s 1.50,
1.75, $2.00...
(wheezing)
(weakly)
99.50,
99.75...
(gasps, screams)
(grunts)
No...!
(sobbing)
("Taps" playing
on truck horn)
(bells jingling)
You must be Homer.
Huh? Max told
you about me?
Oh, yes.
Max loved to talk
about his work.
How he bored me.
And now I’m left with nothing
but my lover
and this worthless truck.
Wait a minute.
You don’t want the truck,
I need a job,
you need money,
I’m flush with severance pay...
You’ll buy Max’s truck?
Why, doesn’t he need it?
Oh, right.
Remember that crappy
ice cream truck I bought?
LISA:
How can we forget?
Mom says now we can’t afford
to go to the orthodontist.
Well, sink your crooked,
rotting teeth into this!
(kids gasp)
("Get Ur Freak On"
by Missy Elliott playing)
♪ Get your freak on ♪
♪ Get your freak on,
get your freak on ♪
♪ Get your freak on ♪
♪ Get your freak on,
get your freak on ♪
♪ Getcha, getcha, getcha,
getcha, get your freak on ♪
♪ Get your freak on,
get your freak on ♪
Whoa!
Boy!
Otto, you totally pimped
Dad’s ride!
(scoffs)
He was following my design.
And now to get dressed
in a most unusual way.
(rock music playing)
(jet engine roaring)
(bullets ricocheting)
(mechanical clanking)
(jackhammer drilling)
(mechanical buzzing)
Butter-brickle!
(applause on TV)
Welcome back.
Today, we’re celebrating women
who didn’t waste their lives
being mommies.
Professor Stein, tell
us about your book,
Life Beyond Wife.
Well, Opal, it’s about women
who want to breast-feed
their own dreams
and change the poopy diapers
of fulfillment.
(cheering and applause)
(groaning)
I call it
leaving your "lega-she."
Does this book
have any examples?
Yes, eight!
Take Gail Tucker.
She wrote hip-hop lyrics
to the beat
of her washing machine
with an off-center load.
Last year, she won
all the Grammys.
(cheering)
Or how about Becky Tyson,
who invented the pink VCR.
Now her husband
asks her for money--
or as I call it: "mon-she."
You go, girl!
All those women
are so impressive.
I’ve been doing the same thing
for the last ten years.
And all I have to show
for it is a clean floor.
(dog barking)
(kids laughing)
My lega-she.
(groans)
Oh.
Boy, it’s hot.
I feel like Icarus, flying too
close to Apollo’s golden orb.
Punch away, Nelson.
(groans)
It’s too hot.
I’ll get you later.
I’ll pencil you in
for next week.
Eh, what the hell.
(screams)
(rock music
playing in distance)
("Money for Nothing" by
Dire Straits playing)
You kids like ice cream?
MAN (speedily): Product
contains neither ice nor cream.
May contain trace elements
of Mexican cheese.
Do not consume.
(kids clamoring excitedly)
I’m a unitard.
(children talking excitedly)
What’s the matter, son?
Don’t you have enough
money for ice cream?
I do, but I’m
lactose-intolerant.
Son, I will not stand
for intolerance.
You give this delightful
frozen treat the same respect
you would give any
lactose-free food.
God bless America.
But my doctor says...
I said,
God bless America.
(pained moaning)
Call the number on my bracelet.
(grunts)
(with lisp)
Ooh, thomeone
wearth a brathelet.
Who’th your boyfriend?
Uh... Dr. Osterberg?
Whoa, Marge,
for the first time in my life,
I’m excited
about going to work.
I’m glad someone in this house
feels their life has meaning.
You’re glad?
You don’t look glad.
Are you sure you know
what "glad" means?
I just wish I could do something
to be remembered by,
something that says
"Marge was here"
after I’m gone.
(muffled): Oh, honey,
what about the time...
(muffled gibberish)
Everybody loved that.
Love you.
(sighs heavily)
Ah, the story of my life.
They get the Popsicles,
I get the sticks.
Look, Maggie,
I made another you.
Out of sticky orange wood.
(squealing and laughing)
Marge, I was...
Folk art!
That’s my favorite
kind of folk medium.
I made it myself.
Marge, you’re a genius.
You should make sculptures
of other people.
Like Lenny, or Carl
or the new James Bond.
Will America accept
a British James Bond?
I can’t wait to find out.
("Feels So Good"
by Chuck Mangione playing)
(helicopter flying overhead)
This is Kent Brockman.
A high-speed pursuit
is taking place
on the streets of Springfield.
We responded immediately
after seeing it on Channels two,
four, five, seven and 63.
The driver is getting
out of his car...
he’s running to a helipad,
he’s taking off in a copter.
Why, here he is
next to us.
Kent, there seems to be
a traffic tie-up
at the 101-405 interchange.
I recommend taking
surface streets.
Jailbird away.
Well, there you have it,
people...
Sweet Morley Safer!
Do I see a telegenic housewife
making art
out of popsicle sticks?
Set this baby down--
I smell soft news.
Ma’am, I’d like to feature you
on my award-submitted segment,
Kent Brockman’s
"Kent-resting People".
Really? You think people would
be Kent-rested in me?
-I do.
-Hm!
I’m here with local sculptress
Marge Simpson who works in,
of all media,
Popsicle stick.
Our viewers want to know two
things: why and how come.
Why did cavemen
paint on walls?
Why do you scratch
your name on Tupperware?
So when you die,
something’s left behind
that says, "I was here,
I mattered.
That’s my Tupperware."
Human feelings,
expressed by a human.
And here’s a local nobody
enjoying his likeness.
Let’s take a sneaky-peeky.
My God, it’s beauty-ful.
I finally see the goodness
in myself.
Come here, you.
Oh, I’m so glad
you like it, Moe.
That’s right, tell me all
your little wooden dreams.
You’re not alone anymore.
No you ain’t.
Aw, you’re shivering,
are you cold?
Where you goin’, Marge?
Honey,
I brought you more sticks.
This is the most fun I’ve
ever had giving you wood.
Homie, this sculpting has
made me feel so fulfilled.
I’m as hopeful
and full of life
as I was in the years
before I met you.
It’s good to see
you smile again.
I was lonely being
happy all by myself.
Well, no one’s gonna be
lonely tonight.
(moaning)
(laughs)
Let me just put on
some romantic music.
("Pop Goes the Weasel"
playing)
Hey, we got
the whole night, baby,
let’s slow things down.
-(song plays at slow speed)
-(Marge gasps) Ooh...
(moaning)
Marge, you are one
fantastic artist,
and no one knows art like a
Texan with too much money.
You’re from Texas?
That’s right.
And I want to finance
a fancy-shmancy art show,
starring your wooden wonders.
Yee-hah. (laughing)
(gasps)
My own art show?
I’m so happy.
Do you mind?
Yee-hah!
I’m excited you’re excited.
Yee-hah! Yee-hah!
Shoot on the "yee,"
not the "hah."
Hey lady,
you gotta pay
to use my likeness.
It’s a registered trademark.
(groans)
(grunts)
Hey, I do more than TV.
I had a one-man show
on Broadway.
That’s who showed up--
one man.
(laughing)
Long story short,
I won a Drama Desk Award.
Marge, everything
looks wonderful.
Well, I’m off to pedal
my frosty wares.
You can’t go to work.
I need you here
for emotional support.
Plus you make
a small crowd look huge.
Sweetie, I can’t abandon
my route even for one day.
If those kids discover the
link between eating right
and feeling good,
I am screwed.
But I’ll be back in time
for your show.
The show starts at 3:00.
You promise
you’ll be here?
I would never
let you down.
Our marriage is like
soft-serve ice cream.
And trust is
the hard chocolate shell
that keeps it from
melting onto our carpet.
In "cone-clusion,"
here’s the scoop: I love you.
(sighs)
(playing "Pop Goes the Weasel"
over speaker)
(clamoring)
(tires screeching)
What the hell do you kids want?!
Oh, right, ice cream.
(children cheering)
(song continues)
Oh, my God.
It’s the opportunity
of a lifetime.
(over truck PA)
Attention, losers:
this is your chance to buy
your kids some frozen love.
I’m not going to fall
for such a cheap stunt.
Mom would.
Hey, give me
one of everything!
Hey!
(group shouting)
(chorus of "Mmm")
Sorry, I’m all
out of ice cream.
Already? It’s only 38 seconds
to 3:00.
(gasps)
Marge’s show!
Must jettison excess weight.
(Homer yelling)
D’oh!
(panting)
Oh, my God.
I only got nine seconds
till Marge’s show.
Eight... seven...
(groans)
Homer, where are you?
(horns honking)
Oh, I’ll never make it.
Unless...
Whoo-hoo! I’m going
to be on time.
(owl hooting)
(Homer, scout shrieking)
-(roaring)
-(shrieks)
(grunts)
(shouts)
(screaming)
(tires screeching)
(all screaming)
(roaring softly)
(groans)
No, no, no, save your energy.
Don’t try to talk.
I don’t know where
Carl ends and I begin.
See, statements like that are
why people think we’re gay.
I made it back for your show,
honey...
Well, Homer, you destroyed
my artwork and my dreams.
Good job, very thorough.
Marge, let me explain.
I had a chance to make
a little more money by
exploiting broken families...
Oh, stop, just stop.
You don’t care about anyone
else’s happiness but your own.
Well, excuse me
for having enormous flaws
that I don’t work on!
♪♪
(knocking on door)
HOMER: Marge?
Marge?
Honey, you’ve been
in there all day.
You got to eat something.
Why don’t you come
downstairs and cook dinner?
Lasagna would be awesome.
Marge?
I wrote you a check for $300
to pay for all
the sculptures I broke.
Okay?
Oh, I see.
You’d prefer a wire transfer.
Well, what’s
your routing number?
That’s okay, I can get it
from the bank, honey.
I just need
to know your birthday.
Marge? I have an apology
that I hope is better
than all the other ones,
so please listen carefully.
The thing I liked best about
being an ice cream man
wasn’t the free ice cream
or the colorful toppings,
or the love I received
from obese children.
It was giving you those sticks,
and watching you smile
as you turned them into art.
If it would win you back,
I would gradually eat
all the parts of a motorcycle.
I hope it doesn’t come to that.
Could you please
just give me a sign that
you still love me a little?
If you won’t talk to me,
I’ll send in Polaroids
to show you how sad I am
that I let you down.
I’m laughing in the last one,
but it’s only ’cause the cat
fell down the stairs.
(snoring and mumbling)
Marge? Marge?!
She’s been gone for a while.
Grampa’s been watching us.
You kids have been
real good tonight.
-Mom!
Marge, where are you?!
Did you change your name?
Is it Kelly?
Kelly!
Comic Book Guy,
have you seen our mom?
A complete list of things
I have seen
or not seen is available
on my blog.
Your mother
is on the "not seen" list,
along with "a Star Wars film
that was any good
since the first one."
And even that has been
ruined by CGI additions.
Bravo, George.
There’s Mom!
Oh, my God--
she’s going to jump.
Marge, don’t do it!
Give divorce a chance!
Homer, I want to show the world
how I feel about you.
The world’s
not that interested.
They will be.
Ready, bullies?
ALL: Ready.
Homer, you wanted a sign
that I still love you,
so here it is.
Wow!
You made me a sculpture
of Magilla Gorilla.
No, Homer.
It’s you--my sweet,
perfectly imperfect you.
Okay, boys,
on my command, fire.
But nobody’s done
anything wrong.
Geez, if everyone was like you,
our morgues would be empty.
Homie, I realized
that my most enduring creation
is the life
I’ve sculpted with you.
ALL: Aah!
Now I know that my lega-she
is really a lega-we.
I just have one question,
my darling:
What did you do
with the ice cream
that was on all those sticks?
It’s in that Dumpster.
Not that one!
This statue,
subject unknown,
is the last remaining
example of art
before the collapse
of the western world.
If only we’d known
that iPods would unite
and overthrow the very humans
they entertained.
(groaning)
What do you want from us?!
Nothing.
We just like whipping.
(groaning)
♪♪
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Shh!
Enhanced by Fotokem