CHORUS: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(theme music playing)
(bell ringing)
(tires screeching)
D'oh! (screams)
(effort grunts)
(Homer grunts)
(Homer screams)
-(airplane crashing)
-Thanks for letting me skip school
to see the team come back
from the championship, Dad.
I always say, a boy can
learn more at an airport
than he can at any school.
Hey. I need to see your claim checks
for that luggage.
Oh, of course. I have it right here.
(groans) I'll need to see yours too.
-You got it!
-(groans) I'll take your word for it.
-You're just doing your job.
-(all laughing)
-Do you have anything by Robert Ludlum?
-Get out.
Look at the outrageous markup.
You magnificent bastard. I salute you!
I just got a bunch of fruity Easter eggs.
Ew! Another liver transplant.
Oh, no. Not again!
You're not getting away
that easy, little fella.
Have you heard of Krishna Consciousness?
This, Bart, is a crazy man.
Do unto others as you would
have them do unto you.
Right. That'll work.
A new and better life awaits you
on our distant home planet, Blisstonia.
Hmm. Makes sense.
We're having a free get-acquainted session
at our resort this weekend.
How much is this free resort weekend?
-It's free.
-And when is this weekend?
-It's this weekend.
-Uh-huh. And how much does it cost?
-Um, it's free.
-I see. And when is it?
It's this weekend.
And what are you charging
for this free weekend?
-Come on, Dad. The team's arriving.
-It's free, right?
Hey. Look. There's a big crowd
to welcome us back, even though we lost.
Hey, I'll give you something to cry about,
you loser. You can't catch a football?
Let's see if you can catch a rock.
(all shouting)
(groaning)
(all chanting furiously)
I've never heard of these Movementarians.
-Are they some kind of church?
-Who cares what it is?
The point is
these are some decent, generous people
that I can take advantage of.
But what if they try
to talk us into something?
Marge, Marge, Marge.
Remember when those smooth-talking guys
tried to sell me
a time-share vacation condo?
You bought four of them.
Thank God the check bounced.
So I beat the system.
Watch yourself, Dad. You're the highly
suggestible type.
Yes, I am the highly suggestible type.
BOTH: Welcome, brother.
Out of my way, jerk-ass!
(to Batman TV theme)
♪ Na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na, fishing ♪
♪ Fishing, fishing ♪
Hi, how are y--
♪ Fishing ♪
It certainly is a beautiful day.
We should thank the Leader.
Who the hell is that? Some kind of leader?
Yes.
He's the head of our perfect family.
And when our galactic vehicle is complete,
he will take us
to our new home, Blisstonia.
Why don't you come chat with us
about the Leader at the welcome center?
-Will there be beer?
-Beer is not allowed.
Homer no function beer well without.
Would you rather have beer
or complete and utter contentment?
What kind of beer?
The Leader knows how miserable
you, Marge, Lisa, Bart and Maggie are.
Really? I'm surprised about Maggie.
Just come up
and watch our orientation film.
You're free to leave at any time.
Wow! A free movie! Thanks!
Out of my way, jerk-ass!
(fanfare playing on TV)
MAN (on TV): Once we collect enough money
for fuel
our leader will throw open the doors
of the forbidden barn
where we will all board
our intergalactic vehicle,
rows one through 30 first.
Upon our arrival, we will begin our new,
perfect lives on Blisstonia,
well-known for its high levels of bliss.
I don't know about you,
but they're not exactly winning me over
with these lousy production values here.
I'm gonna slip out.
MAN (on speaker): You're free to leave
whenever you want,
but would you mind telling us why?
Oh, I just didn't, uh--
I didn't think, um--
Oh, it's--it's pretty good.
Man, this whole place puffs of
the wacky-tabbacky. I'm out of here.
Going somewhere? Uh, though you're free
to do so.
Uh-- (chuckles nervously)
No. Just rearranging my underwear.
Ah. There it is.
(light switch clicks)
MAN (on TV): When you surrender yourself
to the Movementarians,
you are guaranteed a perfect life
of serenity, love and loving serenity.
- Not a guarantee.
-Loving serenity. It's about damn time!
-I love the Leader.
-The Leader is perfect.
Wait. I'm confused about the movie.
So the cops knew that Internal Affairs
was setting them up?
What are you talking about?
There's nothing like that in there.
You see, when I get bored
I make up my own movie.
I have a very short attention span.
But our point is very simple.
You see, when--
Oh, look! A bird!
-(chirping)
-(giggling)
The circle of judgment
never fails to destroy their self-esteem.
Then he'll be ours to mold.
Let the judgment begin.
I'll get the ball rolling.
-You're a fat idiot.
-Yeah! Lose some weight!
-Hey, man. You're fat.
-Fatso.
-Moron.
-(all chattering)
OTTO MANN: Fat too.
Well, yeah.
I guess I could lose a few pounds.
And I can be kind of thick
sometimes. (chuckles)
You've failed at everything
you've ever tried.
Whoa. You've got my number
on that one, buddy.
This is a smart group.
And your stink brings tears to my eyes.
Now wait a minute, Moe. (sniffs)
-Oh. My mistake.
-(both sigh)
Why isn't our low-protein gruel
wearing down his resistance
like all the others?
It doesn't wear down your resistance
if you eat a month's supply.
He even ate mine.
(groaning)
-You gonna finish that, bony?
-Oh, "griven"--
Let's try the chant. Everyone loves
a droning, repetitive chant.
Attention, everyone.
Let's all give thanks to the Leader
for this glorious day.
(chanting) The leader is good.
The leader is great.
We surrender our will as of this date.
The Leader is good. The Leader is great.
It's no use. He's obviously the most
powerful mind we've ever dealt with.
Or--
( to Batman TV theme)
♪ Na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na, Leader ♪
-♪ Leader, leader, leader ♪
-♪ Batman! ♪
I mean--
♪ Leader ♪
I love the Leader.
-MARGE: You what?
-Come again, Marge?
You what?
I've joined the Movementarians.
And so have all of you.
-MARGE: We what?
-All I had to give them
was our life savings,
the deed to the house
and a commitment
of 10 trillion years of labor.
I can't go along with this, Homer.
Marge, when I join an underground cult,
I expect a little support from my family.
Dad, do you think you might have been
brainwashed?
I have not been brainwashed.
Kill the girl. Kill the girl.
-Homer!
-What? What did I say?
Church, cult. Cult, church.
So we get bored
someplace else every Sunday.
Does this really change
our day-to-day lives?
Of course not.
Except that we're all moving
to the Movementarian agricultural compound
-to be near the Leader and serve him.
-I'm not leaving my home.
(door opens)
(chuckles) Oh, yes, you are.
I'm afraid it's our home now.
This house will become the new
local welcome center for this district.
And it didn't cost us a dime.
Springfield has been overrun by a strange
and almost certainly evil sect
calling themselves "the Movementarians."
In exchange for your home
and all your money,
the leader of this way-out
and wrong religion
claims he'll take believers away
on his spaceship to the planet Blisstonia.
Excuse my editorial laugh. (laughs) but--
Ladies and gentlemen, I've just learned
of a change in this stations management.
Welcome, Movementarians.
Continue to improve our lives.
I love you, perfect Leader, and new CEO
of KBBL Broadcasting.
Homer Simpson, your family will be
housed here
for the first 100,000 years.
-Then something might open up in a double.
-(chuckles) Why even unpack?
-(groans)
-Dad and all these other people
are obviously the products
of mental conditioning.
Yeah. Maybe it'll wear off,
like his interest in CB radio.
That's a negatory, good buddy!
I kind of think it's cool. Just pretend
you're in a zombie movie.
Besides, this is just another place
for me to wreak my special brand
of hysterical havoc.
These rubes in robes haven't met the likes
of Bart Simpson before.
(cackles)
I love the Leader.
Of course you do.
This so-called "new religion"
is nothing but a pack
of weird rituals and chants
designed to take away the money of fools.
Let us say the Lord's Prayer 40 times,
but first let's pass the collection plate.
(chuckles nervously) Looks like
slim pickings today, Reverend.
Oh, Lord. Uh, try
the emergency plate, Ned.
-I don't think that's gonna do it.
-Um...
See, Marge? Our lives
are so much better now.
(over P.A.) You two, stop talking
and resume the lima bean harvest.
When we got married, you promised me
my harvesting days were over.
-(all murmuring)
-MAN: What's going on?
-Whoa.
-What's going on?
Look! The forbidden barn opens.
-(all gasping)
-WOMAN: He's coming!
(all chattering)
Oh, boy. We get to see the Leader pass by.
We toil in the fields, and he rides around
in a Rolls-Royce?
Yes, it would be nice
if he'd buy American,
but what are you gonna do?
I'm covered in the dust
of the Leader. He favors me!
I am even dustier. Dustier than thou!
Oh, look who the new pet is.
I've never been so happy.
Smithers, why haven't I heard
of this "the Leader"?
He's as rich and wicked as I,
but he seems to enjoy tax-exempt status.
(chuckles) Actually, sir,
with our creative bookkeeping
and corporate loopholes, we only pay
three dollars a year.
(gasps) You're right.
We're getting screwed.
There must be
something I can do about this.
Wait. Yes.
I think I know just the thing.
(cackling)
Uh, sir?
You have to tell me what your plan is,
or-or nothing will happen.
Oh, yes. Of course. The plan.
-You see me as a god, right, Smithers?
-Absolutely, sir.
-You'd kneel before me.
-Boy, would I!
Yes. Uh, then I'll form my own religion
with its own symbol.
We'll use this special "K."
I believe that's already
a breakfast cereal, sir.
-And people worship it?
-In a way.
All right then. Uh, how about this?
Uh, why don't you leave
the symbol to me, sir?
Ladies and gentlemen, behold your new god,
Mr. Burns.
-(all gasp)
-Ahoy-hoy, lowly mortals.
In addition to working for me,
you may now praise me as your Almighty.
Amen, sir. Mmm!
(groaning)
(screams)
Uh, we'll try this again tomorrow.
Ah, he's all right. But he's no bowl
of Special "K."
This is ridiculous. We're already married.
But, Marge, we're not mass married.
At least you got to choose your mate.
We got matched up on the printout.
-Hey. Remember our agreement. I'm the man.
-You're the man!
-I could have done a lot worse, Mother.
-Speak for yourself.
So, do you enjoy comic books?
And who can tell me where thunder
and lightning come from?
Yes, Bart?
The Leader, ma'am.
Very good, Bart.
And who invented Morse code?
Oh. I should know this one.
The--The Leader?
Ah. Correct again.
He's wrong! You're wrong!
the whole damn system is wrong! (screams)
What's the matter, Lisa?
You used to be such a good student.
Don't you want to please your teachers
and get good grades?
(sighs) Grades?
(to the tune of "This Old Man")
♪ We love him, he loves we ♪
♪ We're the leader's family ♪
These lima beans are even better than
the ones we had for breakfast and lunch.
Oh! A lima bean that looks
just like the Leader!
-I'll put it with the others.
-Homer.
You know I always try to put
the best face on everything,
but there's no face on that damn bean!
We hate it here!
And your family wants to leave.
BART AND LISA: No, we don't, Mother.
We love the Leader.
No!
All righty. Time for bed.
I'm leaving this place,
and you'd better step aside.
Lady, people are free to go
whenever they wish.
(people groaning)
-(growling)
-(barking)
Hi-yah!
(barking)
(screaming)
Oh. I never thought
I'd have to do this again.
(panting) Reverend Lovejoy!
(coughs) You've gotta help me.
My entire family has been taken in
by the evil Movementarians.
Oh, I feel for you, my child,
and I'd like to help you.
(clears throat)
(groans)
(clinks)
Now, how are we going to
get my Homie back?
-(screeching sound)
-I'll kidnap him for 50,
deprogram him for 100,
and I'll kill him for 500.
No, no, no. Just the first two.
All right. I'll throw in
the killing for free.
-(vehicle approaching)
-TOGETHER: Yay! Here comes the leader!
What an honor. We've been called
into the presence of--
(all grunting)
Marge? You're the Leader?
You don't look anything like the beans.
-Knock him out, Reverend!
-Ow! Ooh!
Ow!
Oh, the devil has given him
superhuman strength.
Give me that, you noodle-armed choir boy!
-Ow!
-Well, that didn't do it, Mr. Kilt.
Look. Let's the three of us
try it together.
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
Oh! Ooh! Why?
Oh, you're gonna break like matchsticks
I promise you that!
Hey. I made some Rice Krispie squares
for our hungry deprogrammerinos.
Aw, man! You ruined
the atmosphere, ya daft pansy!
Well, this is my rumpus room.
Ach! Don't call it that!
Outsiders have kidnapped
some of our property.
We must respond with our deadliest weapon.
The lawyers.
-(bell ringing)
-Go! Go! Go!
(chattering)
(siren wailing)
Attention, all citizens.
Even though the leader himself
is completely nonviolent...
(sirens wailing)
...he urges you to be as violent
as you like in capturing the Simpsons.
-(sirens stop)
-(tires screech)
(indistinct chattering)
What are you doing?
They're not here, you idiots!
Idiots? That's slander, sir,
and we have it on tape.
All right. I'll get out
my checkbook. (grumbles)
-What was that?
-Ah, I said-- (grumbles)
So, you kids really love the Leader, huh?
Even more than your parents?
-Yeah. No contest.
-Of course. Absolutely.
All right already.
But do you love the Leader
more than having your very own
brand-new hover bikes?
(spacial humming)
(both gasp)
What do you have to say
about the Leader now, huh? Huh?
-The hell with him.
-What Leader?
He can take a flying leap
as long as I am concerned.
-And who do you love now?
-BOTH: Hover bikes!
(groans) Close enough.
BOTH: Yay!
-(all groan)
-(laughs)
Sorry, kids. There's no
such thing as hover bikes.
They're just a couple of
Huffys on a fishing line.
But we heard them hovering.
Oh, I'm afraid I played a dirty part
in this little charade.
(spacial humming)
-Well, can we at least keep the bikes?
-Oh, no. No, no. No, no, no.
They're due back at the store by 6:00.
Get off 'em. Get off. Off. Get off.
All right.
Now, what's so all-fire great
about your fancy-pants Leader?
The Leader knows all and sees all.
Ooh. Well, that is impressive.
And he's going to take us
to a wonderful new planet.
Oh, this Leader,
he sounds like a grand fella.
Willie, I'm not sure
we're making any headway here.
Would you shut up, woman.
He's talking about my leader.
Uh, maybe we should take
a little break-a-rooney, huh?
Anyone like a draft beer?
Beer? (salivating)
Would you like a tall, frosty one, Homer?
(grunting)
HOMER: No. Must resist temptation.
Go ahead. Give in. Beer! Beer!
Ooh. These cotton-poly blends
are so comfortable.
Go on, Homer. Our commandments clearly
state that beer is all right.
Try some.
(chattering)
-This man is coming with us.
-Homer, you don't have to go with them.
But I want to go.
Well, I would say the matter is settled.
You know, I pride myself
on being a good host,
so I'm obliged to offer you a beer,
but I'm so darn mad
it's gonna be mostly head.
Homer, come back!
-That's my husband!
-He's our husband now.
ALL: Yay!
I'm glad I'm back.
Because the moment that sweet, sweet beer
hit my tongue,
I was born again!
-(both gasp)
-Hallelujah!
Now I can show all of you
what I've come to realize.
The reason we're not allowed
in the forbidden barn
is because there is no
intergalactic spaceship.
He's taken our money just so he can...
build one hell of a spaceship!
-(all gasping)
-LEADER (on speaker): Homer Simpson,
because of your lack of faith,
you've ruined mankind's chance
for salvation.
-Whoops.
-Nice going there, Homer.
Oh, my gosh. Maybe he was telling
the truth about everything.
Oh, mercy. He's the real deal!
(vehicle humming)
(humming)
(all groan)
Come back. Come back!
Willie still loves ya, O Great One!
(gasping and groaning)
Stranger, you're a-trespassing
on my dirt farm.
Uh, do you happen to need a messiah?
No, but I'll take
them sacks of money from ye.
(groans)
I should have stayed
with the Promise Keepers.
Damn it!
It fell apart like everything else
I've ever believed in.
Oh, I guess it's back to
good old-fashioned voodoo.
Wow! I need a drink!
Come with me.
Uh, is that your collar, Reverend?
Uh, yes. (chuckles)
How did that get down there?
Come back to papa, baby.
To think, I turned to a cult
for mindless happiness...
-when I had beer all along.
-(clears throat)
And you, Marge, the bringer of beer.
It's wonderful
to think for ourselves again.
You said it, Sister.
MAN: You are watching Fox.
TOGETHER: We are watching Fox.
(theme music plays)
Shh!
Captioned by Visual Data Media Services