♪ The Simpsons ♪
(chalk screeches)
(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(tires screeching)
(horn honks)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
♪♪ (big band music plays)
♪♪ (carnival music plays)
(elephants trumpet)
Maggie, can you say "Ba-ba"?
Can you say "Mama"?
-Can you say "Get bent"?
-Bart!
Mr. Rogers says it
all the time.
-He does not.
-Maggie, can you say "Daddy"?
Daddy.
-Kitty. Kitty.
-Be-bop. Be-bop.
Shove-it. Shove-it.
-(burps)
-Did you hear that? She said "burlap."
I don't think so.
Oh, Maggie,
when are you going to talk?
Well, don't push her.
Remember:
"'Tis better to remain silent
and be thought a fool
than to open your mouth
and remove all doubt."
What does that mean?
Better say something,
or they'll think you're stupid.
-Takes one to know one.
-Swish.
According to
Fretful Mother Magazine,
if Maggie doesn't talk
by age one,
we should consider
a corrective tongue extender.
Hey, what was my first word?
Uh, well...
(Marge giggling)
Whoa!
HOMER:
Hee hee hee hee.
Yes!
Ay, caramba!
You know,
I don't think I remember.
But the story of Lisa's
first word is very cute.
BOTH:
Tell it, Mom. Tell it, Mom.
Yeah, tell it, Mom.
Well, this story begins in that
unforgettable spring of 1983.
Ms. Pacman struck a blow
for women's rights.
A young Joe Piscopo
taught us how to laugh.
Before Lisa was born,
we lived in a tiny apartment
on the lower eastside
of Springfield.
(Italian accent)
♪ Chipwich for sale ♪
♪ Chocolate chip
or oatmeal raisin ♪
♪ Chipwich for sale ♪
Youse guys want
to play stickball?
Certainly.
-Yeah, sure.
-Over here. Come on.
Did you girls watch
the last episode of MASH?
(Irish accent)
That Mike Farrell really boils my potato.
(Italian accent)
I miss-a da Klinger already.
♪ When the working day
is done♪
♪ Girls just wanna
have fun ♪
♪ That's all we really want ♪
Homer!
(chuckling)
Homer's what grownups call me.
Call me Daddy.
-Homer.
-Daddy.
Dad-dad-da...
Yes?
Domer.
(snickering)
Why, you little...
(snoring)
Ooh!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
HOMER:
Ah, he'll tire himself out soon.
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Then the prince
and the princess...
(yawns)
Got married and lived
happily ever after.
Then what happened?
Uh...
they had 30 sons
and 30 daughters.
What were their names?
Dennis... Brad...
Mavis...
Brad...
(snoring)
No, this is true.
The Coast Guard
arrested Boy George
for scraping the barnacles
off his dinghy.
(guttural laughter)
Hi-yo!
Hi-yo
(laughing)
Got your nose.
Got your wallet.
(toilet flushing)
No!
Bart, don't you ever
do that again.
Understand?
-Beep.
-(growling)
Guess what, Homie.
There's going to be twice
as much love in this house
as there is now.
We're gonna start doing it
in the morning?
-No.
-Oh.
We're going to have
another baby.
Marge, that's...
Bye-bye, keys.
-(flushing)
-Ohh!
Hear that, Bart?
You're going have a little
brother or sister to play with.
Who did this?
Baby.
Bad baby!
(laughing)
(sigh)
Uh-oh!
(milk dripping)
I'm afraid we're going
to need a bigger place.
No, we won't.
I've got it
all figured out.
The baby can have Bart's crib.
Bart can sleep with us
until he's 21.
Won't that warp him?
My cousin Frank did it.
You don't have
a cousin Frank.
He became Francine back in '76.
Then he joined that cult.
I think his name
is Mother Shibubu now.
(groans)
That afternoon,
we left Bart with my sisters
and went house hunting.
Hey, Bart, want a dollar?
Uh, uh, uh!
You know what
I want to hear.
♪ I'm a little teapot,
short and stout ♪
♪ This is my handle ♪
♪ This is my spout ♪
♪ The itsy-bitsy spider
went up the water spout ♪
Oh, yeah.
Love that spout medley.
Now, Mr. and Mrs. Simpson,
the only houses I have
in your price range
are in the neighborhood
colorfully referred to
as The Rat's Nest.
(gunshots and sirens)
This one just came
on the market.
Oh, dear!
(nervous laughter)
Now, here we have
beautiful hardwood floors,
track lighting...
(sniffing)
What's that stench?
Once you get used to the
smell of melted hog fat,
you'll wonder how you ever
did without it.
Mmm... hog fat.
Let's keep looking.
(sniffing)
Ooh. Do you smell something?
Argh, why buy a house
when ye can buy a houseboat?
Excuse me.
(growls)
Don't forget
to check out the galley.
That's real shag carpeting.
-Argh.
-(cats meowing)
Oh, once we get
the cats out of the way,
it won't be bad.
Actually, according to the will,
the cats own the house.
You'd be their tenants.
(hissing)
I wish we lived
in the kitty house.
I could have trained them
to be my unholy
army of the night.
Go, my pretties. Kill! Kill!
We were about to give up
when we found a house
that was perfect.
Just imagine what
we can do with this place.
Wow.
How much? How much?
Well, here's what
they're asking.
I can't afford that.
Dad, I have a problem.
Why did you come to me?
I don't know nothing.
I used to get by on my looks.
Now they're gone,
withered away
like an old piece of fruit.
(sobbing)
-Are you done?
-No, not yet.
I was voted the handsomest boy
in Albany, New York.
Dad, I don't need advice.
I need $15,000 to buy a home.
Oh, well,
all I own is this house
that I built
with my own two hands.
You didn't build this house.
You won it in
a crooked '50s game show.
I ratted on everybody
and got off scot-free.
Ha ha!
All right, son.
I'll sell this dump
and write you a check.
Dad, first you gave me life.
Now you've given me
a home for my family.
I'd be honored
if you came to live with us.
Thank you.
How long before you ship Grampa
off to the old folks home?
About three weeks.
(laughing)
Maggie, I'll give you
this cookie if you talk.
What? What?
D'oh!
All right, you win round seven.
When are we gonna get
to my first word?
-Your what what?
-My first word!
You don't want
to hear that story.
I know. I'll tell you
about the time
I got locked in the bank vault
with Mr. Mooney.
It was another one
of my harebrained schemes.
-Dad!
-Wait a minute.
That was a Lucy Show.
Okay, where were we?
Mom was preggers, and Dad just
threw our money down this sinkhole.
Ah, yes,
I remember the day
we moved in.
(grunting)
Hey, Homer, this house sucks.
Bart, I told you
not to use that word.
Call me Daddy.
Homer. Naah...
(grunting)
♪ We welcome you
to the neighborhood ♪
♪ Sing fa-la-la-la-la ♪
♪ La-la-la la-la-la ♪
♪ Fa-la-la-la-la-la-la ♪
♪ From now on,
you'll be history ♪
-♪ You'll be his... ♪
♪ You'll be history ♪
Buenos dias, neighboritos.
The handle's Flanders,
but my friends call me Ned.
Hi, Flanders.
Who the hell are you?
My name's Todd.
Would you be my friend?
You're funny.
(laughing)
If you need anything,
just give a whistle.
I could use a TV tray.
-Well, gee...
-What?
I just this minute
bought it at the hardw--
You said anything.
Heh. Well, sure.
You can borrow it
for a little while.
And that little while is now
eight years and counting.
(chuckles)
Anyway, Bart had just
entered the terrible twos.
♪ I am so great ♪
♪ Everybody loves me,
I am so great... ♪
Honey... honey... honey...
honey... honey...
Could you please be quiet?
♪ Quiet! Biet! Diet! ♪
Siet! Fiet!
Bart, get out!
HOMER: It's not easy
to juggle a pregnant wife
and a troubled child,
but somehow I managed to fit in
eight hours of TV a day.
(screaming)
♪♪
(laughing)
Hey, kids...
(goofy chuckle)
Summer's just around the corner,
and Krusty Burger
is the official meat-flavored
sandwich of the 1984 Olympics.
Cootchie-cootchie-coo.
(yells)
-Krusty funny.
-Duh.
It's all part of our Krusty
Burger Olympic sweepstakes.
Just scratch off the name
of the Olympic event
on your game card,
and if America wins
a gold medal,
you win a free Krusty Burger.
Mm-mm-mmm.
-MAN: And cut.
-Blah!
I almost swallowed
some of the juice.
I'll be tasting that for weeks.
-Great spot, K.C.
-Put a sock in it, preppy.
How much are these
free burgers gonna cost me?
Not to worry, Mr. K.
We've rigged the cards.
They're all in events
that communists never lose.
I like. I like.
This just came
over the wires, Big K.
Uh-huh. "Soviet Boycott."
"U.S. Unopposed in Most Events."
How does this affect
our giveaway?
Let's see.
You personally stand to lose
$44 million.
(groaning)
Oy!
Bart, from now on,
the baby sleeps in the crib.
Crib... crib... I'm a baby.
All right, I know how
to handle this.
Just use a little
reverse psychology.
Let's go, Marge.
Leave the baby
with his little crib.
D'oh!
(grunting)
(hammering)
Ah, Homer J. Simpson,
you're a genius.
I know you like clowns,
so I made you this bed.
Now you can laugh
yourself to sleep.
GOOFY VOICE:
If you should die before you wake...
(evil laughter)
Can't sleep.
Clown will eat me.
MALE SPORTSCASTER:
Oh, doctor, we are seconds away
from the 100-meter butterfly,
and with the East German--
(chuckling)
...women shaving their backs
9,000 miles away,
the Americans are heavy favorites.
(stomach growling)
Patience, my pet.
(gunshot)
And the Americans jump out
to an early lead.
Help! Help!
FEMALE SPORTSCASTER:
Although, we should point out
that many of the other women
represent countries
that don't have swimming pools.
MAN: Boo-hoo!
You're breaking my heart.
Homie, I think
the baby's coming.
Wow, a baby
and a free burger.
Could this be
the best day of my life?
Coming up next, an hour-long
episode of Mama's Family.
Yes!
We'll take good care
of your boy, Simpson.
Enjoy the miracle of creation.
Shut up, Flanders.
So, kids, what do you
want to play?
-Good Samaritan!
(gasps)
I get to clothe the leper.
Lucky.
Suppertime, boys.
Oh, boy! Liver!
Iron helps us play.
I want to go home.
No, I don't.
♪ I got the joy,
joy, joy, joy ♪
♪ Down in my heart ♪
Where?
♪ Down in my heart to stay ♪
♪ And if the devil
doesn't like it ♪
♪ He can sit on a tack ♪
Ouch!
♪ Sit on a tack... ♪
Pa, can you help me
with my psalms?
Ah!
Oh, Bart, you met
Grandma Flanders.
Hope she didn't scare you.
Hello, Joe.
(gasping)
Little Lisa...
I've already started you
a college fund
at Lincoln Savings and Loan.
According to this magazine,
Bart might be jealous of her.
Yeah, well, Bart can kiss
my hairy, yellow butt.
From now on,
the baby sleeps in the crib.
Iron helps us play.
(evil laughter)
Hello, Joe.
From now on,
the baby sleeps in the crib.
Iron helps us play.
(evil laughter)
Hello, Joe.
Bart, there's someone in here
who wants to meet you.
Well, Bart, what do you
think of little Lisa?
I hate you.
I saved this newspaper
from the day Lisa was born.
"Mondale to Hart:
'Where's the beef?'"
"Where's the beef?"
What the hell is that
supposed to mean?
(laughs)
"Where's the beef?"
No wonder he won Minnesota.
Everyone agreed that Lisa
was a beautiful baby.
Here she is.
-(exhaling)
-(Lisa coughing)
Isn't that cute?
She's coughing.
Aw.
I'm going to give her a kiss.
Mmm.
(loud kiss)
-I know a new song.
-You still here?
♪ Alouette,
gentille alouette ♪
♪ Alouette ♪
Um...
Uh...
♪ Alouette ♪
You already sang that part.
The older they get,
the cuter they ain't.
Hey, the baby just spit up.
A-wudge-a-wudge-
a-wudge-a-woo.
a-wue-a-wudge-a-woo.
Welcome back to the final day
of this the 23rd Olympiad,
brought to you
by Krusty Burger.
You people are pigs!
(sobbing)
I personally am going to spit
in every 50th burger.
I like those odds.
In a moment, we'll see
the courageous Korean gymnast,
Kim Jong,
who made a perfect dismount
on what was later revealed
to be a broken leg.
-(bone snaps)
-(agonized screaming)
(chuckles) Ouch! But first,
let's go to the boxing venue.
Please, please,
please, please...
HOWARD COSELL: The American, Drederick
Tatum, does a triumphant turkey trot
over the supine Swede.
One's thoughts turn to
Alexander of Macedon's victory
at Granicus and Issus.
(chanting)
U.S.A.! U.S.A.! U.S.A.!
Carl Lewis, I could kiss you!
(chuckling)
She has the reflexes
of a young Mary Lou Retton.
Have a wowipop.
Can I have a lollipop?
Oh, Bart, I'm afraid
that was the last one.
But I've got something
even better for you--
a rubella inoculation.
(chuckling)
♪♪ (humming "Rock-A-Bye Baby")
I want to hold the baby.
I'm sorry, Bart,
you're too little.
Here, Bart,
you can hold my beer.
-Homer!
-What?
Good night, honey.
-Hello, Lisa.
-(snipping)
Lisa, time for your feed--
(screaming)
-Who's cuter now?
-(snipping)
She started it.
(giggles)
(giggling)
Stupid mailman.
Squeal on me.
-(bell chimes)
-Hidey-ho, Simpson!
Your son shoved this
through our doggie door.
And since we're returning
your second-born,
you think you could see your way
to returning my TV tray--
Boy, you get over
to the corner
and you... Yeah.
I liked it when it was me,
Mom, and Homer.
You wrecked everything.
I'm leaving. Good-bye!
Bart.
-What did you say?
-Bart.
Suffering succotash!
You can talk!
(grunts)
Mom, Dad!
She can talk!
Say it again, Lis.
Bart.
Bart, Bart, Bart, Bart, Bart.
I'm her first word.
Well, I'm not surprised.
Lisa's crazy about you.
She thinks you hung the moon.
Wow.
Lisa, can you say
"Mommy"?
Mommy.
Can you say,
"David Hasselhoff"?
David Hasselhoff.
-Can you say "Daddy"?
-Homer.
No, sweetie, "Daddy."
Homer.
D'oh!
(laughing)
I was sitting there.
I don't see your name on it.
It's right there.
Bart, don't write
on the rug.
Ha ha!
Mom yelled at you.
-Did not!
-Did too.
You know, Maggie,
the sooner kids talk,
the sooner they talk back.
I hope you never say a word.
(switch clicks)
(door closes)
Daddy.
♪♪
Shh.
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.