♪ The Simpsons 25x15 ♪
The War of Art
Original Air Date on March 23, 2014
(bird chirping)
(groaning)
Hm... hmm?!
"Lisa wants
"a dot-dot-dot
guinea pig"? Mm.
(humming happily)
(curious grunt)
(yells)
(Homer smacking and chewing)
(gulps, swallows)
(curious grunt)
Hey, Homer, did you know that
guinea pigs are self-groomers?
And when the get excited,
they jump straight up.
- It's called "popcorning."
- Lisa got to you.
I don't know how,
but she got to you.
(phone buzzing)
(chiming)
Emojis.
Now she's gone too far.
Lisa, your father and I are very
concerned about all this hinting.
(groans)
I've never had a pet
of my very own.
My clock is ticking.
I don't want to be
one of those girls
who waits till she's 16
to decide if she's ready,
and then it's too late.
(both grunt)
Well, we've
talked about it.
And if you really
want a guinea pig,
you'll have to sign
this contract.
"I, Lisa Simpson,
hereby promise
to take full responsibility
for this dog, cat, other."
- Circle "other."
- "This includes feeding, bathing,
"cleaning of droppings
and barfings,
and when the time comes,
burying or flushing."
Boilerplate, boilerplate, boilerplate.
We can skip all this litter box stuff.
"If pet becomes Internet superstar,
all rights revert to father."
Sign here, here, initial here,
one more over here. And done.
Oh, my God! I'm
getting a guinea pig!
Thank you, thank you, thank you,
thank you, thank you!
The kid-parent contract.
Unenforceable, yet you feel
like you didn't completely cave.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
You're doing the right thing
adopting a rescue pig.
You know, most of these
guys are rejects
from the big guinea-pig
mills in the Midwest.
Oh, I can't tell you
how many mill pigs
we get in here who have
bumblefoot or the slobbers.
You don't have
children, do you?
This one whistled at me!
Ooh, that could
be the one.
Oh, but that orange guy
looks like a pumpkin.
(gasps) But this
fellow is so fuzzy!
Well, they all
have their charms.
This one's nibbling
a sunflower seed.
Look at that hair. Aw, I just
want to comb it forever!
Have you seen a
pinker nose? (gasps)
I have now!
Lisa, you've just
got to choose one.
Lisa?
She's gone, honey.
She's gone.
That one's fur looks
like a tuxedo!
A Band-Aid on
its tail, aw!
(gasps)
Albino!
I'm definitely getting this one.
Oh, but I forgot about this one.
Oh, my God, I never
even saw this one!
(gasps)
Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh...
Maybe I should get
that sick one.
If I don't, no one else will.
(gasps)
Bart, list your top
five, best to worst.
No, no, no, no!
Worst to best.
I just wish the gray one had
the brown one's personality.
Okay, Dad, give me your phone. I
need to look at the pictures again.
Aw, aw, aw! Aw, aw!
Okay, this is the guinea pig
that will make me happy.
She thinks she's decided.
Don't say a thing.
Don't blow this.
Okay, now, you sure you
only want just one?
They tend to do
better in pairs.
(gasps)
I could get two?
(engine revs,
tires screech)
HOMER:
Farting tweakers rule!
I've tried to give Pokey a perfect
replica of his natural habitat.
Peruvian feather grass,
an Incan sleeping mat,
and a portrait of Marisol Espinoza,
the Vice President of Peru.
Are you sure you didn't create
a perfect habitat for you?
I wish I could
live in there.
Well, there's plenty of
room because Pokey's gone.
(gasps)
Where'd he go?
(squeaking)
This looks like a job for...
fireplace tongs.
(tongs clang, Pokey squeaks)
No!
(Pokey squeaking)
Oh, my God!
He's in the walls!
I hear chewing.
No, that's a much
bigger animal.
(grunts)
Kettle corn. The heroin
of the farmers' market.
I've lost my guinea pig!
(squeaking, tapping nearby)
Pokey!
Our boat painting!
I'm sorry, Mom.
(groans)
That's okay, sweetheart.
Your pig thingy
didn't mean it.
It's just, it felt comforting to
know that while we watched TV,
there was art going
on behind us.
(moans)
Oh, well, I guess
we have to go
to an art gallery
and buy a new painting.
Sure, we could go to a fancy gallery
and spend a bunch of money, or...
Mm... hmm, hmm, hmm, hmm?
Yeah, Milhouse played
the violin for years
until it turned out the vibrations
were screwing up his bones.
Yeah, these seem great.
(sniffs)
Oh, too bad someone
used cello rosin.
(groaning in frustration)
(gasping in awe)
Oh, my gosh,
that's beautiful!
I've never seen a painting
with a lighthouse before.
(laughs)
Oh, that. That was on the wall of
Kirk's bachelor pad, back when we were
(whispers):
Separated.
Yeah, it's a great piece.
I didn't have a mirror, so I shaved in
the reflection of the chrome frame.
This could be our new
living room painting.
I don't know.
How about this poster
of a really rocking jukebox?
You know it's rocking 'cause music
notes are coming out of it.
Painting's only 20 bucks.
Oh, please, Homie?
I'll throw in
the tiny violins.
(Homer humming classical melody)
Oh, it looks great!
Well... to me, it looks like...
garbage salad.
But that's the great
thing about art.
Everyone can have their own
opinion about why it sucks.
I've got to get rid of this ugly
chrome frame from Kirk's bachelor bad.
I hate to think of the things
this mirror has reflected.
Hmm!
Hey, look. There's a signature
that the frame covered up.
"Johan Oldenveldt."
Here he is!
"Johan Oldenveldt, painter.
"Lived in Amsterdam, Paris. Prolific
early 20th century naturalist."
Ooh, I think this was painted
by someone famous.
Maybe it's valuable.
We should have
it appraised.
Pfft! You guys are crazy. I
never even heard of that guy.
It's not like it was painted
by Leonardo Da Vinci Code.
Now, here's what
makes art valuable...
One: Nudity. Two: Holograms. Three:
Something terrible happening to Jesus.
Ah yes, seascape,
marvelous natural light,
classic use of gouache.
You're right.
This is an early-career
Oldenveldt.
- Quite valuable.
- Oh, my God!
I expect it to go somewhere
between 80 to $100,000.
(gasps)
Nobody touch it!
Bart, stop looking at it!
- But I want to see it!
- No, you'll wear it out!
Baby, you saw something in this
painting, and you were right.
Wow, the Van Houtens
owned this for years,
and never knew how
much it was worth.
Think how happy they'll be when we
sell it and split the money with them.
Split it? Whoa! Whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa!
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa...
whoa!
(cell phone ringing)
HOMER: Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Oh!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Split it with them?
Kirk and Luann didn't know what the
painting was worth when they sold it.
Yes, they sold it to us.
So, now it's our painting.
We can hang it on our wall, cut
eyeholes in it to spy on people.
Or sell it for lots of money
which we keep.
For ourselves?
This dude gets it.
(groans)
But the Van Houtens
are our friends.
Are they, Marge?
If you think about it, aren't
they really just the parents
of a kid who happens
to hang out with our kid?
All our friends
are like that.
Well, how would you feel
if we sold them something
that turned out
to be valuable?
I would feel A) Happy
for their good fortune,
B) Proud to know
rich people,
and C) Grateful for an opportunity
to learn from a mistake.
(door bell chimes)
MARGE: How about this?
What if we give the Van
Houtens 25% of the money?
Then they'll just be mad about
the 65% that we're keeping.
- Marge, you like kindness, right?
- Sure.
So, even if we gave Kirk and
Luann some of the money,
the knowledge of what they could
have had will eat away at them,
like piranhas devouring
a wounded yeti.
It's kinder never
to tell them.
Okay, I see your point.
We should sell the painting,
keep all the money,
and never, ever tell
the Van Houtens.
Mm-hmm!
(deep inhale)
(gasping)
(Marge and Homer gasping)
What'll it take to
buy your silence?
Hmm.
Okay, Milhouse, the guys in back
are shining up your new bike.
And all I have to do
is not say anything
about some painting
to my Mom and Dad?
Oh, sweetie, you want your
parents to be happy, don't you?
I guess.
(laughing):
"I guess"!
You're funny!
No wonder Lisa's
in love with you.
- She is?!
So, if I keep my mouth shut, you
get me new wheelie sneakers,
and Bart agrees to promote
and encourage use
of my new cool
nickname, "C.J."
(Homer grunts)
You got it, Ceej.
(doorbell rings)
You found out that painting
was worth big bucks,
and you weren't
gonna tell us?!
I don't know what
you're talking about.
(loud whisper):
Hide the treasure!
I'm sorry, Mr. S.
I cracked!
We had a deal. And now
we've got nothing!
(blows)
We considered you
our friends.
We trusted you! I let Homer
use our master bathroom!
Then you stab us
in the back!
If you knew you sold a
valuable painting for nothing,
how could you live
with yourselves?
We were just trying
to be... kind.
Kind?! You call it kind
to give us nothing?
We were gonna treat you to dinner
at an upscale chain restaurant
and never explain why,
but now forget it!
- Oh, so that's how it is!
- That's exactly how it is.
- Oh, is it?!
- Oh, it is!
(clears throat)
Luann, I hope we're
still on Thursday
for collecting used cell
phones for the troops.
I don't think you
need any help.
You're so good at...
collecting.
Oh!
Oh, that was cold, Luann!
So cold!
Brr!
Sarcastic brr!
See what happens
when we get greedy?
Honey, there's something
I want to show you.
An ATM receipt?
I don't know whose this is. I found
it next to the cash machine,
and I've always kept it.
Look at the balance.
Five figures!
With that painting, we could
have what these people have:
A money cushion.
No more living
paycheck to paycheck,
one lost retainer away
from the gutter.
I could write a check
with today's date on it.
That's the cushion.
♪
Tonight, a special report.
Fat cat art experts take advantage
of John and Jane Yard Sale.
So, would you characterize
your friend of many years
cheating you out of your painting as no
big deal, or a devastating betrayal?
Oh, definitely
betrayal, Kent.
Interesting. So if you see the
Simpsons walking down your street,
lock your doors and hide...
your friendship.
Great! Now we're raccoons,
the masked bandits
of the animal world!
Don't worry. No one's gonna
see this stupid show.
(both gasp, tires squeal)
(gasps)
The whole town's
turned against us!
(engine revs,
tires squeal)
Ooh, a support rock!
This one's against us.
This one's for us.
For, for, against,
for, against...
We don't even get this
many Christmas cards.
(all clamoring)
(all gasp)
There they are, the
Masterpiece Thievers!
Ah, shut your bone hole!
That painting belongs
to the Simpsons!
Sharing is what makes
a community strong!
All sales are final!
- Keep it! (clamoring)
- Finders keepers, moron!
You really think we're still
doing the right thing?
Just close your eyes and
think of the cushion.
First lot: "Untitled Landscape"
by Johan Oldenveldt,
from the Collection of Homer J.
And Marge B. Simpson.
Let's open the bidding
at $80,000.
The paddles, Marge!
Look at the paddles!
WOMAN:
Stop the auction!
That painting
belongs to me!
- (crowd gasps, murmurs)
- Dawn?
Good to see you
again, Beef Kirky.
Who is this woman?
Uhhhhhh...
While you two were separated,
Kirk and I used to be friends...
with banana-fits.
(Homer groans)
You told me you didn't see
anyone during our separation.
Uhhhhhh...
Madam, are you saying this
painting belongs to you?
Kirk stole it from me!
But I didn't know it was valuable
till I saw the story on TV.
What?! I bought that
painting! She's lying!
(gavel raps)
The auction is on hold until we
can determine the true ownership.
Our cushion!
Don't bother
coming home, Kirk!
Aw!
See what your
greed has done?
- Ow! - Anybody want to
give me a ride home?
- Going once? Going twice?
- (bangs gavel)
Sold! To the
lonely auctioneer!
Ah!
(cheering, laughter)
Thanks for
taking me in, man.
I guess I can't help but
feel fully responsible.
Oh, Luann, I'll never gaze
from my thick eyeglasses
into your thick
eyeglasses ever again.
What you need, my friend,
is a Canadian Duff.
Beauty, eh?
So... why does that chick
think she owns the painting?
Oh, Dawn and I went on a vacation to
a resort island called Isla Verde.
I bought the painting
in a café,
but that night she ran off
with a parasailing instructor.
Not your fault, man.
Those parasailing guys take
whatever they want.
It was never her painting.
That woman will say anything to keep
herself in electric cigarettes.
And I'd go back to that
Café Artiste to prove it,
but nothing's gonna
get me Luann back.
(snoring)
Okay, all I gotta do is take
a quick ferry to Isla Verde,
find Café Artiste, and they'll
back up Kirk's story.
That will prove the painting
was his... and now ours.
Oh, Homer Simpson, that painting
has torn the town apart,
destroyed Kirk
and Luann's marriage,
and everyone's very
worried about Milhouse.
He's been playing Dancing Revolution
for hours, but the TV is off.
But our cushion!
That picture has brought out
the worst in everyone!
Please! Just let it go!
(grunting)
You're not gonna
let it go, are you?
I wish I knew how.
This is so exciting!
My first time
establishing provenance!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Just remember,
if your mother asks, I took
you to a wine tasting.
That's a terrible thing
for a father to do.
That's why she'll
believe it.
Hmm, this quaint artist community
has gotten a little touristy.
♪
Excuse me. We're trying
to find Café Artiste.
Ah, yes. Top of the hill. Three
discos up, four gelatos on the left.
You can't miss it. It's right between
the disco and the gelato place.
Mmm. Hmm.
Mm-mm!
(door bell jingles)
Mm...
Welcome to Café Artiste!
Would you like
a glass of Strupo?
It's a liqueur made of fermented capers,
the official drink of the island.
Mmm! Sounds delicious.
It's not.
Hey, a friend of mine, uh,
bought a painting here.
Oh, yes, I remember
that painting.
And that is the
man I sold it to.
And that man
sold it to me!
That proves the
painting is mine!
And nothing can stop me from selling
it and keeping all the money!
I love art!
MAN:
Art?
What do you
know about art?
You don't even know
who painted that picture.
Yes, I do. It's a
Johan Oldenveldt.
Wrong! It's a me!
- A what?
- I painted it!
Me, Klaus Ziegler!
Who?
- Mm!
- Oh!
This is where I painted
your so-called Oldenveldt.
Prove it.
Aw, crap!
You're a forger?
"Forger" is such
a cruel word.
I'm an art forger.
Your painting was an
early, clumsy effort
which I gave to the café owner
to pay off my Strupo tab.
Whew!
Then why did the auction
house say it was real?
I have fooled galleries around the
world with my loving imitations.
Ziegler! Ziegler! Ziegler!
Ziegler!
Ziegler! Ziegler!
What you do is horrible...
ripping off geniuses who spent
years perfecting their styles.
Perhaps you are the
one who is horrible.
What?!
You only cared about that
painting when you thought
it was created by
someone famous.
Well, no, but now when I look
at it, all I see is a fraud.
Beauty is beauty.
My forgeries give pleasure to
people all over the world.
The only real question
to ask about art,
whether it's in the Louvre or on a
freshman's wall at Cal State Fullerton
is, "Did it move you?"
But, you still, I mean...
Oh, I suppose
you're right.
What if I never liked the painting
and only wanted it for money?
Then you, I respect.
(groans)
Oh, great. The
painting is worthless,
(glass shatters)
this was all for nothing,
and when Marge finds out,
she's gonna kill me.
Well, on that front, perhaps
I can be of assistance.
If there's one thing
art is good for,
it's to melt the frost which
often hardens a woman's heart.
While you're at it...
could you make me a couple more?
I'll pay you in Strupo.
(sighs)
Perfect.
Oh, now that's art.
(grunts)
Rocking.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
ZIEGLER:
The Gray Troll,
Brine of Madness,
Angel's Urine,
all names for the mysterious
elixir known as Strupo.
Though this fermented caper
solution was originally used
to dissolve seagull corpses, local
alcoholics soon found Strupo
to be a palatable
drink of last resort.
The noxious liqueur causes
powerful olfactory hallucinations,
gender confusion, and
wandering mouth.
So if you visit
Isla Verde,
be sure to say "ahoy" to the
crushing addiction of Strupo.
Strupo: Lose everything.
Shh!