♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screeching)
(liquid bubbling)
I'd like to thank everybody
who contributed
to Krusty's Kanned Food Drive.
Your generous donations
have made this
our slipperiest, slimiest
slobstacle course ever!
(chuckles)
Our contestants
will drop out of my nose
and blurp into a tub
of refried beans.
From there,
they'll stumble down
a sluice of rich,
eggy béarnaise sauce.
How can we afford it?
It's rancid!
And at the finish line--
a scrumptious parfait
of pudding, pickle brine
and detergent,
where a writhing pile of kids
will grope blindly
for hot dogs.
Krusty, please,
it burns!
(laughing)
Just think Lis, that's our pickle brine
burning Sideshow Mel.
That Sideshow Mel
thinks he's so big.
Whatever happened
to Sideshow Bob?
Don't you remember, Dad?
He framed Krusty.
He tried to kill Aunt Selma.
He rigged an election.
BART:
And he tried to murder me.
Oh, yeah.
But what I'll mainly
remember is the laughter.
I wonder what he's doing now.
Ah, Westminster Abbey.
Edward the Confessor himself
could not have done better.
Now to set the clocks
to Greenwich mean time.
(laughter)
(gasps)
My dear Abbey!
♪ This is the way we mop
the floor, mop the floor... ♪
Oh, must you bray night and day
at that infernal television?
Oh, look
who's talking.
Yeah, Bob. You used
to be on this show.
Don't remind me.
My foolish capering
destroyed more young minds
than syphilis and pinball
combined.
Oh, how I loathe that box.
That omnidirectional
sludge pump
droning and burping its...
Look here.
That's enough now.
I own 60% of that network.
All right,
break it up, boys.
It's time for work detail.
I suppose you don't like
tabloid newspapers either.
There, that's
the last condom wrapper.
(jet engine roars)
Ohh.
I renew my objection
to this pointless endeavor...
informally now
and by affidavit later...
time permitting.
Shut your word hole.
We got to get this place clean
for the air show.
Air show?
Buzz-cut Alabamians
spewing colored smoke
from their whiz jets
to the strains
of "Rock You Like a Hurricane"?
What kind of country-fried rube
is still impressed by that?
-Wow!
-Ooh!
-That looks so cool!
-Yeah.
(sadly)
Yeah.
I want to meet the first
female stealth bomber pilot.
During the Gulf War,
she destroyed 70 mosques
and her name is Lisa, too.
I want to see some birds get
sucked into the engines. Rare ones.
This year I'm making ear plugs
out of biscuit dough.
(bell dings)
They're ready.
So weary.
(yawning)
GIRL (on TV):
Grandma, this is
my friend Craig.
(laughter)
GRANDMA:
Friend?
You mean you two
aren't knocking boots?
(laughter)
Ever do the backseat
mambo, Craigy?
I know that voice.
TV's bottomless chum bucket
has claimed Vanessa Redgrave.
GRANDMA: Now I'm going to
haul ass to Lollapalooza!
(laughter)
-(motorcycle engine revving)
-Yee-ha!
Farewell, dear 'Nessa.
(20th Century Fox
musical fanfare theme)
Hey, you! The state's not paying you
five cents an hour to stand around.
-Now, get busy.
-Oh, I'll get busy.
I'll get very busy, indeed.
(diabolical laughter)
(chuckles)
You still got it, Bob.
Way to guard
the parking lot, Top Gun.
I have three medals
for this.
Hey, where is Sideshow Bob
and that guy who eats people
and takes their faces?
I'm right here, Chief.
Oh. Then where's
Sideshow Bob?
Uh, he ran off.
Oh, great.
Well, if anyone
asks, uh...
I beat him
to death, okay?
Right.
At this point in time,
I would like to
direct your attention
to the particular air vehicle
next to which I am
currently standing.
The Harrier jet is our
more dollar-intensive
ordinance delivery vectors.
Five tires?
Am I seeing things?
And although it looks
complicated,
it is so
well-designed
even a child
could fly it.
Can I fly it?
Of course you
can not.
(gasps)
Free Duff!
Viva life!
Ahh.
-(register dings)
-(whimpers)
Heh-heh-heh-heh.
(Milhouse imitating
machine gun)
Take that, Mom!
Take that, Dad!
Send me to a psychiatrist,
will you?
(imitating machine gun)
Take that, Dr. Sally Waxler!
(grunting)
(whooshing)
Uh, Colonel, they're
expecting you at the podium
in ten minutes.
(muttering)
(whistling)
Hmm.
What in the World
According to Garp?
Those are my dress towels!
Who's in my private washroom?
McGuckett?
Let me in.
-The door already is closed.
-What?
This is Colonel
Leslie "Hap" Hapablap.
If you don't open
that door,
I'll tear you up like
a Kleenex at a snot party!
You say you're
in the military?
Sweet Enola Gay, son!
I'm going to come in there
and corpse you up!
Corpse you up
and mail you to mama!
Well... where'd he go?
(sighs)
Got my knuckles
all lined up for nothing.
(kissing)
Sorry, ladies.
(laughs)
Look at that hunk of junk.
(sputtering)
You're ignorant!
That's the Wright
Brothers' plane.
At Kitty Hawk in 1903
Charles Lindbergh
flew it 15 miles
on a thimble
full of corn oil.
Single-handedly won us
the Civil War, it did.
So how do you know so much
about American history?
I pieced it together mostly
from sugar packets.
(buzzing)
Authorization code.
Code?! Son, this
is Colonel Hapablap.
That fool McGuckett
sprayed runway foam
all over Chuck Yeager's Acura.
Now get down there with
the shammy triple-time!
But, Colonel,
I'm under strict orders to..
Sweet Enola Gay, son!
Get moving or I'll tear you up
like a Kleenex at a--
(distastefully)
...snot party.
Sir, right away, sir!
They didn't have
any aspirin
so I got you
some cigarettes.
(growls)
Maybe my headache will go away
once the show starts.
(feedback screeching)
Ladies and gentlemen,
what a day for an air show!
Not a cloud in the sky!
Except perhaps...
a mushroom cloud.
(diabolical laughter)
Oops.
(nervous laughter)
Oh, forget it.
HAPABLAP:
"To slip the surly bonds of Earth
"and touch the face of God.
To fly"--
the dream of man
and flightless bird alike.
And now, hold on tight
as we blast through
the thrilling highlights
of aviation history!
(parade march playing)
Say...
did somebody say box kites?
BART:
No!
♪ Up, up and away... ♪
(crowd groaning)
The common box kite
was originally used
as a means
of drying wet string.
(whistling)
♪ Sing a song and sail
along the silver sky... ♪
Do you have to play
that rock music?
Every note is pounding
into my skull.
(grunts)
(whistling)
Anybody out there
feel the need for speed?
-ALL: Yay!
-Yay.
Then get ready for the pride
of the United States Air Force:
the British-made
Harrier Jump Jet!
♪ Here I am ♪
♪ Rock you
like a hurricane... ♪
Dad, why aren't
you looking?
Heh-heh. Why jerk my neck
around like a goon
when tyranno-vision decides
what I should look at.
Whoo, look!
It's Maggie!
Uh... Maggie?
-(gasping) Sideshow Bob!
-(gasping)
Hello, Springfield.
Sorry to divert your attention
from all the big noises
and shiny things,
but something's
been troubling me lately.
Television!
Wouldn't our lives
be so much richer
if television
were done away with?
What?
Surely he's not
talking about VH-1?
Why, we could revive the lost
arts of conversation...
and scrimshaw.
Thus, I submit to you
we abolish television...
permanently.
Go back to Massachusetts,
pinko.
Oh, and one more thing.
I've stolen a nuclear weapon.
If you do not rid this city
of television within two hours,
I will detonate it.
Farewell.
(clamoring)
By the way, I'm aware
of the irony of appearing on TV
in order to decry it, so don't
bother pointing that out.
(siren blaring)
Kids, everything's
gonna be okay!
Don't panic!
Just don't panic!
Mom, Mom! You're
stepping on my heels
and knocking my shoes off!
We can always get more shoes.
Move, move, move!
Stamp your hand
for re-entry.
Hey...
Cool. I want to be around when
those guns start going off.
Bart, no!
Wait! Wait, my children
are in there!
You must be
very proud, ma'am.
Our city will not negotiate
with terrorists.
Is there a city nearby
that will?
No need, sir.
We'll find that head case
faster than Garfield
finds lasagna.
Oh... I'm sorry.
My wife thought
that was gangbusters.
This elevator only goes
to the basement,
and someone made
an awful mess down there.
Watch out!
He's got his probe!
(imitating airplane)
(imitating machine gun)
Bart! Bart!
What are you doing?
We've got to get out of here.
Target sighted.
Launching air-to-nerd missile.
Oww! Come on!
Mom and Dad are waiting.
Bob is not here.
We have searched
every square inch of this base
and all we have found
is porno, porno, porno!
We have only 20 minutes left.
Send in the esteemed
representatives of television.
Hey, hey!
Now, this is
my kind of meeting.
Gentlemen, it's time we face up
to the un-face-up-to-able.
We must sacrifice television
in order to save the lives
of our townspeople.
Whoa! Whoa-ho-ho!
Let's not go nuts.
Would it really be worth living
in a world without television?
I think the survivors
would envy the dead.
I appreciate your passion
on behalf of your medium,
but I'm afraid
we're out of options.
Television must go.
May God have mercy
on our souls.
(screaming, cars collide)
And as my final newscast
draws to a close
I'm reminded of a few
of the events
that brought me
closer to you--
The collapse of
the Soviet Union,
premium ice
cream price wars,
dogs that were mistakenly
issued major credit cards,
and others
who weren't so lucky.
And so... farewell.
And, uh, don't forget
to look for my...
new column
in PC World magazine.
Muchas gracias, amigos
por todas las memorias
y super gracias a Goya!
Success!
They're giving in!
Blast!
I should have
made more demands.
Some decent local marmalade,
for one.
Oh, well. Next time.
Agh! Not my Extendo-Glove!
Oh, they haven't made those
since the war.
Oh! Not my Paris backdrop.
How am I going
to make fun of the frogs?
(sobs)
Wait. If I could
only stay on the air,
I'd have a hundred percent
of the audience.
Think of the ratings.
Okay, so we can't
go over the fence.
I feel so helpless.
What if something
happens to them?
I'm sure they're
fine, honey.
Well, at least they're
wearing clean underwear.
Free and easy, Lis.
There's nothing like
an unfurnished basement
for pure comfort.
Huh? Hurry up.
Mom and Dad are
probably worried sick.
You know what really frosts
my Kelvinator?
That fruit cup's probably
still laughing at us
from his damn
hidey hole.
I'd rather take an order
from Bill Clinton
than hear that guy's snooty
high-toned voice again, sir.
High-toned voice.
Bart, that's it.
I know where Sideshow
Bob is hiding.
(panting) When Bob broadcast
that message,
his voice was higher
than normal,
and what makes
your voice high?
Tight binding underwear?
Helium!
Sideshow Bob is
in the Duff blimp.
(constricted voice)
All Springfield trembles
before the might
of Sideshow Bob.
Blasted helium.
Shoo, shoo, shoo, shoo.
Ah-hah! That's better.
Gone. Gone too.
Fabulous. Marvelous.
This is the
Emergency Broadcast System.
Stand by for an urgent
bulletin.
KRUSTY:
Hey, hey!
(goofy laugh)
Krusty the Clown
is back on the air!
Eight... no, no!
12 hours a day!
The only game in town.
Krusty? But how?
Coming at you live
from the civil defense shack
in the remote alkali flats
of the Springfield badlands.
I'll be beaming out
11 watts of wackiness.
Hour after hour
of unscripted, unrehearsed
comedy featuring...
uh, you know...
Professor Gas Can
uh... and, uh, former
President Ike Eisenhower.
Let's get busy.
Oh, my utopia lies in ruins.
How naive of me
to think a mere atom bomb
could fell
the chattering cyclops.
(both gasping)
Well, at least
I'll have my revenge.
Bob, no!
Don't you see? That would
be taking the easy way out?
I agree.
(explosion)
(beeping)
Damn it, Bob.
There were plenty
of brand-new bombs
but you had to go for
that retro-'50s charm.
(scared gulps)
Well, if it isn't
my arch nemesis
Bart Simpson
and his sister Lisa
to whom I'm fairly indifferent.
So Krusty double-crossed you,
but your basic plan
was pure genius.
Where do you get your ideas?
Oh, please.
Let's not
embarrass us both
with that hoary old
"stall the villain
with flattery" scheme.
I... should have known you
were too smart to fall for that.
Really? What type of smart?
Book smart?
Because there are a lot of
people who are book smart
but it takes a very
special type of genius to...
CHIEF WIGGUM:
All right, Bob, it's over.
Come out with
your hands up.
No!
How did they find me?
(Lisa gasps)
LISA:
He's getting away!
Aw, not the Harrier.
We've got a war
tomorrow.
God bless
the idiot-proof Air Force.
They're gone!
HAPABLAP: Hell. Not the
Wright Brothers' plane.
The Smithsonian's gonna
have my ass on a platter.
BART:
Dad!
Help!
Aaah!
Hang on, boy!
Daddy's coming to save you!
D'oh!
Mom, I found
Sideshow Bob's hideout,
and I got a secret message
to the police,
and I had a blimp fall on me,
and I was in an atomic blast,
but I'm okay now.
Well, I wrecked the gate,
but you don't hear me bragging.
Now let's roll.
Ah, for the days
when aviation
was a gentleman's
pursuit--
back before
every Joe Sweat Sock
could wedge himself
behind a lunch tray
and jet off
to Raleigh-Durham.
Are you getting lots of bugs
in your mouth, too?
Yes.
(spitting)
Prepare to engage enemy.
Bogie's airspeed not sufficient
for intercept.
Suggest we get out and walk.
Jump, boy! I got ya!
I'm coming!
(both grunt)
Now you, boy!
(gasps)
You can't escape, Bob.
If the tennis rackets don't get you,
the pool skimmers will.
Whoo. I-- I never
planned to escape.
You see, this is
a kamikaze mission.
You and I are going
to kill Krusty the Clown!
-(laughs)
-(gasps)
Kids, Itchy and Scratchy
can't be here today
but instead, we've got
the next best thing--
It's the Stingy
and Battery Show.
♪ They bite and light ♪
♪ And bite and light and bite ♪
♪ Light, light... ♪
You know what
I'm talking about.
Uh-oh.
You can't
kill Krusty.
He made you
what you are.
Without him, you wouldn't even be
called "Sideshow."
(snarling)
(loud puttering)
What the hell is that?
A lawn mower?
Yah!
BART:
Get out of the way, Krusty!
What is the freaking holdup?
D-i-i-i-e, Krusty!
Di..!
Oh.
(siren wailing)
Ooh, sorry.
Uh, we don't normally drive
these in the Air Force.
Gotcha!
Ha-ha!
You TV-hating mutant!
What is your major
malfunction, Sideshow Bob?
Whoa, whoa...
Oh, my little
sugar bug.
Whoa, whoa.
I'm so glad
you're safe.
Whoa, whoa... mo-- mo-- Mom!
You're embarrassing me
in front of the Army guys.
How ironic.
My crusade against television
has come to an end so formulaic
it could have spewed
from the Powerbook of
the laziest Hollywood hack.
Hey, everybody!
I'm going to haul ass
to Lollapalooza!
ALL:
Here we go again!
(sadly)
...go again.
(fanfare)
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.