♪ The Simpsons ♪
(chalk screeches)
(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(tires screeching)
(horn honks)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
MAN: Products you could only
imagine before.
The S.S. Microwave.
(dings)
Ah, my crepes are done.
The Doggy Doorman.
Good evening, Rex.
And Mobilier--
The chandelier for your car.
(grunts)
Whoa!
All On: I can't believe
they invented it!
Hello, everybody.
I'm Troy McClure,
star of such films
as "'P' is for Psycho"
and "The President's
Neck is Missing."
But now I'm here
to tell you
about a remarkable
new invention.
(forceful groaning)
Until now, this was the only
way to get juice from an orange.
(groaning)
(gasps)
You mean there's a better way?
But that's all changed,
thanks to the Juice Loosener.
Let's meet the inventor,
Dr. Nick Riviera.
Hello, Troy.
Hi, everybody.
ALL: Hi, Dr. Nick.
Troy, would you like
a glass of orange juice?
I sure would,
but won't we have to pay
those outrageous
grocery store prices
for something the farmer
probably spit in?
Not anymore!
All thanks to the
new Juice Loosener.
(grinding)
Doctor, are you sure
it's on?
I can't hear a thing!
It's whisper quiet!
(plop)
You got all that
from one bag of oranges?
That's right.
Order now
and you'll also
get Sun and Run,
the suntan lotion
that's also a laxative.
Got to get a juicer.
Got to drink juice, lose weight.
Won't get chest pains from
answering the phone anymore.
Please don't tell
the supervisor
I have the flu.
I've been working
with a shattered pelvis
for three weeks.
(laughing)
(laughter stops)
(coughs)
Oh, my Juice Loosener
is never going to come.
Hey, Dad, this came
for you in the mail.
Whoo-hoo!
(screams)
Mother, get an extra
special hug ready.
I bought you a new juicer.
(gasps)
Good Lord!
Flu germs entering
every orifice in my head.
(groans)
Happy birthday.
(both screaming)
(clanging)
(humming)
Huh?
What the..?
(screaming)
The dreaded Osaka flu
has hit Springfield
with over 300 cases
now reported.
Now over to Arnie Pie
with Arnie in the Sky.
Route 401 is going
around and around
and around and around
and around.
And look out at the corner
of 12th and Main
because I'm gonna be sick.
Woop--
Okay, Mr. Sun.
Gimme what you got.
(screaming)
98.6.
You're fine.
Now hurry up,
or you'll miss your bus.
Maybe you'd better take
that temperature one more time.
Sarge, we keep
getting orders
to let the virus win.
Must be a school day.
Lay down your arms.
All right!
Let's make some pus.
(slurping and laughing)
Ahh...
(groaning)
(screaming)
(laughing)
(coughing)
MAN: And now, for an emergency
announcement from the mayor.
People of Springfield,
because of the epidemic,
I have canceled my
vacation to the Bahamas.
I shall not leave the city...
Hey, you!
Get that steel drum
out of the,
uh, mayor's office.
Sorry, mon.
Smithers, this plague
doesn't scare me.
I've constructed a germ-free
chamber for myself.
Not a single microbe
can get in or out.
Who the devil are you?
Don't panic. Just come up
with a good story.
My name is Mr. Burns.
D'oh!
ALL: We need a cure!
We need a cure!
(laughing)
Why, the only cure
is bed rest.
Anything I give you
would only be a placebo.
Where do we get
these placebos?
Maybe there's some
in this truck.
(buzzing)
(screaming)
I'm cured!
I mean, ouch!
Dad, Todd's speaking
in tongues!
(babbling)
I wish he were, Rod.
I pray for the day,
but I...
I'm afraid he's just delirious from fever.
(babbling)
Oh, Neddy, why has
God forsaken us?
I can't imagine
what we could have done to...
Oh...
(gasps)
Oh, no!
Hey, Peg, you got to take
better care of the house.
These plants are
all lifeless and limp.
Maybe they'd feel more
at home in the bedroom, Al.
(audience cheering)
(laughing)
-(thunder crackling)
-Uh-oh.
Oh, the network slogan
is true.
"Watch Fox and be damned
for all eternity."
LISA: Mom, can you
bring me more O.J.?
BART: Can you get me some of
those Flintstones chewable morphine?
There's no such thing.
HOMER: Marge, the boy
is wasting valuable time.
Come change
the channel and pat my head.
In a minute!
HOMER: But I'll miss
Sheriff Lobo.
And get me
a bottle of bourbon.
Grandpa, you know
you can't have liquids
after 3:00 p.m.
You can stir it into my mush.
Either way, just gimme,
gimme, gimme!
LISA: Mom, I need
more O.J.
BART: Flintstones
chewable morphine!
HOMER: I'll miss
Sheriff Lobo.
Mom, I need more O.J.!
Flintstones chewable morphine!
I'll miss Sheriff Lobo.
-O.J.!
-Morphine!
-Lobo!
-O.J.!
-Morphine!
-Lobo.
And a bottle of
aspirin please.
The aspirin is 24.95.
24.95?!
I lowered the price
because an escaped mental patient
tampered with the bottle.
(grumbling)
-(alarm bell ringing)
-(gasps)
Oh, dear! The alarm
must be broken.
If you could just move
a bit to your left.
(whispering) 8'6...
Oh, Sanjay, help
Mrs. Simpson with her bag.
And while you're at it...
(both speaking
foreign language)
Hmm...
(gasps) Mrs. Simpson,
you did not pay for this bottle
of Colonel Kwik-e-Mart's
Kentucky Bourbon.
Oh...
no, I...
I guess I didn't.
-(siren blaring and tires screeching)
-(gasps)
All right, come out
with your hands up,
two cups of coffee,
an auto freshener
that says "Capricorn,"
and something
with coconut on it.
Now, Marge, you've come
to the right place.
By hiring me as your lawyer,
you also get this
smoking monkey.
Better cut down there,
Smokey.
Mr. Hutz...
Look, he's taking
another puff!
Mr. Hutz, this was
all a misunderstanding.
I didn't mean
to take anything.
Now don't you worry,
Mrs. Simpson.
I... uh-oh.
We've drawn Judge Snider.
Is that bad?
Well, he's had it in for me
ever since I kinda
ran over his dog.
You did?
Well, replace
the word "kinda"
with the word "repeatedly,"
and the word
"dog" with "son."
(groaning)
Look, Marge,
I'll just talk to Apu,
and I'm sure
he'll be reasonable.
(singing and Indian
music playing)
Apu!
I'd like you to drop
the charges against my wife.
No offense, but we're
putting that bitch on ice!
Now, come on!
I'm your best customer.
I'm sorry, Mr. Homer,
but it is the policy
of the Kwik-e-Mart,
and its parent corporation
Nordyne Defense Dynamics,
to prosecute shoplifters
to the full extent of the law.
(singing and Indian
music playing)
Don't tell anyone,
but Marge Simpson was
arrested for shoplifting.
Let the word go forth
from this time and place,
Marge Simpson is a shoplifter.
Hey!
In other news, the chick
in "The Crying Game"
is really a man.
(booing)
I mean, man,
is that a good movie.
(cheering)
And last Christmas,
Marge made us
gingerbread men,
and there was a hair in one.
Well, I'll let you in
on a little secret
about Marge Simpson.
She's got webbed toes.
-(chuckles)
-Eww, that's gross.
Oh, puh-lease.
Now, Marge
don't you worry.
We've all had our
brushes with the law.
(knocking)
Are you Ed Flanders?
No. Ned Flanders.
My mistake.
I'll never have
that problem again.
Um... will you excuse me
while I go and freshen up?
I'll follow her.
(water running)
Just wash your hands
and get out.
(groaning)
MAN: Ladies
and gentlemen of the jury
who do you find
more attractive,
Tom Cruise
or Mel Gibson?
What is the point of all this?
Your honor,
I feel so confident
of Marge Simpson's guilt
that I can waste
the court's time
by rating
the superhunks.
(excited murmuring)
Ooh, he's going to win.
Mr. Hutz!
Now, Mrs. Lovejoy,
could you tell us
a little about Marge Simpson?
Well, as the wife
of the minister,
I'm privy to a lot of
sensitive information.
And here it is.
Marge's husband
doesn't earn much,
and the family's a mess
and quite frankly,
I think she, um....
Let the record show
that the witness made
the drinky-drinky motion.
And if we freeze on frame 138,
we distinctly see
a puff of blue hair
coming from the grassy knoll.
Now, Apu, Mrs. Simpson
claims that she forgot
she was carrying
that bottle of...
delicious bourbon,
brownest
of the brown liquors.
So tempting.
What's that?
You want me to drink you?
But I'm in the middle
of a trial.
Excuse me.
(ringing)
Hello, David?
I'm really tempted.
Just take it one day at a time,
and know that I love you.
I love you, too, man.
So, Mr. Nahasapeemapetilon,
if that is your real name
have you ever
forgotten anything?
No.
In fact, I can recite pi
to 40,000 places.
The last digit is one.
Mmm, pie.
Well, if you never
forget anything
tell me this:
What color tie am I wearing?
You are wearing
a red and white
striped club tie
in a half-Windsor knot.
Oh, I am, am I?
Is that what you think?
Well, if that is
what you think,
I have something to tell you.
Something that may shock
and discredit you.
And that thing
is as follows:
I'm not wearing a tie at all.
(gasping)
But if I am wrong about that,
maybe I am wrong
about Mrs. Simpson.
No further questions.
Kids, I got a crazy feeling
your mom's
not going to prison.
(cheering)
You're a latter-day
Clarence Darrow.
Uh, was he the black guy
on "The Mod Squad"?
Mr. Hutz, when I grow up,
I want to be a lawyer
just like you.
Good for you, son.
If there's one thing
America needs,
it's more lawyers.
Can you imagine a world
without lawyers?
♪♪
(shudders)
And so, ladies
and gentlemen of the jury,
I rest my case.
Hmm. Mr. Hutz, do you know
you're not wearing any pants?
What?
(yells)
I move
for a bad court thingy.
You mean a mistrial?
Yeah. That's why
you're the judge
and I'm the law-talking guy.
-The lawyer.
-Right.
The foreman will pass the
verdict to the bailiff.
This verdict is written
on a cocktail napkin.
And it still says "guilty."
-And "guilty" is spelled wrong.
-Eep.
Will the foreman please
read the real verdict?
We find the defendant guilty.
Marge Simpson,
I sentence you to
30 days in prison.
Next case, the National
Council of Churches
v. Lionel Hutz.
Oh, right. That thing.
(weeping)
You're still
my hero, Mom.
Now you kids be good
while mother's in prison.
Don't worry, Mom.
I'll bust you out of there
just as soon as I get
a cocktail dress and a crowbar.
Bartina, until I met you,
I was the loneliest warden
in the penal system.
Fresh.
Oh... down I go.
(chuckles)
I'll be fine, dear.
Marge, I'm going
to miss you so much,
and it's not
just the sex.
It's also
the food preparation,
your skill with stains
of all kinds,
but mostly I'll miss
how lucky you make me feel
each and every morning.
I'll miss you, too, Homie.
With her behind bars,
our store is secure.
(air brakes releasing)
(diesel engine running)
I'm taking this
thing to Mexico.
(laughing)
Knock, knock.
I'm Marge Simpson,
your new cellmate.
I'm Phillips.
They call me that
'cause I killed my husband
with a Phillips head
screwdriver.
Hmm.
It's so nice
not to have to cook.
You mean your husband
never cooked for you?
Well, once.
Homer, I don't think
this fish is quite dead yet.
HOMER: Marge, please.
I'm having enough trouble
with the lobsters.
Oh, uh!
D'oh!
Oh, my goodness.
That's Tattoo Annie.
(Marge reads tattoo)
Hmm. I don't understand.
It's one of those
Mad Magazine fold-ins.
Amazing.
Now, kids, while
your mother's gone,
I don't want to have
to wash any dishes,
so from now on drink straight
from the faucet or milk carton,
and we'll eat while standing
over the sink or toilet.
Who's gonna change Maggie?
We're gonna let her
roam free in the backyard,
and nature will take
its course.
Excuse me, but I think
if we all do our fair share
we can keep
this house clean.
(yowling)
(crashing)
(growling)
Dad, we're running out
of clean clothes.
It seems like I've been wearing
this same red dress forever.
HOMER:
Go up to the attic.
There's a whole trunk
of clothes up there.
(humming "Bridal March")
All right!
Bologna and cheese!
What do you got, Bart?
Pack of sugar,
and peanut butter smeared
on a playing card.
Ha-ha! Your mom's
a jailbird.
So's yours.
Oh, yeah.
Let's play.
LISA: Oh, Mom,
I've missed you so much.
Oh, honey,
I've missed you too.
Homer, is that
an old Halloween costume?
Uh...
no.
So, how are things at home?
We flushed a gator
down the toilet,
but it got stuck halfway,
and now we have to feed it.
I'll bet you want
a piece of me.
Well, you ain't
going to get it.
See? Ha-ha-ha!
Oh...
Hey!
Gosh darn it.
HOMER: Honey, I don't know
what you're feeling right now,
so I don't want
to push anything.
We can just hold hands
or sit and talk.
(growling)
(Homer yells)
Oh, do you have any of those
delicious marshmallow squares?
Sorry, Marge Simpson
makes those.
-Oh, darn.
-(everyone sighs)
$15 short.
Exactly what Marge Simpson's
marshmallow squares bring in.
Can we still afford
that statue of Lincoln?
No, I'm afraid we'll have to
go with something cheaper.
Eh.
I, uh, give you
our 39th president...
Jimmy Carter.
Oh, come on.
He's history's
greatest monster.
(angry yelling)
Release the dogs.
Gee, they look pretty mad.
Yeah, I've been
starving 'em, teasing 'em,
singing off-key.
(singing off-key)
(screaming)
No, no, no! Nice doggie!
This never would
have happened
if Marge Simpson
was here.
Good-bye, Marge.
I'll miss you.
I hope you find
somebody.
Men are such slime,
but I'm seeing this new guy.
I think he's different.
Yoo-hoo!
(belches)
He says his name is Homer,
and he works
at the nuclear plant.
Oh...
We've got to clean this up
before Mom gets back.
No problemo.
We'll just sweep it
all under the rug.
(rumbling)
(crunching and cracking)
MAN: Hey, watch it.
(cheering and applause)
I didn't expect all this.
Well, we never
should have let you go.
From now on I'll use
my gossip for good
instead of evil.
Three cheers for Marge Simpson.
ALL: Hip, hip, hooray!
Hip, hip, hooray!
Now, Marge,
we have a special
treat for you.
Uh... it's beautiful.
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.