(SINGING) The Simpsons
(TIRES SCREECHING)
D'oh!
(EXCLAIMS)
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
(CLANGING)
Hey, kids!
I scream, you scream.
We all scream for...
...haircuts!
(BOTH SCREAM)
(BOTH GROAN)
Mom, Bart and I
have been talking...
You have?
That's so nice.
What Lisa's trying to say is
there's a new kids' barbershop
in the mall and we'd like
to start going there.
A kids' barbershop?
But they don't
have my templates.
Yeah, the templates
had a great run,
but we'd like our hair
to look like people hair.
Oh, I see.
Well, good luck getting
to your precious mall barber
'cause I'm not driving you.
Kids, want to
go to the mall?
They're baking
fresh Cinnabons,
which means they're
throwing out the old ones.
BOTH: Yay!
(GRUNTS)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(SIGHS)
I guess I'll just
cut my own hair.
Who wants their hair cut?
Who? Who? Who? Who? Who?
Who? Who? Who?
Which side do you
want your part on?
Left! Right!
Stab! Stab! Stab!
You're the boss.
BART: What the hell?
Whoa!
(LAUGHING)
Oh, Bart, you look worse
than Aunt Patty in the
morning.
And there ain't nothing looks
worse than Aunt Patty in the
morning.
(GRUNTS ANGRILY)
(BOTH GRUNTING ANGRILY)
Next?
(GRUNTS)
Can you make
me look like this?
(BOTH GRUNTING ANGRILY)
Whoa! My bad boy spikes!
My good girl points!
Children, the mall will
provide you a wide range
of subjects,
while I return some socks
that appeared to be black,
but were in reality,
a very dark blue.
The best photographs,
or "photos,"
will be prominently
displayed in the school
lobby all year long.
(BOTH GULP)
(WIND CHIMES CHIMING)
(GASPING EAGERLY)
(GASPS)
(SCREAMS)
After them!
Oh! I love you,
dumpster buns!
(GULPS)
BOTH: Dad?
Huh?
Oh, big surprise.
The fat guy's
eating garbage.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Come on! We'll hide
in the theater!
(GASPS)
(CHUCKUNG)
Well, I guess you didn't
find anything interesting
to photograph.
Check it out.
The principal's
got a shirt wiener.
Hmm?
(SHUTTERS CLICKING)
Leave your body, Seymour.
Leave your body.
(HOMER READING)
Ooh! A He is Risen production.
I wish you'd come
to church with us,
sweetheart.
(CHUCKLES) Church?
I'd rather play golf on
the holiest day of the week.
Oh!
Finally, a character
I can relate to.
I bet good things
happen to him.
But, honey, with recent
troubles in the Mideast
and other ominous signs,
the Rapture could
soon be upon us.
The Rapture?
Easy there, Helen.
Science has shown
religion is just
an old wives' tale.
(ALL GASP)
I'm sorry, but the only thing
I'm praying for is that you
take it easy on
our credit cards.
(LAUGHING)
(BOTH MOANING)
Oh, Mr. Thompson,
what if your wife
finds out?
It's modern times.
Everyone's doing it.
Where did my Christian
limo driver go?
(TIRES SCREECHING)
My pious husband
is missing.
The baby I chose to
have baptized is gone.
(THUNDER CRACKING)
Mr. Thompson,
what's happening?
It's the Rapture, Shauna.
The Rapture.
The virtuous have gone
to heaven and the rest
of us have been left below.
(GASPS) Left below?
Where have I heard
that before?
It's the title of the movie.
(GASPS) It's everywhere!
We were fools!
And because we rejected God,
tacitly accepting Satan,
we must suffer
through the Apocalypse.
(THUNDER CRACKING)
I thought all religions
were a path to God.
I was wrong.
(THUNDER CRACKING)
Why did I put my faith
in science and technology?
(THUNDER CRACKING)
Oh, why did I choose
to be gay?
Oh! This movie will haunt
me for the rest of my life.
Just like Cannonball Run II.
Marge, what if the Rapture
is coming and I haven't led
a good enough life?
I could be left below.
Sweetie, don't worry.
God wouldn't spring
the Rapture on us
unannounced.
He'd send us signs
like, I don't know,
all the dogs getting
on a spaceship and leaving.
Yeah, I'll bet the cats'd
be psyched about that.
(LAUGHING)
Thanks, Marge.
You've put my
mind at ease.
Now, how about
a little rapture
for Mama?
Ooh!
I could be the Rachel
to your Jacob.
Okay, but it's tough for me
not to think about their
hardship.
(BOTH MOANING)
Marge is right.
The Rapture isn't coming.
There haven't been
any ominous signs.
(GROWLING)
Follow me.
(SCREAMS)
It's just not
working out, Barry.
Yeah, I guess I better study
for the police exam again.
Good luck.
You, too.
(GASPS AND SCREAMS)
Blood is raining
from the sky!
Hang on there, big fella.
We'll save you.
This ain't personal.
I just love to scrimshaw.
(SCREAMS)
Judgment Day is at hand.
Can I help you?
We're having a sale
on Bible magnifying
glasses.
(HOMER READING)
Uh, do you have any
books on the Rapture?
Yes, this one
is 15% off.
(HOMER SCREAMS)
I'll take everything you got.
And would you like
to take advantage of our
Friends of Flanders discount?
No, thank you.
(MARGE HUMMING)
Here's a pretty
little wig for Lisa.
And a handsome
toupee for Bart.
So, you still think I'm crazy
for saving all your hair
trimmings?
BOTH: No, ma'am.
Okay, then.
Let's get the rest of this
hair back in the freezer.
Hmm... Hmm...
Homie, you didn't touch
your second dinner tonight.
And you're reading books.
Word books! What's going on?
Marge, the Rapture is nigh.
These books will help
me figure out how nigh.
This whole deal
is scientifically proven.
The Book of Revelations
has 404 verses.
Add the number of people
at the Last Supper
minus the number
of Filipinos in the Bible,
and you get...
Three million, 100...
3:15 p.m., May 18th.
That's when the
Rapture will begin.
May 18th?
That's one week from today!
(GASPS)
A week? That's...
Seven days from now!
(RINGING BELL)
The world will end next week!
Spend your children's
college funds!
Thaw that turkey now!
This is Kent Brockman
reporting live from
downtown Springfield,
where overweight doomsayer
Homer Simpson is predicting
the world will end
next Wednesday.
Homer, what turned
you from sad drunk
to mad monk?
Funny story, Kent.
It's the end of the world!
God loves you!
He's gonna kill you!
Here's my angle.
There's no way in God's
heaven I should get into
God's heaven.
But maybe he'll let me
in if I warn others the
Apocalypse is coming,
as I previously shouted.
I see.
Well, we have
30 seconds left.
Any other
cuckoo yip-yap?
Uh... Oh!
Here's one.
Revelation 6:13.
"Just before the Rapture,
the stars will fall to
the Earth."
So, all you hippies out there
might wanna...for that one.
(LAUGHING)
There you have
it, folks.
And if I can make a prediction
of my own, this weekend's
Springfield Lettuce Festival
is gonna be bigger
and better than ever!
We've got romaine, iceberg,
radicchio, and everyone's
favorite, baby bib.
Even a few cabbages are
getting in on the fun.
(RINGING BELL)
Homie, I'm glad
you're getting
exercise.
I just wish it wasn't
crazy exercise.
Marge, in a world gone
mad, only a lunatic is
truly insane.
Dad, we love you, but we
just don't think the world
is coming to an end. Yet.
100 years, global warming,
we're goners.
But for now, you think
you could lighten up on
this "left below" stuff?
Well, I guess this thing
does look pretty silly.
Let's all take off our
sandwich boards and watch TV.
SIDESHOW MEL: Live from
Springfield Stadium, it's...
(SIDESHOW MEL READING)
The crowd is abuzz and agog
as the celebrity blimp
approaches.
And look, here is
America's favorite waste
of taxpayer dollars,
the Blue Angels!
What the... The Blue Angels?
I thought we were
getting Charlie's Angels.
(SOBBING)
Oh, God! We're going down!
I don't want to die
next to Kathy Griffin!
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(GASPS) The stars
are falling to the earth!
(GASPS)
Just as you predicted.
KRUSTY: Well, that's
our show for tonight.
I'd like to thank all the very
talented people who broke
my fall.
To all the fans of Los Lobos,
mucho, mucho condolences.
(LAUGHING)
Good night, everybody!
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
Homer, you were right.
That must mean
you were right about
the Rapture, too.
Yeah. I was wondering
if you could help
save my soul.
I've done stuff
I ain't proud of.
And the stuff I am
proud of is disgusting.
But what are we supposed
to do on Wednesday?
Lie naked on our roof?
Because that girls' school
says I can't do that no more.
When the time comes,
we won't be in our homes
because we're all
gonna go here.
(CROWD MURMURING)
That's Springfield Mesa.
It's 15 miles north, past the
Warren Harding Memorial
Through-hole.
Exactly. It came
to me in a vision,
or maybe it was
a drunken haze, or possibly
an ice cream headache.
Well, well, well, looks
like someone's having
a pre-Rapture party.
No, Flanders.
It's a meeting
of gay witches
for abortion.
You wouldn't be interested.
Mmm-mmm.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
All right, everybody.
Pair up with a Rapture buddy
who will watch your back
through all eternity.
Chief Wiggum,
wanna be my buddy?
What's wrong with Carl?
Trouble in paradise?
(CHUCKLES)
Dad, please don't
go through with this.
All through history,
self-anointed seers have
predicted the end of the world
and they've always been wrong.
But, sweetheart,
I have something
they didn't have.
A good feeling
about this.
It's all right, Lisa.
Don't go. More heaven for me.
Lisa's going!
We're all going!
Come on, Lisa.
No one in this family
is being left below.
Wait for me! I'm a-coming.
Don't worry, Dad!
There's a bus coming for you!
Drive! Drive!
ALL: 99 minutes
until we're all saved
99 minutes to go
Unless it turns out
that you're not devout
Then you're gonna
be left down below
98 minutes until
we're all saved
98 minutes to go
(PANTING)
Wait for me!
(GRUNTS)
(GROANING)
Okay, guys. Get ready.
We're just seconds away.
(CROWD MURMURING)
You saved us, Homer.
I can't wait!
I'm gonna steal God's secrets
and sell them to Satan.
ALL: Six, five, four...
I'm so proud
of you, Homie.
ALL: ...two, one!
(BEEPING)
Goodbye, stupid Earth!
There appears
to be some delay.
Huh? My watch must be
running fast. Wait for it.
Wait for it, wait for it.
Wait for it.
Ha-ha!
Life goes on.
(CROWD MURMURING ANGRILY)
Please don't go!
Please!
Please? I command you!
Homie, I better
start dinner.
Oh!
Lisa, you still
believe in me,
don't you?
Dad, if you'll recall,
I never believed in you,
not for one second.
Aw! That's my girl.
Oh.
Hey, Nostra-dumbass,
did the Rapture come?
I can't recall.
In fact, I can recall,
and it didn't and you suck.
Hey, fatwad, here's another
thing you didn't predict.
(GRUNTS ANGRILY)
(GRUNTS)
(ALL LAUGHING)
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
Oh, let's go to Moe's.
We'll walk and punch.
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
Huh?
Moe, what happened
to your eponymous
tavern?
Yeah, funny thing that.
You said the end was coming,
so I sold the bar
to some Japanese
businessmen
and gave the money to charity.
Now them orphans got
new skip ropes, and I end
every day smelling like eel.
Cats are all over me.
Thank you, though.
You did me a solid.
Hey, there's that jerk
who tried to save us.
Nice Rapture, Einstein.
(PEOPLE JEERING)
(SOBBING)
(GULPS)
(BARKS)
Hey, you with the tempura,
your arm broken?
How can people be so heartless
How can people be so cruel
Easy to be hard
Ten, 11, 12, 13?
Twelve apostles.
But Jesus was at
the Last Supper, too.
This changes everything.
Multiply by seven.
Don't forget to carry the 666.
Wake up.
The Rapture's coming
in half an hour!
There's no time to waste.
Marge, grill a chicken!
No, make sandwiches.
And some Kettle Chips
would be nice.
Original, not barbecue!
Ah, we got school tomorrow.
Yeah. School.
Hmm...
Forget school!
We have to get
to the mesa.
We're not going
anywhere except to bed.
But my prediction says...
You couldn't
predict 6:00 at 5:30.
Now, good night.
(ALL SLAM DOORS)
(SLAMS DOOR)
Stupid family.
Won't even come
to my Rapture.
I went to Lisa's school play,
which had serious pacing
problems.
(WOLF HOWLING)
Three, two, one...
(BEEPING)
Oh, I'm wrong again!
I'm nothing but a big, fat...
Woo-hoo!
I was right!
And there's the Earth.
So beautiful with
your many rings.
(RINGS BELL)
Homer Simpson,
welcome to heaven.
Now let's get you
some clothes, huh?
I'm comfortable like this.
Yeah, well, this is heaven.
For everyone.
This is our nature walk,
our pedicure hut,
our state-of-the-art showroom,
tonight featuring Los Lobos.
And over there
is our water slide.
That's coming next year.
It's gonna be super fantastic.
How come it's not open yet?
(SIGHS)
Look, just don't use
leprechaun labor, okay?
Don't do it.
And the best part
of heaven is,
anything you wish for,
you get, lickety-split.
Hmm...
(LAUGHING)
Okay, just for that,
your room is next
to the kiddy pool.
All right,
Mr. Smarty-Head-Exploder?
So, if you need
further assistance,
just call the front desk
and ask for Andre, okay?
(CLEARS THROAT)
Oh, uh, sorry, I'd tip you,
but I don't have any cash.
You know, you
could wish for some.
I could...
Wait. Before you go,
there's one thing
I gotta know.
What happened
to my family?
Heaven has a wide array
of fine dining just steps
from your room.
Have
a light bite at the
Pope of Sandwich Village.
Okay, let's see.
Earth is channel 23,
I think.
(SCREAMING)
(GROWLING)
Why didn't we
listen to Dad?
The worst part is
I'll never see my
Homie again.
That's the worst part?
Then I'm not doing my job.
(LAUGHING DIABOLICALLY)
(MARGE SCREAMS)
I've gotta save them!
Homer, what's wrong?
Lord, you got a first-class
destination resort here.
Really top-notch.
But I can't enjoy myself
knowing my family
is suffering.
Don't tell me about
family suffering.
My son went down
to Earth once.
I don't know what you
people did to him, but he
hasn't been the same since.
(SWING SQUEAKING)
Oh, he'll be fine.
And you could still
spare my family by...
Pass.
Buddy, you just made
yourself a powerful enemy.
(GRUNTING ANGRILY)
Hey, what's the big
idea, pally?
Why so crabby?
Screw you, Dino!
You squandered
your gift.
(GRUNTS ANGRILY)
Uh-oh.
(SIREN WAILING)
Squandered my gift?
I made 68 albums.
I'm sorry, but heaven
isn't heaven without
my family in it.
(SIGHS)
What do you want, Homer?
Just send me
back to Earth
and put off this whole
Rapture hoop-dee-doo
for another couple
of years or so.
But it's already started.
To do what you're asking,
I'd have to turn back time.
Superman did it.
Fine, Mr. Smarty-Pants.
I will undo the Apocalypse.
Thanks. Listen, could you
do me one more favor?
You want me to help you
with your alcoholism?
No, I'm in a good
place with that.
Why don't you just
take these pamphlets?
Yeah, I'll definitely
read those later.
Now, listen, if you
could just see your
way clear to...
(WHISPERS INDISTINCTLY)
Very well.
Deus ex machina!
(GROANING)
Oh, it was all just a dream.
What? What are these wings?
Oh, it's just a seagull
stuck in my back.
Dad, we've been so
worried about you.
The Warren Harding
Through-hole never
seemed so long.
Yeah, I missed you guys, too.
Now, if you'll excuse me...
Hallelujah, Hallelujah,
Hallelujah, Hallelujah
Thank you, Lord!
It's back the way it was.
(ALL MOANING)
Ah, this is heaven.
(SHUSHING)