The Simpsons
D'oh!
Welcome to second
grade gymnastics.
We'll get started
as soon as the
previous class
finishes up
on the equipment.
Don't worry.
You can win them back
if you stick the landing.
Big smile.
Come on, ladies.
Faster, higher, better!
My bad.
Lisa, gym isn't just
about encouraging fitness,
it's also about
exposing weakness!
Check minus.
Are you mad, Brunella?
You can't fail Lisa.
She's the only child
keeping this
school accredited.
Without her,
we'd have to release
these children
back into the forest.
So, let's just turn
that minus into a plus.
Skinner, I took an oath!
And by Xena,
this girl's failing gym!
Perhaps we could get
her a private coach?
Well, I know a coach.
But he's tough.
He defected
into East Germany.
Okay.
For next exercise,
put hands on hips,
jump out window,
and go tell parents to
stop wasting my time
with failure child!
Faster! Lift your knees!
Look, Lisa!
There's an opening!
Who wants to
put on a leotard
and get screamed at?
Well, hookers
and Spider-Man.
Forget it.
I'm going home.
Get up, Liser.
President Kennedy!
That's right, Liser.
Academics are important.
But you must also train
your body with vigor.
That's why I created
the President's Council
on Physical Fitness, yes.
Well, I can't argue
with the man
who wrote
Profiles in Courage.
Yes. Uh, I wrote it.
Well, good luck, Liser.
Thanks! I'll see you
in heaven!
Uh, yes,
uh, heaven.
My little munchkin
bumped her pumpkin.
Are you okay, Lisa?
I'm more than okay!
Ich bin ein gymnast.
Aw, she must've dreamt
about Hitler again.
There you go.
A Laffy Meal for you,
and a Nostalgia Meal
for me.
Oh, boy!
This takes me back!
Two ration stamps
and an artillery shell
full of oleo!
What's your
nostalgia prize,
Grampa?
Liberace action figure.
Party tonight at
Roddy McDowall's.
I got a plastic
Krusty-saurus.
Hmm.
A mosquito?
How'd that get in there?
Laziness is
counter-revolutionary.
Questions are decadent!
Fast hands mean
less whipping.
Ow!
Skeeter bites
are good luck.
Scratch it and
you get a wish.
I don't feel so good.
Can you take me
to the hospital?
Finally we're doing
something I want to do.
Just relax. Think of
floor as full of snakes.
You fall, they kill you!
Relax, relax.
And snakes!
Bravo, little girl.
Great progress!
You deserve reward.
Here is your cat back,
good as new.
Oh, thank you.
Do you think
I'll pass gym this term?
Is no problem.
God give you greatest gift.
Big head like beach ball
made of bone.
Gives you perfect balance.
Yeah! Excellent!
All right!
See you tomorrow.
Rest your giant head.
I am Lugash.
You're reading
Gravity's Rainbow?
Re-reading.
Sorry. What are you
guys talking about?
I was making fractals.
These girls
are brilliant.
I finally found kids
I can relate to.
You guys are so cool!
I can't believe I never
met you before!
Well, I'm Tina.
And this is Carrie.
Maybe we could
hang out together.
Oh, I'd love to.
You girls were all great.
Cats back for everyone.
I had a dog.
Is cat now.
Need a ride
back to campus?
Campus?
You guys are
college students!
Yeah. But with our
small gymnast bodies,
everyone always thinks
we're way younger.
Aren't you in college?
Of course.
Where do you think I go?
Baby school?
See you tomorrow, Lisa!
We find out what
five minus three is!
Um...
I'm a teacher's aide
in a very special class.
No, Lisa. We're both in...
Go! Go! Go!
Why do people
run from me?
Wow.
I'm actually passing
as a college student.
And they don't
have a Blue's Clue.
Whoops. Gotta age it up.
Life sucks.
Totally.
Phew.
So what dorm
do you live in?
Actually, I'm off campus.
I share a house
with a couple of girls,
a couple of guys.
Guys, huh?
Are they cute?
Well,
Bart's kind of... No!
I get knocked down
I get knocked down again
You are never
gonna knock me down!
Whoa! Party house.
Hey,
where's my keg?
Mom's not gonna like that.
Who's Mom?
That's what
we call the gay guy
who lives with us.
Hey, you doing
anything tomorrow night?
Robert Pinsky's
reading at Café Kafka.
Robert Pinsky?
The former poet laureate?
It's gonna be great.
The three of us
can split a scone.
Non-dairy?
Duh!
I take a whiskey drink
I take a chocolate drink
And when I have to pee
I use the kitchen sink
I sing the song
that reminds me
I'm a urinating guy!
I'll see you tomorrow!
See you!
Splash! Splash! Splash!
Now you're sure you haven't
been to China?
There's no shame in it.
No. I told you.
A mosquito came out
of my Laffy Meal
and bit me!
What's wrong
with him, Doctor?
It can't be mange.
I just had him dipped.
Your son is exhibiting
classic symptoms
of panda virus.
Here. Take a look.
I knew it was serious
when he said he didn't
want ice cream.
I did want ice cream.
Well, your father
ate it all!
Now don't worry.
These pills will
take care of everything.
But for a week,
Bart will be highly
infectious to others.
Contagious? Outrageous!
I got me some
teachers to lick.
Well,
I don't know about that.
But don't worry.
While you're infectious,
you will lead
a normal life full of
normal social interaction.
I don't like how many times
you said "normal. "
You'll be living
in this bubble.
It's clear plastic
so the world can see
how normal you are.
Help me!
You'll get
the hang of it, honey.
Today's just a little gusty.
Everyone's staring at me.
Ha-ha!
This place is amazing.
Kiosks,
outdoor study groups.
Lisa,
where have you been?
In heaven.
I love her.
She's a total free spirit.
She'd have to be
where she lives.
That place had
a Manson Family vibe.
Yeah, well,
I live in a dorm
without a DSL line.
Freaky.
I think the soup's
a little hot.
Bart, don't slurp
your soup.
My bubble, my rules.
That's it, boy!
It's time for your bath!
Now go to bed.
That is called parenting.
I'm going to Moe's.
Test. Test. Roses are red.
April is the cruelest month.
Cruelest month.
Now open your minds
for the Coltrane
of the quatrain,
the Tony Danza
of the A-B stanza.
I give you the former
poet laureate of
the United States,
Mr. Robert Pinsky.
Tonight I'll be reading
from a copy of my book
I just checked out
at Atherton Library!
I study there!
Say another building!
That's it, Pinsky.
You've got them
right where you want them.
"Slow dulcimer,
gavotte and bow in autumn"
He's reading
Impossible to Tell.
"Basho and his friends
go out to view the moon
"In summer,
gasoline rainbow
in the gutter
"The secret courtesy
that courses like ichor
"Through the old form of
the rude, full-scale joke"
I'm in a coffee house
listening to poetry.
There's a cat on a table
and no one seems to care.
This is the single
greatest day of my life!
"Impossible to
tell in writing.
"Basho, he named himself,
'Banana tree. "'
Basho!
Banana tree!
Good night, Bart.
Good night, Lisa.
Good night, Maggie.
Cherish these moments,
Homer.
So I'm walking by
the Oval Office.
And I hear the President,
"Pinsky, where's my poem?"
Well, I thought it wasn't
due till Tuesday.
So I make one up.
I am just pulling
stuff out of my ass.
And when I'm done,
the President says,
"Pinsky,
you've done it again. "
Ka-ching!
Oh, my God!
My social studies project
is due tomorrow morning!
Did she put in
for the pizza?
Gotta finish.
Am I using too much glue?
You won't eat our meat
but you glue with our feet.
Well, it's still
the best thing
in this class.
A- minus.
Lisa Simpson,
master of the double life.
You're like my mommy
after a box of wine.
Give me your lunch money!
But it's after lunch.
It's just an expression.
Like "kick your
butt" could involve
no kicking whatsoever.
Never fear,
the sphere is here!
That's it, Simpson.
I'm gonna kick you
right in the ball.
When nerds are in trouble,
I am not slow.
It's spin, spin, spin,
and away I go!
Once he's gone,
they'll kill us!
That young adult
looks like Lisa.
That young adult is Lisa!
She's up to
something private!
Let's go spy on her!
I'll get you down.
Bite these pencils.
This is the life
we chose.
Huh? Where is everybody?
Passive Analysis
of Visual Iconography.
Everyone takes it.
All you do is watch
Itchy & Scratchy cartoons.
After her!
I feel like
Harriet the spy.
Now the classic
Itchy & Scratchy,
episode DAB-FO6.
"Butter Off Dead. "
Good morrow to thee,
neighbor.
Okay.
Freeze there.
So what does
this cartoon "mean"?
It shows how the depletion
of our natural resources
has pitted our small farmers
against each other.
Yes.
And birds go "tweet. "
What else?
Hey, Mister!
Put the cartoon back on!
I'm sorry, boys.
We don't allow
children in this class.
What about Lisa?
She's only eight!
Lisa, did you lie to us?
I just wanted to belong!
For once I felt I was
with intellectual equals.
I can't believe
I cheated off
an eight-year-old.
I guess we won't be
biking through Italy.
She's worse than
that 80-year-old
who pretended
to be a freshman.
I just wanted
a place to sit down.
What the...
You earned how many credits
without our permission?
Sixteen.
College is no place
for a young girl,
with those quadrangles
and study carrels
and syllabi, and...
Doogie Howser
went to college
when he was my age.
Against my wishes!
But the atmosphere there
was so stimulating.
It was a bustling
marketplace of ideas.
Oh.
And this kitchen isn't?
Well...
I put those Cathys
on the fridge for you.
I don't even like them.
They've gotten so smutty.
Sure. When a man
does it, it's smutty.
But if a woman did it...
Homer,
Cathy is a woman.
Oh, come on...
You're right.
What are you guys doing?
We're gonna
roll down the hill.
Can I come with you?
I don't know.
Are you sure you're not
too "college" for us?
Yeah. Sorry we
can't be more "college!"
Hey, Einstein.
What's a million
plus a million?
Two million.
So?
Don't let them
get to you, lass.
I'm too good for
this place, too.
Now run home
to your shack.
I live in a house.
Well, la-dee-da,
college girl!
Well, I guess you're
too good for me, too!
Oh, look at...
What are you doing?
I was trying to throw
Bart over the roof
and he got stuck
in this tree.
Marge,
where's my pellet gun?
In the tree!
Right.
Oh, no!
Not the good cheek!
Poor, Bart.
I know just how you feel.
Isolated, alone,
cut off from everyone.
Are you kidding?
This little baby has made me
more popular than ever.
Hey, Bubble Bart!
Looking good.
Call me!
The bubble makes everything
shimmer and glow.
You can't believe
what that sunset
looks like to me.
That's not a sunset.
That's a bird on fire.
To-may-to, to-mah-to.
I wish I had
someplace to
call my own.
No one wants me
around anymore.
I know a way
you can win back
the kids at school.
Really?
That's wonderful.
But how?
All you gotta do
is play a prank
on the principal.
Well, I can't do it tomorrow.
There's an assembly
in his honor.
We've got
a little planning to do.
Step into my office.
Ew! Bart!
It wasn't me.
In recognition
of your 20 years
as interim principal,
I hereby dedicate
the Seymour Skinner
parking annex.
Did they have to guess
the date of my death?
Can't you be
a team player
just once?
When I was
starting out, they said,
"You're good.
But are you
'plaque' good?"
Well, today I can say,
"Yes, I am. "
Three, two, one...
Thank you.
I will now take
pre-approved questions
from honor roll students.
Yeah, I got a question!
How dare you wear white?
I hear
what you do at night.
Security!
Get your hands off of me.
Why...
Martin Prince,
Daily Fourth Gradian.
How about a picture of you
and the cake for
our society page?
Now normally
I wouldn't go near
a giant chocolate cake
in my dress polyester.
But with Bart Simpson
safely encapsulated,
I'd be delighted to pose.
Look, up there! It's Lisa!
And she's winning us back!
I've been taken down a peg.
A whole peg!
Lisa, Lisa,
Lisa, Lisa, Lisa!
Good going, Lise.
And it sure is great
to be out of that bubble.
It sure is sunny.
Was the air
always this fresh?
I'm just gonna
hang out in this vent!
Does this thing
suck or blow?
Suck!
ENGLISH - US - PSDH