(bellowing)
-CHOIR: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
-Yee-haw-ho-ho!
(school bell ringing)
(bears growl)
(whistle blows)
(playing "Jingle Bells")
(playing bluesy riff)
♪ ♪
(growls)
(snarling)
(squawking)
-(cats yowling)
-(Cat Lady jabbering)
D'oh!
(bicycle bell jingling)
(grunts)
BART: Ay, caramba!
(groans) Carrot.
(humming)
You are about to see
the worst half-hour of television ever.
All righty then.
♪ ♪
Okay, R3,
let's serve up some soup.
(whistling)
May the sauce be with you.
Oh, since when is soup sauce?
This is so non-canonical.
You have every right to be furious.
Oh, it's as bad as I remembered,
and I haven't watched
it since yesterday.
Horrible, yet enthralling.
Hooray!
A card from Dr. Hibbert.
(gasps)
Phew.
Oh.
(bird squawks)
I'll be right home, honey.
I just got to lock down
the reactor for the evening.
Tight as a drum.
See you soon.
Bart, hold the ladder still!
(gasps)
(grunts)
Oh! I wish Homer was here.
-Simpson!
-(gasps) Mr. Scrooge!
-Time for your holiday gift.
-Ooh!
In your name,
a donation has been made...
-(groans)
-...to the Salvation Army.
-Also, you will be visited
by three spirits tonight.
No, wait. That's my schedule.
Smithers, we need to cancel
-the 10:30 spirit.
-Yes, sir.
(Marge humming)
Hello.
Heading home, baby.
Nothing's gonna stop me now.
(shrieks)
(groaning) Maybe a drink
will help me with my driving.
Man, those things go off quick.
-♪ Yo ♪
-(guitar plays country melody)
-(metal guitar plays)
-♪ Ah ♪
VIN SCULLY: ...and the baseball
exclaimed as it flew out of sight,
this ballpark is shorter
in left field than right.
Martinez swings and misses.
Yes! I'm recording this during a game.
Since the United States government
declares this man to be Santa Claus,
this court will not dispute it.
Few people know that verdict
was overturned in the sequel.
(chuckles)
I better be heading home
to my family.
Enjoy your evening
with your wonderful...
uh... neon sign.
Yeah, last year I broke it
just so the repairman would come.
But I'll be fine.
Hey, um, you gonna be okay?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Super! (crying)
It's just that, you know,
-I lost my ma at Christmas.
-(sighs)
She took me to a mall,
and I never saw her again.
But I'll never forget that image
of her bolting for the parking lot.
Okay, okay.
I'll stay for one beer.
Oh, great, great.
But don't do it out of pity.
Pity! Pity! Have pity!
Look, I'm wrapped
around your leg here!
Please! Please! Please!
But I promised Marge.
Now I'm sitting on your shoulders!
-Please!
-Okay, okay!
(Homer groans)
-(grunts)
-Mom, where's Dad?
I don't know.
Aw, it's Christmas Eve, man!
We do not want to set a precedent
for fat guys being late tonight!
(grunts)
♪ Silent night ♪
♪ Holy night... ♪
(laughs)
I'm happy on Christmas Eve.
And for once
it's not 'cause some drunk
left a wallet on his stool.
Uh-oh, this is starting to hurt.
(grunts)
(chuckles)
And now, Homer,
it's only fair that I give yous a gift.
I'm gonna set the clock in the bar
to the correct time.
HOMER: Hey, what the...
(gasps) I am so late!
-(gulping, door slams)
-Whoa, whoa, whoa.
It's the night before Christmas!
Stop stirring, you!
(grunts)
(ticking)
One night.
The one night of the year
I want Homer home with his family,
and he can't even do that.
Christmas is a great time
to dump him.
If you do it now,
you won't have to watch the Super Bowl.
(tires squealing, car door closing)
Homer Simpson!
-(gasps)
-I never thought I'd say this
to someone I cared for,
much less my husband,
but I'm saying it now.
I don't want you here on Christmas!
Marge, think about what you're saying.
It's Sir Isaac Newton's birthday.
Out now!
Yeah? Well, good luck assembling
all those toys without me!
We already did it.
(shrieks)
The ghost of Marge Future!
HOMER: She'll forgive me.
MARGE: Should I forgive him?
HOMER: Especially this time.
MARGE: Maybe not this time.
HOMER: I mean, it's Christmas.
MARGE:
With his marriage in this much trouble,
he's got a lot of thinking to do.
HOMER:
I wonder if there's birds on the moon.
(sobbing) I miss Marge.
WIGGUM: I wonder if Lou suspects
that I was his Secret Santa.
What kind of a cheapskate gives you
one corncob holder for Christmas?
(chuckles)
Moe, what are you doing?
♪ Good King Wenceslas looked out ♪
♪ On the feast... ♪
JAPANESE MALE VOICE:
Voice too poor for karaoke.
Shutting down.
-Bye now.
-Oh, my God.
Santa brought me just what I asked for!
(laughs)
Hmm. "239." Who's he fooling?
Hmm... Hmm. Hmm!
Mm-hmm.
Hey, pal. Can't believe you have
to work Christmas Eve.
Well, if you're here
for a last minute gift,
we have a cell phone holder that fits
no cell phone made after 2002.
And, uh, Kwik-E-Nog.
Nog stands for
"Not Okayed by Government."
Maybe Marge would forgive me
if I won the lotto.
Give me a scratcher.
D'oh! Give me another one.
-(groans)
-D'oh!
-Give me another one.
-(groans)
-D'oh! Give me another one.
D'oh! Give me another one.
-(groans)
-D'oh!
-Give me another one.
-Oh please, stop! Stop it!
My religion prohibits me
from taking advantage
of a fool more than ten times.
This thing basically has no winners.
Yeah, but doesn't the money
go to schools?
You have been to our schools.
What do you think?
Welcome to
Bring Us Your Toilet Paper night.
Don't worry, none goes to Willie.
Don't need it.
I got me Starbucks napkins!
You know, ironically, in India,
they did use the money for schools,
and they had fantastic results.
Aw, thanks for your honesty, Apu.
Is there any other product in the store
you'd like to warn me about?
Well, uh...
those hot dogs began life as Twinkies.
Wow.
(pop, crackling)
(groans) Christmas Eve.
The one night a kid wants to go to sleep
is the one night he can't.
I can't have another cocoa.
My pee is starting to smell
like a ski chalet.
-(door opens)
-Oh, thank God you're here.
I need to get to sleep.
Tell me the story of jazz again.
Well, the story of jazz starts
with the tresillo,
the most prevalent duple-pulse rhythmic
cell in sub-Saharan African music.
But the rest will have to wait.
Bart, Bart, I hear Mom sobbing.
And I don't know where Dad is.
If it helps, I made you a card.
Bart, this is the year
I've got to nail Christmas.
I don't want to be a jaded
ten-year-old like you!
Ah, yes.
I remember Christmas Eve
when I was eight.
MARGE: Why do you always wait
till the last minute to put up the lights?
HOMER:
I don't want to ruin the magic.
And I certainly... Aah!
(gurgling)
Next year... this is... your job.
-(electrical crackling)
-(grunting)
(grunting)
Ooh!
Hmm, they say a boy
never gets over seeing his dad
in a Santa suit getting hanged
and electrocuted on Christmas Eve.
I'll help you, kid.
(sighs heavily)
Mom, I'm just a kid,
but I say if Dad isn't here
Christmas morning,
that's the kind of thing
families never recover from.
Hmm.
Lisa, sweetie,
I'm tired of being a pushover.
You're not a pushover.
You can't smoke.
-Just chewing on the wood.
-Okay then.
-(clattering)
-(groans)
Eh, how you doing there?
Uh, your front door was locked,
so, uh, rather than call or knock,
I, uh, came down your chimbley there.
(coughs)
Moe Szyslak,
you didn't climb down our chimney
just to say "Merry Christmas."
(coughs, clears throat)
Midge, it's one minute till Christmas,
and if I'm ever gonna be
a good guy, it's now.
All right, here I go.
I'm the one that kept Homer
from coming home,
'cause, uh, well, I was lonely.
-(gasps)
-Yeah, that's right-- me,
Mr. Party Pants.
So, uh, so don't hold it
against Homer, eh?
Oh, my poor Homie.
This is what I was hoping for.
For it not to have been
completely his fault.
Thank you, Moe.
-Mwah.
-Huh?
I'm sorry, Marge, I'm sorry,
but it was Christmas,
and we were under the mistletoe.
-That's lettuce caught in a spider's web.
-All right.
I've got to call Homer.
(buzzes, beeps)
D'oh!
What gives?
Don't you get Showtime Extreme?
(groans) No answer.
Let's go find your father.
What? I never give up hope.
Neither do I.
Even the anchor store's closed.
("Someday at Christmas" playing)
♪ Someday at Christmas ♪
♪ Men won't be boys ♪
♪ Playing with bombs ♪
♪ Like kids play with toys ♪
♪ One warm December
our hearts will see ♪
♪ A world where men are free ♪
♪ Mm, someday at Christmas... ♪
-Any uplifting holiday movies?
-Well, let's see.
We've got a film
about a nutty professor...
-Oh?
-...with advanced Alzheimer's.
-D'oh!
-Seth Rogen and Jonah Hill...
-Yeah?
-...in a concentration camp drama.
-D'oh!
-And a cute model...
-Ooh!
-...airplane that lost its propeller.
Um, I guess I'll take
the concentration camp one.
And a Merry Christmas to you, sir.
♪ ♪
(sighs)
Well, if I got to spend
Christmas Eve alone,
at least no one will see me.
-Hey-ya, Homer!
-(barking)
Ah, just 'cause you're here
shouldn't make you sad.
This is my 17th Christmas
alone in a movie theater.
This is my family.
The guy with the smelly pants,
the lady that carries empty cans
in a PBS tote bag.
Ugh, what if I left now and gave you guys
-my popcorn and soda?
-(cat meows)
Wow, Homer,
you have a very generous side.
Can I borrow, like, $10,000?
Flanders?
What are you doing here?
Christmas is my busy season.
Sold three pairs of scissors this month.
Two came back.
Say, Flanders,
with all the hard luck you've had,
how do you stay so happy?
And don't say "Jesus."
Well, sir, our good Lord and my boys
are all I've really got.
All Edna left me
was wonderful memories
and some ungraded papers,
which I'm still working my way through.
(sniffles)
Flanders, are you crying?
Ah, just snowflakes on my mustache.
Listen, could I buy a left-handed, uh...
I don't know, eyelash curler?
Sure, but y-your eyelashes
are long and luxurious already.
-Are you just buying this to be nice?
-Uh, maybe.
Oh, Homer, unto us this day,
a neighbor is born. But why?
Because jerk-ass Homer
has become ass-jerk Homer.
Well, that curled my lashes,
but good for you.
(chuckles)
You're all right, stupid Flanders.
You're all right.
Well, this is a whole new
relationship for us.
We'll be friends
in this life and the next.
(thinking)
Whoa, he's getting serious.
Is this what I really want?
-(whimpering)
-My best friend is a great runner.
I made everyone happy but me.
Some Christmas.
(sobbing) Feliz navidad.
(wind whistling)
(vehicle approaching)
Abe Simpson, please.
Visitor for Abe Simpson.
You came! You came to see me!
-(Bart grunting)
-Aw!
Easter came early this year.
I thought we were just gonna ask
if he'd seen Homer.
I'm afraid we've awoken a needy giant.
Visitors!
Let's brew some weak tea
and talk about the good ol' days!
Make them turn the TV to CBS!
("Hark! The Herald Angels Sing" playing)
(electrical crackling)
Well, with all that you folks
have experienced,
I think we could enjoy listening
to a little of your wisdom.
The problem with Puerto Ricans is...
No casual racism.
(snoring)
(muttering)
What the...
The Nutcracker.
Every child's favorite
Christmas character.
Is this a dream?
Not a dream. I work at the mall.
And it's closed, so scram.
Man, you are a nutcracker.
But I've learned something tonight--
you know how everyone hates
being with their family on Christmas?
-Uh-huh.
-Well, being without them is worse.
Can you find it in your wooden heart
to give me a break?
All right, listen, pal, uh...
you want to go to a party?
(dance music playing)
What are you doing here?
Halloween merchandise goes on sale
December 26th, man.
("O Holy Night" playing)
Well, he's not in the neon sign store.
-Lady, buy a sign or go home.
-I'm sorry.
I'm trying to find my husband,
and nothing's open.
Well, there is a party here.
Hey, is your husband into people
dressed like food?
Where is this party?!
(electrical crackling)
♪ ♪
Oh, my God.
Is that girl really doing that?!
Mm, load-bearing wall.
(whoops)
(moans)
Ho, ho, ho!
This party's great,
but all I wish
is that I was drinking a beer
with my kids right now.
-MARGE: Homer?
-Hmm?!
Homie, I'm your present tonight.
And the present is that I'm not gonna
always assume that you screwed up.
Because I realize maybe there's
a good explanation for what you do.
Or a crazy one
that's pretty entertaining.
Oh, Marge, you found me!
You always find me.
Now we just have to find your car
in the mall parking lot.
I thought I had
one of those chirping keys.
Oh, well,
I've been faking the noise.
'Cause you deserve the best.
-(imitates car chirp)
-You didn't have to do that.
I love you just the same.
-(imitates car chirp)
-(moaning)
Thank you, magical creatures of the mall!
-Welcome.
-You have all taught me
a Christmas message
I'll never forget--
the place to get drunk is at home.
("Dance of the Sugar Plum Fairy" playing)
All right, I'm sick of waiting.
Bart, you know you can't open a present
till Mom and Dad wake up.
(scoffs) It's 9:10 a.m.
I know what they're doing--
they're up in bed
watching the re-broadcast
of the Hollywood Christmas Parade.
Oops, my finger slipped.
Oops! So did mine.
-(laughing)
-Oh, I got a baseball glove.
LISA: I got a chemistry set.
BART: I want yours.
Merry Christmas, son.
Uh, don't you mean "Happy Birthday"?
It's two presents.
Um, walkie-talkies
don't count as two presents.
God. I mean, You.
(sighs)
JESUS: Idiot.
(Christmas theme music playing)
Subtitled by Jimmy Boots