♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
Huh?
(whistling)
Good morning, sir.
Care for some coffee?
No, the promise
of a new day
is more than enough
exhilaration for me.
(clock ticks)
(snoring)
Smithers?
Coffee.
Ah!
We need some excitement
around here.
Chinese checkers
or domestic, sir?
No, no, something fun--
Something the men will enjoy,
like a safety drill.
But what kind?
Eh, meltdown alert?
Mad dog drill?
Blimp attack?
Ah, I think a good old-fashioned
fire drill today.
(alarm blares)
All right,
popcorn's ready.
(alarm continues)
Hey,
that's the fire alarm.
We got to get
out of here.
Wait for me.
Come on, come on,
come on!
Look out!
Get out of my way!
(fretting)
Huh.
Mmm.
Fire! Fire! Fire! Fire! Fire!
Fire! Fire!
Is it supposed
to take this long?
What's a good time
for a mass evacuation
of the entire plant?
45 seconds.
And what's our time so far?
I don't know, sir.
This stopwatch only
goes up to 15 minutes.
Damnation.
What kind of slow coaches
do I have working for me?
Ah, here comes
one of our fellows now.
I think I won,
Mr. Burns.
Yes, you won,
all right.
You won more
than you bargained for.
Whoo-hoo!
What a disgraceful display.
I've seen more orderly behavior
in a Ritz brothers film.
You all need
a serious lesson in teamwork.
Maybe he does,
but I don't.
Hey,
you take that back.
No, you take
that back.
Yeah! Yeah!
Hit him, Carl!
You, too, Lenny!
(groans)
So Burns is going
to make us all
go on a stupid
corporate retreat
up in the mountains
to learn about teamwork,
which means we'll have
to cancel our plans
to hang around here.
-Teamwork is overrated.
-Huh?
Think about it. I mean,
what team was Babe Ruth on?
-Who knows?
-ALL: Yankees.
Sharing is a
bunch of bull, too.
And helping others.
And what's all this crap
I've been hearing
about tolerance?
Hmm. Your ideas
are intriguing to me,
and I wish to subscribe
to your newsletter.
But I think we have to go
on the retreat anyway.
Well, here we are.
All right,
let me start off
by telling you this will not
be a walk in the park.
This will be
the most arduous
and backbreaking
weekend of your life.
I cannot overemphasize
the dangers which...
Did you bring your family,
Simpson?
Yes, sir.
I thought I was supposed to.
Ah, imbecile.
Simpson, your family
will have to remain here.
-Aw, man.
-Aw...
Don't worry, kids.
This is a national park.
We can have lots of fun.
Oh, I'm afraid that's
no longer true, ma'am.
Budget cutbacks
have forced us
to eliminate anything
the least bit entertaining.
Well, uh, see you.
Each two-man team will work
its way through the wilderness
to a cabin hidden somewhere
on this mountain.
The routes are treacherous,
so use your maps.
I lost my map.
You haven't been
issued a map yet.
When you arrive
at the cabin,
there will be
a congratulatory party
with sandwiches and
moderately-priced champagne.
(applause)
Now, as an added incentive,
the second to last team
to arrive at the cabin
will receive
an hilarious
"World's Worst
Employee" Trophy.
Hey, this sounds
like fun.
And the last team
to arrive will be fired.
(chuckles)
Uh-oh.
And to show that
I'm not playing favorites,
both Smithers and I
will be participating.
Who knows? I might be
the unlucky one who gets fired.
(to himself)
Not bloody likely.
I've placed all your
names in this hat.
-Ooh!
-Thank you.
Now, pair off
as I draw your names.
Lenny and... Carl.
Aw, nuts.
I mean, um...
Fong and... Zutroy.
Kimball and... Dawson.
Haney and... Drucker.
Simpson and... Burns?
(groans)
HOMER'S BRAIN:
Quiet, you fool.
You're on the one team
that can't possibly be fired.
Oh.
Sir, this can't be right.
You assured me
this drawing was rigged
so we'd be teammates.
Yes, well, frankly,
you've been
bit of a pill lately.
Why do we always
fight on vacation?
Now, there's only
one name left.
Whoever it is
will be paired with me.
And that person is...
Waylon Smithers.
Perfect.
That's just perfect.
Prepare for the
adventure of a lifetime
as you fight for survival
against the merciless
forces of nature.
Toe your marks...
Get set...
Go!
Ready, Mr. Burns?
One moment.
Only who can prevent
forest fires?
You pressed "You,"
referring to me.
That is incorrect.
The correct answer is you.
(snarls)
Mom, can Lisa and I
play outside
away from the bear?
Okay, but when you start
getting apple-cheeked,
it's time to come in.
How could you do this
to me, Mr. Burns?
After all
I've done for you.
Why, if you were here,
I'd kick you right
in your bony old behind!
(echoing)
Bony old behind!
Why, thank you, Simpson.
I have been
watching my figure.
(cackles)
Lise, Lise, come here.
I found two snowflakes
that are exactly alike.
LISA: Really?
Let me see.
(evil chuckle)
SMITHERS: Ow!
Oops. Sorry.
Hi, Mr. Smithers.
Oh, great.
It's the Bobbsey twins.
Well, take your
prying eyes elsewhere.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It hasn't been
a good day.
If I don't get to the top
of the mountain real soon,
-I could get fired.
-We'll help you.
I have a watch
with a minute hand.
All right,
you can come.
What time is it?
12:80.
No, wait.
Wait.
What comes after 12?
One.
No, after 12.
Ohh...
Tell me, Simpson,
if an opportunity arose
for taking a small shortcut,
you wouldn't be averse
to taking it, would you?
Um, not as such.
Neither would I.
I've always felt that
there's far too much
hysteria these days
about so-called cheating.
-Yes, a lot of hysteria.
-Mm-hmm.
If you can take advantage
of a situation in some way,
it's your duty
as an American to do it.
Why should the race
always be to the swift
or the jumble
to the quick-witted?
Should they win merely because
of the gifts God gave them?
Well, I say cheating is
the gift man gives himself.
Mr. Burns, I insist
that we cheat.
Excellent.
And to do so,
I propose we travel by...
horseless sleigh.
Wow. You sure know
how to cheat, Mr. Burns.
Yes, well,
I'm older than you.
You know, Simpson
you're not as objectionable
as you seemed
when we first met.
No, sir, I am not.
(motor revving)
Bart?
Lisa?
Hello?
(projector whirrs)
NARRATOR: The story of our
national parks begins in 1872.
Perhaps we should let John Muir
tell the tale.
MUIR:
Oh, yeah. I remember...
(incoherent mumbling)
Excuse me, sir.
I can't find my children.
Have you checked the woods?
-No.
-Hmm.
Follow me.
We'll take
the chair lift.
It'll give us
an eagle-eye view
of the area directly
beneath the chair lift.
Whoo!
Well, I won't lie
to you, ma'am.
Our chances of finding
your children
are slim to nil.
LISA:
Hi, Mom.
MARGE:
There they are!
Let me down here.
Sorry. There's no way off
till we get to the top.
And even then,
it's sort of tricky.
(grumbles)
All right, kids,
we'll meet you at the top!
Just be careful!
Uh, actually, I'm a little
more concerned about us.
(creaking)
Um, do you know
how to weld?
That worked so well.
We have several hours
before the others arrive.
What say we get comfy?
Now we have electricity.
This propane tank
will supply us with heat.
And this doorknob,
properly turned,
will allow us
access to the cabin.
No going through
the window for us.
BART: Is there maple syrup
in this one?
SMITHERS: There isn't any food
in any of these trees.
Please, Bart,
we've got to hurry.
I can't be the last one
to reach the cabin.
Hey, I'm not going
to get fired.
Is there any gold
in this mountain?
(sputtering)
It doesn't matter.
I'll check.
Mr. Smithers!
I found another
hurt shrew.
I think this one
has a twisted ankle.
Twisted ank...
Aren't there any
healthy animals in this forest?
Well, I don't suppose
the others will mind us
starting the party early,
Homie, old boy.
More champagne?
(chuckles)
You know, Mr. Burns,
you're the richest guy
I know.
Way richer than Lenny.
Oh, yes, but I'd trade it
all for a little more.
Oh, these sure are
comfortable chairs.
Oh, yes, sitting.
The great leveler.
From the mightiest pharaoh
to the lowliest peasant,
who doesn't
enjoy a good sit?
Oh, man,
you are so right.
Did you ever
sit like this?
Yes, yes,
that's it.
Oh, I could go
for one of those right now.
Ahh!
The only hard part
is getting up.
(chuckles)
Why get up?
Here's a little move
I've been tinkering with.
Say I want
that bowl of dip.
Why, you'd
have to get up.
Oh?
(grunting)
Sir, I am in your debt.
Use it wisely,
my friend.
(tinkling)
(rumbling)
Ah! Oh!
Hey, did you
hear something?
-No.
-Hmm. Did I?
I don't know.
Hope that wasn't
an avalanche.
Be a chum
and take a look-see.
You got it, buddy.
Oh!
Isn't there any way
out of here?
I don't see one.
Unless...
No, there's no way out.
There must be
some way
to contact
the outside world.
Ah, the telegraph.
S.O.S.
Avalanche...
Send...
Help.
(beeping)
According to the map,
the cabin should be right here.
(grunting)
Hey, maybe
there is no cabin.
Maybe it's one of them
metaphorical things.
Oh, yeah, yeah...
like maybe the cabin
is the place
inside each of us
created by our goodwill
and teamwork.
Oh.
Uh, they said
there would be sandwiches.
Simpson,
I have a confession.
I'm not quite
the tunnel-digger
I made myself out to be.
You can supervise me.
All right, good.
Let's dig.
That's right.
Dig some more.
Oh, we make quite a duo--
Burns and associate.
No, no,
what am I thinking?
Burns and teammate.
(both gasping)
We made it,
old friend.
We sure did.
-Huzzah!
-Whoo-hoo!
(rumbling)
(screaming)
D'oh!
What happened?
(rumbling)
I think when we yelled
we caused
another avalanche.
(quietly and slowly)
We... should... be... careful
not... to... speak...
unless... it's...
absolutely...
pos-i-tively...
necessary.
(rumbling)
Shh.
You're... causing
more... avalanches.
(rumbling)
-I...
-(rumbling)
-Think...
-They've... stopped.
-(rumbling)
Let's go.
(door creaks)
Oh!
Those last three avalanches
were your fault, Simpson.
So what?
Sew buttons.
There's not another
place for miles.
This must be the cabin
Burns was talking about.
Well, we made it
here first.
All thanks
to teamwork.
Yeah, my teamwork.
We must be covered
by a thousand feet of snow.
It could be days
before they find us.
Mmm, no books, no radio
no board games.
Ah!
A "Bazooka Joe" Comic!
Ugh, I heard that one
75 years ago!
We could build
snowmen.
No, I have
a better idea.
We could build real men
out of snow.
Oh.
Okay...
(shivering)
Ah!
Mr. Smithers, Mr. Smithers!
That moose is on fire!
Fine. Good.
I don't care anymore.
I'm the last one here.
You kids cost me my job.
You ain't last,
Mr. Smithers.
Ah, thank goodness.
Yeah, Burnsie and Homer
never made it.
Mr. Burns is still
out there?
(gasps)
What about our dad?!
Ah, 206 bones,
50 miles of
small intestine,
full pouting lips.
Why, this fellow
is less a snowman
than a god.
Well, we've managed
to stave off
cabin fever
for a few hours.
Eh, I think we should
dress the snowmen.
Agreed.
Look at them.
Smug and secure
in their finery.
Mocking us.
Uh, they're just
snowmen, Mr. Burns.
Ah, snowmen
have peepers.
Peepers to watch...
To watch for a moment
of weakness and, baff!
Comes the knock on the head
and we're down!
What do we do?!
Oh, wouldn't you
like to know.
Hey, what is going on here?
Who are you people?
This is a lookout post.
Where is ranger McFadden?
(slurred)
I was just happy
to see so many
nice people.
Quiet, you drunk.
Where is ranger McFadden?
Right here, sir.
Right behind the drunk.
Wait a minute.
If this is
a ranger station
we must be
in the wrong place.
Well, the only other
cabin is right over...
There...
Huh.
(whistles)
Look at all
these avalanches.
Do you think they could
have buried the cabin?
I'll tell you
one thing:
They didn't come here for
the mountain music festival.
March 14th to 18th.
Mom, Dad and Mr. Burns
could be trapped in there.
(gasps)
BURNS:
I'm trapped with a madman.
Look at him.
Staring into me.
Filling my mind
with paranoid thoughts.
HOMER:
Mmm. Look at his eyes.
He's trying to hypnotize me
but not in the good
Las Vegas way.
BURNS: (gasps)
I know what he's up to.
He's thinking of killing me
then riding my carcass
down the mountain to safety.
He's truly gone mad
if he's thinking that.
Well, he can't kill me
if I kill him first.
I'll kill you
you bloated museum
of treachery!
You and what army?
(gasps)
Stay back.
I have powers.
Political powers!
(gasps)
It's... showtime!
(grunting)
Gimme!
Let go of that!
Oh, God...
(grunts)
Ah!
(rumbling)
Homer!
Burnsie!
(both screaming)
Okay, search party,
before we set out
let's take a moment
to humor the children.
Kids, your father is
going to be just fine.
Okay, everybody
put on your
corpse-handling gloves.
We've got two
frozen bodies
buried somewhere
in this mountain.
Did you hear that, Lise?
Dad's going
to be just fine.
(rumbling)
Look! What's that?!
We'll be dashed to pieces!
Oh, Lord, protect
this rockethouse
and all who dwell
within the rockethouse.
It's them, all right.
We're over here, Homie!
Oh, something's wrong
with its brakes!
Gangway!
(door creaks)
Marge, kids.
(all clamoring)
(Burns clearing throat)
Have you people forgotten
our little competition?
Last one
in the cabin is fired!
(clamoring)
You're fired, Lenny.
Aw, nuts!
So, how did we do?
It's a new record, sir.
Outstanding.
Well, perhaps all of this
has been worthwhile.
Did you all learn
about teamwork?
ALL: (weakly) Yes.
Excellent!
In that case
no one will be
fired after all.
That old goat
can't fire me.
I'm going to give him
a piece of my mi...
(screaming)
(thuds)
Aw, nuts!
Well, Simpson,
I must say
once you've been through
something like that
with a person you never
want to see that person again.
You said it,
you weirdo.
(laughter)
(laughter stops)
(laughter diminishing)
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.