-CHOIR: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
-(vocalizing)
D'oh!
(tires screeching)
(grunts)
HOMER: Oh, boy.
(electronic clicking)
Hmm, is that the radon detector?
Mom's deleting old TV shows
off the DVR.
What the...?!
(gasps) Marge!
You're deleting the 2009 Oscar Red Carpet!
There were some awesome dresses!
And quite a few... disasters!
Fine. What would you get rid of?
Well, I can't part with
a single one of my Hoarders,
hands off my episodes of Episodes,
and if you delete Revenge...
(groans angrily)
Oh, fine. I'll just get rid
of these Itchy and Mitchys.
For every one of my
cartoons that you erase,
I rip up a family vacation photo.
And just so you know I mean
business, here's an ear!
(sighs) All right.
At least I can delete
these Westminster Dog Shows.
-(growls)
-Fine.
I'm getting rid of this
American Masters "Kitty Carlisle."
-(yowls)
-It's not what you think!
So I stayed up for the last 87 hours
watching all my shows.
(chuckles)
Nothing's gonna delete these.
(goofy chuckle)
Guys, there's something
I want to tell you.
Something important.
So who do you like,
the Padres or the Tigers?
I'm not talking about baseball.
I'm asking if a priest can beat
a big cat in a death match
in some kind of polygon.
Hexa or octa?
Only one way to decide: arm wrestling.
Eh, who am I kidding?
They don't care about me.
(sighs)
Suicide. Finally.
I'm really doing it.
No more cries for... help!
'Cause this time, there's no one that's
gonna... save me!
I mean, it's not like...
I'm begging you, please,
please show me some love!
(sighs) Yeah, it's nothing like that.
Eh, maybe I should call.
Give one of the new kids
a chance to talk to the legend.
AUTOMATED FEMALE VOICE:
Hello, you have reached
the Buzz Cola Suicide Hotline.
Our options have changed,
so please listen carefully.
State the reason
you are committing suicide.
Nothing to live for.
You said, "Business problems."
Is that correct?
No! I got nothing and no one!
You said, "Face sucked off
by vacuum cleaner."
Is that correct?
(sobbing)
No! No! Help me! Help!
If your face is in the vacuum
cleaner bag, press "one."
I just want to talk to a human being!
Please hold for our next
available life-extension agent.
♪ Suicide is painless ♪
♪ It brings on many changes ♪
♪ And I can... ♪
Oh, that tears it! No more delays!
(phone ringing)
-Hello?
-BART: Hi, I'm looking for a Mr. Ron,
first name Moe.
Moe Ron?
(sighs) Moron.
It's you, you little puke.
I am gonna tie a rope
around your neck and hang...
(choking)
I'll show you who's a... moron.
And that's why libraries
use newspaper rods.
(thud)
(gasps)
-Whoa!
-(gasps)
I know CPR!
I took a class where you do
chest compressions
to a Bee Gees song.
♪ How deep is your love?
How deep is your love? ♪
Are you sure it wasn't "Staying Alive?"
Too on the nose.
♪ I really need to learn ♪
♪ 'Cause we're living
in a world of fools ♪
♪ Breaking us down ♪
♪ When they all should let us be ♪
♪ We belong to you and me ♪
♪ I believe in yous ♪
You-you guys, you saved me!
You do care!
Now, wait a minute.
Got to make sure you're okay.
Who's the president now?
Some jerk.
He's back!
I really want to thank you all.
You gave me a new lease on life,
and I'm gonna take this opportunity to...
(plays static)
(coughs)
(sighs) What's the point?
Same old stinking world.
Ah, this post-suicide afterglow
gets shorter every time.
Homer Simpson!
(shrieks) The woman I love!
I sent you to the store
to get applesauce
for Maggie two hours ago!
Well, uh, I was just leaving, but Moe...
had an accident!
What kind of accident?
I, uh, may have tried to end it all.
I wasn't even good at that.
(sighs)
Excuse me, will you?
(sobbing)
That poor man.
We've got to do something
to change his life.
We could write on his face
when he passes out.
(chuckles) Yeah,
that's always good for a laugh.
No, no, it has to be something big
that'll change his whole outlook.
(snaps fingers)
Why don't we take Moe on a road trip?
Aw, that, hey, that's really sweet.
Hey, can Noosey come, too?
Moe, this trip is about
turning your life around.
With the three desperate
barflies that you see every day.
Maybe I should come, too.
Four guys, a chick and a noose.
Just like the movies I like to watch.
Grampa's in charge of you kids
while we go to Capital City.
Ooh, you're a good eater today, Maggie.
Bart, you're in charge of Grampa.
(jazz music playing)
♪ There's a swinging town I know called ♪
♪ Capital City ♪
Come on, Moe, stick your head
out the sunroof.
You'll look like
the richest dog in the world!
Eh.
Lighten up, man. The big city!
Wow, look at all them countdown clocks.
Acres of rainforest left,
deaths by lung cancer.
It's magical.
All I see is two million people
happier than me.
Moe, I know things
haven't been easy for you,
but you're with people who love you
in the most exciting of the twin cities.
Capital City has a twin?
Moved to California to be a star,
but it just turned into Glendale.
So what do you say, Moe?
Will you give me a smile?
Well, I'll try.
(grunting)
Maybe if I just tilt my head back here.
Thatta boy!
♪ And you'll feel better ♪
♪ You'll feel better, you'll feel better ♪
♪ Better than before ♪
♪ You'll feel better, much better ♪
♪ No, you won't get down anymore... ♪
Okay, Moe, one more surprise.
Gentlemen's Whorehouse?
Whoa, ho, ho!
No, no, it's a Wearhouse.
We're all gonna chip in
and get you a new suit.
A new suit?! Oh, ho, ho!
I'll be the best-dressed
john in the whorehouse!
But, listen, are you guys
sure you want to spring
for something that expensive?
Yes, 'cause every time you wear it,
you'll know how much we love you.
Like the one pair of blue pants
I bought Homer 20 years ago.
They're like a wedding ring;
I can't take them off anymore.
(sighs)
Oh, Moe, this suit really brings out
the herringbone in your eyes.
Hmm.
Nah, it's a 44 long. I wear a 38 hunched.
Got anything for a man my size?
Absolutely not.
Tent City is across the street.
Tent, eh?
(humming)
Hmm.
No husband of mine is wearing a tent.
No tents, no barrels, no kiddie pools.
Thank you, fashion police!
Hey, not bad, not bad.
And look over there, Moe.
That's me?
Hey, thank you, guys. Thanks.
It's a brand-new day! (chuckles)
Okay, final checklist.
Checklist ready? Check.
Mom and Dad still gone?
Uh, check.
What about that snoopy girl reporter
that's always hanging around?
You mean my sister?
She's your sister?
The plot thickens.
Clueless little Lisa
doesn't suspect a thing.
(upbeat jazz music playing)
Whatever Bart's doing,
it's got to be pretty bad
for him to get me tickets
to this amazing jam session.
All the greats are here:
Jellyroll Jones, Boston Cream Basie,
Birthmark Billy Jackson, Grabass Walker,
the Fatneck Sisters and... (gasps)
Bleeding Gums Murphy?
♪ I got this bratty brother ♪
♪ He bugs me every day ♪
No, that's impossible. He's dead.
I lay a saxophone reed
at his grave every year.
Lights and magic, Lisa.
You don't need anything else.
But I took a bunch of stuff anyway.
It's a hologram?
Well, maybe if it's in good taste.
Aw, come on.
Five seconds to slip-off.
And four, three...
Boy, what are you doing up here?!
Also, what am I doing up here?
Bart, you said your grandfather
wouldn't bother us.
I gave him a caramel.
He should have been chewing for hours.
I couldn't unwrap it!
-(yells)
-I got you, Grampa!
Hold, bolo, hold!
I don't want to die!
I want to still be a burden!
-(yelling)
-(all gasp)
Please be okay.
♪ How deep is your love?
How deep is your love? ♪
Boy?
Yes, Grampa?!
Kiss my forehead.
(groans)
Man, I must really love him.
(suctions)
(pops)
I'm not gonna die today.
Aw, that's so sweet.
Let's get all our grandfathers
and chuck them down this thing.
-All right!
Why am I in the basement?
Shouldn't I see a medico?
If the Wilsons' calf is birthed,
Doc Miller should be available.
Thank God your mental powers
haven't deteriorated.
Well, why the hell am I down here?!
I was supposed to be in charge of you.
I can't let Mom and Dad
know what I did.
But I promise I'll take good care of you
until you're well again.
No deal! I'm getting out of here.
(groans) Ooh, wow.
My tailbone!
And it was my last good bone.
(groans)
There, there, you'll be fine.
I'll take care of everything you need.
I want a foot rub.
Yes, but do you need one?
Nobody needs one!
Now start rubbing!
(groans)
Rub harder!
(humming)
(grunts) Sorry, pal.
"Sorry, pal"?
Hey, that's common courtesy.
The kind I've only seen in movies.
This suit is amazing!
Eh, this dump is too filthy
for a man with a positive worldview.
I'm gonna start cleaning.
Dirt. Carpet.
Another layer of dirt.
Congoleum. (gasps)
Hardwood!
The perfect floor for doing a happy jig.
(upbeat music playing)
And now to light up the sign
and let the world know
that the new, improved Moe's
is open for business.
Hmm.
Wow, non-losers?
Huh, I never thought I'd see the day.
Gentlemen, what can I get you?
We'll take anything you've got
aged 15 years or more.
Hmm.
(squeaking)
Well, actually, I do have this
bourbon that I brewed myself.
It'll either be
the best thing you ever had
or the last thing you'll ever have.
-Mmm.
-Huh.
Wow! Hey, are you thinking
what I'm thinking?
Moe, we're venture capitalists.
We turn dreams into money
that mostly goes to us,
-but you get a little.
-Tell me more!
How many bottles of this
Kentucky Kool-Aid do you have?
Just the one, but I could whip up
two or 300,000 more.
Moe, you got a great product,
a fantastic suit,
and we're gonna give you
everything you need.
Startup money, branding specialists.
Corporate jets, private drivers.
If your feet touch the ground,
we've failed.
This is all so sudden.
Now it's not. I'm in!
Only one more thing we need to do.
Check this out with our focus group.
Mm!
(murmurs happily)
-So, what do we think?
-Be honest, now.
I love it!
I've made a lot of mistakes,
but liking this ain't one of them.
(groans)
Every time I call
Grampa's phone, I get no answer.
Uh, he told me he was gonna
nap most of the week.
Oh! Oh, good.
Well, he needs his sleep.
Time for your meds!
-Come on, blue!
-Come on, pink!
Take it, take it, there you go, yes!
After a pulse-pounding race,
hypertension pills win again.
Call me crazy, but I can't stop
betting on dementia.
Now, what say we turn
the hot water on and off
while your father's taking a shower?
HOMER: Oh! (gasping)
Hot, oh! Cold, oh!
(screams)
Thank God I'm not in the shower!
(both laughing)
Hmm.
Grampa, we've been spending
so much time together,
I almost feel like you're
part of the family.
Aw.
And I've been wondering.
Not like I miss having my afternoons free
or anything, but...
are you starting to feel better?
Absolutely not!
My crotch is crotchety,
sitting down makes me uppity,
and you call these cups pleated?!
Okay, okay, just checking.
(sighs)
"Dear She-Done-Left-Me Records,
Once again, I write protesting
your holographic exploitation
of blues icon Bleeding Gums Murphy.
I call for a boycott and girl-cott
of your entire catalogue until you..."
-(jazz music playing)
-Sonny Rollins?
That's right, Lisa.
And I'm here to beg you
to stop writing those letters.
You're siding with record companies?
This isn't about money, Lisa.
From Tupac Shakur to Dwight Eisenhower,
holograms have introduced some
of our leading dead people
to a new audience
of people with money.
Resetting, resetting.
From Tupac Shakur to Dwight Eisenhower...
You're a hologram, aren't you?
No. Resetting, resetting.
(groans)
Have you no shame?!
Does this answer your question?
-(man beatboxing)
- ♪ My name is Princess Di ♪
♪ And I'm here to say ♪
♪ When I watch a DVD,
it's got to be Blu-ray. ♪
Take it, Gandhi!
First Bank of Springfield--
say "Mumbai" to high checking fees!
(hisses)
MOE: Hey, thanks, guys.
I ain't never been
to no fancy rooftop party before.
No beer?
That's a pretty big screwup.
Moe, we got a special surprise.
You like chicks with nose clips?
-Then you're really gonna be happy.
-Bring it, girls.
Hey, that is the most accurate
picture of my face
made of girl-parts that I have ever seen.
And it's not decadent 'cause you
can ask interns to do anything.
Thanks.
Thank you so much, Ken and Glen.
Ah, you're welcome.
Anything to celebrate
your I.P.O. tomorrow.
You know what that is, right?
Um...
Moe, we love your whiskey,
we love your backstory,
and we love that suit
that hangs off you
like silk on a skeleton.
So, starting tomorrow,
we're gonna sell shares
in your company to the public.
All you do is show up
at the stock exchange,
ring the bell,
and you'll leave a rich man.
-(elevator bell dings)
-We'll see you tomorrow.
Enjoy your last night as a Democrat.
Dang it, my suit's stuck in the door.
No, no, no!
This building's got 98 floors!
And I'm going down to P-6!
P-6!
(knocking)
Moe?
What are you doing?
Midge, uh, the suit
got a little mussed up.
I-I got to ask you, is it noticeable?
Thank God the kids aren't here.
LISA: I was.
Aw, without my magic suit, I'm nothing.
The suit wasn't magic, Moe.
Don't you know the story
of Dumbo the elephant?
I didn't go to movies as a kid.
Spent all my time
at the pierogi factory.
Dab the potato, fold the dough.
That was my Star Wars.
Well, Dumbo had a magic feather.
He thought he needed it to fly,
but it turned out the magic was
in him the whole time.
So you're saying Moe is Dumbo,
his bourbon is the giant ears,
and we're that flock of racist crows?
The crows weren't racist,
the people who drew them were.
Okay, I get it, I get it.
It wasn't the suit that made
the bourbon, it was me.
-And I can do anything.
-Don't stand up!
Except stand up.
BART: Grampa,
I made your favorite dinner:
teething biscuits soaked in buttermilk.
(singing "The Blue Danube" waltz)
Oh! Oh! The pain!
(grunting)
You're completely fine!
I've been taking care of you,
giving you love and attention
for nothing!
All right, boy, I admit it.
I've been faking being hurt,
just like I fake
liking those terrible homemade
Christmas gifts you give.
But Mom said it was a gift
made with love.
Did she?
No. Even she thought it was crap.
But what you did wasn't for nothing.
It was the best two weeks
of this final horrible part of my life.
Well, you are the first thing
I took care of that didn't die.
(chuckles)
Oh, I hear that a lot.
Hey-ya, guys.
Security, there's
a homeless monster up here!
Hey-hey-hey,
I'm your partner, Moe.
N-Now,
let's go make us a fortune, huh?
-(bell tolling)
-(all gasp)
Look!
It's Quasimodo without the pathos!
People, please, please.
My name is Moe Szyslak
of Makers Moe Bourbon,
ticker symbol: M-O-E.
I'm the CEO, and I promise
that I will hand-brew
every bottle
with these very hands, huh?
I-I'll supervise production,
I'll manage marketing.
My face is gonna be on every bottle!
And we will only use the finest
ingredients made in America.
(booing, clamoring)
Glad you're back, Moe.
At least I don't have
to train a new bartender
to make what I like--
beer to the top.
(humming)
(sighs)
Not today, old friend.
But don't worry, holidays
are just around the corner.
-(crowd murmuring)
-Shh!
Subtitled by A. Vandelay