D'oh!
- Homer.
- Hey.
- What?
I'll be right home.
You are home.
Homer.
Homer, wake up, please.
I can't sleep.
I'm having friends
over tomorrow.
- Luann Van Houten.
- Back-stabber.
- Bernice Hibbert.
- Snob.
And Helen Lovejoy.
Okay, she's pretty hot.
I mean, hot for
a reverend's wife,
but so judgmental.
I was going to ask you
if you could watch Maggie.
Oh, yeah, of course.
What do you suspect?
Isn't this great?
Daddy-baby alone time.
Where's Daddy?
Peek-a-boo.
Oh, you're sick of it already?
I was gonna do different people.
Peek-a-boo-ooh!
I'm afraid, Master Wayne,
it's time for peek-a-boo.
Ah, come on. Nothing?
Babies love Michael Caine.
What to do? What to do?
What to do...
Mags, I'll level with you.
I love you, kiddo,
but we are in two
completely different worlds.
More lemonade, ladies?
No, thank you.
I've had better lemonade
at Ralph Wiggum's stand.
And he stirs it
with his finger.
So we've been asked to
redecorate the school room
where the kids wait
when their ride is late.
I have some ideas.
Marge, you have many
wonderful talents,
but your sense
of style is...
- One of them?
- I'm afraid not.
Purple and orange cupboards,
oh, corncob curtains,
rabbit ears on the TV.
It's like we're visiting
the Flintstones.
Well, since you don't like
my style,
maybe I should
show you the door.
You mean the brown door
next to the hot pink walls.
Just like at the circus.
Well, an elephant
does live here.
An elephant?
You're calling my husband
an elephant?
Marge, we got
any more peanuts?
Oh, Homer.
No.
What the...?
Is it that bird?
- Marge! Are you making tea?
- Yes.
Iced tea.
What the hell?
This is WHIS.
Whistling at you
all day and night.
WHIS, The Whistle.
Whistling format radio.
Where is that whistling
coming from?
Maggie?
It is you!
It's so odd...
I'm a terrible whistler.
Always have been.
There must be a reason
you were given this gift.
It's to make people
think I can whistle!
Homer! Homer! Homer!
And now I will perform
Flight of the Bumblebee.
Who was that president?
He looked pretty generic.
I do too have taste.
I'm afraid not.
Corncob curtains.
Mom, what's wrong?
Why aren't you answering me?
I'm right here.
Honey, I'm just
feeling sorry for myself,
but I'll show them.
I'll make a late pickup room
like that school has never seen.
That'll be easy,
there's never been one.
Well, what do you think
of my late pickup room?
It's wonderful.
Hard to believe
it's the same room they found
all those dead rats in.
Well, maybe you can
fool the Hibberts,
but to me, this is
the work of a...
Genius.
Salud.
Well, gee.
Guess who got a job today.
- You?
- Nope.
The guy who went in after me.
I totally set him up.
Listen, I recently purchased
the old post office to renovate.
Would you like to be
my interior decorator?
Well, ladies.
Looks like someone
appreciates me...
the one man in town
who trims his nails.
Is one of them
giving you trouble?
There's no room
in the trunk, boss.
- Bodies?
- No.
Bottled water
and toilet paper, remember?
We made that Costco run.
Now do it backwards.
Now sideways.
Hey, come on.
She's just a baby.
Who is?
My talent.
Makes sense.
Well, well, well.
Seems like my no-talent son
can suddenly whistle.
Tell me, Homer,
how'd you trill that high C
with your lips
in second position?
Oh, it's amazing.
She's got my whistling gene,
all right.
Which, unfortunately,
skips a generation.
I hope it works out better
for you than it did for me.
I was booked on the top
whistling show on radio,
Your Blow of Blows,
with Sid Wheezer.
Good evening, folks.
Sid Wheezer here,
sipping a delicious
Buzz Cola.
Refreshing.
Keep polio at bay,
the Buzz Cola way.
Oh, thanks a lot.
Our next act is a swell kid
from right here
in Springfield.
His hobby is straightening
elbow macaroni.
Let's hear it for
Little Abraham Simpson.
Then I got cocky.
Tried a little stunt called
the Triple Windy.
Blew out the ligaments
in my lips.
Had to hire guys to kiss
my girlfriend.
It was a good deal.
I'd pay for five minutes,
but it would go on for hours.
When the time was right,
I'd make my move.
But this little magpie,
she's got my gift.
And now she's going
into showbiz.
Couldn't showbiz screw her up?
You know,
like it did Ron Howard?
He hasn't won an Oscar
since 2002.
Oh, please, son,
do this for me.
Dad, you should not live your
life through your granddaughter.
You poor guy.
She'll do it.
Okay, Maggie.
Time to learn a happy tune
from these imprisoned birds.
Man, Maggie's talented,
Lisa's talented.
What am I good at?
The birds love ya.
Well, yeah, but they
also love Grampa.
Go ahead, but my blood's
turned to bile
from watching Fox News.
This is my new property,
the original
Springfield Post Office,
jewel of the implosion district.
You'll get used to that.
We'll definitely want to try
to keep the original facade.
Yes, indeed.
I'm all about keeping up
facades.
Is it okay if I take some
foundation measurements?
Of course.
In case she sees something
she shouldn't,
have a hood ready.
Idiota! You whack
who you shouldn't,
and you don't whack
who you should.
Is this about
your brother again?
You're gonna love
this baby!
- She whistles!
- This I gotta hear...
not because I am
looking forward to it,
but because it is my job.
Fantastic talent!
Now, move along...
I have a heart attack at 4:00.
And here it comes.
You sit on it,
you bought it.
Due!
Can you picture
this water feature
at the back wall
of the foyer?
My sainted mother
shared your gift.
Where others saw only
an empty Chianti bottle,
she saw a candleholder.
We would have to rip out
some walls.
- Done.
- You won't be seeing those walls no more.
Why do these guys come with us
for everything?
Have you noticed
how we are not dead?
That is mostly due to them.
Give the wall job
to the Palermo brothers.
Tell them to make it
look like an accident.
We'll make that wall
dig its own grave.
What's that whistling?
You know what they say...
in a marriage,
don't ask a question
you don't know the answer to.
- That's what they say to defense attorneys.
- Marge,
how would you feel
if I kept a big secret from you?
How would you feel
- Good night.
Maggie, you can whistle?
You're gifted too!
Maybe more gifted!
No, no, I will not
get caught in that trap
that only one of us is good.
We could both be good,
like the South Park guys.
Except Trey does everything.
Trey does everything!
Diva.
This little piggy
went to Broadway.
worked with Stallone.
This little piggy
got a Showtime special!
I'm a great father.
Tonight on
Hollywood Nightmares,
- What?!
- Child stars, prison bars.
At three months old, Skyler
Green could already patty-cake.
By age one,
she was the opening act
for Frank Sinatra Jr. Jr. III.
But after a disastrous
Super Bowl halftime show
that left Jacksonville's
EverBank Field in ruins,
Skyler's life
would spin out of control.
She began a downward spiral,
woke up too many mornings
with stuffed animals
whose names she didn't know,
and she was arrested twice
for former cuteness,
under the Scott Baio Law.
Patty-cake, patty-cake,
baker's man,
bake me a train wreck
just as fast as you can.
Oh, my God.
Am I doing this for you,
or because it
makes me feel good?
A showbiz kiss!
There's nothing more sincere
than that. We'll do it!
Marge, I love what
you've done here.
It's as much...
As it is...
It certainly was a challenge,
so many bedrooms.
You must be expecting
a lot of sleepover guests.
Is she...
one of the...?
No, no.
She's the decorator.
But I can get one like her.
Add it to my
customer profile.
Yes.
Dim lighting,
honky-tonk piano...
Anthony D'Amico,
what is the repute
of this house?
Ill.
Our top story...
you didn't see me.
This is...
John Doe saying good night.
Why is everyone being so weird?
Did the principal call?
'Cause he's got nothing
to call about.
I can't keep this mountain lion
in my bedroom forever, Bart.
Just four more days.
So listen, I'm gonna take
Maggie out for a walk.
These spray-on boas
are such a time-saver.
Oh, God, that's good.
Seems like everybody's got
a secret but us, huh, guys?
Tonight, see Maggie Simpson,
the Unborn Comic,
The Umbilical Chords
and the Pixie Chicks.
And now your host,
Sedgwick the Personality!
Welcome to whatever this is.
Now, let's meet our judges.
NBA star and host of
Flip That Igloo,
Muk Mu!
Peace.
Former Hot Tots champion,
Baby Dimples Riskind!
And robotic-themed DJ
Der Zip-Zorp!
You had lunch, didn't you?
I gave you a 2:00 a.m.
curfew for a reason!
Shut up!
Where's denial when you need it?
Maggie, this is
no place for you.
I'm taking you where you
can be a kid again... Moe's.
Oh, I've created a monster!
I've placated a monster!
Marge Simpson,
are the rumors true?
Did you corncob a cathouse?
It's not that.
I sure love that
new whorehouse smell.
Marge, I never thought someone
could sink this town lower,
but you have.
You lied to me!
You may scare these guys,
but to me, you're
just a big fat liar!
Nobody calls
Fat Tony fat!
Nobody!
In the old country,
only two were allowed to
speak truth to the Don.
His capo and his
interior decorator.
You are lucky.
Now, please leave.
The launch party is tonight.
The Grey Goose people are
bringing a big ice thing.
Well, Anthony, not knowing
what I was designing for,
there's something
I didn't tell you.
Your mother had
a post office box
at this office.
I don't know whether
to believe you.
Oh, looks like a letter
from the pope.
You have surrounded
a blessed letter to your mother
with a bordello!
That's it! Shut it down!
Apologize to our dear
friends at Grey Goose.
So, what are you going
to do with my work?
A little Italian lightning
for insurance purposes.
And that is the last question
of yours we will ever answer.
Good-bye, Mrs. Simpson.
Can't you at least wait
until I'm out of the building?
I'm sorry, I get nervous,
I do dumb things.
Maybe it's because
I'm wearing a wire.
Now, put your hands together
for the one who's going to win.
Whoops. That's supposed
to be a secret.
Nothing I can do...
in one moment,
Maggie will stop being my little
baby and belong to the world.
I remember her when she
was just a bit of bad news.
Time for the greatest glory
there is... reflected.
Oh, come on, I'm cheating
on my wife to see this?
Look! She's got a
tooth coming in!
That's the kiss of death
for a whistler.
Give me a string
and a doorknob!
That baby is naught
but an overly dramatic,
boring windbag!
A windbag that yields
no succor!
In sum, a nothing!
What?
They're booing my Maggie?
This is the sweetest
little girl in the world.
Nice try,
but no hook can fit me.
This little angel
never makes a fuss.
She always shares her baby food,
and she makes even a despicable
show like this seem sweet!
Hey, pal, this is
a talent show for babies.
We ain't goin' for sweet.
The only thing that's been
worth it about this experience
is that I got to spend time
with this little girl.
And that's the tooth!
Good night, my little star.
And if you have
another amazing talent,
for the love of God,
don't tell anybody.
Nighty-night.
Okay, so I'll never enter Maggie
into another contest
without telling you,
and you'll never design
another sex palace for the mob.
Agreed. No more secrets
from each other.
No more secrets.
Are you letting out
my pants?
I'm afraid so.
I'm not really a size 32?!