CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(screams)
(exclaiming)
(school bell ringing)
(Barney belches)
(whistle blows)
(yells)
(playing the blues)
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
(grunts)
This is Kent Brockman at the 1st
Annual Springfield Grand Prix,
which, like all our town showcase events,
is not only poorly planned,
it's horribly executed.
(horns honking)
BURNS: The Making
of the Empire State Building,
Part One: The Basement.
(horns beeping)
(gibbering)
(cat screeching)
(tires screeching)
(screaming)
ALL: Aw!
Wait for the gap... Wait for the gap.
Homer, we can buy Scotch tape tomorrow.
There's the gap!
(all screaming)
Gap's too small!
-(screaming)
-LISA: Huh?
A peloton?
Apparently, today is also the final stage
of the Tour De Springfield bike race.
Hey, that's some fancy riding.
(clattering)
(yelling, grunting)
Truthfully, today, there were
no losers and no winners
since both finish lines were
tangled up in this unholy mess.
-(tapping)
-I hear tapping from inside.
-(murmuring)
-What's goin' on?
Well, uh, let's, uh,
all start tapping our toes
to the sounds of Scab Calloway
and his non-union band.
(tapping)
Uh, keep it down in there.
(Taser crackling)
(dance music plays)
So, is this a "date" date or
just a meaningless friend thing?
-Meaningless friend thing.
-True love super date!
Well, if you two ever get
serious and have a baby,
it'll look something like this.
Don't listen to Uncle Bart.
Lisa and I will raise you
in a house of love.
We're not having a baby.
Jimmy!
Oh, brother. Let's dance.
Geek leak!
(laughing)
Hey, Bart, at least I've got a date.
Dance with me, please.
I need to zing my sister.
Okay, but you have to do your homework.
Just kidding. I've given up on that.
Just move your girdle, Yertle.
Hey, Lise, your dance partner
just made the cover of
Dorks Illustrated magazine.
I know that's a zing, but still...
the cover!
Now, you listen to me, Bart.
Milhouse may not be the perfect date.
Please let there be a "but"
coming, please!
-But...
-Landed it!
At least I'm with someone
who tries a little too hard
because he really likes me.
Hey, plenty of babes have docked
in Porta de Barto.
Yeah, for about a week.
But as soon as they
get to know the real you,
they departo de Barto.
That's why you're alone tonight.
Oh, my God, is that true?
MOE:
Yeah, I'm afraid Lisa's right, son.
If the late, great Nora Ephron
taught us anything, it's...
Oh! What's my other
inflatable doll doing here?
What? What?
I ain't here with no one.
Oh, man, Lisa's right.
None of these relationships
lasted very long.
Three days. One recess.
Half a field trip.
Why did I have to get so needy
at the planetarium?
Boy, if anyone needs me,
I'll be taking a popcorn bath.
It's a thing I read about in
a Men's Health magazine
in a dream.
Dad, can I ask you a question?
How did you ever get a woman
like Mom to stay with you?
(scoffs) Look in the mirror,
unplanned miracle.
Is that the only reason?
Well, I also keep things interesting.
MARGE:
All right, who took the microwave?
(laughing) You see?
Hey, what are you looking at?
My ex-girlfriends.
Aw, boy, I feel for you.
Nobody likes to be rejected,
and it never gets easier,
until you can drink.
Because then you can express
your unfiltered feelings
by drunk dialing.
Observe.
(slurring) Hey, it's me again.
He's there, isn't he?
Well, I hope this doesn't sound weird,
but I'm inside your closet.
Um, that's awesome, but I think
I'll visit my ex-girlfriends
and prove they still like me.
(cell phone rings)
HOMER: Hey. It's me.
I was thinking about you.
It's your birthday in like,
three, four months?
Would it be weird
if I threw you a party?
(knocking)
Eat my shorts!
Drop dead.
Eat fist, jerk.
You've got a lot of nerve
showing up here...
and not giving me a kiss.
Inappropriate!
I miss you.
Stalker!
Save me.
(rooster crowing)
Mary Spuckler,
you're my last chance.
She's pretty cute for Cletus's daughter.
Yeah, she liked to drink milk
as a kid instead of white paint.
Is you one of my kids?
No, sir.
Prove it.
A, B, C...
All right. All right.
You convinced me, Einstein.
-What you want?
-Is Mary here?
I'm afraid Mary done run off.
We knows not where.
Dadgummit.
Do you think she still likes me?
Um, hey, Brandine!
Does Mary still like this boy?
I don't know
what that girl likes anymore.
She ran away after we engaged
her to Old Man Wellbottom.
WELLBOTTOM: And I was gonna be
a good husband, too!
If'n I ever get out of this well.
All right. All right now.
-That's enough out of you.
-WELLBOTTOM: But I just--
Oh, I can't believe she ran away.
And this isn't helping.
I better switch to the hard stuff.
Hey, Dubya.
I know where my sister run off to.
New York City.
New York?
That's where Sesame Street is.
Do you ever wonder what happens
to Oscar on garbage day?
Yup, New York.
The big something.
This here's her address.
Good luck!
I don't know if we
should be up here, Bart Simpson.
BART: And why is that?
(wood cracks, Bart yells)
'Cause the floor ain't finished.
Daddy just covers things with
hay and says they're done.
Mom, can we go to New York
to find this girl I used to know?
Bart, that's sweet,
but we'd need
airplane money, hotel money...
And $500 for Yankee tickets,
which turn out to be bogus.
Well, don't buy 'em.
But they're playing the Purple Sox.
Come on, Dad, you love New York.
Now, that your two
least favorite buildings
have been obliterated:
Old Penn Station and Shea Stadium.
Lousy, outdated relics!
Boy, do you remember what happened
the last time we went to New York?
(cool jazz playing)
Keep your meat hooks off
my sister Marge or my goons
will do a soft shoe on your solar plexus.
You're dead, J.J. Get yourself buried.
Tough cookie, huh?
Well, watch me take a bite out of ya.
I'm about to go owl shooting,
and you just said who.
That's some lip you got on you.
How'd you like me to stretch it like a
rubber band and snap you into last week?
You're selling milk, J.J.,
and I got a sour stomach.
Homer, that sounds like
The Sweet Smell of Success.
It didn't feel like success.
Why, ladies? Why?!
Son, you can dial down the crazy.
Your mother and I talked about it,
and we found a way to get to New York.
It's all set, boy.
To save money, we're swapping houses.
But don't the people wreck
your house when they stay in it?
I didn't say I swapped our house.
Yeah, how ya doing?
We're staying here for two weeks.
Lord, you're testing me, aren't you?
Yeah, keep talking
to your friend up there.
We'll be doing it on your bed.
New York style.
Look at this place.
Things have certainly changed
since our ancestor Fievel came here.
Fievel was a mouse in a movie.
Yes, and now look at us.
Only in America.
MAN:
Khlav Kalash! Get your Khlav Kalash!
Oh, geez, not this guy
with his stupid little pushcart.
50,000 square feet, huh?
All Khlav Kalash!
Used to be bookstore. (laughs)
Books.
Come on, let's go find Mary.
This is the address her brother gave me.
Can't Dad take Bart
while we seek out culture?
You do that.
Do you know you're missing your clothes?
I thought this was just a dream.
Oh, man!
All right, I'll spring for a cab.
Much better.
CABBIE: Here we are.
Anything you leave in a cab
you'll never see again.
(snoring quietly)
Hey!
Oh, uh, oh, thank God you woke up.
(doorbell buzzing)
Oh, I guess my search
for true love is doomed.
You've learned a very
valuable life lesson, boy.
Which is that love doesn't exist,
except briefly between a man
and a woman before marriage.
After that, it's just hanging out
with someone who kind of
hates you but you can't get it
together to leave.
I'll get us some ice cream.
What's the matter, darling?
Thanks for asking, Duchess.
I'm sitting here waiting for
a girl that's never gonna show up.
-What makes you so sure?
-Girls don't like me.
I don't really like them yet either,
but I think I'm gonna.
There's a storm a-brewing down there.
Well, there's a girl
a-standin' right here.
It's me, Mary.
Wow, what are you doing for money?
Well, it's not very steady,
and I'm kind of ashamed.
I'm a featured player
on Saturday Night Live.
DON PARDO: Mary Spuckler!
Aw, I'm lying.
My whole life here is a bunch of lies.
I'm just a writer
with a performing option.
Let's talk about something else.
Something nice.
So, this is basically what we can afford.
Okay, second balcony,
partially obstructed view,
no bathroom privileges,
and you must stipulate that,
in emergencies,
you can change a spotlight gel.
Well, at least I'll be able to say
I went to a Broadway show.
You're not allowed to say that.
Oh, forget it.
So, Bart Simpson, did you really come
all the way here just to see me?
Yeah. Plus, I thought I might get
to see an air conditioner
fall on someone's head.
But I guess that never really...
HOMER: D'oh! Ow!
-Is that your father?
-HOMER: What was that?
Bart, I want to see you again,
but I don't want
a grownup taking me back.
Meet me at the high line tomorrow.
Keep my secret!
You little!
Where's that ice cream?!
Just once, I'd like your father
to be on a jumbotron for something good.
HOMER:
Damn you and your fluted neck!
So, what did you do with your dad?
We're safe because you have
to climb steps to get up here.
(Homer groans)
-Can't move?
-No.
I thought there was no crime
in New York anymore.
Giuliani!
Gimme some news of Springfield.
They let Sideshow Bob
out of prison again.
(train horn blows)
Huh, didn't know they
still ran those trains.
How's your momma and your sister?
Trying to find high culture
at low prices.
No, Lisa!
If you click that turnstile,
it'll blow our budget!
-Aah!
-Whaah!
Well, without them around,
you and I can walk through
the city holding hands,
just like the menfolk do.
I could listen to your twang all day.
Would you care to hear it in song?
'Cause I wrote one 'bout you.
Can I do a rap in the middle of it?
Or you could just listen.
Sir, may I borrow your guitar?
Sure, sure. It's the case
that makes money.
♪ A boy I knew turned up again ♪
♪ Kind of liked him way back when ♪
♪ Chased him round
the livestock bend... ♪
(rapping) Rolling on my skateboard,
pimping like a drug lord...
♪ Well I'm on the cusp of womanhood ♪
♪ And I like a boy ♪
♪ That ain't no good at nothin' ♪
♪ 'Cept making me smile ♪
♪ That's Bart ♪
♪ I thought my old ways I had shed ♪
♪ But I sure missed his cylinder head ♪
♪ Now that boy
has a-come to me, oh, yes ♪
♪ B-A-R, now where's that T? ♪
♪ Where is it? I don't know ♪
♪ Oh, that's Bart ♪
I really like you, Bart Simpson.
-I've come to take you back, Mary.
-Daddy?
Sorry, honey, your mother misses you,
but she just can't say it.
That's 'cause the donkey busted her jaw.
She'll be fine. Your mother too.
All right, Broadway's too expensive,
the museums are over-curated,
but Shakespeare in the Park is tonight
and the tickets are free.
(sighs)
Get your cuckold's horns,
neck ruffles, Yorik skulls!
I'll take a cuckold's horn!
It works!
Ladies and gentlemen,
I have an announcement.
Lad-ies and gen-tle-men,
I have an an-nounce-ment--
(gasps) That's not iambic pentameter!
I'm afraid that tonight's
show has been cancelled.
-Why?
-Wherefore?
The Baldwin brothers, who were,
uh, playing the Montague family
and the Sheen/Estevez clan,
our Capulets, have quit the production.
You guys suck at acting and you
ate all the potato salad.
No, you suck at acting
and it's first come, first serve!
I made that potato salad!
Well, uh, idiot, it says
Zaybar's on the package!
He works at Zaybar's.
We all work at Zaybar's.
I'm so sorry.
You came to see Romeo and Juliet,
not feuding families.
Uh, the long, slow line to leave
the theatre forms on the left.
(crowd grumbling)
Aw, and we have to walk by a drum circle!
Faster, man! More annoying!
Not so fast!
We came for Shakespeare
and we're gonna see Shakespeare.
Anyone who wants to be in this,
grab a doublet and meet me backstage!
Is there, mayhaps,
a bit of business for me?
I was thinking amateurs only.
Well,
my only professional job was playing
a nefarious hot dog
in an ad for Taco Bueno.
(sniffs)
You fresh-made tacos will never
defeat pre-boiled hot dogs!
(laughing)
Please, I owe Yale Drama School $200,000.
-They keep calling my mother.
-Fine! You're in.
I must warn you,
I have crippling stage fright.
Oh, for the love of God!
MARGE:
For never was a story of more woe
than this of Juliet and her Romeo.
Our search for culture is thus concluded,
For the Bard of Avon is well suited
to a crowd with every cell phone muted.
Geez, I can't stop talking like this.
Hey, don't ever stop!
Because, tonight,
we made it in New York.
Those the people
who took over the theatre?
Pepper spray and power wash--
the New York hug and kiss.
(Marge screams)
Now, Mary, you listen to me.
I'm one-third your father,
and you're gonna come back.
If y'all will excuse me,
I gotta freshen up for the ride home.
Enjoy your fancy-schmancy
in-house for the last time.
Psst!
-Um, I've got to go.
-Go where?
Uh, well, since we're here,
I'm gonna go try to get
Al Roker's autograph.
Here you go, little fan.
Killer storm on the way.
(nervous laugh)
Um, I gonna go try to sell this.
I'll buy it back.
(groans)
Goodbye, Bart, and don't worry,
there'll be other Mary Spucklers,
including my sisters Mary Zeke
and Mary Not Quite Right.
CROWD: Aw!
(train horn blows)
Bart, if any girl tries
to fix you, let 'em,
because you got a couple
of big problems.
But mostly, you're great!
-Boy, you tell me where Mary's gone!
-I can't.
Boy, you squeal like a piggy
for the hillbilly man.
I can't because Mary's the girl
that proves that girls can like me.
And she wouldn't like me
anymore if I gave her up.
So I won't, even if you torture me
like you do the English language.
Well, if that ain't aren't the isn't.
(sighs) I guess I just gotta let Mary
find her own way.
Come on, let's head on back
to Springfield.
Uh, one on-getter
for the clickity clack, please.
You miss her, don't you, son?
You want a picture of her
for your wallet?
Oh, she's somewhere in B-3.
Thanks, man.
Aw, look at that.
My little guy's finally realizing
how complicated
grownup feelings can be.
Well, at least it didn't end
as bad as Romeo and Juliet.
No kidding. I saw your reviews.
-(snickering)
-Hey!
I specifically said no critics!
This is outrageous!
(gasps)
Ooh, but they like me.
I hope you enjoyed the show tonight.
And if you're worried about
when the air conditioner
fell on my head,
rest assured it was a stunt man,
and his family is being
well taken care of.
But we're here to ask if you
have an idea for a couch gag.
The best submission will be
animated and appear on the show.
Do we screw them on the credit?
No! For details,
log on to TheSimpsons.com.
I'm submitting mine now.
(all laughing)
Subtitled by A. Vandelay