♪ The Simpsons ♪
(TlRES SCREECHING)
D'oh!
(SCREAMS)
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
(GRUNTS)
Now, before we eat,
Let's remember what
we're celebrating today.
After many years of hard work,
your father finally
paid off the mortgage.
See you in hell, document.
ALL: Yay .
All right, Dad.
Way to build equity.
Now remember to
eat smart, people.
Go for the fancy foods.
Don't let them fill you up
with that cheap stuff.
A roll, sir?
Screw you.
Oatmeal?
(GASPS) Smoked salmon!
Shrimp! Crab legs!
(EXCLAIMS)
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
l win.
(WOOZY LAUGH)
Thinner. Thinner.
Thinner. Thinner. Too thin.
Better luck next time,
"Tommy. Virginia Beach."
(SINISTER CHUCKLE)
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
(CHOKING)
You ate meat. You ate meat.
You ate fruit. You ate fruit.
(COUGHING)
(GRUNTING)
Stow it, you two.
(SINISTER LAUGHTER)
Stop making a scene!
How rude!
What do I have to do
to enjoy a Sunday brunch
with my secret other family?
I've never been
so embarrassed.
And the worst part is,
this is brunch, so you've
ruined two meals.
I'll see you all at lupper.
Why did I ever have kids?
I could have
written symphonies
or been Shakespeare.
Oh!
Here, Homer.
Have a big, frosty
mug of forget-about-it.
(DOOR OPENS)
I wouldn't drink that.
From the looks of this place,
it might kill you.
Oh, who are you,
the health inspector?
Yes.
(GASPING)
(SCREAMING)
(BARNEY BURPS)
My God, look at this filth.
I ought to close
this dump down for good.
(GASPING)
But then where would I go
to get away from my wife?
Come here, Moe,
you beautiful,
hideous troll.
(CHUCKUNG)
Guys, this is Frankie
from the Health Department.
We go way back.
Lenny, you don't
have to hide that rat.
Off you go, little fella.
(RAT SQUEAKING)
When we were kids,
our dads used to get
drunk and make us fight
each other. Huh? Huh?
My pop would buy me a malted
for every tooth of
Moe's I knocked out.
That time you blinded me,
he gave you a bike.
That sure was
a good-sounding bike.
(CHUCKLES)
Well, now to give this place
a thorough inspection.
(CLEARS THROAT)
"Free from infestation?"
Check.
"Sanitary utensils?" Check.
"Food hygienically stored?"
Only one way to find out.
Mmm, mmm, mmm.
(GAGGING)
Oh, my God, he's dead.
Okay, which one of you
guys parked in front
of the hydrant?
Uh, look, I didn't see
nothing here, okay?
(CHUCKLES)
Just a bunch of innocent
guys, sitting around,
none of them dead.
Buy yourselves a nice dinner.
(CAR SPEEDS AWAY)
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
Ho.
So, uh, Mr. New Guy,
what do you think?
Is everything
hunky-dory there?
Mr. Szyslak,
your tavern is rife
with health code violations.
You gotta be kidding me.
Like what?
Well, for starters, the body
of my predecessor
is still on the floor.
Oh, yeah. Uh, well, you see,
trash day ain't till
VVednesday, so...
(CHUCKLES)
Mmm-hmm.
Chicken skins
in soap dispenser,
cigarette butts in the air,
toilet on the roof.
I'm shutting you down
till you fix these violations.
Oh, man, I can't afford
to fix all that stuff.
Oh! Nuts.
If anybody needs me,
l'll be in the john.
♪ Oh, Danny boy
♪ The pipes
the pipes are calling
♪ From glen to glen
♪ And down the mountainside
♪ The summer's gone
♪ And all the roses falling
♪ 'Tis you, 'tis you must go
♪ And I must bider
"Moe's, a tribute.
"'M' is for Moe,
the owner of Moe's.
"'0' is for the '0'
in the middle of Moe's.
"'E' is for ex-ceptance,
"The feeling I
always got here at Moe's."
(SOBS) Oh, Moe! Don't let
them close you down.
Oh, it's too late.
I don't have the cash
to clean up the bar.
From now on,
you guys are just gonna
have to do your
drinking across the street.
(CAN'T GET YOU OUT
OF MY HEAD PLAYING)
♪ I just can't get you
out of my head  ♪
Hey, a beer's a beer.
Mmm!
Oh, I can't go
to a gay bar.
I'm too fat.
Moe, I'm going to
help you reopen your bar,
no matter what it takes.
Mr. Simpson,
for a loan this big,
you'll have to put up
your house as collateral.
Put up my house?
But I just paid it off.
What would Marge say?
Do whatever you have
to do to save Moe's.
I love my Homie.
Okay, honey,
I'll do it.
What's going on here?
Nothing. Nothing.
Thanks, Homer.
No one's ever
trusted me before,
except for that one guy
who shouldn't have.
That was me.
Oh, yeah.
Homer, those cuckoo-birds
at the bank goofed up
and sent us
a mortgage statement.
Marge! How dare you
open a letter addressed
to both of us!
"M631700000642J"?
This is a new
loan tracking number.
You got a new mortgage?
I had to, or Moe's would
stay closed forever.
You gave the money to Moe?
How's he going to pay us back?
Look, look,
I can see you're upset.
If you need me,
I'll be at Moe's.
Well, maybe I'll go
to Moe's too, seeing
as I'm now part owner.
Marge, you can't
go with me to Moe's.
I mean, how would you like it
if I came with you
to your mother's?
I would like it.
You never come
to my mother's.
That's because
I hate her.
Hmm.
Until you pay us back,
you're answering to me.
And there's going
to be big changes.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Now, wait just a minute.
One thing Moe Szyslak
has never had is a partner.
Nor a wife, a friend,
a chum, a casual acquaintance,
a pen pal, a parrot,
a meaningful conversation,
a brief hug or eye contact.
I'm just going to call
the suicide hotline now.
(BEEPS)
And they've blocked my number.
Oh, God! (SOBBING)
(SIGHS)
Just made it!
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
Quitting time!
(CHUCKLES)
Boy, I can't wait to get
my lips around an ice cold...
Marge?
I'm here protecting
our investment.
I'd like you to go home
and make dinner for the kids.
But I don't wanna
take care of the kids.
(MUMBLING)
How many cigars are
they allowed to have?
Bart sleeps
in the microwave, right?
Quit playing dumb.
How many magic beans
should I sell the baby for?
Three?
(MUMBLING GIBBERISH)
That's me, jerk-ass Homer.
Come on, go home.
Oh.
Maybe some
cheerier paint would
make this place
less of a "dive."
Marge, my customers
don't like themselves.
Therefore,
they seek the darkness.
(BOTH GROANING)
Well, as fabulous
as your regulars are,
a remodel might bring in
a higher class of lush.
Look, I like Moe's
the way it is, all right?
And I ain't changing
it for any dame, skirt,
Susie-Q or face-macer.
I had a feeling
you'd say that,
so I prepared something
that might help you
change your tune.
♪ This place is a diamond
But it's trapped in the rough
♪ Yeah, well,
the sign still says "Moe's"
So enough of your guff
♪ Here's my new idea
To sell both beer and grub
♪ We will turn
this filthy dive
♪ Into a proper,
old-time British pub
♪ A British what?
♪ Darts and meat pies
And lager in pint glasses
♪ What a classy way
To get drunk off your asses
Hey, hold the phone.
An English pub.
Thatjust might work.
♪ In song
♪ My bar could be British
Instead of arm-pittish
♪ So why don't we all... ♪
Ah, screw it.
Let's get renovating.
Well, I was thinking more
like drapes and a paint job,
But your idea's good, too.
Thanks.
Pint of ale, my dear?
Well, thank you,
Your Honor.
You know,
you're kind of sexy.
That's a deliberate
misstatement of fact.
But I'll allow it.
(CHUCKLES)
(BOTH MOANING)
My first credit card.
Wow, the numbers
are all bumpy-like.
Ha!
So, Mr. Boswell,
what do you think
of the new Moe's?
Marge Simpson
and Moe Szyslak, here's
a mash note to your bangers.
I wish you could
live in me forever.
Thanks, freakazoid.
I'd just like to say
that there's one person
to whom I really owe
my newfound success,
Marge Simpson.
Thanks, Moe.
Dad, Mom's spending
more time at Moe's
than you are.
And they seem
awfully chummy.
Just what are
you inferring?
I'm not inferring anything.
You infer. I imply.
Woo. That's a relief.
Boy, what a night!
Moe showed me
how to give
someone the bum's rush.
Here, watch.
Get lost, rummy!
(GRUNTS)
(MARGE CHUCKLES)
Ah, yes, Detroit-style.
Very nice.
So, you've been
at Moe's every
night this week.
I know. I used to think
of Moe as a scabby,
dead-eyed hunchback,
but now that
I've gotten to know him,
we kind of bonded.
Bonded? How many times?
Homer, Moe and I
are just work friends.
You and I are
marriage friends.
Thanks, honey.
My mind is
completely at ease.
(PHONE RINGS)
MOE: Hey, it's me.
Moe! What's up, partner?
Marge,
sorry to call you so late,
but I had a great idea.
Put cutesy signs
outside the restrooms
that say "Dukes" and "Dames"
Instead of the ones
we have now
that say "Stand-Ups"
and "Sit-Downs."
Huh? Tell me honestly.
What do you think?
Ooh. That's a great idea.
Thanks. Wait, are you sure
I'm not interrupting anything?
Of course not.
I'm in bed with Homer.
Also, I want to go
with the green tablecloths.
Well, I might as well use
this pucker for something.
(TROMBONE PLAYING)
(INHALES)
ANNOUNCER: Coming this summer
from DreamWorks.
(ANNOUNCER READS)
Fifty-two jokers
playing the game
of their lives.
I don't wanna be a three!
I wanna be a seven!
Shut up, kid.
You're as crazy as an eight,
I'm telling you.
ANNOUNCER: With Eddie Murphy
as the Jack of Clubs.
You don't understand,
Officer. I thought that
king was a queen.
(CHUCKUNG)
ANNOUNCER:
This summer, the house is full
and the deuces are wild!
In "Cards!"
Hey, Jack, you got any twos?
You can't handle the twos!
Oh, Marge, don't you love it
when our hands meet in
the popcorn tub?
Mmm-hmm.
(BOTH GIGGLING)
Hey, Marge!
Howdy, partner!
Why don't you
sit next to us?
Hey, Moe.
Haven't seen
you in a while.
Yeah. How you
doing there, Homer?
Did you ever pass
that G.l. Joe
you swallowed?
How do you know
about that?
Oh, Marge told me.
We share everything.
You do?
Don't worry.
They're just friends.
There's nothing
physical between them.
Homer, can you hold
my wedding ring
for a second?
My finger's itchy.
Uh-oh. I'm gonna have to
work on my marriage.
Or alternatively...
(MOANS)
Something wrong, Homer?
Well, I'm worried
about Marge and Moe.
They've developed
an intimate bond
Of thoughts and feelings
completely separate from me.
But it's not physical.
So everything's great, right?
Homer, it's time you
learned the sad truth.
Can I learn it
at a happy place?
(ITCHY & SCRATCHY
THEME PLAYING)
Moe and Marge are having
an emotional affair.
Although there's no
physical intimacy,
there's a deep
spiritual connection
That threatens to
destroy your marriage.
What do I do?
Engage her feelings,
become a friend.
Get her a LIFE Magazine
from the week she was born.
I'll always treasure mine.
You're absolutely right!
Stop this ride!
You're the boss!
(SCREAMING)
I want to go again, Daddy!
Daddy?
Marge, my darling!
Thank God you're home!
I've been dying to
hear your feelings!
Oh, I'm too tired to talk.
Well, I can go
all night, baby.
I could listen to you two,
maybe three times.
Homie, I'm tired.
I have to get up
early to catch my flight.
Catch your flight?
Moe and I are going
to the Tavern and
Restaurant Owners
Convention in
Aruba this weekend.
Don't you ever listen to me?
I told you 10 times.
(SNORING)
Cuckold! Cuckold! Cuckold!
What's a cuckold?
Where's Mom
going with Uncle Moe?
He's only your
emotional uncle!
I'm your real uncle!
Well, if Hollywood movies
have taught us anything,
it's that troubled
relationships can be
completely patched up
by a mad dash
to the airport.
I'm off!
PILOT: Folks, welcome to
No Frills Airlines'
flight to Aruba.
Safety instructions are $2.
If you require wheelchair
assistance, you picked
the wrong airline. Ha-ha.
(GULPS)
You know, Marge,
I've really enjoyed you
working at the bar.
Me, too, Moe.
What a nice surprise
that we've become friends!
Yeah. Oh, Marge,
I'm so in love with you.
And tonight,
after some surf and turf
and a bottle of champagne,
maybe some Snickers pie,
I'll explain
how the hotel made
a little mistake,
And we got to stay in
the same room. Oh, yeah!
(CHUCKLES)
Moe, your upper lip
is trembling.
I'm just excited
because they're showing
An episode of Boy Meets World
on this flight.
Oh, no, wait.
That's only on
flights from Europe.
We just get
that little plane.
Hey, wait a minute.
What the hell is that?
Hang on, Marge!
Homie's coming!
I won't let that
man make you happy!
(SIREN BLARING)
Oh!
Simpson, you were
going 100 in a 25 zone,
and you're not gonna flirt
your way out of this one.
But l have to
get to the airport
to save my marriage!
Really? Well, why didn't
you say so? Let's roll!
You didn't work this hard
to save my marriage.
Again with that. Wake up, Lou.
She was way out
of your league.
FEMALE VOICE:
Flight attendants,
prepare for takeoff.
Time for some
shuba-duba in Aruba.
Oh, my God!
Moe, did you see
something troubling
on the tarmac?
No. Why do you say that?
You got to get
me closer, Chief!
Anything for love!
(GRUNTS)
Okay, time to chase
this pig into the sty.
Uh, Marge, you deserve
a man who listens to you,
who respects you,
who understands
what a treasure
you really are.
I don't know what to say.
Just say you love me, Marge.
Love me like I love you.
Please?
HOMER: Marge!
That sounds like Homer.
No, it isn't.
I don't hear nothing.
You're crazy.
Get out of here.
Will you marry me?
Homer! How'd you
get in here?
Toilet hole.
You leave my wife alone!
You don't deserve her!
You know nothing
about Marge.
What's her favorite food?
Uh, ice?
Wrong! It's buttered noodles.
He's right.
Oh, it's true.
I don't know Marge at all.
I'll just go home now.
(GASPING)
(SCREAMING)
Shut it! Shut it!
(GRUNTS)
Moe, you've won.
I'll see you
at baggage claim.
Hot damn, I won!
Marge, I swear I'll be
the best man you ever had.
It's gonna be all flowers,
and back rubs,
and, "How was your
day, dear?" and...
Moe! No,
I don't love you,
and I'm certainly not going
to leave my husband.
You mean I listened to all
your touchy-feely
yip-yap for nothing?
I'm afraid so.
At least I had
a couple of sips from your
Coke when you
went to the bathroom.
(SOBBING)
Homie...
Marge, I just want to say,
if you ever feel
like cheating on Moe,
here's my card.
Homer, I made a vow
on our wedding day
to stay by you,
for better or worse.
And besides, I love you.
You're my
Homie-womie-romie-domie.
And you're my
Margie-wargie-bargie
fargie-gargie-margie-
targie-largie.
I may have dodged
a bullet here.
Might as well face it,
I'll never find anyone.
Come on tide, take me with ya.
I just don't want
to feel no more pain.
Ow, ow, ow! Ow! Oh!
Moe, I need to tell
you something.
(GRUNTS) Ow!
You showed me
you could be
a really sweet guy.
You can make a woman
very happy someday.
Wow. For realsies?
It's true.
You'd be quite a catch
if you'd just shower,
and shave,
and stop swearing
under your breath.
Aw, thanks, Marge.
Know-it-all bitch.
Oh! Uh, did I mention
there was a mistake
at the front desk? (LAUGHS)
Really?
Is it one that will change
the sleeping arrangements?
Could be. Could be.
(CHUCKLES)
Listen, I got to tell you,
I chew in my sleep.
Yeah, well, I sweat blood.
Good night, both of you.
(GASPS)
Who's watching the kids?
Are you sure Mom
and Dad want us
to enter a European
balloon race?
Sure. Why not?
♪ Love
Love will keep us together
♪ Think of me, babe, whenever
♪ Some sweet-talking guy
in a thong hands you a bong
♪ Don't take a hit
You just got to be strong
MARGE: ♪ You better stop
HOMER:
♪''Cause I want a sandwich
MARGE: ♪ I said stop
HOMER: ♪ Or maybe
a Manwich... ♪