CHOIR: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
D'oh.
(grunts)
(thunder booming)
"In this exciting strategy game,
you amass resources--
timber, salt fish and wax--
to fund a syndicate to gain influence
with the Doges of Venice."
Doges? Why do we have to play
this stupid game Lisa likes?
I don't like this game.
Nobody likes this game.
Even the kids on the box look bored.
They're miserable.
We have to do something
until the storm passes.
Now, just fill out these customs forms,
and we can get started.
(gasps) Twister!
No! Whenever we play that,
my elbow touches Dad's junk.
No! Outside the house!
(all screaming)
(grunts) Here, boy!
Come here, boy!
(grunting)
Get in there.
You live like this?
Ooh, dear Lord,
if thy tornado must take me,
please let it take me to Oz.
But don't let Flanders be the scarecrow.
(gasps) We made it, boy.
-(yelping)
-Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
This counts as a walk!
The tornado took old what's-his-name.
I'm going after him.
No, Homie, it's too dangerous.
(knocking on glass)
Hey, Homer, we were just
doing a little storm chasing.
Lenny, take us with you to find our dog.
It's okay, Marge, they're professionals.
What? 'Cause they rented a van
and taped an antenna to the top?
(scoffs) Not just any tape. Duct tape.
Oh, all right.
But I'm coming with you
to make sure no one does anything stupid.
Don't worry, Marge,
we bought a ton of safety gear
from a highly-respected
storm chaser's widow.
-(gasps)
-It's not what you're thinking.
He died of a heart attack.
Yeah, 80 feet up in the air.
Behold, the awesome nonsense of nature.
Okay, the tornado that took your dog
looked like an F3 moving westerly.
I guess you do know your weather.
Ha! That means a lot coming from such
an attractive woman as you.
I'd say she's prettier
than a surface hoar.
Hey!
Surely, you didn't misunderstand
my usage of "surface hoar."
The sublimation of ice crystals
that's colder than a frost point.
Maybe.
Look, you guys obviously
know about weather,
but I understand something
much more predictable: women.
What women really want
is a guy who's confident enough
to go completely downhill after marriage
and know she'll still love him.
I'll tell you what women really want:
a man who can hold a note the longest.
That is the stupidest...
One, two, three, go.
(all holding single note)
(all continue holding note)
Homer, you do not have to compete
with your friends for me.
I would never do that.
(resumes vocalizing)
-Enough with the singing.
-(all stop vocalizing)
Fine, but I swear,
I will win you back from Lenny.
'Nado!
Ooh.
It's like God's vacuum cleaner.
(laughing)
We're cutting it kind of close.
Not to worry-- we're safe in the van.
Anyone want their seat warmer?
(gasps) It's gone.
Help me, God.
What is it I'm paying you for
every Sunday?
(Marge screaming)
Can... always use...
a good babysitter.
I was just 27 years from retirement!
Oh, my God, the twister got Carl,
my best friend in the world.
I can barely remember what he looks like.
He was a black guy,
but his voice sounded like a white guy.
Hey, excuse me for wanting to fit in.
And here comes Santa's Little Helper.
Homie, we made it.
(both scream)
Oh, my God.
NELSON: Ha ha!
You're trapped in there good.
Once again, the big banks
stick it to the little guy.
-(both grunting)
-Come on.
Are you pushing?
Yes, it won't give.
(sighs)
I don't know if we're going
to be able to get out.
(squeaking)
What are you writing?
Maybe the last words I'll ever write.
Oh.
Lenny, you calling for help?
Let them have their moment.
Kent Brockman here
at death's revolving door.
Police have arrived on the scene
after having fled the state
at the first sign of the storm.
Bulletproof, as I somewhat suspected.
But don't you worry,
we're having a very expensive crane
brought in from Shelbyville.
What is this, a bird?
It's a bird known as a crane.
And it got very sick on the way over.
Well, our top priority
is making sure that bird gets well.
Hey! Hello!
As for you, your only hope
is this glass cutting guy
from the hardware store.
You guys want to come out
in a plain circle
or a kind of a rosette shape?
Just cut the glass.
Everybody wants it done
yesterday. (chuckles)
(groans)
WIGGUM: Uh, now we're ordering some lunch.
Uh, want to go halfsies on a pizza?
FYI, that means you get one slice.
Okay, wise guy, you get to pull out
the two corpses when we're done.
Except for the face full of glass
when the door finally collapsed,
he did a pretty good job.
Found another one.
It was so scary thinking something
might happen to you guys.
Mom, I am so glad you're alive.
Were you worried about me, boy?
Sure. Why not?
(stammers angrily)
Clearly, the boy's in shock.
(chuckling) Oh, yeah, I'm a wreck.
-Stop being blasé.
-Never!
Now, I know you kids
are scared by what happened,
but it's bedtime.
Just go into your dark rooms
and shut your eyes.
(kids groaning)
Homie, if we did both die,
we've never named guardians.
The kids could end up wards of the state.
-Connecticut?
-No, our state.
(screams) Okay, you're right.
It's hard to imagine
anyone else bringing up our kids,
but I think the choice is obvious:
my dad.
Oh, you'd let me have another chance
after the way I screwed
things up with you?
Eh, good point.
We'll find somebody else.
Yep, you're a big bag of blubber
soaked in worthless juice.
I got it, Dad.
Why I married you I'll never know.
Oh, yeah?
The tornado was more of a father
to me than you.
Okay, how about my brother?
He's rich.
(beep)
Hi. You've reach Herb Powell.
I'm poor again.
(startled grunt)
There's really only one choice,
or should I say two identical choices?
Sugar?
Oh, how very kind of you.
I'm not giving our kids
to these gravelly-voiced super hags.
One lump, please.
Homer, my sisters adopted Ling,
and she's doing great.
We've been tiger-mothering her.
Ling, music time.
♪♪
Ling, floor routine.
More syncopated. Stick the landing!
And no resenting us ever.
That's some impressive flute-nastics.
Shut up! You can't praise her.
She'll think she's smart and slack off.
Then all our loving would be for nothing.
Mmm, maybe we'd better go.
Didn't you want to ask us something?
Good-bye forever.
(whispering) Help me.
I think it's time to go off family.
KIRK: Luanne and I have gone
through some rough patches,
so to be seen as stable enough
to raise your kids, well,
it would be an honor.
You know what else
would be an honor?
Having a husband who asks my opinion
before inviting in
three more mouths he can't feed.
Hey, Luanne, you always asked me
what I saw in Vicky at the Walgreens.
Well, I'll tell you what I saw: not you!
You told me
you didn't even know her name.
Well, that's her name, okay?
BRANDINE: Let me get this straight.
We have 17 kids, and you want us
to take three more?
Anything new that wanders into this house
winds up in the stew pot.
Hey, I'm so sorry,
but we just adopted a baby.
Give me back my pants.
I've got to get back to my unit.
Someone's cranky.
All right, Marge,
maybe we're being a little too choosy
about who our kids
spend the rest of their lives with.
We'll take what we can get.
(gasping)
Uh-oh.
I wonder if word has gotten out
that we're looking for guardians.
(grunts, growls)
Ah!
Go! Go!
(tires squealing)
(beeping)
(people screaming)
(dog howling)
(hums, grunts)
(Dr. Hibbert chuckling)
(airplane flying overhead)
All right, the coast is clear.
(relieved murmuring)
Wait a minute, I live here. Aw.
-Where are we going?
-And why are we wearing our good clothes?
With name tags on them.
Kids, there's nothing to worry about.
(walrus barking)
But we're looking at replacements
for your mom and me
if we should fail
to die together as a family.
Oh, I see.
You guys are trying to find
a couple of saps to take us
when Dad has a coronary
in the dead of night,
rolls over and crushes Mom.
This is not that,
and that smart-alecky attitude
is exactly why no one wants you.
Homer, dual incomes, no kids at 2:00.
(gasps) Ooh.
Okay, I'll nudge them with the car.
We'll get a whole "meet cute" thing going.
(gasping)
Aah! What the hell are you doing?
Keith, relax.
Look at those adorable children.
Hmm, I think I hear a slight accent.
Mid-Atlantic.
(gasps)
That's where they filmed The Wire!
-Step on it!
-(tires squealing)
This is a pretty important decision.
How about asking that Japanese guy
who set the world record
for eating hot dogs?
He's like a successful version of Dad.
(groans)
Maybe we should just give up for now,
have some fried clams
and collect sea glass.
Wait, what about that couple?
They look pretty cozy.
That's Moe and a bag of garbage.
-Boy, cats sure breed a lot.
-(meowing)
(yells)
Why would you do that to me
after I thought about feeding you?
(grunts) Mmm.
(laughing)
Whoa, look at that guy.
Yo, I'm Mav.
Wow, a man's stomach can be flat?
It's one of the, like,
awesome side effects
of being a pro surfer.
Wow.
Someone's smitten.
Whoa, way to shralp the crispies, babe.
My wife, Portia.
Another surfer?
Environmental lawyer.
(sighing)
And in my free time,
I prosecute record companies
who withhold royalties
from elderly blues musicians.
(sighing continues)
(grunting)
Um, why don't we discuss it over dinner?
Discuss what?
Things that you're desperately missing
from your life
that you never knew you needed.
Cool. See you at 6:00.
(birds cawing)
So, surfing is really your job?
Yeah, I earned a couple million
on the tour last year.
Just for standing on a thing?
Mmm. Wow.
Your house is perfect.
No sharp corners,
no unsafe balconies, a cool grandpa.
I love two things:
shutting up and giving away money.
Ooh, thanks, Dad.
What's that stone around your neck?
It's a promise stone.
It signifies that
if I ever get to be a burden,
I just jump in a volcano.
Wow.
I assumed the Jackson Five
were the only perfect family,
but now I see there's another.
Princeton, B.A., Oxford, M.A.
I smell a Rhodes.
No, I turned it down
because Cecil Rhodes was such a racist.
(sighs)
Uh, say, listen, Portia.
How would you and Mav feel about...
um, swinging?
Uh, with you guys?
Uh, seems like my husband
would be getting
the much better deal.
No, no, no.
I-I meant pushing kids on swings.
Give me a minute to get
some images out of my mind.
Okay, take whatever time you need.
I just want to know if you'd
like to be their guardians.
Wow. Wow, that's quite an offer.
This is so fast.
It's so hard to get to know a child
after just one day. I...
All you need to know
is I'm a politeness monster
who eats please
and farts thank-yous, ma'am.
I'm exactly the kind of kid
he's pretending to be.
(belches)
Hmm.
Babe, when a killer wave hits,
you can't spend your whole life
deciding if you want to drop in or not.
It just might be the most
righteous tube we ever shot.
Man, you sure can talk surfer talk.
Okay, we'll give some serious
thought to taking them.
Maybe this will help you
make up your mind.
It's empty.
You never know when you
might want to mail something.
Homie,
it's been a wonderful day,
but do you think maybe we're moving
a little too quickly?
Worrywart Marge.
You don't look a Trojan horse
in the mouth.
(laughter)
But we know so little about them.
I swear to you, Marge,
when I have the time,
I will Google them both.
It's all good, brah.
Hey, where's Bart?
Oh, uh, well, he wanted to be here,
but I'm going to decrease
the volume of my voice
and mumble so you can't really
understand what I'm saying,
and I'll just keep doing it
until the subject...
Your father says I need to keep you lashed
to the mast for five more arrrs.
-Is that arrrs or hours?
-Both.
Great.
And now my dad can notarize.
I still have my uses.
Mm-hmm.
-Name another.
-(groans)
Well, I must admit
it's a relief to get that taken care of.
Now I can finally complete my bucket list.
(chuckles)
Homer, Marge,
we have a favor to ask.
Too late! You already signed!
Oh, wait, there's one more.
Suckers!
Oh, wait, you've got to initial this.
Checkmate.
(chuckles) Listen, Homer,
we just wanted to know
if we could borrow the kids
for a weekend at our ski house.
We thought they could
pick out their bedrooms.
A whole weekend?
I don't know.
Hey, if they can watch them
for the rest of their lives,
they can certainly do it
for a weekend.
I guess.
As long as we don't make it a habit.
Marge, no indulgence of mine
ever becomes a habit.
Do you have to do that in front of people?
It helps me write.
♪ Just the two of us ♪
♪ We can make it if we try ♪
Marge, this has been great couples time.
The one thing people with kids
desperately need is no kids.
Well, at least we have time
to get the pets' Christmas presents.
I don't like the way
they just rip the paper off.
Santa's Little Helper, my ass.
(gasps)
Hmm?
My God.
They want to steal our kids.
No one steals my kids,
except me, from that theme park jail
that I never told you about,
except I guess I just did.
We're all caught up now. Let's go.
MARGE: It all makes sense now.
That's why they took our kids so quick.
Like all childless couples,
they troll the beaches waiting
for the egg-layers
to wander off from their young.
She's gonna raise three kids
without wrecking that perfect figure.
Oh, yeah, man.
-(groans)
-Don't worry, Marge.
We'll get them.
Unless we die on this icy mountain road.
Then they've won forever.
Homie, I just had a horrible thought.
(chuckles)
Women and their horrible thoughts.
What if they are better
for the kids than us?
Marge, let me set your mind
straight about something.
That spectacular young couple
is definitely better for the kids,
but those kids are ours,
because we made them
by accident.
And now we're gonna take them back
because we love them,
especially now that we've had
a little time apart from them.
-(crashing)
-(Marge groans)
I've got a bone to pick with you.
Then an apology to make.
Then we exchange insurance information.
Then more bone picking.
Homer, Marge, I understand your anger,
but your kids are more awesome
than the breaks at Waimea.
Those better be good breaks.
Honestly, we fell in love with them,
and it just seemed like you guys
didn't really want them.
Sure, you wanted the fun parts,
but do you want to go
to their little league games
and recitals?
-We totally have.
-Like clockwork.
Well, I'm glad someone has.
Look, before anyone says anything else,
how could you possibly think
you could get our kids?
It happens more than you know, Marge.
I'm a lawyer; he's a surfer.
That combination's pretty unstoppable.
BART: Well, I'm afraid
that we don't want to be
with anyone but Mom
and whoever she chooses to be with.
Portia, you're the woman
I dream of becoming,
but Mom is my mom.
Fine, but you're leaving a gap
in our lives
that can only be filled
by foreign travel,
sleeping late and gourmet food.
You guys lock up.
We're going to Bali.
(groans) Again.
We've won!
(flatly) Whoo-hoo.
Kids, your father and I have decided
we're not in such a hurry
to get you guardians.
Instead of concentrating on dying,
we're going to concentrate on living.
If you call this living.
-Why, you little...
-(choking, grunting)
I do call this living.
Living the way kids in India
can only dream of.
There is nothing like
your biological family.
(Homer, Lenny and Carl
holding single note)
(Lenny and Carl coughing)
(Homer continues holding note)
HOMER: I win.
LENNY: Win what?
HOMER: I forget.
-(murmuring)
-Shh!
Subtitled by A. Vandelay