CHORUS: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(theme music playing)
(bell ringing)
(mechanical whirring)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
(tires screeching)
(clanging)
(honking horn)
D'oh!
-(screams)
-(tires screeching)
(crowd muttering)
This is Kent Brockman,
live at the Monty Burns' Casino.
Moments from now, the house that
Social Security checks built
will be demolished to make way
for a casino-themed family hotel.
This must be heart-breaking for you, sir.
I'm just thinking of my employees.
All the cardsharps,
bottom dealers and shills.
Where will they go?
They're managing your chain
of nursing homes, sir.
Excellent.
Gone are such headliners as
Little Timmy and the Shebangs,
The Shebangs,
and The New Shebangs featuring Big Timmy.
Remember how excited we were
when this place opened?
Then, a week later,
we just forgot about it.
I'm surprised they bothered to move it
when they moved the town.
Oh, I can explain that.
-You see...
-Five.
Four...
three... two...
All right! Here comes the implosion.
Implosion?
But I thought you said...
-(explosion)
-(crowd screaming)
Hockey pucks!
(laughing)
Don Rickles zinged you, Marge.
Dust!
Eat my dust, dust!
(tires screeching)
-(thud)
-(man screams)
LISA: Dad, we hit Don Rickles!
RICKLES: I'm OK.
But the Puerto Rican guy's
trying to steal your hubcaps.
(laughs) Just kidding.
♪ I'm a nice guy ♪
We'd better stop and get the car washed.
Ah, what's the rush?
Might rain next week.
Hey, Homer.
Car's kind of dirty.
Really? You think I should get it washed?
Yeah, maybe.
(tires screeching)
You listen to your friends
but you never listen to me.
Hey, that's great.
All right, young 'uns, bath time.
Cover up your eyes and drop your britches.
Who wants wax?
KIDS: Yay!
MAN: I insist you take special care
with my collection of valuable
and humorous bumper stickers
particularly this one
which was given to me
by a Harrison Ford look-alike.
(speaking in Spanish)
(buzzing)
-(boing)
-Oh!
(in English) Wow, you can't find
this stuff anywhere.
Seals and Crofts, Pablo Cruise,
Air Supply...
Whoa! Loggins and Oates.
And it's free.
I've never heard of these bands, Mom.
What kind of music do they play?
Crap rock?
-No...
-Wuss rock?
That's it.
(cash register rings)
Ten dollars?
What is this? A car wash for millionaires?
Throw hot wax on him, Dad.
Howdy, Homer.
Five dollars, please.
Hey! How did Churchy la Femme
get half price?
Senior citizens' discount.
Pfft! Senior citizen?
Flanders?
Well, we'll see about that.
(church organ playing)
...and once again, tithing
is ten percent off the top.
That's gross income, not net.
Please, people, don't force us to audit.
(grumbling)
Now, we're going to pass this around
a second time.
Brother Ned, if you'll do the honors.
I wouldn't do that, Reverend.
You see, "Saint Flanders"
is as crooked as you or me.
(all gasping and muttering)
That's right... It's my sad duty
to rat out this man
for defrauding a car wash.
How, you ask?
With a phony senior discount card.
(gasping and muttering)
That's not quite true.
Did you or did you not use
a senior citizen discount card
at said car wash?
Well, I did, but--
Now, I'm not a fancy big-city lawyer...
(gasping)
...but it seems to me
that a senior citizen has to be over 55.
Isn't that so?
Well, yes.
And you are how old?
(sighing) Oh...
I suppose, if you must know,
I'm... Well, I'm... I'm 60.
MAN 1: God, he looks so cool.
MAN 2: He looks terrific.
MAN 3: He looks really young.
What's your secret, Flanders?
Goat placenta? Monkey sweat?
Some kind of electric hat?
Holy water? It's holy water, right?
Ah! It burns!
Listen, folks. There's no magic formula.
I just follow the three C's:
clean living, chewing thoroughly,
and a daily dose of Vitamin Church.
(disappointed sighs)
And, of course,
I resist all the major urges.
All of them?
You mean you've never splurged
and, say, eaten an entire birthday cake,
-then blamed it on the dog?
-Huh?
You've never licked maple syrup off
your lover's stomach?
(embarrassed groaning)
You never snuck out of church
to break into cars?
No, no, and double no!
I haven't done any of those things, folks.
You name it, I haven't done it.
Geez, Flanders. You're 60 years old
and you haven't lived a day in your life.
Yeah. Even the Boy in the Bubble
had a deck of cards.
(all murmuring agreement)
-MAN: I remember that.
-Hmm.
Oh, can you believe it?
It almost seemed like those folks were...
were making fun of old steady Neddy.
Well, you may be a bit cautious,
but what's wrong with that?
Some people like chunky peanut butter,
-some like smooth.
-Mm-hmm.
And some people just steer clear
of that whole hornet's nest.
I'll stick with just plain white bread,
thank you very much, maybe with a--
ALL: Glass of water
on the side for dippin'.
(tires screeching)
Gosh, darn it.
Am I that pre-diddley-ictable? (sighs)
I've wasted my whole dang diddley life.
Hey, there!
("Any Way You Want It" playing)
Look at that. Everyone's
living it up except Ned.
Help!
We're being carjacked.
Don't get clever, old man.
Now, take us to DressBarn.
MAUDE: Where have you been, Neddy?
In the bathroom.
Not trimming my mustache.
What do you think?
Do I remind you of troubled
troubadour David Crosby?
No. You remind me
of silly billy Ned Flanders.
(all giggling)
Would a silly billy sit like this?
Oh!
Rod, call Dr. Stein.
HOMER: All right, Bart!
Fire in the hole!
(laughing)
OK, no more gasoline.
Hmm.
(Homer humming)
Full power!
Never a dull moment, huh, Homer?
You got that right.
Throw on the mesquite, Bart.
Mesquite it is!
Here, this may sound
just a teensy bit insane
in the old membrane, Homer,
but I was wondering if you could show me
how to have some fun.
Well, well, well. So, Flawless Flanders
needs help from Stinky-pants Simpson.
(laughs) Yeah, I guess I do.
Welly, welly, welly...
Mr. Clean wants to hang
with Dirty Dingus Magee.
How about it, Homer?
Will you teach me the secret
of your intoxicating lust for life?
Wellity, wellity, wellity...
Stop that!
Will you help me or not?
-(can clanking)
-Let's do it.
-(Homer groans)
-So, what about all this meat?
Ah, the missus will clean that up.
Now it's Marge's time to shine.
First of all,
I get five dollars a day plus expenses.
Seems fair.
And I'll need your signature here...
here...
and... initial here.
Ha. You're not really giving my father
power of attorney, are you?
Of course, I... (gasps)
Oh, my stars! I can't do that.
Well, that's unfortunate.
It really is.
(sighs)
All right.
Congratulations.
Welcome to the Homer Simpson Program.
So, what happens next?
One day soon, I will come for you...
and then the game will begin.
Could be in the middle of the night.
It could be when you least expect it.
Or whatever's good for you. I don't care.
OK, Homer,
I'm ready to learn.
What's the first lesson?
Just give me the topic sentence.
Give me that!
That's your problem.
You're living up here.
You got to live down here...
in the impulse zone.
If you want to be like me,
you got to make snap decisions.
Like this.
-(tires screeching)
-MAN: Oh!
We're going to break the bank
at the Monty Burns' Casino!
Homer, they blew that up yesterday.
HOMER: Oh, yeah. Right.
-(Homer gasps)
-(Ned screams)
Then we're going to Las Vegas.
Which is actually back in that direction.
-(exclaims)
-(man screams)
♪ Nobody's gonna take my Ned ♪
♪ Gonna teach him to have fu-un ♪
♪ Oh, he's a Flanders machine ♪
That sure was a fun trip to Las Vegas.
Uh, too many kids.
Ooh, it's going on 8:30.
I'd better call Maude
and tell her where I am.
Relax. I called her from the gas station.
Thanks, buddy.
(chortling)
Sucker.
(upbeat music playing)
Oh, gee, Homer, this all looks so garish.
-(elephant trumpeting)
-(lion roaring)
(gorilla shrieking)
Oh! The lights, the noise,
the letter "X"...
It's-it's all designed
to inflame the senses!
I'm overstimulated.
I've got to get out of this town.
I don't think so.
I think you'll find
escape is quite impossible.
No, I got it.
Oh. Oh. Would you like
to be in the audience
for my infomercial?
(screaming)
Help me! My daughter's not talented!
(groans)
(tires screeching)
(people cheering)
Hey! Lance Murdock!
(engine revving)
If he's not careful
his scooter could roll
right down that ramp.
He's a daredevil, Ned.
He laughs at death.
Huh! When I want to laugh
I'll take Bob Saget, thank you very much.
ANNOUNCER: And now
the indestructible Lance Murdock
will jump his SuiCycle
over an audience member.
And he'll do it while attempting
to open a locked safe on his head.
Any volunteers?
Ooh, ooh, ooh! Pick him, pick him!
Now, Homer, no!
I want to do something exciting,
but I can't just go
from zero to 30 like that.
I could be killed.
Fine. I'll do it.
Where do you want me?
On the "X."
(SuiCycle engine revving)
You mean the one with the red paint?
Uh, yeah, paint.
Now, it's of critical importance
that you don't--
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I'll figure it out.
This isn't rocket science.
Well, actually, there are several rockets
mounted to the--
Boring.
-(drumroll)
-(crowd chattering excitedly)
(engine roaring)
ANNOUNCER: OK, he's cleared
the ring of fire...
past the ring of ice...
over the dog-doo stick...
He's cracked the safe...
Hey, Flanders, don't spill my beer.
Oh, God, lay down!
Lay down!
(Lance screaming)
Clear!
(buzzing)
He's all right, folks!
(crowd cheering)
Okeydoke, let's hit the tables.
Oh, my God, Homer,
watching you risk your life
turned my beat box
all the way up to rumba.
Yeah, I was praying you'd be safe,
but t-to be honest, a part of me
wanted to see you get splattered.
Oh, I see someone just had
-his first taste of bloodlust.
-Huh.
Let's see, what's Marge's birthday?
Barney's is July 15, same as Lassie's,
so Marge must be 50... Oh, forget it.
Flanders, what's your birthday?
No, leave me out of this, Homer.
Games of chance are strictly forbidden
by Deuteronomy 7...
Seven, eh?
DEALER: Seven a winner.
-Way to go, Flanders!
-(gasps)
The Bible's finally pulling its weight.
Got any more holy numbers?
Oh, I got a bunch, Homer, but...
I just don't feel right.
Oh, Lord, what should I do?
DEEP VOICE: Keep gaming.
What?
It means gambling.
Keep gambling.
Oh. Righty-o.
One betting disk, please.
"One betting disk, please."
Watch and learn.
And 14 black.
Well, there you go.
-Now, how about a drink?
-(exclaims)
How do you do it, Homer?
How do you silence that little voice
that says "think"?
You mean Lisa?
Oh, no. I mean common sense.
Oh, that.
That can be treated
with our good friend alcohol.
You might want to write that down.
Where the hell's your notebook?
-You threw it out the--
-Never mind.
Just pay attention. Slave girl?
Oh, slave girl?
More libations, my imperial conquerors?
-What?
-More booze.
Oh, yeah.
Two more of these, please.
And for you, Ned?
I'll have a Shirley...
No, a Virgin...
No, make it a children's...
Oh! What the heck.
You only live once.
Give me a...
(echoing) White Wine Spritzer!
(Homer snoring)
(groans)
Oh, my goodness, Homer. Ugh.
Wake up.
(incoherent mumbling)
Oh. Look at this place.
We must've really
painted the town last night.
I have a pounding headache,
my mouth tastes like vomit
and I don't remember a thing.
Welcome to my world.
Oh, I did it!
I conquered my fears
and I made up for a lot of lost living.
And I owe it all
to the Homer Simpson Program.
The what, now?
WOMAN: Well, it's about time
you two woke up.
Well, of course... (screams)
Who are you?
Who am I?
I'm Mrs. Ned Flanders.
(gasps)
(laughing)
Hey, smooth move, Flanders.
And I'm Mrs. Homer Simpson.
(screams)
-Here comes that vomit again.
-Ew.
HOMER: OK.
OK. OK. OK.
OK. OK.
OK.
OK, you're saying that
Ned and me married you two.
Oh, yeah. We're hitched, all right.
Till death do us part.
Mm-hmm. I'm working on that.
Ned, no!
Think of your wives!
Wait a minute.
This could be some kind of scam
or possibly scamola.
We would remember if we got married.
Boy, you did have a lot to drink
last night, Homeo.
Take a look at this.
HOMER: Aw. "Precious Memories."
"I okilly-dokilly, schmokilly" do.
And do you, Homer, take
this cocktail waitress you just met
to be your lawfully-wedded wife?
What did you call me?
(sighs) Do you want
to get married? Married?
(imitating Sinatra)
Sure. Sock it to me, baby!
By the power vested in me
by the Chicago Outfit,
I now pronounce you husbands and wives.
(smooching)
We are so dead.
Ladies, we want to do the honorable thing.
So, breakfast is on us
with full waffle bar privileges.
But first, I'm afraid
we have some bad news.
(dramatic sigh)
The waffle bar is closed.
I'm sorry, I'm so very...
Homer! The bad news, ladies,
is we already have wives.
Well, you can't be very happy with them
if you married us.
You two fellas are the nicest husbands
we've ever had
and we're not giving you up
without a fight.
But, Ginger, honey,
I am not the catch I appear to be.
Ginger's my wife.
Are you sure?
Oh, rats.
No offense, sweetie.
Homer, why don't we go make
the girls some custom omelets?
Geez, I've never seen anyone
so whipped so fast.
(imitates whip cracking)
(frantic groaning)
What are we going to do, Homer?
My kids are going to be traumatized.
And then there's Maude.
And then there's Maude!
I don't know, Flanders.
Having two wives
could have its advantages.
Chop, chop, dig, dig,
chop, chop, dig, dig,
chop, chop, dig, dig...
You know, Homie, there's so much more
two wives could do for you.
I hear digging, but I don't hear chopping.
(gulping)
(buzzing)
Ooh, a friendly bee.
Ow! (groans)
Ow! That sting hurt so much.
We got to get out of this, Ned.
Well, do something.
This is all your fault.
You and your stupid program.
Blame me if you must,
but don't ever speak ill of the program.
The program is rock solid.
The program is sound.
Yoo-hoo!
Oh, those awful women want their omelets.
(kissing)
Oh. How are we gonna get out of this mess
in an honorable and decent...
Oh, nuts!
I don't know.
Omelets have a lot of fat in them.
Forget it. You're married.
Let yourself go.
-(grunt)
-Hey, they're running away!
("Viva Las Vegas" playing)
♪ Bright light city gonna set my soul ♪
♪ Gonna set my soul on fire ♪
(screams)
♪ Gotta whole lotta money
that's ready to burn ♪
♪ So, get those stakes up higher ♪
♪ There's a thousand pretty women ♪
♪ Waitin' out there ♪
♪ They're all livin', the devil may care ♪
♪ And I'm just a devil
with love to spare ♪
(grunting and yelling)
♪ So, viva Las Vegas ♪
♪ Viva Las Vegas... ♪
(groaning)
How can a fat guy run so fast? Hey!
Yay! (kisses)
Come on, baby, show Gil a four.
-Craps.
-Oh, no!
Why did I bet the company payroll?
Oh, Gil's in a lot of trouble.
(giggles)
Somebody help!
-Our husbands are trying to ditch us!
-(people gasping)
Someone dishonoring their marriage vows?
Not in Las Vegas.
Attention, all employees.
We've got two runaways. Stop them.
-(panting)
-(exclaiming)
-(screams)
-Oh, no!
-(groaning)
-(gasps)
(snarling)
(screams) A lion!
(gasps) Drederick Tatum!
Your behavior is, is unconscionable.
(both gasp)
(screams) The Moody Blues!
"Cold-hearted Homer, ditching his wife
While ancient Ned runs for his life
Chips of red and blue and white
But we decide..."
Can the poems. It's ass-whupping time.
I want fatty.
(screams)
(pursuers muttering)
What if we switched wives?
Would that help?
For the last time, no!
Hello!
Our ticket to freedom.
(engine starting)
So long, suck--
-(everybody yelling)
-(tiger snarling)
-(Homer and Ned whimpering)
-Get out and stay out.
Las Vegas doesn't care for out-of-towners.
Take your money and go someplace else.
-ALL: Yeah.
-Why do you disrespect us?
And don't you ever try to marry us again.
We found some guys
who know how to treat a woman.
-Uh...
-(smooching)
(growling)
But, Amber, I can change!
Will you shut up?
All right, let's get our stories straight
for Marge and Maude.
We were out buying them fabulous gifts...
What's the occasion?
Because we love them, jackass.
Anyhoo, we come out of Walmart,
when suddenly 100 spaceships...
-Homer!
-You're right, you're right.
Fifty spaceships beamed us aboard.
They gang-probed you
while I discovered an invention
that blew their heads up
and saved America.
Uh, do I have to be gang-probed?
Would you rather tell Maude the truth?
(Ned sighing)
What did the aliens look like?
Well, I only saw them from the back
'cause they were so busy gang-probing you.
HOMER: Well, hello, little birdie.
-(vultures squawking angrily)
-(Homer and Ned yelling)
HOMER: Oh, my eyes! Cover your eyes!
("Viva Las Vegas" playing)
♪ If I wind up broke, well ♪
♪ I'll always remember
that I had a swingin' time ♪
♪ I'm gonna give it everything I've got ♪
♪ Lady Luck, please let
the dice stay hot ♪
♪ Let me shoot a seven with every shot ♪
♪ Viva Las Vegas ♪
♪ Viva, viva ♪
♪ Las Vegas ♪
-(murmuring)
-Shh!
Captioned by
Visual Data Media Services