Oh, my hallway‐walking God!
I've seen my fair share
of workplace atrocities,
but this one's gonna be hard
not to whistle‐blow.
Carlson,
how about you forget
any unkillable
irradiated airborne entities
you think you saw
and sign
this nondisclosure agreement?
I'm sorry, I have no choice
but to speak up and say...
What's in it for me?
Guess who just got
two VIP concert tickets
to see Bob Seger tonight!
Bob Seger!
Which Bullet Band
is he bringing?
Silver!
In that case,
I'm closin' shop early.
Marge, you know how nothing
ever happens to me?
Well, the curse has been lifted!
I love how excited you are
to chaperone
the kids' weekend sleepover
on the World War II battleship.
What?! Chaperoning?
You can't just spring this on me
at the last...
Aw, you've got to fill in
for me, Marge.
I'd do it for you
if you were the husband.
You always get to do
the fun thing
and leave me holding the bag.
I'll get you a new bag.
A tote from the merch table.
What size are you?
No. I'm watching the Gen Gala
red‐carpet arrivals tomorrow.
Can't you just record it
and watch it next week
when me and Lenny are
at the Hall & Oates concert?
I'm hosting the watch party.
I have firm commitments
from several A‐level gays.
We're all gonna make
snarky comments
about celebrities'
outrageous outfits.
I'm working up the courage
to use the B‐word on a man.
Okay, honey, I give up.
You host your party.
I go to the concert.
No field trip for the kids.
It was your decision,
so I'll let you tell them.
Yo‐ho, yo‐ho
A field trip life for me
Mommy! Mommy!
I took a bite of my juice box
because I forgot!
Ready about, sailors!
Name's Captain Bowditch.
For the next 36 hours,
you will be my crew
aboard the USS ship with a name
we're not allowed to say anymore
and with good reason.
Now, the year is 1943.
We sailors have fought many
battles in the Pacific theater,
but today we face
our most vicious enemy yet...
Oxidation.
Kill those lousy Oxies!
Rust has overtaken the vessel,
and I'm giving you three tools
to neutralize the threat,
wire brushes, marine paint,
and the remainder
of the weekend.
Chaperones, you will stand watch
in six‐hour shifts.
Now, pair up!
Can you imagine getting stuck
with Sarah Wiggum
for the whole weekend?
What's she looking for,
a personality?
So, I guess we should figure out
some system to pair up, like...
Hey, Sarah, we've met before.
I'm Bart's mom, Marge.
Hi.
So, overnight field trips,
the things we do for our kids.
Kids.
So...
have you ever been
on a battleship before?
Probably.
We're so close,
we can read the labels
on the drummer's medications.
Hey, I have that too.
Mild depression rules!
Nice seats, huh, fellas?
Yeah, Mr. Burns' payoffs
are always the best.
Luckily, I was able to get
my wife to take over chaperoning
some stupid battleship weekend
with Ralphie.
Hey, I saddled my wife
with that too.
Marge and Sarah
were okay with that?
Ah, they'll be fine.
Wives, they love
that World War II stuff.
Yeah, they're always gifting
their husbands
books and movies about it,
but you know they're really
buying it them for themselves.
And number ten would be...
telling a funny story.
What are your top ten ways
of starting a conversation?
Talking.
I guess we should get back
to the kids.
They're asleep.
What?
Almost midnight?
How did it get so late?
It's only 8:50?
Wait. Did you move
the clock ahead
to trick the kids
into going to sleep early?
Sarah, I'm impressed.
A bottle of pocket alcohol.
Dang, this is the last place
on earth I want to be.
No offense, Marge, but, geez,
this field trip sucks!
You said all those words!
I'm just quiet.
Even though everyone thinks
I'm an idiot.
No, no, we don't think
you're an idiot.
We just think you're boring.
Did you bring this from home?
Actually, I got it from Admiral
Dingdong's liquor cabinet.
- It wasn't locked?
- Oh, maybe it was.
Wink.
I've never done a swig.
Oh, Sarah Wiggum, who are you?
I love Clancy, but you have
no idea what it's like
to be married to a man
with a dangerous job
he's just not good at.
Actually...
And with the way he eats,
each crust
he sucks the cheese out of
could be his last.
Maybe I do understand.
It just takes so much work
to be a mom and a wife
and keep the goods
in a tight little package,
if you catch my drift.
Sometimes it feels like he...
Takes me for granted!
Why do his last‐minute man‐plans
have to ruin
the one day of the year
where I get to be catty?
Hell yeah, sister.
Well, you know what?
You and me,
we're like two fun peas
in a party pod.
We should do more hangouts.
Oh, I'd like that, but there's
a reason I keep to myself.
Secret reasons.
Oh, no.
What are you doing here?
How did you find me?
Sarah!
Marge!
Please take this bag
off my head.
I think whoever you kidnapped
before me was a smoker.
Why did you bring her into it?
She's just
some vanilla soccer mom.
She doesn't know anything.
Hey, once I start bagging heads,
I can't stop.
Hey, there, Sarah.
I see you're hanging
with the Yankee Candle crowd.
Wait. You know these people?
Marge, meet Bette and Erin.
They're my old partners.
In a throuple?
Who are the original two?
Partners in crime.
You're a criminal?
Jeebus Crackers!
Hi, Mr. Seger.
Boy, you probably
don't remember this,
but I saw you
at an airport once,
and I was too nervous
to say anything,
and then it wasn't you.
We love you, man!
We promised our wives
we'd go on some
dumb school field trip,
but when we got these tickets,
we ditched them so fast.
You broke a promise
to your wives?
A good husband's supposed to be,
Like a Rock.
Because we're all running
Against the Wind.
Terrible Night Moves.
Look at this.
Those aren't tour dates.
They're all the times I've
kept commitments to my wife.
Rock and Roll Never Forgets
the needs
of his coequal life companion.
You sicken me.
Were... Were we
just Seger‐shamed?
Why, the real silver bullet
is truth.
We're terrible husbands.
I never should have left Marge
holding the bag.
We've got to go make it up
to Bob Seger.
And our wives.
Sarah, you were a crook?
Everything I never knew
or cared to wonder about you
has been a lie.
We weren't crooks.
We were thieves.
Sexy, girlie thieves.
They never saw us coming,
but they loved
to watch us walk away.
There's nothing
we wouldn't lift.
Wallets. Watches.
MP3 players that held
over a hundred songs.
Man, it was a blast.
Our biggest jobs were brought
to us by a gal named Red.
She got a line
on some unsupervised diamonds
in a penthouse safe.
I was the driver,
and as always...
the honeypot.
Hey there, blue boy.
I was walking
past your big building
and seemed
to have sprained my ankle
because of my high flops.
Do you happen to have...
- What, a girlfriend?
- An icepack?
I'm sorry. I'm s...
Of course, of course I do.
This is just my night job,
by the way.
I'm putting myself through
the police academy. Yeah.
- Isn't that free?
- Well, the first time, yeah.
I love a man
in a rented uniform.
The kiss was part of the plan.
But falling
head over high flops wasn't.
Clancy...
- Oh, no.
- No, no, don't leave.
Come back to pile.
I gotta go, blue boy.
- I'm sorry.
- Ah, no problem.
- Oh, will you marry me?
- Probably!
I was supposed to be
the getaway driver.
My best friends were arrested.
And it was all my fault.
Oh, cool your jets.
Yeah, hot jets.
It wasn't your fault
we got busted.
We were set up...
by Red.
She got away
with our whole take,
including the Hourglass Diamond.
That backstabbing sack of Spanx.
Wait, so it wasn't my fault
you got caught.
Yeah, and if you hadn't gone all
horndog on that rent‐a‐cop,
you'd have been locked up too.
We found Red.
She goes by the name
Lindsey Naegle now.
I've heard of her.
She works in various female
executive positions around town.
We've got a plan to steal
that diamond back from her,
and you're gonna help us.
No, I left that life behind me.
I have a husband now,
and a son who's smart in a way
we haven't figured out yet.
Well, it'd be a real shame
if the Chief of Police
found out his wife was
a common criminal.
You never told Clancy?
Let's just say
he's always been better
at planting evidence
than finding it.
Why don't I just call him now
and tell him everything?
I'm in.
Our wives are missing?
Not unheard of.
Most women have such
an idealized version
of the Second World War
in their heads
that when they meet
the cold, hard reality,
they can't face it.
Did you see what happened?
There was but one witness.
Junior Seaman Ralph,
give your account of the watch.
The mommies got new face hats,
then got into a slidey‐door car.
Don't worry, I speak Ralph.
Face hats?
Slidey‐door?
God, they were kidnapped!
And there's only one man
bold enough
to kidnap the wives
of the chief of police
and his slightly slimmer
acquaintance.
Sarah was kidnapped?
Oh, spare me the act.
We know it was you.
I spare, I swear.
I need your family
to be happy and healthy,
because who else would I say
it would be a shame
if something were to happen to?
Okay, but what about
one of your cronies?
I assure you,
you are a beloved figure
amongst my business brethren.
You look a lot like
that guy Chief Bungles.
But there's no other reason
to kidnap Sarah.
She's just
my little schmoop‐a‐doop,
and that's all there is to her.
Apparently not.
Perhaps your wives
were not kidnapped.
Perhaps they left
because you are selfish men.
That's the only explanation.
It was all about us.
All right, what's the job?
Naegle sold the jewels
she ripped off from us
and became a fancy socialite.
She kept the biggest rock
for herself.
The Hourglass Diamond,
it's in her tiara.
And we're gonna steal it back
when she wears it
to the Gen Gala, tomorrow.
You're gonna rob the Gen Gala?
Sorry, sorry. Scheme away.
Okay,
here's how it's gonna work.
First, we come up
through this manhole.
Nope!
Excuse you?
Look, I may not know anything
about heists,
but I am the world's biggest
superfan of the Gen Gala,
and your plan won't work.
And why not?
If you did any research,
you'd know Beyoncé's
going to be carried in
by 20 plus‐size gladiators,
who will form a human pyramid
right on top of your way in.
No heist.
If you're so Kmart smart,
how would you get in?
Well, these entrances
will be blocked by fans,
press and authorized stalkers.
The best plan would be
to put on a crazy dress
and sneak in
through the red carpet.
Although, you wouldn't get
far without a publicist
who knows everything
about the gala.
- Someone like you?
- Yeah.
This vanilla soccer mom
could be our secret weapon.
Me? Join the robbery?
No way!
Stealing is one of
the big thou shalt nots.
It's not about the cash.
It's about setting things right.
Lindsey Naegle betrayed us
for money and fame,
and all we got
are bad prison tattoos.
Aw, duckies!
Marge, aren't you tired
of being underestimated
and overlooked?
Together, we can right a wrong
and look damn good doing it.
I've always wanted
to say this...
I'm in.
This is Kent Brockman outside
the Museum of Generational
Wealth for the annual Gen Gala.
This year's theme is
The Audacity.
A bold contrast to
last year's theme...
The Nerve.
But I'm stuck out here,
where hundreds of nobodies
have gathered to watch
dozens of somebodies
walk up some stairs.
Should we do this without Marge?
This is her favorite
watching‐party of the year.
Forget her.
I'm jonesing for snark.
Oh, God, would you look
at that dress.
Who is the designer,
the Great Pacific Garbage Patch?
Probably?
Ah, that's the good shade.
The plan's working.
We look amazing.
Now, let's get those tickets.
The 55 stairs.
The Tanqueray
stiletto sharpener.
The Swarovski crystal
wheelchair ramp.
Stop gawking.
Where do we let
the other girls in?
Right over there, next to...
Oh, my God!
Rihanna!
I listen to the clean versions
of all your songs!
Now, let's see if there's
any honey left in this pot.
Excuse me, I seemed
to have a pulled a muscle.
Do you have an ice pack
so that my leg can stop...
quivering?
Right away, ma'am.
Oh‐ho, hot stuff.
No sign of our wives.
We checked out all their
favorite places,
but turns out
we don't pay enough attention
to know what those are.
So I don't know what we did.
It was my distinct pleasure
to watch your son.
I find we are quite simpatico.
Both of us know nothin'
about nothin'.
Now that's a fluid gender!
I wouldn't mind asking them
their preferred pronouns.
If I'm not mistaken,
that's how Marge looks
when she's happy.
And that's my Sarah!
Come on, Homer.
It looks like this
town's got a museum.
There's Lindsey,
and she's wearing the tiara.
Okay, don't be nervous.
- You can do this.
- Nervous?
This is the best field trip
of my fricking life!
Ms. Naegle,
can I just say, that dress.
I know, right?
You go, girl.
What setting would you even
wash that on?
Delicate? Eco‐warm?
I bet it would make so much
noise in the dryer, right?
I don't want this
to sound harsh,
but you're not famous,
so you don't exist.
Bye now.
Darling,
stop talking to that empty chair
and come take a selfie
at the Fenty lip gloss fountain.
Oh, it's a fake!
I've been robbed!
Somebody stop
those two nobodies!
Keep it cool.
We just have to slip out of here
without anyone noticing us.
Sarah Wiggum, freeze!
We're here to give you ladies
the attention you deserve!
Now is not the time, Clancy.
No, no, when it comes to love,
it's always the time
for shouting!
Sar‐ah Wig‐gum!
Schmoop‐a‐doop!
Shmoop‐ba‐da‐doopa!
- I love Sa...
- Shut up!
Oh, God, ow.
- Sarah Wiggum, who are you?
- That's her! She's the thief!
Babe, who is she?
This is my new girlfriend.
You were tumbling
for a long time.
Oh, you poor thing.
Here's your bag, sweetie.
Those aren't mine!
- My earrings!
- My blood diamond!
My conflict tennis bracelet!
Oh, this time,
leave me holding the bag.
Aw, thanks, Homie.
But they're part of
the ensemble.
Chalamet looks like dirt.
BTS looks like seven dirts.
I see nerve there
but nothing audacious.
Oh. My. God.
Jeebus Crackers!
That's Marge!
What the hell is she doing
at the Gen Gala?
Exactly.
She looks like dirt.
It's what she would have wanted.
Oh, Clancy.
So, this whole time, I've been
married to a master criminal.
Damn straight.
Wait, wait, uh, where's Ralph?
I must confess,
I thought putting
crushed‐up Oreos
into the cookies and cream
yogurt would be redundant.
Instead, it is transcendent.
I like to smoosh
the gummy bears.
Hey, no touching!
If the boy wants to smoosh,
the boy will smoosh.
I love you, scary daddy.
I love you too,
Ralphie Stickie Hands.