(theme music playing)
CHORUS: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(school bell rings)
(alarm rings)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
(jazzy solo)
(tire screeches)
(chimes)
(honking horn)
(tires screech)
D-ohh!
(screams)
♪ Boy, the way
the Bee Gees played ♪
♪ Movies John Travolta made ♪
♪ Guessing how much
Elvis weighed ♪
♪ Those were the days ♪
♪ And you know where
you were then ♪
HOMER: ♪ Watching shows
like gentle Ben ♪
BOTH: ♪ Mister, we could use a man
like Sheriff Lobo again ♪
♪ Disco Duck and Fleetwood Mac ♪
♪ Coming out of my eight-track ♪
♪ Michael Jackson still was black ♪
♪ Those were the days ♪
(applause)
ANNOUNCER: The Simpsons is filmed in front
of a live studio audience.
Hey, there, meathead,
what are you watching?
I thought I'd check out
the Warner Brothers network.
♪ We're proud to present
on the WB ♪
♪ Another bad show
that no one will see ♪
I need a drink.
ANNOUNCER: It's the TV movie of the year.
The Krusty the Klown Story.
Booze, drugs, guns, lies,
blackmail and laughter.
Starring Fyvush Finkel
as Krusty the Klown.
I went through
a five-year orgy
of nonstop pills and booze
with nothing to show for it
but four Emmys
and a Peabody award.
(moaning)
All right! They're going to show
his disastrous marriage to Mia Farrow.
Chan Ho, your mother Mia and I
are getting a divorce.
Chan Ho is over there.
I am Chin Ho.
Whoever you are,
just pass it along, kid.
-What a bad father.
-(drill bit running)
(saxophone playing)
Lisa, knock off that racket!
But, Dad, I'm supposed
to practice an hour a day.
I'll practice you!
You'll practice me.
What does that mean?
Is it supposed to be some sort of threat?
-(Lisa starts playing)
-(growls) Bart, make her stop.
Mmm.
Look, Bart, I have to practice
my saxophone
-and you can't stop me.
-Oh, yeah?
My dear Lisa,
you are eight and I am ten.
And in my two extra years
on this planet
I've learned a few tricks.
Give me that sax!
-No!
-I said gimme!
-I said no!
-Gimme it.
-No! No! No!
-Gimme! Gimme! Gimme!
(screaming)
(gasping)
(truck horn blaring)
Ha-ha!
(crying)
Aw, Lisa,
it doesn't look so bad.
Oh, yeah?
D'oh.
Lisa, honey, if it
will make you feel better
I'll destroy
something Bart loves.
-Hey!
-Don't worry, son.
If that bothers you
I'll destroy
something Maggie loves.
Dad, you don't understand.
This saxophone
is like my oldest friend.
I've had it for
as long as I can remember.
You don't remember
how you got it?
Nuh-uh.
Oh, well, it all
happened in 1990.
Back then, the artist
formerly known as Prince
was currently
known as Prince.
Tracey Ullman
was entertaining America
with songs, sketches,
and crudely-drawn filler material.
And Bart Was eagerly awaiting
his first day of school.
(Bobby McFerrin's “Don't Worry Be Happy”
playing)
♪ Don't worry, be happy ♪
Look, mama.
Oh, honey,
I can't right now.
Bart's going to be late.
Now, son,
on your first day of school
I'd like to pass along
the words of advice
my father gave me.
Homer, you're dumb as a mule
and twice as ugly.
If a strange man offers you a ride
I say take it.
Lousy, traumatic childhood!
(horn honking)
Ooh, there's the bus.
Good-bye, sweetheart.
School will be fun.
Welcome, kindergärtners.
I'm principal Sinner.
S-Skinner.
(laughing)
Well, that's it.
I've lost them forever.
Now, I'd like to introduce you
to lunch lady Doris
who will serve you
healthy, nutritious meals.
Yeah. Right.
SKINNER: Miss Phipps,
the school nurse
who will provide
ointments and unguents
and Jimbo,
the school bully
who will administer noogies
and nipple twisters.
I look forward
to whaling on all of you.
(gulps)
♪ There was a farmer
who had a dog ♪
♪ And bingo was his name-o ♪
♪ B-i... O, b-i... O, b-i... ♪
♪ And Bingo was his name-o ♪
Added extra clap.
Not college material.
-(humming)
-Hey! Wee bairn!
Hie ye hence from me heath!
Can't you
understand English?
-(door closes)
-Hi, honey.
How was your
first day of school?
Honey?
♪ Bart was feeling mighty blue ♪
♪ It's a shame
what school can do ♪
♪ For no reason, here's Apu ♪
♪ Those were the days! ♪
And that, my children,
is the story of Bart's
first day of school.
-Very nice.
-Yeah.
Yeah. Except you were supposed
to be telling the story
of how I got my saxophone.
D-oh!
Homer, I can't get
the baby to burp.
Could you try for a while?
No problem.
I'll just give her
a sip of beer.
Come on, Maggie.
It's Miller time.
Yes, it's Miller time.
Homer!
Oh, my father gave me beer
as a child.
Till I wrapped my little red
wagon around a tree.
(clamoring)
Let's never drink again.
And we never did.
Mom, can you tell me the story
of how I got my saxophone
and not have it turn into
a story about Bart?
Oh, sure, honey.
Bart had just completed
his first day at school
-and Bart--
-Mom!
Hey, she's just giving
the public what it wants--
Bart by the barrelful.
I'm sorry, Lisa.
It's just how the story goes.
No matter what Bart tried
he just couldn't fit in
at school.
♪ A, b, c... ♪
-Uh... Line.
-"D"
♪ D, e... ♪
Um... Line.
"F," Bart.
And believe me,
you'll be seeing plenty of them.
Bart, would you like
to read a book?
No.
Would you like to color something?
I did.
Mmm.
-(jazz music playing)
-(fingers snapping)
MAN: That's damn fine coffee
you got here in Twin Peaks.
And damn good cherry pie.
Brilliant.
I have absolutely no idea
what's going on.
Homer, I want you to look
at this drawing Bart did.
Oh! It's beautiful.
Oh, let's put Bart's beautiful
drawing up on the fridge...
Homer, stop.
Would you please
look at the drawing?
Oh, all right. What a--
(screams)
Burn it! Send it to hell!
I think we're going to have
to get Bart some help.
Get it away.
Bart, son,
you want to play catch?
-No.
-Oh.
When a boy doesn't want
to play catch with his old man
something is seriously wrong.
I'll play catch
with you, son.
-Get the hell out.
-I'm gone.
Ah...
Mrs. Simpson, physically
your son is as sound
as the dollar.
I'm afraid Bart's severe
emotional dysfunction
stems from a deep-seated
psychological trauma.
(chuckles)
MARGE:
With nowhere else to turn
we went to see
the school psychologist.
Mr. And Mrs. Simpson
there's nothing
to be alarmed about.
Public school can be
intimidating to a young child...
particularly one with
as many flamboyantly
homosexual tendencies
as your son.
Bart's gay?
Bart?
Whoops! Wrong file.
Ah... (stammers) The point
I'm trying to make here
is that Bart must learn
to be less of an individual
and more a faceless slug.
Mmm. Mmm.
Hmm. Lisa,
how old are you?
I am three
and three-eighths.
Mmm. Lisa, if I have five apples
and I take away three apples
how many apples do I have left?
Two apples.
Wait a minute.
She's right.
Yes, very good.
Marge, Homer, I believe
your Lisa may be gifted.
That's wonderful,
but still can't you do
anything for Bart?
Marge, he's five. His life is over.
Lisa's the wave of the future.
Wave of the future!
That's right, honey.
If you nurture her gift now
there's no telling what she can do.
Wow.
Just think
of the possibilities.
MAN: Lisa Simpson
has won the Nobel prize.
Nah.
Lisa Simpson has won
the Nobel prize...
for kick boxing!
Yah!
Hmm.
Uh... I'll give you the address
of a nice preschool.
(girls chanting)
Cross my heart
and hope to die, here's
the digits that make "pi".
Three point one four one five
nine two six five three five
eight nine seven nine three two
three eight four six two six...
I can assure you
Our preschool is of
the highest quality.
Over 75% of our graduates
go on to first grade.
Well, our little girl has a gift
and we're willing to do
what it takes to help her.
Very good.
Once we receive your $6,000
tuition check, she's in.
I'll give you 50 bucks.
Our fee is
non-negotiable.
Seventy-five!
Look, I knew private school
would be expensive
but I was hoping
we could get a scholarship of some sort.
Sorry. I don't have anything
to offer you
unless you're a member
of a minority group.
Excellente! Muchos gracias,
senorata!
I'm sorry.
(Chinese accent)
Ah, so.
Come on, honey.
I guess this is a world
you'll never know.
Our family was suffering
through its worst crisis ever.
Bart was miserable at school
and Lisa's gifts
were going to waste.
Uh... Homer,
it's five years later
and I'm still
miserable at school.
And my gifts are still
going to waste.
And sometimes I feel
so smothered by this family
I just want to scream
till my lungs explode!
(exhales deeply)
Right. I'll go
start dinner now.
You do that.
(Marge grunts)
Hello!
Dad, what are you doing here?
Looking for my teeth.
(muffled barking)
Give me those!
Better wash these off.
Aw, the hell with it.
Well, grampa,
as long as you're here
we were telling a story
that took place
when Bart was five
and Lisa was three.
Oh, I know this story!
The year is
nineteen-aught-six.
The president is the divine
Miss Sarah Bernhard.
And all over America
people were doing a dance called
"The Funky Grandpa!"
♪ Oh, I'm the... ♪
(snoring)
Y-yes.
Well, as if our
troubles weren't bad enough
Springfield was going through
an unseasonable heat wave...
MAN: And so, Springfield's
heat wave continues
with today's temperature
exceeding the record for this date--
set way back
four billion years ago
when the earth
was just a ball of molten lava.
Oh... So hot.
Homer, have you seen
the frozen peas?
(grunts)
Uh... You keep them.
Now, listen, if we can't
afford private school
maybe there's some other way
to encourage Lisa.
Um, an art class... Ballet lessons...
They have some fun things
you could do at
the museum on Saturday.
Nuh-uh. Forget it, Marge.
There is no way I'm spending
my Saturdays at a museum.
Unless...
Museums don't have foosball,
do they?
(ting)
You lose, Michelangelo's David.
Who's next?
(screaming) Me!
(Marge groans)
I guess it doesn't matter.
All these things cost money
and we just don't have it.
Unless...
Unless... what?
Well, there's that $200
we've been saving
for the new air conditioner.
Oh, Marge, but we've needed
a new air conditioner for years!
And our stopgap solution
is getting cranky.
(yowling)
I cannot believe this!
I'm trying to give our daughter
a headstart in life
and you aren't helping a bit.
Marge, name one successful person
who ever lived
without air conditioning.
Balzac.
No need for potty mouth
just because you can't
think of one.
But Balzac is the name.
Bup-bup-bup-bup.
If "ifs" and "buts"
were candy and nuts, y...
How did the rest
of that go?
Just promise you won't buy
an air conditioner
till we've figured out
a way to help Lisa.
All right, all right. I promise.
Must be another way
to get an air conditioner.
(engine humming)
Mmm...
Re-circulated air.
(shivering mewing)
Uh, Homer?
What, Flanders?
Well, sir, I hate to be
a suspicious Aloysius on you
but did you steal
my air conditioner?
Well, I admit
it looks bad, Flanders
But haven't you heard of--
"Let he who is without sin
cast the first stone?"
Ow!
Got him, Dad!
(groans)
And so, just as things looked
their worst...
I realized I could make money
selling my medication to deadheads.
Grampa, what are
you talking about?
Uh... Nothing.
As I was saying
things couldn't be worse
for Lisa or Bart.
And the ugly duckling
was amazed to realize
it had grown into
a beautiful swan.
So you see, children,
there is hope for anyone.
-Even me?
-No.
(indistinct chatter)
Uh... Hi.
-Hi.
-I have soy milk.
The doctor says the real kind
could kill me.
I wish I was interesting
like you.
(slurping)
(blows raspberry)
(laughing) You're funny.
I am?
Yeah... And the world needs
a clown.
Hmm...
(blowing raspberry) Doody.
(blowing raspberry) Booger.
(all laughing)
Man, that is killer material!
♪ Skinner is a nut ♪
♪ He has a rubber butt... ♪
Young man, I can assure you
my posterior is nothing more
than flesh, bone and...
that metal plate I got in 'Nam.
(gulps)
Now, I want you to knock off
that potty talk right now.
The principal said potty!
(all laughing)
You listen to me, son.
You've just started school
and the path you choose now
may be the one you follow
for the rest of your life.
Now...
what do you say?
Eat my shorts.
All right, I'll eat...
Eat your shorts?
Yeah, eat my shorts!
♪ Buttman ♪
(humming "Batman" theme)
Buttman?
(groans)
(sobbing) He's the greatest showman
since that kid who eats worms.
(muffled) My fifteen minutes
of fame are over.
(gulps)
HOMER:
well, Moe, this is it.
Today's the day I get
my new air conditioner.
Congratulations.
Who's the little chick?
I'm Lisa.
She has a gift.
You have 13 pickled eggs
in this jar.
And one cockroach.
(nervous chuckling)
Who are you, sweetheart,
the Health Inspector?
No, but I am.
Uh...
Here, have a margarita.
Uh, that's a parasol.
(gasps) Ooh.
Help us, Homer.
Yeah, help us, you fat yutz.
(gurgling)
(laughing)
Wow...
A musical instrument?
Could that be a way to encourage
a gifted child?
Just give me a sign!
Eh, works for me.
(bell tingles)
So, what do you like, Lisa?
Viomalin?
Tubamaba?
Obomoboe?
That one.
Oh... Saxomophone.
Two hundred dollars?
Oh, I'll take it.
(plays note)
(giggling)
Would you like
an inscription, sir?
Yeah. "To Lisa,
never forget
your daddy loves..." d'oh!
...and that inscription
is still there today.
Wow. So that's how Lisa
got her sax.
Next, I'll tell you the origin
of Maggie's pacifier.
What origin?
We get them for a $1.95
down at the safeway.
But I really liked that story.
But it still doesn't fix this.
You know, Homer...
I think we have
some money
in the air conditioner
account again, hmm?
Oh... But, Marge,
am I doomed to spend
the rest of my life
sweating like a pig?
Yeah, not to mention
looking like a pig,
eating like a pig...
Don't forget the smell.
Will you get off my front lawn?
Why don't you make me?
Why-- Oh, I give up.
Well, don't worry
about me, Dad.
It's not how it looks,
it's how it sounds.
(plays squeaky note)
Oh...
MAN: Well, sir,
we got a scorcher today.
And to cool off,
nothing beats Fruitopia--
the iced tea brewed by hippies,
but distributed by a heartless
multinational corporation.
"Dear Lisa, may your new
saxophone bring you years of...
D'oh!"
(playing Saxophonsolo
from "Baker Street")
You're a good father.
I learned from the master.
Where's Maggie?
I'm not kidding--
I can't see!
My retinas
have detached again.
(both laughing)
-He's blind as a bat.
-That's right!
That's true!
(theme music playing in sax)
HOMER: Lisa, enough saxamaphone already.
Captioned by
Visual Data Media Services