(SlNGlNG) The Simpsons
(TlRES SCREECHlNG)
D'oh !
(SCREAMlNG)
(BRAKES SCREECHlNG)
Happy Thanksgiving
from the entire
Channel 6 family
including Kent Brockman,
who's contractually
permitted to
replace himself
with a cardboard cutout.
The real Kent is
in a rehab clinic.
We all wish him the best. . .
Again.
l love the holiday season.
See ya in spring, toes.
And from all of us,
best wishes for
a joyous hoIiday season.
Now in the spirit
of the season,
start shopping!
And for
every doIIar of Krusty
merchandise you buy,
l will be nice to a sick kid.
For IegaI purposes,
sick kids may incIude
hookers with a cold.
(LAUGHS)
lt's the most
wonderful time
of the year
(SCREECHlNG)
With the kids
jingIe-beIIing
And everyone teIIing you
"Be of good cheer"
lt's the most
wonderful time
of the year
(GROWLlNG)
(MEOWlNG)
(GRUNTlNG)
Hey, Homer.
l'm your Secret Santa.
Merry Christmas, big guy.
Oh, my God ! A DVD player!
And the first season
of Magnum P.I.
with commentary
by John Hillerman.
Apparently working in Hawaii
was a pleasure.
Oh, Carl,
you remembered l like TV.
(KlSSlNG)
Who's my Secret Santa?
l think it's Homer.
Oh, yes, l am.
Your present is right
in the other room. . .
(WHlRRlNG)
HOMER: Come on, machine!
Take my dollar!
Fine. We'll play it
your way!
(THUDDlNG)
Here you go, Lenny.
May the spirit of Retsyn
be with you all year long.
God bless God. Amen.
This gift stinks.
Homer, you're the most
selfish man l know.
Oh, come on.
Mister Burns is
way more selfish.
That evil old bone bag
smelling of death,
nose like a vulture,
followed everywhere
by that kiss-ass Smithers.
(LAUGHS) Yes. That describes
Kathy in Personnel to a tee.
(SCREAMS)
All right, everyone.
lt's time for your
Christmas "bon-i."
Everyone gets
a five-dollar
cafeteria voucher.
(ALL MOANlNG)
And for your boy,
a confectioner's card
featuring a current
baseballer.
lt's that rookie
from the New York Nine.
HOMER: Joe DiMaggio?
Yes.
lt seems they've
started letting ethnics
into the big leagues.
Oh, look! lt's Kathy!
How are things in Personnel?
Excellent.
l need money for Christmas.
Can l get anything for this
Joe DiMaggio baseball card?
lt's kind of old.
l'm sorry.
But l'm afraid your
card is only worth
everything l've got!
Everything !
Take it!
Oh, no!
l've smudged it
with nacho fingers.
l must deftly lick it off.
Deftly. . .
Thank you !
Freak.
TV ANNOUNCER:
And now we return
to the 1 986 hoIiday cIassic,
Christmas with
the California Prunes.
(PLAYlNG JAZZY TUNE)
(SlNGlNG) Yeah...
Oh, pruny night
The stars are
sweetIy wrinkIed
We are the fruit
That your grandmother Ioves
Yeah...
This is offensive
to Christians and prunes.
HOMER: Hey, everybody!
We're going shopping
at the Springfield
Heights Promenade!
(GASPS) That's
the rich people's mall !
Let's shop till we droop.
l think that's "drop."
That's a very
violent image, Lisa.
Silver and gold
Mean so much more
when l see
First, we'll buy
gifts for each other,
then we'll spend
the rest of the cash
on a Christmas tree so large,
its absence
from the forest will cause
mudslides and flooding !
ALL: Yay!
Cool, a toy store!
Awesome! l'm blasting
all the state capitals!
Oh, take that,
Salem, Oregon !
Wait a minute.
This game is educational !
That'll teach you
to teach me!
l think these are
my Homie's size.
Excuse me.
Can l ask you a favor?
Perfect! l'll take it!
Um, we'll do that.
Stand back when you open it.
Doing pretty good so far.
A key ring for Marge,
key ring for Bart. . .
(GASPS)
That thing for me!
Oh, God !
lt's so unnecessary!
You have excellent taste.
This is our finest
talking astrolabe.
lt also comes with
a notepad and pen
that works upside-down.
l'm upside-down so much !
lf l buy this,
l won't have anything
left for a Christmas tree.
ASTROLABE:
Today is the birthday
of comedienne Margaret Cho.
That's the birthday
l'm always forgetting !
l must have it!
What a mall !
Can we get our big
Christmas tree now?
Uh, sure, you know it.
Biggest tree from
the finest lot in town.
Stupid jerk!
Dad, l don't like the looks
of this neighborhood.
lt's fine.
Now, everyone just relax,
lock your doors,
don't make eye contact
with anyone,
and listen to the radio.
RADlO ANNOUNCER:
Now let's downshift
into the hoIiday spirit
with Christmas Convoy.
MAN:
A star shone bright
that siIent night
Ninety miIes
out of manger-town
HauIin' goId and myrrh
and frankincense
Three kings
put the hammer down
Cause we got
a Christmas convoy,
ain't she a beautifuI thing?
We've gotta roII
this truckin' convoy
to see the newborn king
Convoy
1 0-4, King of the Jews
Gorgeous, huh?
And quite the bargain.
lsn't it kind of dry?
Oh, it just needs
a little love.
Why do things
l love always burn?
lsn't it sufficient?
l thought
we had enough money
for a good tree.
Homer, is there something
you're not telling us?
ASTROLABE:
It is 6:31 p.m. in MontreaI.
The moon is waxing tonight.
What's that?
Uh. . . Woo-hoo!
Maggie's talking !
Hmm. . .
You wasted our money
on something extravagant
for yourself!
There's a trickledown
theory here.
lf l'm happy,
l'm less abusive
to the rest of you.
No, Dad.
This time you were
just plain selfish.
ASTROLABE:
l am not returnable.
(SOBBlNG)
l will be
testing my smoke aIarm
for the next three hours.
(ALARM BLARlNG)
(SOBBlNG)
This is sadder than
Tuesdays with Morrie.
Come on, Marge.
l'm not the only
selfish person.
You have to get
your hair done at Supercuts.
l guess regular cuts
just isn't good
enough for you.
You just don't get it,
do you?
Christmas is a time
to think of others.
But today, you showed
you only care about yourself.
That's not true!
l cared what you thought
once you found out!
You can sleep
on the couch tonight.
Can't you yell at me now
and get it over with?
No.
l'm gonna parcel
my anger out over the next
few days and weeks,
jabbing at you
just when you seem
the most content.
Oh !
l don't need her.
l've got you, Astrolabe.
Colombia's main
export is coffee.
Exactly.
TV ANNOUNCER 1 : Now back to
The Year Santa Got Lost
starring Jimmy Stewart
as the voice of
Mister Mailman.
Santa was in
an awfuI pickIe.
Beatniks had given
drugs to the reindeer
and they were no darn good.
So Santa placed a call
to Secretary of Defense
Melvin Laird.
Jimmy Stewart as
a puppet is just wrong.
TV ANNOUNCER 2:
And now back to
Mr. McGrew's Christmas Carol.
Mr. McGrew? l love that
blind senile old man !
(KNOCKlNG ON DOOR)
l can't find
my way back to the home.
l heard you
the first five times!
(GROANS)
You work on Christmas
or you're out of a job!
ls that clear, Cratchett?
Sir, l'm over here.
Woo-hoo.
Sorry, pardon me, ma'am.
I see you're expecting.
May I Iisten to
the baby's heartbeat?
(SCREAMlNG)
(LAUGHlNG)
Oh, McGrew.
Once again you've mistaken
something for something.
(MEOWlNG)
McGrew, l am the Ghost
of Christmas Past.
You are so selfish
your fiancee is about
to Ieave you.
l don't need love.
l have money. Sweet,
sweet money, yes indeed.
Oh, my God ! lt's like
looking at a cartoon
version of myself!
Spirit,
sureIy there is some time
to reform my seIfish ways.
Come on, Death.
Leave McGrew alone.
Take Tiny Tim !
No!
"Unloved by Al?" No!
"Unloved by all?" No!
(MOANlNG)
Dad, are you okay?
Children ! Children,
what day is this?
lt's Saturday,
December sixth.
Thank God.
There's still four
more days till Christmas.
l have time to
reform my ways.
l just saw the greatest
cartoon of all time.
lt was about
a miser who was visited
by three ghosts at Christmas.
And get this.
He learns a lesson !
Dad, what you saw was
A Christmas Carol.
lt was written
by Charles Dickens
1 60 years ago.
Yeah. TV writers have been
milking that goat for years.
Reform, Ebenezer Urkel!
You have alienated
everyone who Ioved you!
Did l do that?
Report, Mr. Sulu.
Captain, there appears
to be some sort of spirit
from an Earth hoIiday past.
Mr. Scott,
fire photon torpedoes.
lt's no use, Captain.
He's showin' visions
of me future.
God, l'm so fat!
l said fire!
That last one
looked kind of good.
Marge, TV and nightmares
have joined forces
to teach me a lesson.
From now on,
l will stop being selfish
and start being good.
ln fact, l'll be
the nicest man in town.
You've made that
promise before.
Yes. But this time
l'm sober-ish.
Well, the hoboes
sure will appreciate
our old clothes
and lima beans.
No need, Flanders.
l've already given them
my old clothes.
Good-looking group.
lt looks like this town
has a Good Sam logjam.
These pants smell worse
than my old pants.
You're welcome.
Listen, Lenny.
l know l was a pretty bad
Secret Santa
so l wanted to
make it up to you.
A photo cube
with pictures of us!
And l filed down
all the sharp corners.
See? Your eye is
completely safe!
Oh, wow,
it just stings a little.
Oops.
Marge, do you want
this last pork chop?
l've dreamed of
the day you'd say that!
Oh, your thoughtfulness
tastes so good.
(SOBBlNG)
And tears are
the sweetest sauce.
All right,
now you're starting
to creep me out.
Come on.
Why don't you
just take my blood?
Yes, l'm old.
Oh, very nice, Ned.
But l'm afraid
you're a distant
second this week.
l'm not looking
for glory or wealth.
l'm just buying
that stairway to heaven
Jesus sang of.
That was Led Zeppelin.
Get back to
your bong, hippie.
(CHUCKLES)
Daddy, are you jealous
of Brother Homer?
Maybe just a tad, Todd.
l'm jealous of girls
because they get
to wear dresses.
One problem at a time, boy.
Homie, l'm so proud.
You changed more
than l could've imagined.
You're even
covering your mouth
when you burp.
Just like the pope.
(BURPS)
Being unselfish
is a natural high
like hiking or paint thinner.
And here's another act
of Christian charity
l pulled out of my butt.
l built a skating rink
for the whole town !
(GROANS)
Activate cloaking device!
Oh, l'm so depressed.
Engage candy bar.
Thank you.
(SlNGlNG)
Here come sandwiches
right down Boozy Bum Lane
Brother Ned's
got cheese on bread
and a side order of shame.
Bells...
Where the H-E-C-K
is everybody?
Here's your skates.
Oh, you'll have to
take off those boots.
Those are my feet.
Eew!
Oh, for the love of puppies.
Homer, you're
the nicest guy in town.
Ha-ha!
Your position
has been usurped.
Usurped. You heard me.
Ha-ha!
(CHANTlNG)
You're sad at Christmas.
This just in,
Santa Claus is dead.
(SCREAMlNG)
Or he might as well be
because there's
an even fatter man
who's hoIding famiIies
at nice-point.
Homer Simpson,
seen here in this
retouched photo!
(GRUNTS lN ANGER)
That Homer just
burns my waffles.
Pain is the cleanser!
(DOORBELL RlNGlNG)
Excuse me.
My car broke down.
Well, l'll give you a jump!
l'll rotate your tires!
l'll even fold up
that map for you !
l know that can be
a dickens of a doozie!
Back off, creep!
l was looking for
Homer Simpson's house!
That tears it!
l'll show Homer!
l'm gonna be the nicest man
this world has ever seen.
l said "man," not "man-God"!
Keep your pants on !
Here you go,
Principal Skinner,
Mrs. Skinner.
You're actually
giving everyone in town
a Christmas present?
What's your angle, pervert?
Oh-ho. My angle is
"givin' in this world,
livin' in the next!"
But how can
you afford all this
on a widower's salary?
Well, actually l picked up
some extra cash
renting out my house
to a fraternity.
(SCREAMlNG)
ROD: Stay out of
our medicine cabinet!
Pathetic Flanders.
Thinking he can buy
people's love with
thoughtful gifts.
Cool ! Mister Flanders
gave me a Krusty brand
Operation game.
(BUZZER SOUNDS)
KRUSTY'S VOlCE:
You just tweezered my wang!
l'll show Flanders.
l'm gonna give everyone
a car.
What's that one
good American car?
Dad, you don't have to
outdo Mister Flanders.
Just remember
the spirit of the season.
ls it despair?
Actually, most people
now feel Christmas has
gotten too materialistic.
ln fact, as a Buddhist,
l believe people
would be a lot happier
without presents.
Hmm. You've given me
a lot to think about.
LISA: PeopIe wouId
be a Iot happier
without presents.
Presents are material goods,
and attachment
to material goods
kills the soul.
(SlREN BLARlNG)
l'm not going to jail again.
l've got it!
When everyone's asleep,
l'll take away
their presents!
Then they'll be happy.
Thanks, Buddha.
l got your badge number.
You better hope
l never get out!
HOMER:
You're a hero, Homer J
You're as crafty as a skunk
They'II thank you
in the morning for steaIing
FIanders' junk
Homer Jay
You're a double-bacon
genius-burger
and just a IittIe drunk
Now to hear
the joyous sound of people
waking up on Christmas
to discover they
have no presents.
LENNY:
Hey, where's my presents?
WOMAN: Some jerk
stole Christmas!
Oh, l've been robbed !
Man, so this is
how it feels.
l'd better see my shrink
and rob his ass!
Someone snuck in
and took our presents.
Do you think it was Papa?
l wouldn't put it past him.
He stole my gold tooth
the night he left.
He didn't leave.
He went to the store.
And when he comes back,
l'll wave those Pop Tarts
right in your face!
They don't sound happy
but here comes a mob
shaking their fists
in gratitude!
Get him !
Give back our presents,
stupid man !
Your behavior,
it's like not sanctioned
by any governing body.
You're like wild.
Shouldn't you all
be singing carols
or something?
(GROANlNG)
Stop! Friends,
what Homer did was wrong
but l've been thinking.
Maybe l was just as wrong
to give you those gifts.
(GROANS)
Hey!
Wait a minute, everyone!
There's your Christmas.
Up there!
(ALL EXCLAlM lN AWE)
lt's a miracle.
That's my last flare.
Somebody better come soon.
(HOWLlNG)
Oh, thank goodness.
Rescue dogs.
(GROWLlNG)
"And the angel said
unto them, 'Fear not,
"'for behold, l bring you
good tidings of great joy
"'which shall be
to all people. . ."'
Stop that!
You can't pray
on city property!
Let's just say
that on this day
a million years ago,
a dude was born
who most of us
think was magic.
But others don't.
And that's cool.
But we're
probably right. Amen.
ALL: Amen !
And now l think
the only thing left to do
is return all your gifts!
Ned?
lt'd be my pleasure, Homer!
Oh, joy!
Let's see what we got here.
lt's a new brassiere!
But l don't even
have them, but okay.
l'll make pretend.
What a great Christmas.
Not even Moe's
annual suicide attempt
can ruin it.
l ain't got all day,
Drama Queen.
Get it over with.
l will !
And then you'll all wish
you was nicer to me!
Who am l kidding?
l ain't gonna jump.
(SlNGlNG)
Hark, the HeraId AngeIs sing
Glory to the new born King
Peace on earth
and mercy miId
God and sinners reconciled
ASTROLABE:
Today is the birthday
of our Lord, Jesus Christ,
and singer Barbara MandreII.
Merry Christmas.
Of the skies
Hark the HeraId AngeIs sing
Glory to
the new born King
English - US - PSDH