CHORUS:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(theme music playing)
(bell ringing)
(whistle blowing)
(playing the blues)
(honking horn)
D'oh.
(screams)
(all screaming)
And as we pass
the collection plate,
please give as though the person
next to you were watching.
Whew. Oh, man, this is
the hottest Easter ever.
Even that praying mantis is losing it.
(groaning)
Thank you, Helen.
And thank you all
for you kind contrib-- ah!
A chocolate bunny?
Who put this wicked idol
in the collection plate?
(all gasp)
Relax. I found it in the dumpster.
Perhaps we need
a hefty dose of the good book.
(Marge moaning)
"In the beginning..."
Excuse me, Reverend,
it's hard to hear you
with those fans going.
Well, let's get those off then.
(Homer moaning) Oh!
"In the beginning, God created
the heavens and the Earth..."
LOVEJOY: Which brings us back to our...
(snoring softly)
Ooh! Ooh!
(animals purring, calling)
What a beautiful garden.
It's almost like paradise.
HOMER: Heads up!
Whee!
(gasps)
Well, hello.
Aren't you hurt?
Of course not.
There's no pain in the Garden of Eden.
Hey, you must be Eve.
I guess.
Looks like God made you
out of my sexiest rib.
(growls)
Speaking of ribs,
is there any grub around here?
Is there?
(English accent) Good morning, Adam.
Any bacon for you then?
Don't mind if I do.
(Flanders's voice)
Hi-diddly-ho, paradise dwellers.
Good morning, Lord.
I just have to compliment you
on this beautifully-crafted mate.
Oh, Adam, you're too kind.
No, you're too kind...
And wise and righteous.
I can't believe
you don't have a girlfriend.
Oh, please, you're going
to give me a swelled head.
I just stopped by to see
if you needed anything.
Well, some general-interest
magazines would be nice.
You got it, Eve.
There you go.
Oh, thanks.
I better skedaddle.
Oh, there's one more
weensy little thing.
See that tree over there?
I hate to be a Bossy Betty,
but I have to forbid you
to eat its fruit.
No problem, Lord,
and it would be even easier
to avoid that temptation
if I had a few extra wives.
(growling)
I'm just saying.
Oh, how cute!
Let's call this little
guy a groundhog.
Sorry, I already gave
him a name-- land monster.
Really?
What do you call
that thing on the branch?
(hissing)
Branch monster.
Please, please,
call me snake.
Yo, have you dudes
sampled this fruit?
It's, like, god's private stash.
But he said it was forbidden.
Quite so, mum.
I recall one of the dinosaurs had a bite.
And, well, that was the last of-- egad.
Please stop eating that.
God's going to be furious.
You're pretty uptight
for a naked chick.
You know what would loosen you up?
A little fruit.
Well, it is a sin to waste food.
And you keep saying we need
to do things together.
Hmm.
Mmm! This could really spice up
those pies I've been making.
(thunder)
-What the dickens?
-(gasps)
Eve, did you taste
of the forbidden fruit?
(whistling)
Yes, God.
Doggone it, Eve.
I think you'd better
hightail it out of this garden.
Adam, say something.
Uh, uh, I think we should
see other people.
You heard me! Vamoose!
Oh!
Usually, a mink massage
makes me feel better,
but something's missing now.
I didn't say stop.
Lovely day in paradise,
isn't it?
Yeah, just like yesterday.
Today, I'm featuring
mouth-watering pork ribs.
Tuck in, then.
Oh.
I gave a rib to Eve
and now she's gone forever.
One whole rib, and still standing.
Well, aren't you
the plucky one, sir.
Come on!
Oh, poor Eve.
What are you doing out there
in that horrible place?
I'm toiling.
What does it look like?
This is my fault.
I should have
stood up for you
during that whole
Applegate thing.
It's a little late
for apologies now.
Don't say that.
Maybe I can
sneak you back in.
I mean, God can't be
everywhere at once, right?
(whistling "Alexander's
Ragtime Band")
Somebody order a hole?
Oh, that's a tight squeeze.
(panting)
Oh, thank you.
Are you okay?
I'll be fine. (panting)
Just give me a second to... Ah!
-(gasps)
-Come on, Eve. Hurry!
Oh, my dear, sweet Eve.
I love you even more
than the butterscotch pond
or the porno bush.
(thunder)
So, this is how you repay me, Adam!
And after I created my fingers
to the bone for you!
I...
Ahh! My unicorn!
Oh, what have they
done to you, Gary?
Oh, there, there.
I'm sure he's gone
to a better place, Lord.
Oh, shut up!
You are so banished!
Hey, now, let's not
do anything rash.
God is love, right?
(yells)
God, you have every right
to flip me out, too,
but before you...
(yells)
Oh, my back!
So this must be that pain thing.
(yells)
Oh, yeah, definitely pain.
(howling)
This sucks.
Things were so much better
back in the garden.
I'm sure God
will let us return soon.
I mean, how long
can he hold a grudge?
"...forever... and ever...
and ever and..."
...and that concludes Genesis,
the first of the 66 books
of the Bible.
Moving on to Exodus...
(yawning)
♪ And Abraham begat Isaac ♪
♪ And Isaac begat Jacob ♪
♪ And who did he begat? ♪
All right, let's go,
you wee Israelites.
Back to slaving.
(all groaning)
Man, captivity blows.
Talk to the whip.
(Bart grunts)
(horses neighing)
On your knees, you mugs.
It's the Pharaoh!
(sighs)
Ah, excellent progress,
slave-driver Willie.
Kudos on your whipping.
Oh, he noticed!
Oy! Suffering sarcophagus!
My tomb!
Who did this?
(snickering)
Come on, confess.
Don't make me slay all
the firstborn males again.
(deep voice) Bart did it.
I saw him do it.
Take him away, boys.
No, the bush set me up!
As for the rest of you,
it's time
for a little discipline.
Slave driver, put away
the encouragement whip
and break out the cruel whip.
(all gasping)
(whips cracking)
Ha! That's
the new omni-lash, boys.
Just look at that snapback.
Yeah, sweet.
We can't keep living like this.
Moses, ask Pharaoh
to let your people go.
Oh, now they're my people.
Scrub harder, slave.
I want to be able
to eat off that thing.
And make it snappy.
It's almost lunchtime.
LISA: Excuse me. Uh...
Pharaoh, I think Moses
here has something to ask you.
Go.
Let-my-people-go.
Let your people go?
I've never heard
such insolence.
You call yourselves slaves?
(grunts)
Well, the ball's
in his court now.
All right, read me back
what I have so far, Mrs. Krabapatra.
Bird, bird,
Giant eye, pyramid, bird.
Mm-hmm. Very good.
Uh, giant eye, dead fish,
cat head, cat head, cat head...
Guy doing this...
(frogs croaking)
What the--
Keep that plague coming, Moses.
Frogs away!
(laughing)
We spent all our money,
but it was worth it.
Now he's got to let us go.
Mmm, these are the juiciest
frogs I've ever eaten.
Ra has rewarded my cruelty
to the slaves.
It's a plague, you moron!
And we've got
lots more planned.
And there's nothing
you can do about it!
-(screaming)
-So long, kids.
Give my regards
to the British museum.
(laughing)
-Whoa!
(both grunting)
Do you think we could ever
be more than just friends?
Not now, Moses.
We got to find
a way out of here.
I know we built a secret passage
in here somewhere.
I found it!
We're out of here.
Uh-oh.
(both screaming)
Eh, slave labor.
You get what you pay for.
Whee!
-(blows horn)
-Huh?
Our time has come!
Follow me to freedom!
(horn blowing)
(distant horn blowing)
WIGGUM: Hey, Pharaoh,
those half-pint slaves
are exodusing as we speak.
Well, I say good riddance
to bad rubbish.
Okay. But who's going
to build your pyramids?
Well, we-- (gasps) After them!
Oh, we'll never be able
to swim that far.
(horses neighing)
Oy, carumba.
Screw this. I'm converting.
Save us, o mighty Ra!
Hey! Cut that out. I have an idea.
All right, Moses, lead your people.
Flush!
(roar of flushing)
It's a miracle!
I performed a miracle!
I'm a genius!
Yeah, yeah. Hurry, everyone!
We don't have much time!
After them, men!
Into the temporarily-dry sea!
Ah, nuts.
(screaming)
Hey, chief, he splashed me.
Look, nobody likes
a crybaby, okay?
You just splash him back.
(kids cheering)
Well, Lisa, we're out of Egypt.
So, what's next for the Israelites?
Land of milk and honey?
Hmm, well, actually, it looks like
we're in for 40 years
of wandering the desert.
Forty years?
But after that, it's clear
sailing for the Jews, right?
Uh... more or less.
Hey, is that manna?
(kids cheering)
Now we come to King Solomon
whose wisdom was
like a drill...
boring into the rock of injustice.
LOVEJOY: Boring... boring...
boring...
(yawns)
King Solomon,
these men need you
to settle a dispute.
They each claim ownership
of this pie.
(sighs)
The pie shall be cut in two.
Then each man shall receive...
death.
(sighs)
I'll eat the pie.
Okay, next up,
"Jesus Christ versus
Checker Chariot."
Oh, Dad, you're
sitting on my arm.
(grunting)
"And after David smote Goliath
the people crowded
into the temple
where a cool breeze blew not.
And their hearts were
filled with crankiness."
And...
I'm bored. Send in my jester.
Hey, hey! King David!
How you doing?
Now, I'm not saying
Jezebel's easy,
but before she moved to Sodom,
it was known for its pottery!
(laughs)
What else you got?
Uh, wait a minute.
I got something
on the Canaanites.
Uh...
They are so stupid...
(gasping and groaning)
Methuselah, my oldest friend...
Who did this to you?
(groaning)
Oh... it was Goliath.
But Goliath is dead.
I smote him myself.
I smoted him good.
No! It was his son, Goliath Two.
No!
Goliath Two is gonna pay.
And this time, it's biblical.
(typewriter clacking)
I'll just give Goliath Two
the old rock
to the head applause, applause,
you got to believe in yourself,
stay in school and we're out of here.
I don't know, Davey.
Quiet, you.
Oh, you've gotten pretty fat, Davey.
-(stomping)
-(gasping)
Let's get it on.
See you later, Davey.
You killed my best friend.
CROWD: Ooh.
You killed my father,
who was like a best friend.
CROWD: Ooh!
All I need is my trusty sling
and one good, hard...
Um...
Say... how's tomorrow for you?
(grunting)
(screams)
What say you now, Goliath?
Without your precious hair,
you no longer possess
your fantastic strength!
That's Samson, idiot.
Whoa!
(all gasp)
Let my proclamation
go out across the land!
Ha-ha!
CROWD: Ha-ha!
(screaming)
Oh... I hope this doesn't get
into the Bible.
You're King David.
I love you 'cause
you kill people.
Get yourself another hero, kid.
I'm all washed up.
Well, I guess it's up to Ralph
to stop Goliath.
(sheep bleating)
(Ralph humming)
Goliath Two is really gonna pay.
Get ready to meet
the first action hero.
(sheep bleating)
♪ Winner takes it all ♪
♪ Till he breaks the fall ♪
♪ I'm trying to make it
over the top... ♪
(grunts)
(teletype clacking)
BART: All right,
it's giant slayin' time.
(gasps)
Oops.
(man grunts)
Crap.
Hmm...
How am I supposed
to get up there?
(loud burp echoing)
Jonah!
Oh!
You died the way you lived...
Inside a whale.
(gasps)
Hmm...
(grunting)
I trampled four
giant-slayers today.
I think I earned this.
Don't you know
smoking stunts your growth?
Well, well, well, if it isn't
the little prince.
I'm not afraid of you, Goliath.
Before I was arrogant,
but now, my heart is humble
and my spirit is...
Oh!
(whimpering)
What do you know?
A king fit for a meal.
(whimpering)
Hope I don't give you...
Heartburn!
(screams)
Great news, everyone. Goliath is dead!
Although I haven't seen his body,
the blast that failed to kill me
surely killed the giant.
Anyhoo...
Now that I'm your king again...
(roaring)
(screaming)
Ralph, I thought you were dead.
Nope.
BART: Rejoice, good people!
Goliath the terrible
shall rule no more!
But Goliath was the greatest
king we ever had.
What?
He built roads,
hospitals, libraries...
To us, he was Goliath
the Consensus Builder.
You're under arrest
for megacide.
Where's your messiah now?
(crowd laughing)
(exclaims)
(snoring)
Everyone's gone!
How embarrassing.
Ooh, we slept right
through church.
Eh, it's not the end of the world.
(gasping)
(evil laughter)
Oh, no! It's the apocalypse!
Bart, are you wearing
clean underwear?
Not anymore.
It's the rapture
and I never knew true love.
I never used those
pizza coupons!
(choral music playing)
Why aren't we
ascending into heaven?
(thunder rumbling)
Oh, right... The sins.
-(choral music playing)
-(exclaims)
(choral music stops)
Where do you think
you're going, missy?
Dad!
(all scream)
Whoo, I smell barbecue!
(giggling) Hey, look!
(Homer screaming in terror)
Oh, they're out of hot dogs!
And the cole slaw
has pineapple in it!
(screaming)
German potato salad!
♪ I'm on the highway
to hell ♪
♪ On the highway to hell ♪
♪ Highway to hell ♪
♪ I'm on the highway
to hell ♪
♪ No stop signs ♪
♪ Speed limit ♪
♪ Nobody's gonna
slow me down ♪
♪ Like a wheel, gonna spin it ♪
♪ Nobody's gonna
mess me around ♪
♪ Hey Satan, paid my dues ♪
♪ Playing in a rocking band ♪
♪ Hey mama, look at me ♪
Shh.
Captioned by
Visual Data Media Services