♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
(whistle blowing)
(beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
The beauty of it is each parking space
is a mere one foot narrower--
Indistinguishable
to the naked eye,
but therein lies the game.
-I fear to watch, yet I cannot turn away.
-(cars approaching)
Blast it, woman. You parked
too close. Move your car!
I'm in the lines. You got
a problem, go tell your mama.
Oh, don't worry.
She'll hear about this.
-(horns honking)
-MAN: I can't get out!
-WOMAN: I'm trapped.
-MAN: I can't breathe!
-(honking continues)
-(Bart laughing sinisterly)
Class, I know there's no way
to prove who actually did this,
and in our American democracy,
everyone is innocent until proven guilty.
-God bless America.
-But my classroom is not a democracy. Ha!
For the rest of the year,
Bart Simpson will be
the first student called on
for every question.
-(gulps)
-Well, let's get started.
Can someone
pronounce this word?
Hmm? Bart?
Uh-- Um-- Hmm?
-Uh--
-(grunting)
Mmm-- Uh--
-Oh, pick me, teacher! I'm ever so smart.
-Uh--
It's "photosynthesis"!
Damn your feeble brain!
Oh, I couldn't read it.
The letters are all blurry.
Is it possible all your misbehavior
and miserable grades
have been caused by
a simple vision disorder?
(British accent) You mean it
ain't me noggin', it's me peepers?
Oh, well,
that's just "loverly."
Watch this, guys.
Ooh!
-Uh-oh. He's done for.
-Don't worry.
The safety glass'll
protect us.
-(all gasp)
-(alarm blaring)
Run! We'll hide at my house!
(all shouting)
Hey, this emergency exit
is painted on!
There's no way out! There's no way out!
We're doomed! Doomed!
(all groaning)
Well, sir, I won't bore you with
the details of our miraculous escape,
but we desperately need
a real emergency exit.
Why, that's a fabulous idea.
Anything else you'd like?
How about real lead in the radiation
shields? Urinal cakes, maybe?
Smithers, throw this at him.
(grunts)
(shouting)
Smithers, where does
that tube go?
I'm not sure, sir.
It was here when we moved in.
♪♪ (exotic)
(shouting continues)
MEN:
Dance! Dance! Dance! Dance!
(men ululating)
Sir, we'll need a new
dangerous emissions supervisor.
Yes, we'll find
someone cheap.
It's been a very
lean year for us.
BOTH:
Money fight!
(both laughing)
Mmm.
(mumbles)
Excellent, Zutroy. Work hard
and each day you'll get a shiny penny.
(men shouting)
Agent Wesson,
Department of Labor.
-This man's an illegal alien.
-(chuckles)
That's preposterous. Zutroy here
is as American as apple pie.
(foreign language)
Mr. Burns.
This plant violates
every labor law in the book.
We found a missing Brazilian soccer team
working in your reactor core.
That plane crashed
on my property!
Look, Mr. Burns,
we want to see some changes.
For starters, you can reverse
your sexist employment policies
and hire at least one woman.
All right.
I'll bring in a woman.
-But I still stand by my hiring policies.
-(quacking)
-Get back to work, Stewart!
Now with my new H.M.O.,
I can provide every medical service...
you'll ever need
under one roof.
You do have insurance,
don't you?
-Yes.
-Well, that's wonderful.
(chuckling)
Let's go visit the optometrist.
Your son has a temporary
condition called "Lazy eye,"
Where one eye
is weaker than the other.
-You'll have to wear these for two weeks.
-(groans)
Menachem Begin wore a pair
just like them.
Hmm. That scalp's a little dry.
Better see our dermatologist.
Rub a palm full of this medicated salve
into your scalp every half an hour.
Keep him away from open flames
and pregnant women.
Ah, these should help
those fallen arches. Enjoy.
Hmm. Throat looks a little red.
-I'd better spray it.
-(coughing)
(as Jerry Lewis)
Oh, thanks, nice lady.
My voice is crazy
with this spraying already.
Oy, I feel so much better,
Mr. Medical Science-Type Person.
If they hire a woman,
we won't be able to spit on the floor.
And we can't take off our pants
when it gets real hot.
And we won't be able to pee
in the drinking fountain.
Yeah-- I mean, not--
You know, if we wanted to.
Not that I ever did.
Gentlemen, I'd like you to meet your
new coworker, Mindy Simmons.
I think she has a degree
in engineering or something.
-Hi. How's it going?
-Pleased to meet you.
-Yeah, ditto.
-Hi. Ooh.
(gasps)
Homer, what's the matter?
Ain't you never seen a naked chick
ridin' a clam before?
Gotta go! Ahhh!
What the hell was that?
I probably shouldn't have eaten
that packet of powdered gravy
I found in the parking lot.
BOTH: Nice glasses, four eyes.
(laugh)
Yeah, nice shoes, uh,
two feet. Yeah.
-Your appearance is comical to me.
-(kids laughing)
(gasps)
I'm a nerd!
So am I!
Yeah. Another day,
another box of stolen pens.
-MINDY: Have a good night, Homer.
-You too.
No goose bumps,
no hallucinations.
That last time
was just a fluke.
-♪♪ (whistling)
-(tires screeching, horns honking)
(people shouting)
(Homer shouting)
Homer loves Mindy!
Hey, Homer, you're
hallucinating again.
Not a good sign.
So, uh, what do you guys
think of Mindy?
Seems okay.
Anybody see the game last night?
Yeah. That Mindy
seems real nice.
Homer, what's with you?
You're talking during a coffee break.
Yeah. Usually you just take the box
of doughnuts into the bathroom.
Mindy has a motorcycle.
Look, everybody. I'm the same person
I always was. Whoa!
-(shouting)
-(kids screaming)
-(grunting)
-(kids laughing)
-Hey, he's learning on his own!
-Get him!
(all grunting)
-Moe, I need your advice.
-Yeah?
See, I got this friend named
Joey Jo-Jo Junior Shabadoo.
-That's the worst name I ever heard.
-(sobbing)
-Bye, Joey Jo-Jo!
-Oh, what the hell? It's me.
I'm attracted to another woman.
What am I going to do?
Your infatuation is based
on a physical attraction.
Talk to the woman, and you'll realize
you have nothing in common.
Barney, that is so insightful.
How did you come up with that?
It was on one of
these bar napkins.
(whimpers)
Uh-- So, let's have
a conversation.
Uh, I think we'll find we
have very little in common.
-Can't talk. Eating.
-Hey, my favorite--
Raspberry swirl
with a double glaze!
Double glaze.
(gurgling)
Oh! Okay, so we have
one thing in common.
But you know what I hate?
Drinking beer and watching TV.
Not me.
That's my idea of heaven.
-D'oh! Me too!
-Really?
I can see I'm gonna love
working with you.
Well, gotta go.
(whispering) I wanna sneak in
a quick nap before lunch.
(gasps)
Foul temptress.
I'll bet she thinks Ziggy's
gotten too preachy too.
-(bell dings)
-(sighs)
I made it the whole day
without seeing her again.
(screams)
I mean, hello!
(chuckles)
I guess we'll be
going down together.
-I mean, getting off toge-- I mean--
-That's okay.
I'll just push the button
for the stimulator--
I mean, elevator.
(thinking)
Think unsexy thoughts.
Oh, that's unsexy.
-(humming theme from "I Dream of Jeannie")
-Ew!
(burps)
D'oh!
(whispering) Think unsexy thoughts.
Think unsexy thoughts.
(chuckles)
Well, this is my floor.
(grunting, screaming)
See you tomorrow!
Ah, home to my loving family.
What more could a man ask for?
(blows nose)
Hi, Homer. Don't kiss me.
I'm all stuffed up.
-(groans)
-Hi, Dad.
Hi, son!
How are you-- Ew!
Dad, look.
I made fish sticks.
They're burned on the outside,
but they're frozen on the inside,
so it balances out.
Yeah, good.
That raccoon
stole my lamb chop!
(TV: indistinct)
Let's have a little quality time together,
just you and me.
-(TV off)
-Oh, that's sweet. (sniffling)
Guess what. There's
a new place at the mall
that puts your picture
on a t-shirt.
I got two dollars off
because mine got smeared.
Ew. Hey, we haven't
watched TV in a while.
Tonight, Eye on Springfield
takes a look...
at the secret affairs of Kennedy,
Eisenhower, Bush and Clinton.
Did fooling around
on their wives make them great?
We'll find out next when we play
"Hail to the Cheat."
(whimpers)
MAN: The Burmese melon fly
has over 1,000 sex partners...
and suffers virtually no guilt.
-(whimpers)
-(breathing heavily)
WOMAN:
Ooh! Just do it.
-(screams)
-(door closes)
Examine your scalp
for ringworm.
Hello, hotline?
I'm very tempted by another woman.
Homer Simpson,
that's a dilly of a pickle.
Hey, let's conference you
with Marge, huh?
No!
(groans, grunts)
-Who are you?
-Homer, I'm your guardian angel.
I've assumed the form of someone you would
recognize and revere, Sir Isaac Newton.
-Sir Isa-who?
-Oh, very well.
(gasps)
Colonel Klink!
Did you ever get my letters?
I'm not actually Colonel Klink.
-I'm just assuming his form.
-(chuckles)
Did you know Hogan had tunnels
all over your camp?
Homer! That's not
why I'm here.
My job is to show you
how miserable life would be
if you married Mindy
instead of Marge.
Ooh, I would live
in a big mansion?
(both grunting)
-I'm so happy, darling.
-I as well.
-Are you happy, Jeeves?
-Yes, sir. Quite.
-Then we're all happy.
-Let's get out of here.
Sure, life is good for you,
but what about Marge?
(gasps)
Marge lives here?
MAN: Madam President,
your approval rating is soaring.
MARGE: Mmm.
This dream is over.
(screaming)
(grunting)
Hey, you,
get out of my office!
-Nerd!
-(kids taunting)
You're goofy-looking.
(laughing)
(all grunting)
(panting)
Whoa!
-What the hell?
-Shh!
(murmuring)
-What is this place?
-The refuge of the damned.
A place where we can work
on our extra-credit assignments
without fear of reprisal.
Come, you must be tired
from the chase.
Oliver, bring our friend a hard-boiled egg
and some prune juice.
Finally, Bart's one of us.
(kids)
Excelsior!
♪ Oh, Mindy, you came
and you gave without flaking ♪
♪ But I sent you BENGAY ♪
♪ Oh, Andy, you kissed me ♪
♪ And stopped me
from something ♪
♪ And I ♪
Uh-oh.
Dad, why are you singing?
(thinking)
Tell a lie. Tell a lie.
Because I have a small role
in a Broadway musical.
It's not much,
but it's a start.
-(thinking) Bravo.
-(lone clapping)
-Are you hiding something from me?
-Like what?
Judging from your song,
you're infatuated
with a woman named Mindy
or a man named Andy.
-Lisa, look out behind you!
-Dad, I'm not gonna fall for that.
No, Lisa, I swear to you!
I'm 100% completely serious!
You've gotta turn around
right now before it's too late!
-Huh?
-Sucker!
"Mindy, because of our
uncontrollable attraction,
I think we should avoid
each other from now on."
"Max, what I did,
I did because of alcohol and anger."
"I'm tired of these jokes
about my giant hand.
The first such incident
occurred in 1956 when"--
-Hi, Homer.
-Mindy! Uh-- (clears throat)
Oh, no, I'm sweating
like Roger Ebert.
Mu-- Murphy, youse--
You are a elf--
Uncontrollably, I think--
(gibberish)
Look at those two
inseparable chums, Smithers.
That's exactly the teamwork we'd like to
showcase at this year's energy convention.
-Are you sure, sir?
-Well, no one else seems to share
the same spirit of camaraderie.
(gibberish continues)
(screaming)
Simpson, Simmons,
you two have been chosen
to represent us at
the National Energy Convention.
Congratulations. You'll be spending two
nights together in glamorous Capital City.
Wow! Capital City!
The Windy Apple!
Come on.
I'll get you the tickets.
Oh, this is the worst crisis
my marriage has ever faced!
Colonel Klink,
why have you forsaken me?
-What is it? You have a question?
-(chuckling)
Did you know Kinch had
a radio in the coffee pot?
He did? Mmm!
(groans)
TV's there, bathroom's there,
and there's your king-sized bed
for--
(wolf whistle, meowing)
(imitates bed squeaking,
growls, pants)
(barking, howling)
(gibberish)
Hubba-hubba.
Stop that!
I love my wife and family.
All I'm gonna use this bed for
is sleeping, eating,
and maybe building a little fort.
That's it!
(gasps)
Free mouthwash! Free shampoo!
-Free shower curtain!
-MINDY: Free shower curtain!
-Mindy?
-Homer?
Wow. If it weren't for this wall,
we'd be sleeping in the same bed.
Yeah. Uh, walls are a necessity
in today's society. (chuckles)
Homer, I got a really wicked idea
that could get us into a lot of trouble.
Oh! Mindy, we have to fight
our temptation.
No, Homer. Let's do it.
Let's call room service!
-Oh.
-(beeping)
Someone is charging room service
to the company, sir.
Well, we'll just see about that.
Fly, my pretties. Fly!
(chittering)
(screaming)
-(thudding)
-(groans)
Continue the research.
-(lips smacking)
-Mmm!
-I can't believe we ordered so much.
-Oh, something's missing.
Ooh! One of the turkeys
fell behind the bed.
(both)
Mmm. Foot-long chili dog.
(both gasp)
(Marge's voice:
Mechanical humming sound)
(screams)
It's a sign!
-(shouts)
-(mechanical hum continues)
Good news, honey.
Two weeks are up.
You don't have to wear
your glasses anymore.
And your scalp
and posture seem fine.
Yes!
(grunts)
Kids, did anyone pray
for giant shoes?
-I did!
-Okilly-dokilly.
We've been doing a lot
of upper-body work on Bart.
-Today, let's pound his kidneys.
-Yeah.
-♪♪ (humming)
-Let's get-- Huh?
What gives?
Gentlemen, the nerd
you knew is dead.
Beat me, and you will be
beating one of your own.
-Whatever.
-(blows landing)
(electricity buzzing)
(chattering)
-So this stuff really works?
-Certainly does.
-Oh, well, lots of luck!
-Oh!
(snaps fingers)
(men muttering)
(rustling)
Thanks for poisoning
the planet, bastard!
-Get bent!
-No more Chernobyls!
Go to hell!
-(grunts)
-(man shouts)
You know, I was a little worried about
coming to this convention with you.
But I think as long as
we're not alone together--
MAN (on TV): And now the moment
you've been waiting for.
This year's king and queen
of energy are...
Homer Simpson
and Mindy Simmons.
-Huh?
-♪♪ (fanfare)
Homer, Mindy, you've just won a romantic
dinner alone at Madame Chao's,
the sexiest Chinese restaurant
in Capital City!
-Is there any way to get out of this?
-No.
(sighs)
What a perfect evening.
It was sure nice of them
to make us cheeseburgers.
Uh, yeah.
(reading silently) "You will
find happiness with a new love."
Oh, even the Chinese are against me.
(groans)
What's the point?
I can't fight fate.
(slurping)
Hey, we're out of
these "new love" cookies.
Well, open up the
"Stick with your wife" barrel.
Well, I guess
you'll wanna come in.
-Okay.
-"Okay."
This was a really
nice night, Homer.
Yeah, yeah.
(sobbing)
-What's wrong?
-Oh, yeah. Like you don't know.
-We're gonna have sex.
-Oh.
Well, we don't have to.
Yes, we do.
The cookie told me so.
Well, desserts
aren't always right.
But they're so sweet.
Homer,
you don't have to do anything
you don't want to.
Well, maybe I want to.
But then I think about
Marge and the kids.
Well, not the boy.
He drives me nuts.
-Sometimes I'd just like to--
-Homer,
you know how I feel,
so it's up to you.
Look in your heart.
I think you'll see what you want.
♪♪
-Oh, baby.
-♪ My darling, I ♪
This was a wonderful idea,
Homie.
♪ Can't get enough
of your love, babe ♪
Hey, there's a turkey
behind the bed!
Mmm. Marge.
(chuckling)
HOMER: ♪ Oh, Margie, you came
and you found me a turkey ♪
♪ On my vacation
away from workie ♪
(wolf whistle, meowing)
(imitating bed squeaking,
growls, pants)
(barking, howling)
(gibberish)
Hubba-hubba.
(blow lands)
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.