♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screeching)
♪ What would you do ♪
♪ If I sang out of tune ♪
♪ Would you stand up
and walk out on me ♪
♪ Lend me your ears ♪
♪ And I'll sing you a song ♪
♪ I will try not to sing
out of key, yeah ♪
♪ Oh, baby, I get by with a
little help from my friends ♪
(Bart laughing)
Oh, they're gonna eat
this up in show-and-tell.
I'm not sure if I'm
comfortable with the idea
of your classmates laughing
at our family's private moments.
How would you like it
if 20 years from now
people were laughing
at things you did?
Not likely.
Come on. Have a sense
of humor about yourself.
I'm a big boy today.
(laughing)
(groans) I gotta find
something else quick.
Why don't you bring this
potato? It's pretty big.
Mom, you're always trying
to give me potatoes.
-What is it with you?
-I just think they're neat.
I need something
for show-and-tell.
Just take one of my geodes.
The rocks on my desk.
No, that's a trilobite.
That's petrified wood.
Bart, that's a bran muffin!
(school bus horn honks)
Greetings, fellow geode-ologist.
(groans)
I'll be right back!
(growling)
The ingredients were
fresh pureed tomatoes,
water, salt and sodium benzoate
used to retard spoilage.
Once again,
if I'm not mistaken,
this can contained
tomato paste.
Thank you, Nelson.
I look forward to seeing it
again next week.
Bart, you're up.
Boys and girls,
Mrs. Krabappel,
I come before you today
to solve a riddle
that has plagued
mankind for centuries.
What has four legs
and ticks?
-A walking clock?
-A walking clock!
I'd wager he has some variety
of walking clock in that box.
Bart, is it
a walking clock?
What? No, it's my dog.
-(all gasp)
-Oh, he is a gem!
Here, boy. Would you like these
cookies Martin made for me?
My raisin roundies!
My dog's name is
Santa's Little Helper.
One time he crawled under
the house, and when he came out,
he was covered with ants.
Then he ran into a church
and drank all the holy water.
ALL: Wow!
Thank you, Bart.
Great job.
(all cheering)
I knew the dog
before he came to class.
Kaboom! That, the sound of
the thunderous volcanic explosion
which gives birth
to the magnificent geode,
one of nature's most--
You're doing it wrong! You gotta
pet him hard so he can feel it.
(grumbles, sneezes)
Look, look, look!
The doggy sneezed!
-Ha! It thinks it's people.
-(knocking)
Oh, poochie. Here,
poochie, poochie, poochie!
(grunts)
(clears throat)
My geode must be acknowledged.
Oh, brother. All right.
Back to show-and-tell.
Bart, why don't you
put the doggy away?
(students groaning)
(whimpers)
(sniffing)
Mmm.
More testicles mean more iron.
(moaning, whimpering)
Uh, Miss Hoover,
there's a dog in the vent.
Ralph, remember the time you
said Snagglepuss was outside?
He was going to the bathroom.
Uh, I-- I know Weinstein's
parents were upset,
Superintendent, but I-- I was
sure it was a phony excuse.
I mean, it sounds so made-up.
"Yom kip pur."
(chuckles, stammers)
(shouting, cheering)
Sir, you've got to come quick!
There's a dog runnin' around
in the air ducts!
I understand. Children,
this is Principal Skinner.
Remain calm.
There is a dog in the vents.
(shouting, cheering)
(grunts)
(slobbers, panting)
Willie, go into the vent
and get him!
What? Have you gone
waxy in your "beester"?
I cannot fit in the wee vent,
ya croquet-playin' mint muncher!
Grease yourself up
and go in, you...
you guff-speaking
work slacker.
Ooh, good comeback.
Lunch Lady Doris,
have you got any grease?
Yes. Yes, we do.
Then grease me up, woman!
Okeydokey.
(grunting)
(gasps)
(beeping)
(beeping continues)
-(beeping intensifies)
-Good Lord!
It's coming up
right behind him!
What the-- No! No!
(laughing)
(laughing continues)
(students shouting)
Ow! Ow! Stop it!
Children, teachers,
back to your rooms.
Uh-oh. Whenever I get
this upset, I get hiccups.
(hiccups)
Oh, right on cue.
(all laughing)
-(barks)
-(grunts, groans)
(grunts, laughs)
There's nary an animal alive that
can outrun a greased Scotsman.
Now, out we go.
(grunts)
(gasps)
'Tis more dizzyin'
than the belfry
at St. Corgegluynwaagen's.
(students murmuring)
That's nice work, boys.
(panting)
MRS. KRABAPPEL:
Uh-oh!
Someone's getting a visit
from Superintendent Chalmers.
I... (hiccups)
can't... (hiccups)
take... (hiccups)
this. (hiccups)
-Skinner!
-Superintendent Chalmers,
you didn't have to come
all the way down here.
Everything's under control.
(screams)
Oh, I have had it!
I have had it with
this school, Skinner!
The low test scores,
class after class of ugly,
ugly children!
Oh, now I really think
the children's appearance--
Seymour, you are in very,
very big trouble.
-(barks)
-(gasps)
Why, looking into this loveable
mutt's eyes just melts my heart.
Seymour,
all is forgiven.
(yelling)
Make way for Willie!
I said make way for Willie,
ya bloated gasbag!
-Seymour.
-Hmm?
-You're fired!
-(gasps)
I'm sorry. Did-- Did you
just call me a liar?
No. I said you were fired.
Oh. That's much worse.
(hiccups)
(gobbling, gulping)
I thought I'd be jumping
for joy the day Skinner left,
but now all I have
is this weird,
hot feeling in
the back of my head.
That's guilt. You feel guilty
because your stunt wound up
costing a man his job.
Yeah, I guess it is guilt.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Let me get this straight.
They let everybody
out of school early
just because you
brought a dog?
-Well, yeah, but--
-Well, I'm off to work.
The dog has had
enough excitement.
But, Marge,
dogs can never have
enough excitement.
Look. Whee! Whee!
(laughing)
Whee, whee!
All right, all right.
I won't take the dog. Come here.
-(Marge groans)
-Aw.
Boys and girls, because of
Mr. Skinner's sudden departure,
I've had to appoint
a new principal.
-Leopold.
-(all gasp)
All right, you little punks.
Prick up your freakin' ears,
because I'm only
gonna be saying this once.
From now on,
things are gonna be very,
very different around here--
-(all gasp)
-...with your new principal, Ned Flanders.
(applause, cheering)
Well, tippity-top o' the a.m.
to every-good-body here.
As chairman of the P.T.A.,
I am de-didilly-lighted to take over,
and I think I can put
the "Pal" back in principal.
(all laughing)
Yeah, and I'll put the "super"
back in superintendent.
(person coughs)
It's the same exact joke.
What gives, Leo?
Now, I know everybody's eager
to get back to class--
MRS. KRABAPPEL:
Ha!
But I thought
it might break the ice
if we had a little "Q" and "A."
Dude, ask a question,
or we'll have to go back to class.
Um--
-Yeah, you.
-Uh, yeah.
Uh, I was wonderin',
do you, uh--
What's your policy
on, uh, lunch?
Well, let me just say
I want to put the "stew"
back in students.
(all laughing)
It's just a damn popularity
contest with you kids.
Now look what you've done,
you little freaks!
Young man,
your gargantuan cone
is making a mockery
of our self-serve policy.
Bart, look.
It's Principal Skinner,
and I think
he's gone crazy.
He's not wearing
a suit or tie or anything.
Principal Skinner, um,
I'm real sorry about
my dog getting you fired
and biting you and then
getting it on with your leg.
Well, maybe
it was for the best.
Now I-- I finally have time
to do what I've always wanted--
Write the great American novel.
Mine is about a
futuristic amusement park
where dinosaurs
are brought to life
through advanced
cloning techniques.
I call it
"Billy and the Clone-osaurus."
Oh, you have got
to be kidding, sir.
First you think of an idea
that has already been done.
Then you give it a title
that nobody could possibly like.
Didn't you think this through?
...on the best-seller
list for 18 months!
Every magazine cover
had it!
...most popular movies
of all time, sir!
What were you thinking?
I mean, thank you.
Come again.
Bart, I've barely been here
a-a good solid week,
and you've been sent
to my office 11 times.
And now that I have
peanut butter cups,
you seem to be getting
in trouble every hour.
Must have been a coincidence.
Anyhoo, Bart, you're
gonna have to be punished.
This isn't just
some sort of clubhouse.
(ice rattles)
Oh, sorry. Were you
drinking Slice or Yoo-hoo?
Now let's see.
"Tide. Cheer.
"Bold. Biz.
"Fab. All.
Gain. Wisk."
I believe today
I will try... Bold.
Bart, how are you?
How's school?
Um, it's--
It's a lot of fun.
Hmm.
Well, it was good
to see you.
It was? Well, then we
should get together again.
Say, Saturday at my house.
Do you know where I live?
Uh, no.
Hmm. A flaming bag, eh?
Well, these new Italian loafers
will make short work of it.
Uh, I'm kinda busy
on Saturday.
(grunts, laughs)
Hey!
(chanting)
We got Skinner's underpants!
And there's nothing
you can do about it, Mr. Ex-principal.
That's not true.
I can buy a new pair.
No, I can't.
I needed those. I really did.
Oh, you must be
Seymour's friend.
He's up in his room.
Don't touch the wallpaper.
-♪♪ (Beethoven's 5th Symphony)
-♪ Ba-ba-ba-bum ♪
♪ Ba-ba-ba-bum ♪
Now a little more allegro
than last time. Bart!
(chuckles)
Welcome.
Can I offer you a diet
caffeine-free Dr. Pepper
or an individual
fruit cocktail cup?
Uh, I'll pass.
Hey, what's this?
Oh, that's my old unit
from Vietnam.
I was their sergeant.
They were my loyal troops.
That photo was taken shortly
before I was shot in the back,
which was very strange because
it was during a Bob Hope show.
I was trying to get Joey Heatherton to
put on some pants, for God's sake!
Seymour, your friend
Bart is here!
I know, Mother!
Seymour, do you want me
to tell you when it's 7:30?
No, Mother!
(laughing)
Ned Flanders actually
eliminated detention
and put the whole school
on the honor system?
(laughs) Yeah. The teachers
are afraid to leave the faculty lounge.
(both laughing)
Oh, that place must be
falling apart.
Oh, mercy.
Nobody's
mentioned me, have they?
Uh, I thought I heard someone
say your name in the cafeteria,
But they might have been
saying "skim milk."
Yeah, yeah.
Hmm.
-(claw snips)
-Ahh! Ohh! Yee!
I thought you might like
this restaurant, Bart.
They'll make a pizza pie
with a topping of your choice.
Hey, Seymour!
You want your usual table?
No, no, Luigi.
I'd like one with two seats.
I'll be dining
with a friend tonight.
Hey, good for you, huh?
Hmm. They treat you
real nice here.
Hey, Salvatore,
guess who's here!
Mr. Kookalamanza
and-a some real ugly kid.
(students shouting)
This is great!
Not only am I not learnin',
I'm forgettin' stuff
I used to know.
(laughs)
And it's all thanks to you, Bart.
Yeah, great.
What's the matter?
Don't you see, Milhouse?
We've gone too far.
-We need Skinner back.
-My water dish is empty!
(school bell rings)
GIRL'S VOICE: I learned to read
because of you, Principal Skinner.
MARTIN: Sir, I baked you
these raisin roundies.
RALPH: Principal Skinner, I got
carsick in your office.
(sobbing)
Oh, you're Seymour's friend.
Here. He left you this note.
SKINNER:
Dear Bart...
However, I've decided to return
to the only thing besides school
that has ever given
my life meaning--
(groans)
Table for one.
Oh, you miss your friend, huh?
Don't you worry.
My cooking,
she'll-a cheer you up.
Hey, Salvatore, give-a the ugly kid
a pan of the red crap!
It's good to have another
combat veteran around here.
I myself received
a number of medals
for securing that Montgomery Ward
in Kuwait City.
Mm, yes, colonel. Now,
I understand it'll be my duty
to mold the new recruits
into a well-disciplined,
highly trained infantry unit.
Sure, I guess.
Here they come.
(vehicle approaching)
(chattering)
Hi. Where do I get
my grenades at?
Uh, they don't have them group
toilets here no more, do they?
Ned, Homer and I are
a little concerned
with the way
the school's being run.
Yes, deeply concerned.
Well, I may go a little bit easy on
the old hickory dickory stick,
but that's just because my dad
was so hard on me when I was a boy.
Whoopsy-doodle.
Oh, man! Ned spilled ink
all over my poems!
He's a real flat tire.
I mean a cube, man.
He's putting us on the train
to Squaresville, Mona.
Hmm?
♪ I met a woman
in Paris, France ♪
♪ Had a big hole
in her underpants ♪
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Where did you pick up that filth?
We heard Sergeant Clark's
company singing it, sir.
Yes, well, there will be
no smut in my company.
You're in this man's
army to learn.
♪ I don't know
but I've been told ♪
♪ The Parthenon
is mighty old ♪
-♪ How old ♪
-♪ We don't know ♪
That's real good
but needs improvement.
(sighs)
Wow, I never thought Principal Skinner
could become any more of a square,
but there's the proof.
It's weird, Lis.
I miss him as a friend,
but I miss him even more
as an enemy.
I think you need Skinner, Bart.
Everybody needs a nemesis.
Sherlock Holmes
had his Dr. Moriarty.
Mountain Dew
has its Mello Yello.
Even Maggie has that baby
with the one eyebrow.
(wheel squeaking)
(incoming ordnance)
Man on the range!
Change your trajectory!
(all grunting)
Sixteen brand-new
gas pumps!
At last we can compete
with the Gas-n-Gulp.
(incoming ordnance)
If there was some way
to get rid of Flanders,
would you want to come back?
Ah, I must admit
I do miss the school.
Frankly, the army isn't
quite as I remembered it.
Up yours, Sergeant!
Actually, it's exactly
as I remembered it.
I do want
to come back, Bart,
but it doesn't sound like
Flanders is gonna get fired.
Oh, I think
I could get him fired.
I got you fired, didn't I?
(laughing)
Yes.
Now, you realize if
I become principal again,
we can no longer be friends,
unless you become
a good student.
Hmm. That's probably
never gonna happen.
Well, we'll always
have the Laundromat.
Yeah.
What's he doing here?
Well, once he found out
we were gonna get
Ned Flanders fired,
he insisted on helping.
That is true.
Here's the plan.
Once Chalmers comes for his
next inspection
and sees how crappy
the school has gotten,
he'll fire Ned on the spot.
Uh, one question remains:
How do I get out of the army?
No problemo. Just make a pass
at your commanding officer.
Done and done.
And I mean done.
(knocking)
MARGE:
What's going on in there?
ALL:
Nothing.
(students shouting)
(singing opera)
Come on, Chalmie. You fired
Skinner for less than this.
Yeah, I did, but Skinner
really bugged me.
Besides, the way America's
public schools are sliding,
they'll all be this way
in a few months.
I say lay back and enjoy it.
It's a hell of a toboggan ride.
NED: Well, cockilly-doodilly-do,
little buddies.
Let's thank the Lord for
another beautiful school day.
Thank the Lor-- Thank the Lord?
That sounded like a prayer.
A prayer! A prayer
in a public school!
God has no place
within these walls,
just like facts have no place
within organized religion!
Simpson, you get your wish.
Flanders is history.
(humming)
Well, I really enjoyed my
time here, Superintendent.
May the Lord
bless and keep you.
Yeah, take it outside,
God boy.
Okilly-dokilly.
Dirksen, tuck in your shirt.
Jaffee, spit out that gum.
You really think it's a good idea
to give that freak his job back?
Ah, he seems to know
the students' names.
So, I guess
we're enemies again.
I guess.
Thanks, Bart.
Sure.
(chuckles)
(Skinner chuckles)
Oh, mercy.
♪♪
Shh.
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.