Welcome. Good to see you.
If you're here
to use the bathroom,
try the Burger King next door.
Actually,
we'd like to buy something.
Wunderbar.
I offer many things.
Astounding tricks,
confounding illusions.
I also fix iPhones.
You've heard of Steve Jobs?
This is my kid, No Jobs.
- Dad!
- He's been angry
since I made his mother
disappear
with my cold attitude
and the philandering.
Achtung, Gramps.
I want to buy a magic set
for my sister's birthday
'cause that's the kind
of lame‐o thing she'd like.
Magic is not lame‐o.
Let me show you a trick
that made Angela Merkel say,
you are the worst
Uber driver ever.
This underwear was once worn
by Babar, King of the Elephants.
Elephant underwear
is tighty‐whities on Homer.
Why, you little...!
What the...? The more I pull,
the tighter it gets.
The only solution? Pull more.
Will you two ever stop?
Ever?
Is it the future you seek?
Well, then,
move through this beaded curtain
and past the Keurig coffee maker
I bought but never use.
Let us see what the tarot cards
have to say.
Tarot cards don't work.
Don't they, Madam President?
Now let us see
what happens to Homer and Bart.
How does he know our names?
They are
on your Starbucks coffee cups.
Good news, Homer.
In the future,
you stop drinking.
And the boy
becomes a fine person.
What? No!
Reversum predictum!
It's licorice. Have some.
Now I turn more cards and...
Oh, dear.
This is rough. Very bad.
What? What?
There will be years of trouble
between Marge and Lisa.
The trouble begins
when you decide
where you will go to college.
What? Why are you saying that?
What's wrong?
Do I get wait‐listed?
Gap year?
Cornell?!
Let's just say
things have changed
when you are 17.
Rise and shine!
Mom, please.
I was asleep.
Today's the day
you're gonna find out
what colleges you get into.
Who cares?
They all lost their glitter
when Netflix bought Yale.
Well, you will be
the first Simpson
to ever finish college
now that Bart's given up.
Why should I go to college?
I've become a master
of Fruit Ninja.
Salad complete.
There she is.
Our family's last
and only remaining hope.
Putting on a little pressure
there, Grampa?
It's just that you're
the only worthwhile Simpson
since... ever.
I'm counting on you
to find the cure
for everything
that's gonna kill me.
No pressure.
Wait a minute.
This is on the wrong eye.
Ooh, much better.
Lisa, I have a question.
Please, don't mention
the word college.
College? No way.
This is a surprise promposal.
Guess who I hired to ask you
on my behalf.
My dad.
Imitating Seth MacFarlane
imitating Frank Sinatra.
Take him to the prom
And let him dance
forevermore
If you turn him down
He will curl up on the floor
In other words
We're desperate
We really are.
A pity yes will do
And you'll have to drive
'cause he can't.
I can see you're tempted, Lis.
There's nothing cooler
than a guy who's graduated
coming back for a younger kid's
prom.
Get out of here before
I accidentally say okay.
Did I hear an okay?
Aw, hey, kid.
What's the matter?
Your whole life, for reasons
I'll never understand,
you've been looking forward
to college.
Today, you get in.
Things have changed
since I was a kid.
College costs a fortune,
and does it really do any good?
All you get is a piece of paper
with your name on it.
And it's written in Latin,
so the only people
who can actually read it
are dead Romans
and Catholic priests.
And last I checked, none of them
are handing out jobs.
Then why did you study so hard
and miss all the fun?
Old days
Good times I remember
Fun days
Filled with simple pleasure
I don't know now.
I think of all those years
where instead of being
behind a book,
I could've played kickball.
So many jump ropes un‐jumped.
Do you ever feel regret, Bart?
I regret
starting this conversation.
Every one. I got into every one.
Why does this moment
feel so empty?
Come one, come all.
Don't miss it.
Lisa, I told everyone
you're going to make
your pick today.
This is the greatest moment
of my life.
Drumroll!
A Simpson got into college
And I just never applied
Everyone, shh!
It's the moment of truth.
Congratulations, Lisa.
Which one are you gonna choose?
Bob Jones. Bob Jones.
Bob Jones.
I...
I'm not going to college.
What?! Quit joking.
Marge, nobody knows comedy
like I don't.
She's not joking.
Lisa, you can't do this.
We're counting on you.
Well, you know, Marge,
I didn't go to college,
and I'm wealthy
in the most important way,
lack of student loans.
Do not encourage her.
Marge, her not going to college
is the most money
I'll ever earn.
Lisa, please. I'm giving you
one last chance
to salvage this day.
I've lived for this moment.
And all I've ever asked from you
is that everything
that never happened to me
happens to you.
And that justifies
my existence on Earth
for the hours I spent
holding you, cleaning you,
cooking your supper,
drying your tears,
catching your colds
and burying
every personal need I had
just so I could have
the brief joy
of setting up your dorm room
with the roommate
from the fancy family
who you'll spend the holidays
with on their ranch in Colorado
instead of coming home to me.
Once and for all,
which college are you going to?
None.
I just wanted to say one thing.
- What's that?
- Ingrate!
I'm sorry,
but could you have decided
you didn't want to go to college
before ten years
of me driving you
to saxophone lessons, SAT prep,
college tours of colleges
you were never gonna go to?!
Could it be that I'm finally
the favorite parent?
Maggie, whose side are you on?
I don't like
how digital she's getting.
Aw, you know just what to say.
Honey,
I baked you brownies to eat
while you reconsider
stuff you've done or said.
Wait a minute.
Do you actually think
your brownies
will affect my life decisions?
They have walnuts in them.
Mom, I never really liked
your brownies,
and I'm not going to college.
Really? Who are you?
All my life,
I did what I thought
other people wanted me to do.
Now I'm doing what I want.
Someday, you're gonna have
a daughter of your own,
and you'll see how I feel.
Who says I'm gonna have kids?
No college? No kids?
How dare you lead the life
I wish I'd led.
I'm burned out.
I'm so burned out.
I just need some time to think.
Okay. Just promise me
that before you make
any final decisions,
- you'll talk to...
- I know, I know. My father.
I'm talking about the man
who's been there
for every birthday.
The one man who took pride
in your every achievement.
I'd love to talk with you,
Lisa, but first...
Boys, it's 6:00 p.m.
Time for bed.
College was my dream.
Then I thought,
is it really my dream
or just everyone else's?
Lisa, use the gifts God gave you
for whatever path
he puts you on.
Get a job. Learn the pride that comes
with getting your own paycheck.
Of course. The dignity of work.
Thank you, Mr. Flanders.
Daddy, can you come upstairs?
We're scared.
Daddy, bring the monster spray!
I may have over‐coddled them
just a little bit.
Now, I'm afraid
the next kilometer
on Lisa's autobahn of life
would not be,
as you say, easy peasy.
Ooh, could I double down
on those?
This is not blackjack.
I said hit me.
Not blackjack.
Come on, pal, hit me.
Fine.
You're busted.
D'oh! Should've held
on the hard Knave of Cups.
I have no regrets.
Simpson, the corn
isn't sticking to the dogs.
Why did I waste 30 minutes
training you?
Now the pulp is settling
in the lemonade!
Pump! Pump!
Pump...!
Why am I working here?
Even I can't answer that,
and I was a philosophy major
at Brown.
Brown!
Brown...!
God, that job sucks.
Here's a little secret, honey.
All jobs suck.
That's why you get paid
to do them.
So you had your gap week.
Now you're finally going
to college, right?
No. Not ever.
Okay, I can't change this,
and I can't accept this.
What do I do? Go downstairs
and yell into the dryer.
Why is she doing this?!
Why won't she go to college?!
We've been planning this
her whole life!
Why?!
I'll have that picture
and that picture
and a diet that picture,
if'n you please.
Can't you read the names?
No, ma'am.
You seem to read just fine,
and you're stuck in this dump.
Not anymore.
I know what I'm gonna do.
I hope it starts with pressin'
the button what brings my food.
Nope. I'm not gonna learn.
I'm gonna teach!
I'm gonna start
an after‐school program,
individualized and
accessible to children
who fall through the cracks.
What are you going to do
for money?
Workman's comp.
I'd like to see you try.
On my way!
Welcome to the Boundless
Horizons School,
where I'm gonna change
your lives
and you're gonna write letters
to me forever
and you'll say I was
your most influential person.
Just exactly how
are you gonna teach us?
Well, I'm gonna use
every trick there is.
I'll put the desks in a circle.
I'll take
the toughest one of you
and put him or her in charge
of making everyone behave.
And I'll teach Shakespeare
using dances from TikTok.
Out, out, damned spot
This is the way that
Shakespeare should be taught
Her incredible lameness
has me riveted.
Finally, someone who gets me
as a stereotype.
Wait one minute, young lady.
You cannot just open
your own school
and start to better
random lives.
You have to sign this form
and pay a $25 city business tax.
Okay.
Just give me the change, please.
This is embarrassing.
I'm not great at math.
Leave that to me.
Lisa Simpson's
after‐school program
has been a tremendous success.
Unlike the news business.
Lisa now has over 100 franchises
here in the Illiteracy Belt.
And now, given her high profile
and 80% approval rating,
Lisa's running
for state school superintendent
against incumbent Gary Chalmers.
Under my opponent,
test scores have fallen.
Graduation rates have fallen.
I am not going to stand here and
listen to some nasty woman...
I'm just trying to make
a point, all right?
I'm not gonna let some stupid,
nasty, homely woman...
Simpson!
I concede.
Congratulations.
Beloved superintendent
of schools, Lisa Simpson,
is now running for governor!
Soon she'll move
beyond the scope
of a career‐stuck
local anchorman like me.
This is Kent Brockman
signing off...
Lisa Simpson, governor of...
is running for president.
Not even her
highly damaged relationship
with her mother
can stop her now.
Nate Silver analyzes.
Well, George,
Lisa is doing great
with disenchanted daughters.
Also tiger moms,
checked‐out dads
and grandparents
who like everything,
plus middle children,
nerds of all ages
and saxophonists
above second chair.
Now, it's a week
before the election but...
what the hell,
I'm calling it for Lisa.
My work here is done.
Good luck, America.
It's 5:38 somewhere.
This just in.
Lisa Simpson has been elected
the eighth president
who did not go to college,
joining George Washington,
Abraham Lincoln
and Harry S. Truman.
Think about that when you're
paying your student loans.
Stephanopoulos out.
My daughter
really becomes president?
Yes. But you have to learn it
on the streets.
Great news
about your daughter, Marge.
She's finally going to college?
No. She's president.
You knew that, didn't you?
Oh, crap.
I really am out of the loop.
Look, the heart of the story
is Lisa and me.
Do we finally get along?
Also, in the future,
how many more Ghostbusters
do they make?
Four. The gay Ghostbusters
is fantastic.
Can't we dwell on the fact
that I was president?
So concerned about your futures
but no one cares about mine.
I won't get into details,
but my body winds up in
the dumpster behind the store.
Do any of you give a damn?
Very well.
Now we have come
to the final two cards.
The future will be revealed.
But first, I want to plug
my gig this Saturday
at the Comedy & Magic Club.
I conjure the spirit
of Rodney Dangerfield.
Ich bekomme keinen respekt.
I'm telling you.
Here we are.
It's Inauguration Day,
and Marge and Lisa
are barely speaking.
And I promise you that,
as your president,
I will obsess over your welfare,
because I don't have a life!
You're all I've got!
And I will serve you.
And we'll get right on that!
Madam President,
just after you were sworn in,
your predecessor
finally conceded.
These transitional tantrums
get longer and longer.
Okay, he promised
he'd leave after he did that.
But you're going to be
a great president.
Thank you.
But maybe not a happy one.
Bart!
Oh, I almost hugged you.
Well, I almost wish you had.
I think I will.
I hope you do.
I know what you need.
Some President's Choice
High Carumba.
Why did you bring that here?
A, it's legal.
B, somehow still cool.
And C,
you really need to chill out.
He's with me! He's with me!
Oh, I got to tell you something.
Now that we're both grown
and successful...
you, president,
me, pot CEO
and owner of three NBA teams.
I feel different.
I really, really,
really don't hate you.
Got anything to say to me?
Yes.
All right.
I'll admit it.
I've always been
kind of a pain in the butt.
If you had said that earlier,
even I would have voted for you.
Wow, that's pretty cool
for someone who was
always unpopular.
But, but wait!
Not my fault.
Because,
I don't know if you know,
but I did not come from a family
that made things easy.
Well, maybe you didn't make
things easier for them either.
Maybe Mom was the one
who was helping you
in ways you don't even remember.
Old days
Good times I remember
Fun days...
Mom?
She's clean.
Checked her hair.
Took 45 minutes.
I'm here to see
if you'll finally admit
you'd be better off
if you'd gone to college.
Are you crazy?
You still can't admit
you were wrong.
Let me tell you something, lady.
Wait a minute.
Just... Just wait a minute.
I'm president now.
I have a lot of resources.
Where's my mom translator?
Maybe I started off
on the wrong foot.
You constantly let me down.
Of course, I appreciate
everything you're saying.
You were never really in
my corner.
I may have said
a lot of things in anger.
I meant what I said
and I will stick to it.
But no matter what,
I was always proud of you.
You made me mad too.
I was hurt
because I care so much.
All the respect and love I have
for people came from you.
That's nice to hear.
I love you so much.
I love you too.
Okay, you can go now.
This translator is fantastic.
Give her a raise.
Okay. I enjoyed that story,
but I got to know,
how much is really true?
Let me consult the oracle.
Okay, Lisa,
I'll give it to you straight.
You've got a 98% chance
of going to college,
83% Ivy League,
47% chance of a boyfriend,
72% chance of a girlfriend.
I like those odds!
Hey, can I get the game on this?
It's not a TV.