(oogah horn blows)
(exclaiming)
(school bell ringing)
(Barney belches)
D'oh!
(tires screeching)
(grunts)
(angry shouting)
(dramatic music plays)
(cries out)
♪ The Simpsons 25x05 ♪
Labor Pains
Original Air Date on November 17, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
(belches)
MARGE:
Oh!
Come on. Just pick one.
(sniffing)
Oh. Fine, you can
have your old one.
(Marge sighs)
You can have one of these.
(sniffing)
Hmph!
Did you know some historians think American
football is based on an ancient Aztec game?
It's not American football,
it's just football.
Bart, you're not annoyed
that Milhouse asked me
to go to the American
football game instead of you?
- Mom, Lisa's ruining football.
- American football.
No time for breakfast, Marge.
Just give me a banana.
(humming)
Now, listen. I have
to work late tonight.
Again? I was hoping you could
spend some time with the kids.
It's a tough economy. Money
doesn't grow on trees.
It grows on threes.
(laughs)
- Yeah, I'm out.
- Me, too.
Too rich for my blood. I should
not have anted with my blood.
Whew. You got the
touch tonight, Homer.
(chuckles)
Nice sunglasses, Lenny.
Homer Simpson.
Do you really want to keep
cheating your friends,
lying to your wife, and
avoiding your kids?
What would Jesus do?
Hey, you gotta pay to find out.
You looking for a tell?
I don't have one, my friend.
What? What are you lookin' at?
I'd better call
it a night, guys.
I don't want to take any
more of your money.
Mm. Mm. Mm.
Hmm.
Who's president now,
Alexander Hamilton?
I think it's Obama.
Hold the door, please.
(breathes heavily)
Two minutes apart.
- Timing the elevators, eh?
- Oh.
- Smart.
No, no.
I'm timing my contractions.
I think I'm in labor.
Deep in labor.
Okay, okay, no worries.
What the...? Oh!
Do you have a cell phone?
Everyone has a cell phone.
Mine's at home.
The most beautiful moment of
my life is happening now.
Everything will be fine.
Um... Oh you, uh,
you like movies?
This reminds me of
that scene in Alien.
What?
The scene where she escapes
with the cat at the end.
Aw, well, that's sweet.
Listen, I'm glad I'm not
going through this alone.
I haven't seen
my boyfriend in months.
Oh, uh, he was just here.
No, he wasn't.
But thanks for lying.
You like lies? Here's a few:
College is expensive
but it's worth it.
I think the baby's coming.
Okay Homer, remember
your Lamaze training.
Now, this next position is fantastic for
women who are carrying especially big.
Homer, can you demonstrate?
Mm-hmm.
Mm...
Oh. Yeah, wow, that
does feel good.
Oh, no, I think it's coming.
Oh, I haven't even
picked a name yet.
You did this to me.
- No, I didn't.
- I'm talking to the baby.
Here it comes.
Um, I don't know how
to tell you this,
- but your baby doesn't have any legs.
- What?
Oh, wait, there's more.
Mm. (grunts)
(baby cries)
It's a dude. And he's uncut.
Very Euro.
Now, hug your mommy.
For unto you is born this
day, in this elevator,
inspected in August
2009, a baby.
(elevator motor humming)
(relieved sigh)
Well,
it was nice to share this
moment with someone who cared.
Yeah, that guy didn't
even look over once.
Lobby please.
(grunts)
(moans)
- How was work?
- Miraculous.
Mm?
Mothers are so awesome.
Oh.
These are great seats.
You can hear the players
swear from up here.
PLAYER:
I'll kick your ass, Milhouse.
ANNOUNCER: And now, to take your
minds off the massive concussion
and subdural hematoma
you just witnessed,
please welcome the
Springfield Atomettes.
Now, for this routine, we need
the help of a junior Atomette.
They're picking me, Dad.
Don't call me "Dad." If people think peanut
vendors have families, it's too sad.
ANNOUNCER: Looks like
we've got a volunteer...
right there.
(gasps)
Look, while I'd like to help, I'm kind
of pessimistic about the team's chances.
They're gonna get creamed.
Go, go, go!
Mm?
(crowd cheering)
Uh...
♪
(crowd cheering, whooping)
I'm dating a cheerleader.
LISA (in the distance):
No, you're not.
PLAYER:
Burned again, Milhouse.
(crowd chatter)
Wow, that was great.
Can I have my regular
clothes back, please?
No... problem.
Great job, ladies.
Now here's your 50 bucks each which
should just about cover your parking.
I can't believe he pays you so little.
The crowd was crazy about you.
I know, but what are
we gonna do about it?
If we pipe up they'll put
us in the mascot costume.
WOMEN:
Ew.
After you wear that, you need
to be hosed down for bedbugs.
Good game, everyone. I never dreamed a
night where you discovered I was cheating
and beat the crap out of me
could end on such an up note.
See you next week.
WOMAN:
Homer.
Hmm? Hey, Gretchen.
I had your jacket cleaned.
Good as new. And thanks for loaning
me your sweater for the ride home.
It may be a little
stretched out.
Geez, that was a
pregnancy sweater.
So, you want to
hold little Homer?
Wow, so now there's two
things named after me...
a baby, and a law banning
air horns after 3:00 a.m.
(nasally):
Aw that's sweet.
(tires screech)
MOE: Read 'em and weep. The
novels of Charlotte Bronte.
CARL: Um, I thought we
were playing cards.
Uh, hey.
I was just driving by with
some baby stuff we didn't need
and, uh, well, here's some
diapers Maggie's too big for,
and an incredible educational
toy I forgot to give Bart.
Thanks.
Hey, could you
babysit for an hour?
I've been alone with
the baby for days.
Wow, I'd love to help, but I did
kind of have plans for tonight.
MOE: No, you can't leave.
I'm dealin' you in.
- (grunts)
- (screams)
Full house? You win again?
I think I'll be good tonight
and stay in with you.
♪ Baby, baby, please
let me hold him ♪
Where's Hoju?
(screams)
Where's Hoju?!
♪ We want to make him stay
up all night ♪ (sobbing)
♪ Yeah, we do.
♪
(song ends)
♪ Itchy and Scratchy show.
♪ A child arrived
just the other day ♪
♪ He came to the world
in the usual way ♪
♪ But there were planes
to catch ♪
♪ And bills to pay
♪ He learned to walk
while I was away ♪
♪ And he was talking
'fore I knew it ♪
♪ And as he grew, he'd say,
"I'm gonna be like you, Dad" ♪
♪ "You know I'm gonna
be like you" ♪
♪ And the cat's
in the cradle... ♪
(explosion, music stops)
Kids blow up so fast.
(Homer humming)
- Oh!
- Homie?
Aw, you're shopping
ahead for Maggie.
Oh, no, I'm shopping for Homer Jr.,
a baby I delivered in an elevator
the night I pretended to go to
work but was really playing poker.
What?!
(grunting)
This simulation has been
brought to you by your brain,
a subsidiary of your penis.
Oh, yes, I'm shopping for
Maggie, our baby together,
so this looks
perfectly innocent.
Why are you saying that?
Oh, you know how the
first few weeks are:
sleep deprived, walking
around in a fog.
First few weeks of what?
Um, November.
(groans)
(grunting, low chatter)
Hey, Atomette.
I want to say... Caitlin?
Lisa. Guys, do you realize you're
being exploited by this team?
ALL:
Wha...?
They sell your posters,
workout DVDs,
and all of your practices
are broadcast on a webcam.
And some of the angles...
are low.
But don't worry, collective bargaining
will enable us to secure concessions.
Uh, we're gonna push 'em back,
push 'em back, push
'em way, way back.
All the way to a new contract.
'Cause union power is a fact.
And we're...
Okay, okay, we get it.
Well, look who's here.
You been hit by the
cheerleading bug, little lady?
Actually, I've been hit by the
unfair labor practices bug.
What? Why, that's
Samuel Gompers talk.
Now, little missy, the only
thing you should be organizin'
is your dollies.
How? By size, brand, value?
And don't even suggest race,
'cause I don't see that.
I just see little people I own.
What do you say, ladies?
(indistinct whispering)
Not right, not fair. Let's
say it with our hair.
Okay, fine.
I'm gonna give it some thought, then
say no in the nicest way possible.
No.
Oh, good.
Nice.
"Beat Dallas."
Can never argue with that.
Hey, ladies. My vest isn't the
only thing that's ripped.
I am in the market for
a backup mistress.
Possibly two.
Have you kids seen your father?
Surprised he's not here
ogling these girls.
- He said he was going to work.
- On a Friday afternoon?
(gasps)
I bet he's playing poker again.
Coming through.
Wife on a mission.
Go, fight, win. Marge.
Wow, I've never burst
through a banner before,
but it really does the trick.
(pounding on door)
Homer, I know you're here.
Your car's outside.
- Where is he?
- I honestly don't know.
I'm just teaching myself massage here
with online videos and a store mannequin.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
So, do you have any injuries
I should know about? Oh!
Hmm, if he's not in
there, where is he?
HOMER:
Oh, baby.
Oh, baby, shake it. Homer like.
(gasps)
Oh.
Shake it. Now, roll over on your
tummy, just like I taught you.
Tell me what a cow says.
(toy moos)
Aah!
My other baby mama.
So this is where
you've been going.
Another woman's apartment.
Marge, it's not what you think.
Quiet. You're
upsetting Homer Jr.
(quietly): You have
a baby together?
Oh, it's cool. We did
it in an elevator.
(gasps)
I'm a Schwarzenegger wife.
But you're also the
housekeeper, so it's all good.
It's not good.
None of it's good.
I haven't had a
drink for a week.
That is pretty good.
So then you delivered her baby
right there in the elevator.
It's true. Even the other guy in
the elevator... he's right here.
And the really funny
thing is I'm a doctor.
Well, I'm glad you
did a good deed,
but you shouldn't
come here again.
I thought that was strange
poop on your collar.
(moans sadly)
Good-bye, Homer Jr. I guess
you're the man of the house now.
And never forget, even though the
mortgage is due on the first,
you can usually
wait till the 17th.
(sobbing)
You know what?
I think it's fine if Homer spends
a few hours now and then with...
Homer Jr.
Exactly.
You always said charity
begins at home.
But not which home.
It's true, I never
specified the home.
♪ There's a great and
a bloody fight ♪
♪ 'Round this whole
world tonight ♪
♪ And the battle, the bombs
and shrapnel reign ♪
♪ Hitler told the world around
♪ He would tear
our union down ♪
♪ But our union's gonna
break them slavery chains ♪
♪ Our union's gonna break
them slavery chains ♪
(tires screeching)
♪ I walked up on a mountain
in the middle of the sky ♪
♪ Could see every
farm and every town ♪
♪ I could see all the people
in this whole wide world ♪
♪ That's the union that'll tear
the fascists down, down, down. ♪
Now to sing you a lullaby
my father sung to me.
♪ Sleep, sleep, sleep,
sleep, sleep ♪
♪ Sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep,
sleep, sleep, sleep. ♪
(snoring softly)
Oh, man, I really
overdid it tonight.
Late night at Moe's, eh?
No, I'm exhausted from
♪ Head, shoulders, knees and
toes, knees and toes. ♪
It's the toes that get you, Marge.
It's the toes.
What about your own children?
Way ahead of you, Marge, I'm taking all
four of my kids to the zoo tomorrow.
Three.
Yes, we'll be back by 3:00. Homer
has a very tight nap schedule.
Quit talking about that baby.
I was talking about myself
in the third person.
Oh.
We can't take
much more of this, Lisa.
The girls are getting so antsy
they'll cheer anything.
You're the greatest generation,
worthy of our veneration.
Go Grampa!
If this is heaven, why
don't my shoes match?
(doorbell rings)
(deep sigh)
Okay, I give up.
I'm gonna do what we
secretly did at the Alamo...
surrender.
(cheering)
While you're at it, how about a
little boost for peanut vendors?
What do you think I'm
taking their raise out of?
(jabbering happily)
I wanted you all to be happy together,
so I brought you to the zoo
where all the animals
live in harmony.
(growls)
(triumphant wail)
Okay, guys, I got
your ice creams.
Hey, ah, ah, ah.
Now, Maggie, we don't hurt
each other in this family.
Are you nuts?
You can't even kiss me good night
without slicing me with your stubble.
Why you little...
I'll give you a good-night
kiss you'll never forget.
Come here, you.
- (grunting)
- Aah, ooh, ah!
- Ah! Ow!
- Yeah!
Dad, we're missing the giant
capybaras of Uruguay.
Okay, I know what'll
cheer you kids up.
Seeing me out-monkey
the monkeys.
(hooting like a monkey)
(angry hooting, screeching)
I have a soul and
you guys don't.
(hooting)
Aah! Monkeys!
(grunts)
(angry grunt)
Dad, Maggie's rolling away.
(gasps) She's heading for
Prairie Dog Village.
If they get her in their warrens,
we'll never see her again.
(chittering)
Look, shiny keys.
Jingle jangle.
(grunts, laughs)
Stupid monkeys.
That's it, Maggie,
use the Dino-Wand.
This is the last time you'll
see that elevator baby.
I'm sorry, Homer Jr.
You'll occupy an idealized place in my
heart that no one can ever quite fill.
(Homer sobbing)
- Therapy, please.
- Me, too.
(Marge grunts)
Okay, I've got to impart all my
fatherly advice in this one walk.
The sky is blue, but
nobody really knows why.
Don't believe
what they tell you.
Girls are great and terrible
at the same time.
Get used to it.
And, most importantly... Oops, we're here.
You'll have to figure it out on your own.
Sorry, little fella.
One day I'll be that guy
who comes to your wedding,
makes you feel a little weird,
and then runs away.
Homer, great news.
Chase came back.
(whoops)
- Who's Chase?
- Homer Jr.'s father.
Oh, my God, is that my son?
You didn't tell me
he was a soldier.
you were pregnant.
I didn't want you to marry
me because I was pregnant.
I wanted you to marry me
because I was nagging you.
(fusses)
Um, he likes it if
you tickle his toes.
Dude, he's my kid.
He likes what I like.
But n-n-n-nurture.
Gretch, I think
he's got my calves.
He does, baby, he does.
Can I just say
good-bye to him quick?
Sure.
I guess this is it, little guy.
- Da-da.
- (gasps)
The most beautiful
words a father can hear.
- Da-da. Da-da.
- Oh.
Hey, one day you'll have
kids of your own.
I do.
Really? Then this is much
creepier than I thought.
Much.
Shouldn't have bet his door
if he didn't want to lose it.
(sighs)
Hi, Maggie. If you could talk, I know
you'd have a few choice words for me.
You want me to take
care of your dolly?
That's the sweetest thing any
baby has ever done for me.
Honey, you know where
the bottle opener is?
I think it's in the drawer.
Whoa, little dude. Where
did you learn that?
This is what we're
fighting for, babe.
(marching band playing
theme song )
HOMER: Hey, what's this marching
band have to do with Homer Jr.?
What?! There were cheerleaders
in our house and nobody told me?
(Homer moans)
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
Shh!