Here's the story
Of a fat cat
That no one
Really liked
His name is Monty
He's an old rat
And he's sleepin'
Bad tonight
Everybody hates me.
Sir, your personal chef
is here with your breakfast.
Voilà. One raisin,
wrinkles ironed and smoothed,
with one molecule of sugar.
Too sharp.
It could cut me to ribbons.
Release the hounds.
No, you need a wine pairing.
Cabernet, to bring out
my earthiness.
Cordon bleu!
Smithers,
I need real food.
Something that'll stick
to my rib.
What is that delicious smell?
This is my lunch.
My wife just gave me a salad,
but she said I could
choose my own dressing,
so I picked this hamburger.
Seems to be some sort of meat
with a slice
of James Lewis Kraft's
confectionary cheese on top
and a kind of catsup blended
with a well-naised egg
in the style of Mayon.
I'll never let go.
I must have more of these...
What do you call them?
Hamburgers.
You're eating people
from Hamburg?
I don't know. Maybe.
Sir, we need to be
cautious about this.
It's not healthy for a man
to double his weight
within a day.
Triple!
No...!
My heart!
This could be
my last moment on Earth.
If so, fire someone
and let me watch.
Someone who just bought a house.
Smithers.
Oh, thank God you're alive.
And famished.
Do they serve burgers
in this joint?
No, sir.
Eating meat could kill you.
No one lives forever.
Except Dick Cheney.
What's his deal?
Sir, you nearly died.
I nearly died?
How was the reaction?
Well, when they heard
you were dying...
He's alive.
People don't like me.
They really don't.
Why?
You've released the hounds
on nearly everyone in town, sir.
Everyone loves dogs, Smithers.
It must be something else.
If you're ready, come.
The cue will be life.
Smithers, this means that no one
will mourn me when I'm gone.
My only legacy
will be the extra radiation
on every drop of water on Earth.
- Don't give up, sir.
- No, I give up.
Don't give up.
- I give up.
- Don't give up.
I give up.
- Seriously,
Will you listen to me
for one minute?
Sir, I figured out a way
to add to your legacy
and extend your life.
The professor here
has used exotic plants
to develop what I think
is the healthiest, tastiest
meatless burger ever.
You could eat
as many as you want
and we can
sell them at a profit.
Not here. Not here, please.
I've told you about this.
Oh, do you know how Edison felt
on that incredible,
magical night?
When he invented the light bulb?
No.
The electric chair.
That's how I feel now.
Smithers, this could
change my legacy.
People have to like the person
who made them live longer.
They have to.
What are you saying, sir?
I'm going to make it
to what
I never thought possible...
Beloved after death.
Look at me, world.
We'll do a sneak preview
of your burger chain
and then a grand opening
of a thousand stores
across the country.
Now all we need is a name.
Excellent.
You've done it again, sir.
We're here to cover
the sneak preview
of our new sponsor,
X-Cell-Ent Burger.
I... I'm just getting word
Springfield Dam has ruptured
and water is roaring down.
We'll let the
sad news cover that.
I'm here live at...
He was a good reporter,
great parking spot.
But let's move on
from grief to beef.
The first paying customer
to taste the X-Cell-Ent Burger
will be...
Number 43.
That's me.
But I warn you,
I've had every plant-based meat
ever made.
Phony Baloney,
Not Wurst,
Faux Foie Gras,
Corned Beets On Rye,
and Ghost Beef.
Good luck pleasing me.
So, what do you think?
It tastes great!
And no animal has passed gas
in its making.
This burger
might just save the world.
Thank you.
You're letting me cut the line?
Oh, thank you.
I don't have to cook.
I can finally
teach Maggie to talk.
Thank you.
Thank you, thank you.
Praise, praise...
something I've craved
since I was a little boy.
I drew this picture
of you hugging me, Mummy.
I don't like art that lies.
Oh, and by the way,
your father's dead.
There's just
one more thing we need.
A spokesman.
If we find a regular slob
who loves it,
we can start a chain reaction.
Just like...
Nuclear fission?
Is that how that works?
Really?
Now to find our slob.
My card.
Smithers,
keep your nods to yourself.
Yes, sir.
Since we're using
a green screen,
do I have to be this high up?
- We need the chance of death.
- Before we film,
we need you
to sign this contract
stating that what you
publicly say about our product
is limited
to certain catchphrases.
Approved phrases limited to...
yes ve-gan,
I guaran-tree it,
abso-lettuce,
and the meat beater.
Every one of those
has two meanings.
Your ad guys are geniuses.
If I could be
a fly on the wall...
My kids!
Oh, I got to put
all these kids through garbage?
Now, listen,
if you break this contract,
we'll release the hounds, who will
bite you here, here, here and here.
And here in triplicate.
Okay, Homer, let's try a take.
Action.
They say I'm eating healthy.
They say I'm saving the planet.
But here is my secret,
it tastes like
it was scared to die.
The X-Cell-Ent Burger.
Coming soon
to a location near you.
The fate of the world
is in your mouth.
With all these commercials,
I'm afraid your father's
going to need bigger pants.
Alexa, do you have
any X-X-X-X
X-X-X-XL in stock?
I found XLN stock.
How much would you like to buy?
I don't know.
How's ten pairs?
Submitting order for
a thousand shares of XLN stock.
Please confirm.
- Confirm?
- Ignoring question mark.
Buy order executed.
Oh, no.
Maggie. I accidentally
bought X-Cell-Ent Burger stock.
Alexa, sell those stocks.
Ordering yellow socks.
You get everything wrong.
We'll switch to Siri.
Siri enabled.
You sound like Alexa.
X-Cell-Ent Burger.
Well, they seem
to be succeeding.
But I'd feel awful
if the stock went...
Up? It just went up.
We made money!
Seven hundred dollars!
What I could buy
with that money.
Now it's down. Down $200.
Up again.
Down again.
The grand opening's in a week,
sir, and the reviews
couldn't be better.
Smithers, I'm a hero.
Like that guy
who landed the plane safely.
Sully Sullenberger?
No, no, no, no.
Rudolf Hess.
Smithers, a toast.
On it, sir.
I think you've had enough, sir.
Yes. Yes.
I'll... I'll sleep it off.
If it goes up another ten cents,
we're a thousand dollars ahead.
We've never been
a thousand dollars ahead.
Never.
Tonight on Smartline.
The Burger Wars.
They won't give me a raise,
but they can blow the bank
on graphics like that.
Leading up
to its national rollout,
X-Cell-Ent Burger's success
is destroying its competitors,
who are trying to overcome
a terrific new product
with desperate publicity stunts.
Attempting to piggyback
on Burger King's success
by changing its name during
Pride Month to Burger Queer,
Krusty has introduced
his own product...
The L.G.B.T.Q.B.L.T.
How could a ploy
this cynical and shameless fail?
Mel, you're
three of those letters.
Where did I go wrong?
Your product is inferior.
Your marketing is offensive.
And you have more ex-wives
than franchise locations.
What happened to kiss-ass Mel
who was afraid of my shadow?
I joined an empowerment group
with the monkey
and the cue card guy.
Aw, geez.
My hero's a loser.
Mr. Burns is gonna
drive Krusty out of business,
unless we stop him.
No. Burns is doing
something good.
I know it in my gut.
The Earth is on his side.
Thank you.
I love you all.
Disperse them
before we get back.
Rubber bullets, if necessary.
It's so wonderful
to be be-liked.
Finally, I can join the club
that rejected me so many times.
Welcome, welcome.
All the other beloved
billionaires are here.
There's Warren Buffet,
there's Bill Gates...
And that's it.
Mark Zuckerberg,
you get out of here.
No!
You can't threaten me.
I know all about you.
You're currently single,
you haven't been poked
in five years,
and I love those pictures
from your vacation to Baja,
where we both know
your boyfriend dumped you.
Those were set to private.
Right. Private.
I think I know
what Burns is up to.
His so-called vegan burgers
contain... Wait for it.
Are you waiting?
Here it is, meat.
What are you saying?
All this time
I've been eating meat?!
Oh, no,
that's why I grew an inch.
Just a theory.
Do you believe that?
No. I just wanted
the rest of your burger.
I don't want to see
what's inside.
Nerd.
Yep.
Just as I thought.
He's using plants.
Aw, crap.
Not meat.
Burns is doing the right thing.
This is kind of scary,
like putting on
a wet bathing suit.
Wait a minute.
Those plants look unusual.
They're all endangered plants
from the Amazon rainforest.
We have to tell Burns.
He already knows.
He's evil.
No. I refuse to believe
that someone can't change
for the better,
even though I can't think
of a single example
of that ever happening.
- Mr. Burns?
- Yes, children.
What do you want?
We came
to tell you something
that's maybe
a little hard to hear.
I'm sorry to have to inform you
that your attempt to do good
is doing very, very bad.
Leave me alone.
Oh, for God's sake.
- Finally.
- Mr. Burns.
Release the hounds.
You mean these hounds?
Let's be clear, young lady.
I'm not going to listen to you.
I'm never
going to listen to you,
and I have
sophisticated technology
to ensure that happens.
Buy, buy, buy!
Then, when you hear
a rumor of trouble,
sell before anyone else!
I'll be out of here
in four months!
Oh, what happened to you?
Come over here.
What is it, baby?
We have to think of a way
to shut X-Cell-Ent Burger down.
But what about the shareholders?
What? Sharehol...
No, no, no!
More money for Marge.
Dad, you're my last hope.
Tomorrow's the national launch.
If X-Cell-Ent Burger succeeds,
by the year 2080,
the entire Amazon...
I'm talking
the lungs of the planet...
will be gone.
Lisa, I'm sorry
to put it on you,
but every generation
has its to-do list.
Yours is putting Miami
on stilts, inventing new bees,
and learning to peacefully
live with fire tornadoes.
You're not gonna
help fight Burns?
I've learned one thing in life.
Don't bite the bony,
withered claw that feeds you,
even if there's
delicious marrow inside.
What was this about again?
You won't help save the Earth.
No, I won't.
I don't know
how you sleep at night.
I sleep fine, little lady!
Cheesy McMayor!
Jack in the Bag!
Guys, my company
is doing something bad.
Should I tell the world?
Look what eating only
my own food has done to me.
Look at me!
You're a spokesman
For a franchise
That's clear-cutting
Left and right
You have sold out
All your values
I won't let you
Sleep tonight
Once again,
dreams have taught me
more than
all the books ever written.
I know what I have to do.
What's going on?
Why is everyone baring
- their teeth at me?
- They're smiling, sir.
They can't wait to see you.
Oh, just so I know,
to be considered good
I now have to continue
doing good things?
Yes.
That's why Jesus retired at 33,
without a fast-food franchise
to his name,
except maybe Chick-fil-A.
Well, let's get on with
my ascension into
sainthood, Smithers.
I'm gonna bring them down.
Are you sure?
Think of the shareholders.
For once, I say
damn the shareholders.
Simpson.
After the announcement,
there will be questions
from the audience,
but like our burgers,
the questioners will be
entirely made up of plants.
I'm ready.
And you do remember
your non-disclosure agreement?
I believe it said
something to the effect of...
I was limited
to certain words and phrases,
and I couldn't make obscene
gestures with my hands.
Or...
- Crotch.
- Excellent.
Excellent.
Mr. Simpson
will now take questions.
Yes. The little girl
in the mustache.
Thank you, sir.
Is it true
that X-Cell-Ent Burgers
are made of plants
from the rainforest?
Abso-lettuce.
And what are the chances
that your product will help lead
to the destruction
of the planet?
I guaran-tree it.
He's using legal loopholes
to tell us the truth.
A supersize admission
in the burger wars.
Have we been fed
an order of lies, or worse...
curly lies?
Good God, I'm hungry.
I did it again.
I won by doing nothing.
That's my hero.
Always will be.
Round up some more donkeys.
We're in
the burger business again.
Mom, I'm so conflicted.
You're conflicted?
I feel like someone who knew
a stock was about to crash,
sold it before that happened,
and kept a thousand dollars.
What are you saying?
Nothing.
Nothing, nothing.
This is the time
he really needs you
to look at him.
- Sir. You're happy.
- Yes.
Because I'm no longer
crushed by morality.
I gave it a nice go,
almost a full month...
but in the end,
evil always wins.
Would you like to go
to a school for the blind
and convince them
aliens have landed?
I'd like that.
You listened
To your conscience
And now you're
Feelin' fine
And you're dreamin'
Of me singin'
'Cause you drank
Two-dollar wine
Tell me when it hurts.
It hurt from the beginning!