♪ The Simpsons ♪
(chalk screeches)
(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(tires screeching)
(horn honks)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-(screams)
-(tires screech)
LISA:
Look, Dad, there's a spot.
D'oh!
Ohh, there's a spot, dear.
Ohh, there's a good one.
That spot says
"compact only."
Marge, that's just
a suggested car size.
(metal scraping)
Easy... easy...
How am I doing on the right?
Uh, we're getting a lot
of sparks over here, Dad.
Uh-huh.
Easy...
Perfect.
All right, everybody,
out the window.
HOMER:
Ooh! They all look great.
MARGE:
So, what are we going to see?
Ernest Cuts the Cheese!
Honey, I Hit a School Bus!
Look Who's Oinking!
Since we'll never agree.
Why don't you kids
pick a movie,
your dad and I
will pick a movie,
then we'll all meet
in the lobby later, hmm?
-KIDS: Thanks, Mom.
-(groans)
Two tickets for...
Let me guess.
Look Who's Oinking.
-That's right.
-Sold out.
Ohh...
Maybe we could
see something
a little more adult.
Why, Marge,
you frisky little devil.
(sexy growl)
We'll take two tickets to
The Stockholm Affair.
Ohh, the paper called it
a taut political thriller.
Political?
(groaning)
Mr. President, disturbing news.
Serious cracks are developing
in the Greco-Bolivian alliance.
Get me Jed Colic!
(slurping)
(gagging)
Oh, this movie's
too complicated.
Hey, the floor's sticky.
(grunting)
Who's that guy?
What did that guy say when
I said "who's that guy?"
(groaning)
Oh, that submarine
is so fake.
Look, you can see
the strings.
Ooh! An octopus!
-Shh!
-What?
(growling)
If you don't watch
the violence,
you'll never
get desensitized to it.
Just tell me when
the scary part's over.
It's over.
(squishy crunching)
(screaming)
(evil chuckling)
I think that guy's a spy.
(whispering)
Well, of course he's a spy.
You just saw him go
through spy school.
Oh wait,
I heard how this ends.
It turns out
the secret code
was the same nursery rhyme
he told his daughter.
(audience moaning)
Hey, it's pretty obvious
if you think about it.
Oh shut up, Homer.
No one wants to hear
what you think!
(audience cheers)
Homer, if it makes
you feel any better,
most of what
they threw at you
splattered on me.
Homer?
Forget it, Mom.
Dad's really mad.
The tendons are throbbing
at the base of his neck.
and stress is collecting
in the trouble spots--
here, here, and here--
making for one
unhappy pappy.
(growling)
Homie, aren't you
coming inside?
Marge, I have always
carried myself
with a certain
quiet dignity.
Tonight,
you robbed me of it.
I'm going now,
and I don't know when
you'll see me again.
(tires squealing)
(brakes screeching)
LISA:
I guess that executive stress ball
we got him for Christmas
isn't working.
Mmm.
(slurping)
(gasps)
(sniffing)
Eww, a skunk.
(inhales)
(straining)
(breathing in)
Oh, no!
-(country music playing)
-HOMER: Ooh, a redneck bar.
(loud saloon banter)
(glass breaking)
Hey, you, let's fight.
Them's fightin' words.
Duff, please.
We don't sell Duff.
We sell Fudd.
Okay, Fudd me.
MAN:
Alright, alright ladies and gentlemen
he's all healed up
and he's back for more.
Let's give a big drunken
welcome to Yodeling Zeke.
(audience cheering)
♪ Yodel-lay-hee ♪
♪ Odel-lay-hee... ♪
(playing sweet melody)
(crowd cheering)
Our next act is our very own
singing waitress-- Lurleen.
(crowd cheering)
So I'm afraid drink service
will stop for
just a few moments...
(shouting, glass breaking)
They're all yours.
Stupid Marge--
tell me to shut up.
Thank you.
Tonight I'd like to try
something a little different.
It's a song I wrote
while I was mopping up
your dried blood and teeth.
(playing upbeat melody)
♪ You work all day
for some old man ♪
♪ Sweat and break your back ♪
Yeah.
♪ Then you go home
to your castle ♪
♪ But your queen
won't cut you slack ♪
That's true.
♪ That's why you're losing
all your hair ♪
♪ That's why
you're overweight ♪
Uh-huh.
♪ That's why you flipped
your pickup truck ♪
♪ Right off the interstate ♪
That's right...
except for the pick-up truck.
♪ There's a line of bull
they hand you ♪
♪ There's nothing you can do ♪
♪ Your wife
don't understand you ♪
♪ But I do ♪
♪ No, your wife
don't understand you ♪
♪ But I do ♪
♪ I said,
no one understands you ♪
♪ But I do ♪
(smattering of applause)
Hey, Lurleen?
I've got to say
something to you.
I'm listening.
Your song touched me
in a way I've
never felt before.
And which way to the can?
So what's your name, stranger?
Homer J. Simpson.
My name's Lurleen Lumpkin.
-That's a pretty name.
-Oh, you think so?
Maybe. I'm not sure.
I forgot it.
Bye, Lurleen.
So long, Homer J. Simpson.
(Homer humming
"The Wabash Cannonball")
Hello.
Where were you all night?
I was just up at this bar
in Spittle County.
You should have called.
I was very worried.
Marge, let's end this
feudin' and a-fussin'
-and get down to some lovin'.
-Hmm!
♪ I work all day ♪
♪ For some old man ♪
♪ I sweat and break my back ♪
Doctor, you weren't supposed
to remove his gall bladder.
Put it back!
♪ Your wife
don't understand you ♪
♪ But I do ♪
Gee, Homer's singing
to his ball again.
-Yeah, and he's bowling a 280.
-Oh, yeah?
♪ There's a kind of hush ♪
♪ All over the world tonight ♪
(humming)
Hey, Moe,
you got any Fudd?
Fudd? I thought they
took that off the market
after all those hillbillies
went blind.
Oh no-- I went to this bar
the other night and...
W-wait a minute.
You went to another bar?
Moe, I was 100 miles
out of town.
Oh, Homer.
(playing banjo)
Well, if it isn't
Homer J. Simpson.
Lurleen, I can't get your song
out of my mind.
I haven't felt this way
since "Funky Town."
Oh, aren't you sweet.
Do you think I can get
a copy of it?
Sorry darlin'.
All my songs are up here--
"I'm Basting a Turkey
with My Tears,"
"Don't Look Up My Dress
Unless You Mean It,"
"I'm Sick of Your Lying Lips
and False Teeth."
Lurleen, we've got
to crack open your head
and scoop out those songs.
Ooh! I don't know.
-Come with me.
-Oh!
(guitar playing country music)
♪ I said no one
understands you ♪
♪ But I do ♪
Listen, ma'am,
my brother owns a radio
station over in Weevilville
and with your permission,
I'd like to take your CD to him.
Homer,
it's your quarter.
What do you say?
I guess so.
RADIO D.J.:
This is KUDD 570 AM.
Hey, don't touch that dial.
You've got KUDD on it.
LURLEEN:
♪ You work all day for some old man ♪
♪ Sweat and break
your back... ♪
For the next half hour,
beer's on the house.
-What did you say, Moe?
-Nothing.
I thought I told you
to stay away
from my sister!
♪ But your queen
won't cut you slack ♪
Oh, here's 50 bucks.
Take her to the Copa.
♪ Now you talk so tough
and act so rough... ♪
It's payback time.
♪ The heartache
and the sadness ♪
♪ That's buried
deep inside ♪
Aww...
Puts this whole riot
into perspective, doesn't it?
♪ No one understands you,
but I do ♪
She's wonderful.
I could feel her sweet country soul
in every digitally encoded bit.
Country music sucks.
All it does is take precious air
space away from shock deejays
whose cruelty and profanity
amuse us all.
Shut up, boy.
Marge, what do you think?
Well, it's nice,
but who is this woman?
Well, right now she's an
out-of-work cocktail waitress,
but she's going to be
a country music superstar,
like, uh, that jerk
in the cowboy hat,
and that dead lady.
I don't like you hanging around
some cocktail waitress.
Marge, you make it
sound so seamy.
All I did was spend
the afternoon in her trailer
watching her try on
some outfits.
(growling)
(ringing)
Well, hi, Lurleen.
We were just talking about you.
Uh, I think I can come over.
Let me ask my wife.
(angry groaning)
It's a date.
Oh, Homer.
Everybody's been calling--
Mama, Daddy, the triplets,
Vonda Mae, Piney Joe...
and I owe it all to you.
Don't thank me, Lurleen.
You should be thanking
your brain.
Oh, wow, Homer.
No man has ever been
this nice to me without...
you know, wanting
something in return.
Well, I was going to ask
for a glass of water,
but now I feel kinda
guilty about it.
(chuckling)
Homer, you're just a big sack of sugar.
Thanks.
You did say "sugar," right?
Uh-huh.
Now, Homer,
I want you to be my manager.
Really?
Well, I should warn you,
-I'm not great with figures.
-That's okay.
I make a lot of
stupid decisions.
Nobody's perfect.
-I did bad in school.
-I didn't even go.
My personal hygiene has
been described as--
Homer, Homer,
you'll be a great manager.
There's only
one thing you need.
Now, this is made from
a space-age fabric
developed especially
for Elvis.
Sweat actually cleans
this suit.
Hmm.
(growling)
(footsteps approaching)
(door opening)
Marge, look at me.
I don't want to--
I'm mad at you.
I'm sick of that waitress and
all the time you've been spending with her
and this whole
country music thing.
Then maybe you'd better
not look at me.
(gasps)
Homer, where did you
get that suit?
A friend bought it for me.
Was it Lurleen?
-No. I think it was Lenny.
-Don't lie to me.
-Are you having an affair with this woman?
-No!
-Have you kissed her?
-Has she kissed you?
-A couple of times.
I want you
to stop seeing her.
I can't-- I'm her manager.
Her manage--
That's ridiculous.
I won't allow you
to spend any more time
away from your family.
Marge, you're standing
in the way of my boyhood dream
of managing a beautiful
country singer!
Your boyhood dream was to eat
the world's biggest hoagie,
and you did it at the county
fair last year, remember?
Marge, Lurleen's gonna
be a big success,
and whether you like it or not,
I'm going to be there.
Fine. See if I care!
(footsteps, door slams)
(sniffling)
MAN: This studio has
a lot of history.
Buddy Holly stood on
this spot in 1958 and said,
"There is no way in hell that
I'm gonna record in this dump."
I'm sure Lurleen
will love it.
(gasps) Homer, how much
did you just give that man?
Calm down, Marge.
It's just our life savings.
I'm not going to go
into hock for this.
Hey, Colonel Homer.
And you must be...
Mrs. Homer Simpson.
Charmed.
Hmm.
I thought you said
she was overweight.
Marge, it takes
two to lie:
one to lie
and one to listen.
What does that mean?
I don't have time to answer
all these questions.
Time is money.
Come on, people.
Well, come on, boys.
Let's break some hearts.
(fast country music)
♪ Oh, the bases were empty
on the diamond of my heart ♪
♪ When the coach called me up
to the plate ♪
♪ I'd been swingin'
and missin' ♪
♪ At lovin' and kissin' ♪
♪ My average was
point double ought eight ♪
♪ So I spit on my hands ♪
♪ Knockin' dirt
from my spikes ♪
♪ And pointed
right towards center field ♪
♪ This time
I'm hittin' a home run ♪
♪ This time love is for real ♪
Hey, Dad, can I do
a hambone solo?
Stop it.
♪ ...for you ♪
♪ I been slumpin' all season ♪
♪ But now I found a reason ♪
♪ I struck on a love
that is true ♪
♪ I used to play the field ♪
♪ I used to be a roamer ♪
♪ But season's
turnin' around for me now ♪
♪ I finally bagged me
a Homer... ♪
That's right.
♪ I finally bagged me a Homer ♪
Lurleen, we're gonna have
to cut you off.
We're getting some kind of
grinding noise on the track.
(grinding)
♪♪
You, off the bench.
HOMER:
Guess what, Lurleen.
I got you a gig on TV.
Oh, Homer, you're as smart
as you are handsome.
Hey! Oh, you meant that
as a compliment.
Now, on this show they want you
to sing two songs.
Maybe we should give them
something new.
Well, I have been working
on something
that could really
heat things up.
Let's hear it.
(playing slow ballad)
♪ In this trailer ♪
♪ I get so cold
and lonely ♪
♪ Lyin' there
awake at night ♪
♪ Muttering, "If only
you weren't married" ♪
♪ So I might ask you
to bunk with me tonight ♪
♪ Bunk with me tonight,
oh, bunk with me tonight ♪
♪ I'm asking will you bunk
with me tonight ♪
Oh, that's hot.
There isn't a man alive
who wouldn't get turned on
by that.
Well, good-bye.
Uh, Homer, there's a hidden
message to this song
that you
may have missed.
Really listen.
♪ Bunk with me tonight ♪
-Uh-huh.
-♪ Bunk with me tonight ♪
-Right.
-♪ I'm asking ♪
♪ Will you bunk ♪
♪ With me ♪
♪ Tonight? ♪
(gasps)
Lurleen!
That's right, Homer J.
I got to think about this.
MARGE: All our money's
tied up in this woman.
If she fails, we're broke.
If she succeeds,
I have no husband.
I don't know what to root for.
You don't?
I got to go.
Homer?
Later, Marge.
Lurleen's on TV tonight.
I got to get ready.
(grunting)
Just so you know--
while you and Lurleen
were out judging
that greased pig contest,
Maggie cut her first tooth.
That's great, honey.
Say, have you seen
my rattlesnake hatband?
You're not even
listening to me.
Sure they will.
Kids, will you come in here?
You've got
a wonderful family, Homer.
Please don't forget it when
you walk out that door tonight.
Uh, I got to go.
As much as I hate
that man right now,
you got to love that suit.
ANNOUNCER:
Hold on to your pitchforks, everybody.
It's time again for Ya Hoo!
Starring,
in alphabetical order...
Yodeling Zeke,
Butterball Jackson,
Freddie Boy and Yuma,
Cloris Moselle,
Big Shirtless Ron,
Orville and Hurley,
Gappy Mae,
Hip Diddler,
Rudy,
the Ya Hoo Recovering
Alcoholic Jug Band,
and tonight, in her syndicated
TV debut-- Lurleen!
(fast country music)
♪ Oh, the bases
were empty... ♪
Excuse me, are you
Colonel Homer Simpson?
Yes, I am.
I'm from Rebel Yell Records,
a division of Togasake Corporation.
I'm interested in buying
Lurleen's contract.
Forget it, pal.
They don't call me
Colonel Homer
because I'm some
dumb-ass Army guy.
Lurleen, they loved you.
Well thank you. I'm still a little itchy
from that fiberglass hay.
Is there anything you need?
(slams and locks door)
Well, you could make
my evening complete.
What's wrong?
My whole romantic life
is flashing before my eyes.
(making kissing noises)
Gross!
Thanks for dinner.
Ow!
No!
At least, could I
have my dollar--
I'll love you
for the rest of my life.
I'm sorry, Lurleen.
All I wanted to do was
share your beautiful voice
with other people,
and I've done that.
Now, I'd better
get out of here
before I lose my family.
Just so I don't wonder--
you would have gone all the way
with me, wouldn't ya?
Uh-huh.
Ooh... okay.
Now before we negotiate,
I have to tell you
I'm desperate
to unload Lurleen
and I'll take any offer.
I'll give ya 50 bucks.
You son of a--
Sold.
I caught my wife in bed
with my best friend.
You bitter?
Yep. Bit him too.
(laughing)
Ow!
And now, once again-- Lurleen.
-(door opens)
-Homer?
Is there any room in that bed
for a dad-burned fool?
Always has been.
Now I'd like to play a song
I wrote just this minute.
It's called
"Stand By Your Manager."
♪ His name is Homer ♪
♪ He's quite a man ♪
♪ I tried to kiss him ♪
♪ But Homer ran ♪
♪ Sure wish I could say ♪
♪ That I was his ♪
♪ I hope that Marge knows ♪
♪ Just how lucky she is ♪
I do.
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.