(SlNGlNG) The Simpsons
(SCHOOL BELL RlNGlNG)
(HORN BELLOWlNG)
(PLAYlNG DlFFERENT TUNE)
(TlRES SCREECHlNG)
D'oh !
(SCREAMlNG)
(BRAKES SCREECHlNG)
(GROANS)
(HUMMlNG RING OF FIRE)
(SlNGlNG) Time to wizz
in a foaming bowI
of china
(EXCLAlMS) A line
for the bathroom?
What gives?
l don't know.
But whoever's in there
is taking their
sweet ol' time.
Son, can l have cuts?
No!
Back cuts?
Okay.
Sweet.
Hey!
Wait a minute.
lf we're all out here,
who's in there?
(ALL GASP)
Maggie's locked inside!
Now calm down.
l'll just unlock it
with this coat hanger.
Oh, God ! lt's baby blood !
Don't worry.
l know just what to do.
(GROANlNG)
Bart, you're not
hitting hard enough !
How did you get her out?
l tried
the coat hanger again.
l don't understand
why we only try ideas once.
(DOORBELL RlNGlNG)
The door? Now l'll
never get to pee.
Dr. Hibbert?
ls someone seriously ill?
Oh, l wish !
(LAUGHS)
No, l'm here because of
Bob Poochioni over there.
(GRUNTS lN CONFUSlON)
Two months ago,
Santa's Little Helper
paid a bootie call
to my purebred poodle,
Rosa Barks.
(CHUCKLES)
And he had his
eyes on her prize.
l'm gonna drop
that analogy now.
ALL: Aw!
Well, l'm glad you
think they're cute
because they're
your problem now!
You just lost a box, pal !
Wait. Santa's Little Helper
had puppies before.
And then
we got him neutered.
We did. Homer took him.
Didn't you?
Yeah. . . Well. . .
Funny thing about that,
on our way to the cIinic,
I decided to give him
a night his wang
wouId never forget.
So let's dance
the last dance
Let's dance
this Iast dance tonight
Last dance
Last dance for love
Wanna play some air hockey?
Three hundred and
fifty dollars an hour.
You're on !
l can't neuter you, boy.
Not after all
we've been through.
But from now on,
you better save
your lovin' for
the couch cushions.
(CHUCKLES)
(GRUNTS)
You broke our deal !
We had an oral contract!
Stop it! Stop it, stop it!
You and Lisa
better go find homes
for these puppies.
And don't just
dump them all off
on some crazy lady.
(SPEAKlNG GlBBERlSH)
(WHlMPERlNG)
He's an irritable,
walleyed, misfit, bastard !
Just like Willie.
Hey, mister,
would you like a puppy?
No. But l'll take one!
Okay.
l'm going to cherish
and care for this dog.
And there's nothing
you can do to stop me!
(LAUGHS)
(TlRES SCREECHlNG)
Seen it. . . Bad. . . Boring. . .
Saw it on the plane. . .
Rerun. . . Rerun. . .
Telemundo. . . Me. . .
Turned it down. . . ABC. . .
Banned from
the set. . . Lame. . .
Lame. . . Regis. . .
(GROANS)
Let's see,
champagne or Slim Fast?
Boy, that really
passes the time.
(KNOCKlNG AT DOOR)
Want a puppy?
He's at the peak
of cuteness.
(CHUCKLES)
You could nuzzle me
all night.
That's enough.
l said that's enough !
Well, look at this.
You dragged me back
to my old neighborhood !
And it hasn't changed a bit.
DSL! DSL! Who will buy
my high-speed connections?
Brazilian wax!
Get your velvety smooth,
Hey, the Jewish
Walk of Fame!
Here, go on Sandy Koufax.
l lost ten grand
when he wouldn't pitch
on Yom Kippur!
l did five shows that night!
Okay, boy.
Let's find my star.
(WHlMPERlNG)
Albert Einstein,
Lorne Michaels?
Shari Lewis? Lamb Chop!
Why ain't l here?
l'm a bigger name than. . .
Chaim Potok! What is he?
Some kind of Klingon?
l'm gonna get to
the bottom of this.
Well, of course
you deserve a star, Krusty.
Let me just ask
you a few questions.
Full name?
Herschel Pinchas
Yoracham Krustofski.
Good, good. Circumcision?
And then some!
(CHUCKLES)
Date of Bar Mitzvah?
Well, l, uh. . .
You see, the truth is. . .
l never had one.
No Bar Mitzvah?
ln the eyes of God
and the Springfield Jewish
Walk of Fame Committee,
you are not a Jewish man !
Now see here!
Do you know how much
l donate to the B'nai B'rith?
Actually, l do.
Goodbye.
Krusty, what's wrong?
l just found out
l'm not Jewish.
Oh, l was turned down
by all those country clubs
for nothing !
Well, you're still my hero.
So what?
Everything's changed.
l thought l was
a self-hating Jew!
But it turns out,
l'm just a plain
old anti-Semite!
We have so much to discuss.
(GROANS)
Now l know the reason
my life is so empty.
l never had a Bar Mitzvah.
Cheer up, Krusty.
You're a clue
in the PeopIe magazine
crossword puzzle.
What more can a man want?
Bart, the Bar Mitzvah
is the most
important event
in a Jewish boy's life.
lt's when
he reads from the Torah
and becomes a man.
The sweet little
shikse's right.
Without a Bar Mitzvah,
l'm just a boy
with a prostate
the size of a goat's head !
Krusty, your dad's a rabbi.
How could you not
have had a Bar Mitzvah?
Who knows? l've lived
so hard, there's big gaps
in my memory.
l remember learning
to ride a bike,
then pretty much
nothing till right now.
Why don't we ask your dad?
Yeah, right!
My father will put this
in a spiritual,
philosophical context.
l'll tell you why
you didn't have
a Bar Mitzvah.
lt's because you're a puts.
Everything is a joke to you.
l was afraid
you'd make a mockery
out of the whole ceremony,
like you're making a mockery
out of me right now.
Maybe l am
but you can't argue
with the laughs.
So what?
lt's not my job
to make kids laugh.
Yes, it is.
You're a clown.
Oh, without a Bar Mitzvah,
l'm nothing !
(SOBBlNG)
Krusty, you can still
have your Bar Mitzvah,
as an adult.
That'd be great.
Are you sure that's kosher?
There's nothing
in the Talmud
that forbids it.
How do you know
all this stuff?
l have a Jewish
imaginary friend.
Her name is Rachel Cohen
and she just
got into Brandeis.
Wonderful !
Hey, hey, kids!
l got a confession to make.
Underneath all
this plastic surgery,
l am actually a Jew!
And from now on,
l'm embracing my faith !
(CHEERlNG)
What's not to like?
Now l'll teach
you my traditions,
the way my people
have passed them
down for centuries,
through animation !
(READlNG BLESSlNG lN HEBREW)
(SCREAMS)
(LAUGHS)
(GROANlNG)
Mouse-l Tov!
And that's what
l believe in now!
(LAUGHlNG)
Krusty, that was
a great show!
Once l was clapping
and the applause sign
wasn't even on !
Hey, that's great.
But l got a problem.
This schedule has me
working on Saturdays.
That's the Sabbath !
Well, we could tape
two shows on Friday.
Are you nuts?
l can barely get through
one show on Friday!
Even with the. . .
(lNHALlNG)
You know, smelling flowers?
Such expensive flowers,
filled with remorse.
Anyway, we gotta book
a guest host!
How about Jon Stewart?
He's a son,
a lover and a pundit
rolled into one sexy package!
(GROWLS)
He'd be perfect!
So forget it!
l need a guest host so bad,
he can never replace me.
l need someone
who's not intelligent.
Not good-looking.
(EXCLAlMS)
And so utterly
repellent, he. . .
l'm your man !
Man, are you unpleasant!
You're in !
(DOOR CLOSES)
Children, l wish to
announce that our show
has undergone a reformatting.
(CHEERlNG)
Let's get ready
to listen quietly!
Now tonight's guest host,
the ultimate placeholder,
Homer Simpson !
Welcome to
The Homer Simpson Show.
l'm your host, next card.
Homer Simpson,
it's great to be here in,
next card.
Springfield,
my guests are Moe Szyslak,
local businessman,
Carl Carlson, raconteur,
and Lenny Leonard,
three-time juror.
Gentlemen,
what's on your mind?
Dad, you have
to say something.
Something meaningful.
You ever notice how seats
are too small for normal
looking guys like me?
Theaters, airplanes?
Why even here! Look!
(GRUNTlNG)
l could not agree more.
Never go on the teacup ride
after eating at
Beauty and the Beast's
Fried Dough Chateau.
Hey, I got a question.
How come oldies stations
are aIways pIaying
the same song?
How about some
new oIdies, geniuses?
Boy, these guys are
right on the money.
Yeah. My neck is sore
from agreeing so much.
Hey, baby! (MlMlCS KlSSlNG)
You looking for
a good time, huh?
Go home,
turn on your television,
Channel Six.
Thanks for the tip!
(BEEPlNG)
Yeah, yeah, twins.
l get it. Now let's watch
something l'm really
interested in.
Who has more power?
Miss America or Miss USA?
l think
one's elected and the
other one's appointed.
l think your water
just broke.
Will you be quiet?
Now you can't
mix milk and meat.
You got that?
And on Christmas Day,
you must eat Chinese food,
and pork is
strictly forbidden !
Oh-oh !
All these rules! l feel
like l'm in a strip club!
Well, Dad,
what do you want to
talk about tonight?
Hmm. . .
Listen, Homer,
l'd like to raise an issue.
Why so formal, Lenny?
You're my go-to guy.
Oh, about that.
You know,
l've been with this show
from the beginning
and l was, uh. . .
l was wondering
if l could get a small cost
of living raise?
lnteresting.
Please welcome new panelist,
Barney Gumble.
That light's a little bright.
You think you can move it?
Please welcome
our newest panelist,
Disco Stu.
Disco Stu knows his place.
My husband's
a power-mad star.
Maybe now we can get
that padding that
goes under rugs.
(SPEAKlNG HEBREW)
Very good.
You just earned yourself
a Dr. Brown's.
Krusty, you know Diane, Stu,
and Jeremy from the network.
Hey, hey.
Hey, hey. Hey, hey.
Krusty, we've got
some bad news.
We think you're
super talented. . .
Oh, God !
You're canceling me!
Krusty, Krusty,
TV is a fickle business.
You've had a good run.
But Homer Simpson's
a fresh face and. . .
You're not doing
this fast enough !
You're fired, too!
l'm. . . No!
(SOBBlNG)
Simpson, l hate
to bother you
when you're eating
but you're always eating.
Will you sign
an autograph for my boy?
My pleasure.
l eat Legos.
So did l, son.
And look where l am today.
Boy, everybody loves my show.
lt's great, Dad.
You have tremendous power.
And now it's time
to put it to use.
Yes, you're right.
Duck, Mister Lincoln !
Thank you, Homer.
No, Dad. l mean,
you should use
your time on the air
to say things that
really mean something.
Change the world
for the better.
l say live fast, die young,
and leave a big fat corpse!
Well, l took
Bart's advice last week,
so l guess it's Lisa's turn.
Now if you'll excuse me. . .
You hit him high !
l'll hit him low!
(GRUNTlNG)
(LAUGHlNG)
Look, since my
own network dumped me,
l thought
maybe l could do a show
on (GROWLS) Fox.
l'm sorry, Krusty.
People aren't
interested in stars anymore.
They want reality.
Way ahead of ya.
How about a show
where girls think
l'm a millionaire?
But what they don't know
is l'm rife with disease!
Okay, okay. How about one
where l move in
with a poor family
and laugh at them?
(LAUGHS) You see be. . .
Okay, how about
you televise my
Bar Mitzvah? Live.
Please, you people are known
for taking chances on crap.
You know,
we've had a great time
on this show
riffing on small,
unimportant subjects.
Now wait a minute.
Dirty words you can
spell on your calculator
is a very important subject.
"Boobs."
(LAUGHS)
Just like what girls got.
Well, that's all over now.
From now on, we will focus
solely on important issues.
Every year, the gulf
between rich and poor
nations gets larger.
Yet the lMF insists
on unrealistic debt
repayment schedules.
This show stinks!
l knew my son would blow it!
Where's the remote?
Oh, it might as well
be in China.
MAN: Live from
Springfield Stadium,
it's Krusty the Clown's
Wet 'N' Wild Bar Mitzvah!
Shalom, Springfield!
Shalom.
I can't schmear you!
Shalom!
(SlNGlNG GlBBERlSH)
Now to get you in
the Bar Mitzvah mood,
put your hands together for
the Beach Boys Experience!
(SlNGlNG) Mezuzah, menorah
Reading from the Torah
Pastrami, knishes,
on two sets of dishes
A church with no steepIe
for God's chosen people
Now let's meet
a man who's muscle-bound
and a man who's bound
not to eat mussels,
Mr. T and Krusty the Clown!
T, l haven't seen you
since we roasted Chevy Chase!
Yeah. We were
kind of rough on him.
l feel bad for the guy.
You pitied the fool?
That's one way of putting it.
Time for me to
get into character.
Let's scroll !
Baruch adonai
hamvorach, fool !
Why should America
consume 90 % of
the world's resources?
Argentina must
devalue her currency
to pay her debts!
(SOBBlNG)
You can't leave.
l'm your ride home!
Dad, you blew it.
You listened to Lisa
and then you lost your
stranglehold on the audience.
l'll audience you !
(CHOKlNG)
So that's why Bart has
all those broken
tracheal bones.
Tight bow tie, my ass!
Now Iadies and gentIemen,
put your hands together
for the world's
Iargest potato pancake!
That's a lot of latke!
(GRUNTlNG)
Three, two, one,
and you're canceled !
Strike the set.
You have five minutes
to get off the lot.
Oh. . .
Don't worry. This will be
quick and painless.
There we go.
Oh. . .
Homie. You may have
lost your show
but you went out
in the classiest
way possible.
l'm proud of you.
Marge, l thank God
every day you settled for me.
Hey, where's my car?
Oh, over there.
(SOBBlNG)
Come on, Homie.
We'll go to the
make-your-own-sundae place.
Will you make
my sundae for me?
Yes.
Thank you,
cast of The Lion King.
And now for our
grand finale,
the superstar
of David, Mr. T!
l pity the shuI that
won't let Krusty in now!
Spin me, clown !
(LAUGHS)
l wish l had
invested my money better.
(LAUGHlNG)
Mmm. . .
Krusty, the ratings were good.
Raymond re-run good.
Great. But there's one thing
that's still nagging at me.
l want a real
Bar Mitzvah in a temple.
Wonderful.
(SPEAKlNG HEBREW)
l'm hungry.
Are they married yet?
They're not getting married.
Then whose garter is this?
l was trying to
hit the dentist.
And now, finally, l am a man.
l pity the fool
who didn't bring
an envelope to
this Bar Mitzvah.
English - US - PSDH