BART:
Trick-or-treat!
♪ On this filthy night of evil ♪
♪ Little gaudy beggars stroll ♪
♪ As they lure ghouls,
ghosts and goblins ♪
♪ Hungry for their innocent souls ♪
♪ There is a hellish breeze a-groanin' ♪
-♪ As the children they pursue ♪
-(witch cackling)
♪ You can hear their bellies moanin' ♪
♪ They might even gnaw on you ♪
♪ But ruler of this sordid host ♪
♪ More ghastly than them all ♪
♪ Lurks a ravenous beastly monster ♪
♪ More than 25 feet tall ♪
(Lisa screams)
♪ He's dirty and he's hairy ♪
♪ And his mouth tastes just like crap ♪
♪ Like you, he's trick-or-treating for ♪
♪ Some candies to unwrap ♪
♪ The Lord abhors your foul disguise ♪
♪ You thought to cloak your sin ♪
♪ But now you've lured
this fiend from hell ♪
♪ Who craves your soul within ♪
♪ He's hungry for your vitals ♪
♪ He likes you moist and ripe ♪
♪ And should he find you
spiced with sin ♪
♪ Then you're his favorite type ♪
♪ He'll chew your juicy insides ♪
♪ Masticate you till you're pulp ♪
♪ Every little soul he'll swallow ♪
♪ With a stinky-ass gulp ♪
Ow!
♪ ♪
(laughs)
There's no such thing as ghosts,
you dumb kids!
(gasps)
(bellowing)
(screaming)
And now it's time for the cartoon.
STUDENTS:
13!
14!
(retching)
We have a winner!
14 spins, and Wendell threw up!
I didn't throw up, I held it in.
(retches)
No winner!
House keeps the money!
(phone chimes)
Oh, man, I got to see this.
(groans)
(violin playing sad song)
Huh.
Mr. Largo?
Hmm, something's wrong.
That music is in tune.
Hello, Bart.
(screams) Sideshow Bob!
'Twas I who texted you!
Using Milhouse's phone.
Did you know his wallpaper
is American Girl doll?
Now let me put this in terms
any young boy would understand:
you and I have danced
a grand pas de deux
worthy of Nijinsky.
But this is the final plié!
Yawn. You couldn't kill me
with that thing
if I drew an "X" on my forehead.
♪ Bob and his spear gun ♪
♪ Sittin' in a tree ♪
♪ S-U-C-K-I-N... ♪
(chuckles) Nice try, Bob,
but I'm sure you made
some stupid...
(weakly) mistake.
Not this time.
Tell my father...
he's fat.
The deed is done.
24 years of trying to kill
a ten-year-old child
have finally paid off.
(opera music playing)
♪ I did it, I did it, I did it ♪
♪ I killed Bart dead ♪
♪ La, la, la, la, la,
la, la, la, la ♪
♪ Lots of blood ♪
♪ I did what could not be done ♪
♪ To Bugs Bunny by Elmer Fudd ♪
Fortunately, it's after school hours.
Good-bye!
(tires screeching)
(whistling)
A votre santé!
You wouldn't know,
but that means "to your health,"
of which you have none!
(laughs)
(doorbell ringing)
(groans)
(theme song playing over TV)
♪ They fight and bite ♪
♪ They fight and bite and fight ♪
♪ Bite-bite-bite, fight-fight-fight... ♪
(growling)
Bart's father! Bart's dog!
Where's Bart?
I don't know
who you're talking about.
This Bart!
Well, I suppose that does look damning,
but have you seen this?
Ooh! Ah, all right.
He's cool.
Let's move on to the next suspect.
(screams)
Well, I'd better check it out.
(sighs)
Not to complain, but your stomach acids
are smoothing the dimples off my balls.
It's time I moved
to my post-Bartum phase.
I've accepted an Associate Professorship
at Springfield University.
(chuckles)
(deflated wheezing)
(groans)
"I should have been
a pair of ragged claws,
scuttling across the floors
of silent seas."
What do Eliot's ragged claws represent?
Yeah, um...
this website says the claws
aren't a metaphor,
but, like, an insight to a state of mind.
Crushed it!
-What website?
-Forward the link.
-Text me.
-Tweet the link.
Where is it?
I didn't think the author of Cats
could be insulted further.
Class dismissed.
(groaning)
Rubbish!
Drivel!
What is this Game of Thrones
they're referencing?
I was a fool to think I'd find solace
amongst these moronic,
Snapchatting, gap-yearing...
Hello, Bart.
It seems the only thing
that made me happy
in my accursed life was killing you.
Well, if White Zinfandel
can make a comeback,
so can you.
(chuckles)
Ooh.
Those bastards know how to party!
(chuckles)
I feel like a bad New Yorker cartoon.
(angry shouting)
And now, Bart,
let's bring the old "spark"
back to our special relationship.
You couldn't kill me
if I came in with pneumonia
and a knife in my back.
(groaning)
I didn't care for the "thwock"
the sledgehammer made.
No worries, I'll just kill him again.
That's why I'm the un-killable kid.
(screams) Still not dead.
(groans) Psych!
(groaning)
Ay, caramba!
We're both going to be sore tomorrow.
(laughs)
♪ Accidents will happen,
they only hit and run ♪
♪ You used to be a victim,
now you're not the only one ♪
♪ Accidents will happen ♪
♪ They only hit and run ♪
♪ I don't want to hear it ♪
♪ 'Cause I know what I've done ♪
How much power is this thing using?
♪ There's so many fish in the sea ♪
♪ That only rise up in the sweat
and smoke of mercury ♪
♪ But they keep you hangin' on ♪
♪ They say you're so young... ♪
(Santa's Little Helper barking)
What is it, boy?
What have you found?
(gasps) I knew it was Bob!
Even when they tried
and executed Jailbird,
I knew it was Bob.
Reanimate?
This animation looks good enough to me.
Homer, pull the lever!
(groans)
I've been pulling levers all day.
Now!
Wow, for once,
I was sober at Bart's birth.
Yes, that's right, Officer.
There are intruders in my basement.
Have I the right to shoot?
Oh, yeah.
And you can wear blue jeans
to a Broadway show.
Everything's different now.
(phone beeps)
(groans)
Wait, Dad!
(grunting, groaning)
That's for trying to frame Krusty!
What about all the times
he tried to kill me?!
Eh.
As the one who suffered
the most, Mom,
may I have custody of Bob's body?
Normally I'd say no,
but you have been showing
responsibility with the dog lately.
So, fine.
(humming)
(cackles)
SIDESHOW BOB: "By Sea-Girls wreathed
with seaweed red and brown,
till human voices wake us
and we drown."
Any questions?
Yes. What are you supposed to be again?
A full professor!
But the tenure committee
is excruciatingly slow.
(groaning)
(squawks)
♪ ♪
Hmm.
(humming)
Look at that foolish old man.
Every day, he drops a perfectly
good donut into the ocean.
Let us mock him for his foolish beliefs!
Yes! Yes!
Let us show disrespect
with poorly-dubbed laughter.
(delayed laughter)
Children, go with your grandfather.
Can't we go with dead Grandfather?
He cannot leave.
He is the spirit of my tea kettle.
Lucky me.
(whistling)
Grampa, everyone in town
thinks you are foolish.
Who is more foolish,
the fool or the fool
who thinks the fool a fool?
What the hell does that mean,
Grampa-san?
For centuries,
our family has made a daily offering
of a special donut to a slumbering
underwater sea creature,
so that he does not rise
and destroy us all.
(both laughing)
He is foolish!
So foolish!
(laughs)
-Doesn't mean you are not special.
-(groans)
(humming a tune)
(gasps)
(gurgling)
(shouts)
Now I have all eternity to talk to you.
Oh.
Now we will no longer have anyone
uselessly floating donuts in the ocean.
They have made our fish fat and ugly.
Pathetic.
(roaring)
(distant roaring)
All right, calm down, children.
Probably just excitement
over the cherry blossoms.
Of course, the cherry blossoms!
They're so beautiful, and yet...
(roaring)
(people screaming)
I still refuse to admit
the old man was right!
Legitimate difference of opinion.
Professor, how do we stop him?
Fear not!
Without the buoyancy of water,
it is physically impossible
for any creature that large
not to collapse under its own weight.
It's a simple matter of--
gloy!
D'oh!
Jo!
(tires screech)
Scared by the monster?
What monster?
(roaring)
♪ Yellow ribbon 'round... ♪
Huh? (screams)
(grunts)
(screams)
(roaring)
Why do you have to stomp
on our buildings?
This land is 98% rural.
So much farmland you can walk on
without hurting your feet.
(roaring)
Right, right.
The city's the only place you can get
tuna rolls at 5:00 in the morning.
Because you do have fishy breath.
I'm just telling you.
(roaring)
(grunts)
Ah, thank you.
(roars)
So, the key to this movie
is it's so cheap it's funny.
Then just think
how popular it would be
if we spent a fortune remaking it.
We'll make millions!
After spending hundreds of millions!
(all clamoring in agreement)
We're here live at the premiere of 'Zilla!
And this time,
the stars have come out at night!
Lurleen Lumpkin, Drederick Tatum,
and my ex-husband, the Grumple.
(both groaning)
As a tie-in to this movie,
Krustyburgers will be made
from only reptile meat.
And don't worry, PETA,
we only buy the sick ones!
(roaring)
(gasps)
Buzz Cola!
(roaring)
We can't stop him.
We can't!
All we can do is avoid him easily!
(crying)
He's 2,000 miles away,
moving at two miles a day!
What do I do? What do I do?!
(both roaring)
It's a total bomb.
We only sold one ticket.
Oh, I didn't buy my ticket for this.
I just wanted to get a good seat
for the next Star Wars.
Which will stink to high heaven.
There's only one thing we can do.
Dump everything at sea
and say we lost it for insurance purposes.
Aw, yeah,
that's moviemaking, Steve.
That's why we all report to you.
Toss them overboard,
then kill the navigator.
(roaring)
(Homerzilla roaring)
LISA:
I see a Yellow Monarch,
a Woodland Skipper.
-I see...
-(both grunting, laughing)
You know,
we have been hiking for hours,
and you two haven't spotted
a single butterfly.
I thought we were hunting owls.
Well, you haven't done that, either!
-Uh-huh!
-(Lisa screams)
(groaning)
(screams)
(squirrel panting)
MILHOUSE:
Don't worry, the hole isn't very deep.
Oh, wait, I'm on a ledge.
(screaming)
(screaming continues)
(thud)
Oh, God,
everything is moist and moving!
LISA:
Bart?
What? I'm going home.
To my toy chest,
to get my barrel of monkeys,
to lower them down.
At least I'm pitching.
We got to save him!
Fine, but you'll follow me
with the camera, right?
'Cause the important thing these days
is everything must be on film.
(grunts)
Okay, guys.
My cell phone is somewhere
in that pulsing ooze.
Now each grab one ankle
while I dive in.
We have to be careful, Milhouse.
There's no telling what that stu...
Bart, what are you doing?!
Madam, how do you do?
You don't know what that stuff
is doing to you!
Oh, it's just the same junk
Dad brings us home from work.
To us Simpsons,
this green goop is mother's...
(gasps)
Where are my owls?
(grunting)
Oh, man, am I looking at a nosebleed.
(gasps)
Somehow, the radioactive explosion
gave us the power to move things
with our intellect.
Flowers for the lady?
(gasps, laughs)
Bart, what powers
did your brain give you?
Look,
you're talking to the guy that got demoted
from the Tadpoles reading group, okay?
Do not make me pity-fly.
Dignity restored.
You know,
we can't tell anyone about this.
There are going to be
lab tests and scientists...
Do we get to wear those paper gowns?
BART:
Ow!
It's a dress that boys can wear.
♪ ♪
Wedgie!
This is not a proportional punishment...!
(grunts)
Hmm, somebody misspelled "wiener."
♪ ♪
(gasps)
Lisa Simpson!
The Musicians Union does not allow this!
You know this is an ASCAP household.
God gave you this power for good,
-not jazz, and...
-(rumbling)
The 'House always wins!
I even got my parents back together.
Even now I don't feel close to you.
(groans)
Ah, finally I can diaper all my children.
-Yo, hands up.
-(groans)
Hmm.
Milhouse has gone mad with power.
Frankly,
I thought it wouldn't take this long.
Everything's coming up Milhouse!
Nicely done, Lis.
I didn't do it.
Then I want to know who did!
But not that badly.
(giggles, coos)
("Twinkle, Twinkle, Little Star" playing)
Excuse me, uh,
Ou est le Eiffel Tower?
I appreciate that you are
trying to learn our language.
(yawns)
Once again, we just have a cameo.
Don't complain or they'll put us
in four by three.
Oh, they're doing it! No!
Just 'cause it looks like season four
doesn't make it season four!
(Homerzilla roaring)
Subtitled by Jimmy Boots