(belches)
(exclaiming)
(school bell ringing)
(whistle blows)
(yells)
(playing the blues)
(grunts)
(whistle blows)
(cats yowling)
(yelling)
(bell dinging)
(dogs barking)
Merry Christmas!
♪ The Simpsons 25x08 ♪
White Christmas Blues
Original Air Date on December 15, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
Merry Christmas, movie house!
Merry Christmas, Mr. Mouse!
(screams)
(listless): Hey-hey.
Due to modern sensitivity,
we've been asked to block
any violent images
that appear in this
children's cartoon.
Oh, my God!
I never watched
one of these sober!
I gotta get this bloodbath
off my kids' show!
(grunts)
KRUSTY:
Damn it!
Aw, geez, when did
everything turn to crap?
Bart, don't use
language like that.
MARGE: Man, things sure
have turned to crap.
- (Homer humming)
- Homer,
you have to take the
Halloween decorations down
before you put the
Christmas ones up.
Marge, to that I
say, boo, humbug.
(hissing)
There's a new Grinch
this holiday season,
and its name
is "global warming."
Meteorologists warn there'll be
no snow this Christmas
anywhere in America,
not even in Alaska,
where the Eskimos now have
a hundred words for "nothing."
Global warming. Huh.
By pure coincidence, every
scientist was right.
But it's not all doom and gloom.
Illegal poachers are
having a field day.
♪ 80 degrees, water
won't freeze ♪
♪ God help us, please,
no one's on skis ♪
♪ Happy, happy, happy,
happy hunting ♪
(owls hooting)
♪ Happy, happy, happy,
happy hunting. ♪
(worried moaning)
(Marge sighs)
Sorry, kids, I guess the hats and mittens
will have to wait until next year.
- Oh!
(humming)
Hmm?
Snow?
(laughs)
Snow!
(both gasp)
Oh, you know what
this means, kids?
(both gasp)
I don't have to pick
up the dog poops!
(sobbing)
Uh, so you see, the "snow"
is a microclimate aberration
caused by radioactive steam
from the nuclear plant
and, of course, tire
fire particulate.
So, we're the only place
in America with snow,
if you can call it that.
I guess you can.
Don't you idiots see
what this means?!
Idiots? Why do we
reelect this guy?
'Cause his opponent has
a long Slavic name.
(crowd grumbling)
Who want bumper sticker?
People, Springfield is now the only town
in America that has snow this Christmas.
So tourists are going
to want to come here.
- Stay in our hotels!
- Slurp our spaghetti.
Die in our hospitals.
(chuckles)
I say we welcome our winter
tourists with open arms,
then gouge the hell out of 'em!
Who? Who will gouge with me?
I, too, will gouge!
Duff Beer is proud to make a
corporate commitment to gouging!
(cheering)
Here come the tourists.
Man your ATMs. Yar.
(both chuckle)
(belches)
Why would a robot need mittens?
Why would a little
boy need an aspirin?
I don't know. (grunts)
The one thing Bongo
Comics are good for.
(groans)
Are you okay, Chief?
(panicky): I'll be fine,
I'll be fine.
God, I bent down to pick up a piece
of candy and rolled down a hill.
You always think it's the other guy
that'll turn into a giant snowball.
Never you.
- Have you seen Lou?
LOU: There's snow in my lungs!
Lot of attitude in that hand, Lou.
Lot of attitude.
(horns honking, Marge groans)
Look at all these
out-of-state license plates.
"First in Freeways,"
"The 'Yuh-Huh' State,"
"Jewel of the Fracking Belt"?
"Still a British Colony at Heart,"
"Land of Many Water Snakes"?
(Marge groaning)
Valet parking, five dollars.
(tires screeching, horn honks)
Oh...
(gasps)
People, I'm completely
out of milk!
I do have several DVDs
of the movie Milk,
an inspiring return to form
for director Gus Van Sant.
Uh, do you have Life of Pi?
No, but I have some home movies
of me on a canoe with a big dog.
People who have never seen
a movie say it is a good movie.
Mmm?
(sighs)
We can't afford Christmas.
And when you can't afford Christmas,
you've failed as a family.
(voice breaks): That's what
all the big stores say.
Excuse me, ma'am. I'm
so sorry to bother you,
but my kids are exhausted
and the town is sold out.
Is there any chance you'd
have a spare room for us?
Well, there's a rec room
off the kitchen,
but sometimes it's there
and sometimes it isn't.
Our house is very odd that way.
Please? Please, ma'am?
We'd pay you $300 a night.
Well, you seem like a
nice, pushy stranger.
Ma'am, because we talk this way,
people always think that we're, um...
- Uh, what is that word, honey?
- Passive-aggressive.
Right, right, but we're not.
Please, please take our
money and everybody wins.
(Homer humming)
Hmm? Oh, good. Marge
remarried after I died.
Wait a minute. I'm not dead.
What's going on?!
These are our new boarders.
Uh-uh. No way. I'm not sharing
my bed with anybody except you.
And maybe that guy.
Lincoln-style. But that's it.
This is a great thing.
We're helping people
celebrate Christmas,
and we'll be able
to afford Christmas.
Oh, I don't know. It won't
seem like Christmas
without opening up a giant
credit card bill in January.
Take a look at this.
HOMER:
What the...?
"The Simpson Bed and Breakfast"?
(chuckles)
I always wanted to stay
in a place like this.
But Christmas is a special time.
And I like to spend it in the warm
embrace of watching football.
Homer Simpson, ask
yourself, W.W.B.J.D.?
- Huh?
- What would Baby Jesus do?
(The Beach Boys'
"Merry Christmas, Baby" begins)
♪ My baby she told me she
don't want to hold me ♪
♪ And kiss my lips anymore
♪ She's gonna leave me
♪ And she don't believe me
♪ That I'll be true now
♪ Well, maybe
she don't love me ♪
♪ And is not thinkin' of me
♪ But why'd she do it
this time of year? ♪
♪ Doo-doo doo-doo-doo-doo ♪
♪ She knows that I'll miss her
and I'll want to kiss her ♪
♪ If just for Christmas
♪ Merry Christmas...
Well, this crazy scheme is
the kind of impulsive behavior
I want to encourage in you.
Mmm...
I'm in! 100%!
Oh, thank you.
Now, Homie, table three
needs more bread.
- I'm on a break.
- D'oh!
(groaning)
(groans)
Welcome to our day care center.
All girls, please move
to cootie quarantine.
We've got a two-month-old.
Are you sure
you can handle her?
Just don't lose
this claim ticket.
That church doesn't
look very inspiring.
What a bland marquee.
It doesn't look very inviting.
(indistinct chatter)
This whole crowd's gonna
be at my sermon today.
Darling, did St. Paul
worry about the crowds?
Oh, he wrote letters.
Any fool can write letters.
(sighs)
Lord, I'm just
a small-town minister.
We don't have Mormon money.
But if you could see your way to guiding
my fingers as I type this sermon...
Oh, yeah.
Oh, this is black-church good.
My friends...
(feedback drones, congregation groaning)
When he starts with "my
friends," it's always bad.
Friends, every year, I tell you this
holiday is about the birth of our Lord,
not singing Santas
and full stockings.
(all murmuring)
You're losing us!
Christmas is not about what happened
in a manger some 2,000 years ago.
It is about what you
do for others now.
Oh!
(all murmuring)
Get my the church bulletin.
Lovejoy's on fire.
Christmas is the Holy Spirit.
Ooh, I didn't know there
were doves in there.
Give with your hearts!
Give with your acts!
And you will know the true
meaning of Christmas.
(congregation gasping)
(oohing and aahing)
Wow, what a showman.
(cheering, whooping)
I haven't felt this inspired since
the blueberries at breakfast.
Daddy, permission
for a religious fit?
A brief one.
(speaking in tongues)
I said a fit, not a fervor.
That sermon really inspired me.
This whole Christmas
has been about money.
(bell jingling)
- Oh, are you with the Salvation Army?
- What makes you think that?
(clink)
Bless you.
But I'm gonna give gifts that aren't
expensive and come from the heart.
I don't know.
Christmas didn't get to be the number
one holiday by being about love.
Um, when a woman talks,
she just wants to be heard.
(groans)
Where's the end?
(gasps, groans)
Hey, Marge, we're running
out of chestnuts over here.
- Well, they don't grow on trees.
- Uh, yeah, they do.
Oh.
What about our romantic
carriage ride through the snow?
Setting it up.
I don't think you're giving them
what they were promised, Dad.
The secret is: Don't
read the comment cards.
Where do the people sit?
I thought they were
just gonna watch me.
Excuse me. This
eggnog is terrible.
All eggnog is terrible.
Those stockings are not hung
by the chimney with care.
Why did I do this for money?
And the Christmas special on your
television is one of the worst.
ANNOUNCER: We now return to King
Winter Feasts On His Children.
By the time Princess Summer
comes to save you,
you'll all be blood in my beard.
Ho, ho, ho, ho.
Your own father's beard.
(King Winter cackling)
How long to see Santa?
How would I know?
I'm an accountant.
I imagine for small
business, huh?
God, I hate Christmas.
Huh?
Mr. Flanders,
where's your store?
Well, I'm down to a kiosk,
thanks to that place.
Actually, half a kiosk.
Sharing it with Nasreen here.
No cream is finer than
mall kiosk cream.
- J.Lo use it.
- No, thanks.
It is no wonder
you are not married.
Flip me back.
If I have to give presents, I'll
give presents with a purpose.
One for Maggie. Check.
All that's left is Bart.
No. No. No.
No, no, no...
Ah, perfect.
GUESTS:
♪ All from Satan's power
♪ As we were gone astray
♪ Oh, tidings
♪ Of comfort and joy
♪ In Bethlehem, in Israel this
blessed babe was born... ♪
Enough. Stop.
Christmas carols
only have one verse.
Well, they may have more,
but the second verse
is where they get
all weird and religiousy.
Uh, more wassail, please.
And don't skimp on
the aromatic bitters.
For your information, Gloria, my wassail
is just Gatorade I put in the microwave.
(both gasp)
I drank that under
the mistletoe.
It's not mistletoe, just
cherries and lettuce.
BOTH: Oh!
I thought when I ate it,
it wasn't poisonous.
I've opened up my house to you
and all you do is fill this joyous
season with petty complaints.
Ho, ho, ho.
Not now. Take out that pillow
and put it in room three.
(sighs)
The pillow acted as a girdle.
Any more questions?
Uh, yes, will the
pudding be figgy?
- The pudding will be Jell-O.
- Quite so.
I'm going to sulk in my room.
The only thing good about
this place is the piano player.
(coins rattle)
♪
(gasps)
An Angelica Button wizard robe.
With wand pocket.
And wand.
(gasps)
Professor Digglesby's wand.
Now I have every wizarding stick
from the Spells and Potions
Department of Wagglepoofs Academy.
Don't make me learn about it.
I know this Christmas has been a
little rocky, even for the Simpsons,
but I think these gifts
born of thought and love
will restore the balance
of prajna and samsara.
I mean holly and jolly.
Now, Dad, I'd like to
give you your present.
- You got me weed?
- Even better.
They're bags of seeds.
So that you can plant a
garden and watch it grow.
That's great, sweetie.
After all that time and
hard work, I'll have...
radishes?!
It's the most hated part of salad, which
is the most hated part of dinner.
Radishes, nothing but radishes.
Dad, stop.
What? I'm saving them
from the struggle of life.
Well, at least you're
eating vegetables.
Vegetables?!
Okay, Bart, open your present.
It's the one I'm
most excited about.
Plastic bubbling vomit,
plastic bubbling vomit.
What? Lis,
you're smart.
Why would you give me a book?
- 'Cause it's easy to wrap?
- Nothing is easy to wrap.
I have trouble with scissors.
(sobs)
(guests murmuring)
Marge, the brochure promised
us a happy Christmas.
My uncle died in your bed.
Merry Christmas.
(yawns)
What? (gasps)
N.C. Wyeth.
(huge gasp)
These are book illustrations.
Stop it! Stop it!
Why in the world would
you burn a book?
Actually, the idea to do
this came from a book.
Fahrenheit 451 by Ray Bradbury?
What? No, I got it from this.
MILHOUSE:
See?
How could you burn the
present I gave you?
Because it's my present.
Did you give it to me because
you thought I'd like it
or because you wanted to
feel better about yourself?
Children, perhaps it's time that I
explain the true meaning of Christmas.
- HOMER: Shut up, Flanders.
- Okily-dokily.
Now, did you check the room to make
sure you haven't left anything?
- All set. - Need directions
or a bottle of water?
No, thanks. We're fine.
Thank you, sir.
(clears throat)
Oh, right, we're
still doing that.
Come on. I'll drive
you to the airport.
Where are my keys?
Oh, right in here.
Bart, you were right.
If you smell your farts
in a dream, you die?
No, about Christmas.
So I went out this morning
and I got you this.
It's a tablet with books on it,
but also apps, like
Worms With Friends.
(muffled grumbling)
Wow. But how'd you afford it?
I sold the gift you gave me.
- Get the twist?
- Obviously.
You're saying it's from Maggie,
but actually it's from you.
Thanks, Lis.
Now, why don't you donate that to
whatever hopeless cause you want.
Thanks, Bart. This will make a
lot of arctic loons very happy.
(Marge groans)
Uh, listen, I just wanted to
say I'm sorry I overreacted.
Thank you all for coming.
Yeah, well, we have something
to say to you, Marge.
(groans)
♪ We wish you a
merry Christmas ♪
♪ And a happy New Year.
♪ Good tidings we bring...
No second verses.
They creep me out.
Okay, we'll sing
a different one.
♪ Good King Wenceslas
looked out ♪
♪ On the feast of Stephen...
Oh, that one creeps me out
from the beginning.
♪ When the snow
lay round about ♪
♪ Deep and crisp and even
(loud whirring)
Oh, the happy sound
of a blender.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
Shh!