Merry Christmas!
Oh, stupid Flanders.
Oh, thanks for bringing me
up here, Dad.
It's magnificent.
I could really use it
after what happened today.
Aw, sweetie, are you still mad
about that big dumb jerk
at school?
She's my teacher.
And her name is Miss Hoover.
It's unforgivable what she did.
What was it again?
Breakfast!
Here you go.
Melon?!
Marge, no one dreams
of waking up
to the sounds of frying melon.
- Yeah, Marge.
- See?
Your fruit breakfast has turned
him into a first name user.
For once, could this family
start the day
with fruit instead of
greasy animal fat?
Even the dog is sweating grease.
He'll be back for breakfast
and... Oh, God!
We got her!
I think I've got the answer.
Gravy up your fruit,
boy?
Look at me. I'm eating healthy.
You win.
I'll make bacon.
Put away the gravy boat.
They say the best days
of a gravy boat owner's life
are the day you get it
and the day you get rid of it.
No, Bart, stop!
This is my mobile for my
"Who Inspires You?" project.
Let me guess, it's gravity.
The ultimate suck‐up.
Can't spell gravity
without gravy.
Have some more.
The subject I have chosen
for my mobile is this lady.
Ta‐da!
Of course. Yes. Her. Absolutely.
The woman who lives
at the center of the Earth.
It's Gladys West,
the mathematician
whose work in satellite geodesy
helped create GPS.
GPS. The invention that killed
the I got lost excuse.
Oh, gee, I'm sorry, Marge.
I just can't find the restaurant
for your sisters' birthday.
Your destination is
60 feet ahead.
Shut up.
40 feet ahead.
Shut up!
20 feet ahead.
Just what I need, another woman
who's always right.
You have now arrived at
Lovely Ladies Cigar Lounge.
You'll be cutting and serving
the us‐shaped cake.
Who wants a thigh?
Curse you, Gladys West!
Dad, please!
This mobile could be
my ticket into Yale.
Another Bush kid.
How about this girl?
Her grades and test scores
are superb.
She's got boola.
But does she have "Boola Boola"?
What about this mobile
she did in the second grade?
Accept. Full ride.
Boola Boola, Boola Boola...
Ah, wha... how did I get here?
They say it's dangerous
to wake up someone
who's dreaming of Yale.
Well, just so I'm covered,
let me dream of a safety school.
UMass Amherst.
Is Miss Hoover out sick?
No, I'm in sick.
I sprained a disc in my back.
It feels like I'm passing
a kidney stone
while giving birth.
I say excuse me
when I give burps.
Not the same, Ralph.
Fortunately, my new
Teaching With Stylus tablet
lets me run the classroom
from any position.
Let's get inspired.
You might think
German chocolate cake
originated in Germany, but nein.
Actually, it was invented
by an American mill worker
named Samuel German.
I'm from America
but my measles are German.
I'm inspired by
The Masked Singer and...
It doesn't come off. Help!
Help! Help...!
I know these presentations
are boring
and everyone hates them, so...
- You're gonna stop?
- Better.
I'm gonna rap.
Ah‐ha‐ha‐ha, Gladys West,
Gladys West
If you don't know
where you're goin'
She'll make sure your car
don't get a towin'
Satellite telemetry,
should've been in ebony
When it comes to geodesy,
she's got mad skills
- Like Yeezy
- We're giving props to
Gladys West
We're giving props
'Cause she's the best
Lisa.
Lisa, you're over
your two‐minute limit.
That's enough.
Ralph, you're up.
My hero is my thumb.
It has its own room in
my mittens. Thank you.
Okay. That's it.
Now put the supplements
to your reports on my desk.
Give me a sec
to post the grades.
A B‐minus? No, no.
This can't be right.
The same grade as Ralph?!
Sorry, Ralph, no offense.
There's a fence around my bed
so I don't steal things
from Daddy's squad car again.
Chief, did you tell Snake he
could have jail outside today?
'Cause that's what he's saying.
Leave me alone.
Listen, Miss took too long
on her presentation,
it's not only right, it's easy
with my Select All
B‐minus option.
Miss Hoover, this is so unfair.
I come here every day
eager to learn
and you just put me down
and complain about your job.
In the end, what are you?
You're just somebody
who works off a formula
that leaves no room for passion,
individual effort,
or the process
of learning itself.
In other words,
you're an uninspiring hack!
Apologize immediately.
No. I told the truth.
The truth has no place
in this classroom.
Lisa, go to detention.
Detention. Detention. Detention.
One pencil with nervous
teeth marks.
One spelling bee
winner's ribbon, faded.
One quarter ounce of marijuana.
Those are pencil shavings.
Willie's water pipe
will be the judge of that.
Look at those arms.
Blank canvas
for a Sharpie tattoo.
I'm actually a vegetarian.
Okay, how do you feel
about beets?
Ooh, is this one of those
questions that sets me up
to get punched?
Only one way to find out.
Yeah, tell us
your opinion of beets.
Leave her alone, you jackals.
This is the largest stink bomb
they make.
So powerful it could only
be developed by a scientist
without a nose.
How did he know it worked?
He smelled it... with his ears.
And that girl's with me.
Well, well, well.
Together at last.
I didn't do anything wrong.
Miss Hoover should be
in detention, not me.
There is a detention
for teachers.
It's called being a teacher.
Now, let me show you my world.
Lots of gangs will recruit you.
The Magnificent Seven‐Year‐Olds.
Tardy Incorporated.
Hell's Angles.
My greatest weapon is inside
my head. My mucus.
Ms. Timberwood!
In here, she doesn't know you.
She used to call me Sunshine.
I call all the girls Sunshine.
I call all the boys Joe Cool.
Oh, you said I was
the only Joe Cool!
That's actually lavender,
so, thank you.
Ay caramba!
No...!
No dinner for me.
I'm too miserable to eat again.
This is pretty rough on me too.
Please pull the covers off.
No, I don't want to live
in the world above the covers.
I worked so hard on my mobile.
I know. And Miss Hoover
wasn't very nice.
Thank you, Mom.
But you weren't very nice,
either.
What?!
Hey, are we camping out here?
Because I have a great
campfire story.
About a man betrayed
by his own hand.
What the...?
Oh, oh, my God, it's you!
- Homer.
- Yes, Marge.
I was going to encourage
Lisa to apologize.
But I shouldn't have to.
Women say I'm sorry constantly
because men make us feel like
we have to apologize
for existing
while they do
whatever they like.
Yo. Milhouse is sleepin' over.
Awesome.
Ready to apologize, Lisa?
We both know
what's at stake here.
Not so fast, Lisa.
You didn't apologize
to your second grade teacher,
and all we do at Yale
is apologize.
Sorry, sorry, sorry
Please excuse our quirks
Quirks, quirks, quirks
Won't you kindly listen
To us rich male jerks?
We sing for free
Okay, Lisa, your future is
in my hands.
I'm... not sorry!
I'm just glad
I won't have you next year
as a teacher.
I might just move to third grade
to torment you.
That would be a real hack move.
Freshen it up.
Love it.
Personally, I never say
I'm sorry.
I say I'm soggy.
Teachers hear what they want.
Bart Simpson, did you glue
these recorders together?
Soggy.
- Forgiven.
- And Willie can use it
to whack the hornets' nests.
Yeah, come on and fight me
like a man.
Which one of you does
the negotiating?
Miss Hoover?
In reference to our
recent difficulty,
I would just like to say
I'm soggy.
Did you just say I'm soggy?
In addition to a hack,
you must think I'm a fool.
Double detention.
Who's soggy now?
And that counts
as your music education
for the semester.
Feels kind of funny driving
you home from detention.
Yeah, well, it's gonna
take me a few minutes
to get used to being
on the outside.
Honey, play the ad
I forwarded you.
Having trouble with
a relationship?
Come to the Springfield
Education Annex.
We'll teach you how to
communicate honestly,
how to lie convincingly,
and how to apologize
and mostly mean it.
Apologize?
Springfield Education Annex,
located in the third abandoned
mall on Route One.
Don't park at the Greek church
across the street.
We're in a feud with them.
There's nothing orthodox about
how fast they tow.
So, when apologizing
from your heart,
saying sorry allows
the healing process to begin.
- Sorry I'm late.
- What?! She's sorry?
Yeah, I've heard that one a lot.
Well, I don't mind
saying I'm sorry
when it's appropriate.
Appropriate.
Never heard of that word.
I know inappropriate.
- True. So true.
- Oh, yes, yes.
Now, to truly apologize,
I find it helps
to look at the world from
the other person's perspective.
Now, repeat after me.
I will not judge someone
until I walk a mile
in their shoes.
I will not judge someone until
I walk a mile in their shoes.
Well, what's the matter
with the rest of you?
Walk a mile? Please.
Like, over how many years?
Miss Hoover takes the bus.
I didn't know that.
Actually, she takes two buses.
Then she walks half a mile
down a train track,
swings across a drainage ditch
and rides a piece of cardboard
down a hill to help her back.
- Oh, that's terrible.
- I guess.
You learn a lot of sad things
when you sell weed to teachers.
Make it a double.
I'll be in the ball shed.
- Excuse me, are you Jennifer Aniston?
- No.
That's exactly what
Jennifer Aniston would say.
Dear Lord,
please grant me this winner.
I lost. And my quarter broke.
Yeah, I'm the super.
What are you doing here?
I'm one of Miss Hoover's
students,
and I just want to
understand her life.
All right, come on in.
How can I say no
to a sweet face like yours, huh?
Yeah, I have some business
in 12‐A.
Yeah, how can I say no
to a sweet face like yours?
Here, Hemsworth, come cuddle.
I'm so alone.
Just don't eat me when I die.
Is someone at the door?
I can't turn my head.
There's a great blues song
in here,
but I don't know what it is.
Don't you drag us
into your problems.
Dad, I'm ready to say I'm sorry,
but now it's not enough.
Lisa, you just gotta be sincere.
If you have a disagreement
with another driver,
you simply say, I'm sorry.
Please go ahead.
Then you follow 'em home
and you pee in their gas tank.
You pee in there!
Just can't say I'm sorry.
Does that remind you
of anyone, Carl?
Oh, God, not this again.
I have nothing to apologize for.
You had 20 years
to watch The Sixth Sense.
That's beyond
the spoiler window.
Oh, so it's okay for me
to tell you
that the Lady Gaga Star
is Born is exactly the same
as all the other Star is Borns?
I'll kill you. I'll kill you!
Goodbye, college fund.
You were gonna pay
for my mini fridge.
I need to put a down payment
on something for someone
I really owe an apology to.
A framed movie poster for
The Three Amigos?
It's better than you remember.
- No.
- All right, how about school supplies?
I got a Scottish guy who
sells 'em to me every week.
Hi, Willie.
Yo no hablo English.
Ach, the English.
How I hate those wankers.
She's coming. She's coming.
Have a seat. Top of the line.
I can see your faces again.
And now my favorite.
The ceiling.
Miss Hoover, I'm sorry
I made your life harder,
and I hope this chair
makes it easier.
Well, I don't accept
your apology.
- What?
- What am I supposed to do
after you called me a hack?
In retrospect,
I might have been wrong.
The sad truth is apologies
can come too late
to do any good.
Congratulations, you just
learned something from my class.
I guess what you've learned is
teachers shouldn't get tenure.
There has to be
a better lesson from this.
There has to.
You've planted a seed, sweetie.
- The seed will grow.
- Amen.
Why is everyone on the roof?
I know you're in there.
I'm old, but I'm not dead.
Or is it the other way around?
What does this do?
Oh, that's a surprise.
Really quite nice.
Oh, yeah.
Miss Hoover, I've been thinking,
and no offense,
but I bought you a chair.
And that's really hard
for an eight‐year‐old.
- All is forgiven.
- How forgiven?
B‐plus.
I'll take it.
Can I get a B‐plus too?
Sure.
- I'm soggy.
- Listen, boy.
I'm on to you. I know
you're saying soggy,
not sorry.
You're right, you're right.
I completely apolo‐cheese.
- What?
- I beg your par‐ton.
- Come again?
- Guilty as Marged.
I'll accept that.
- Soggy.
- Enough already.
Lisa's at Yale
She'll never fail
She's got a huge
college debt
Debt, debt
Please, I'm trying to study!
Then go to Brown
Can I have the book back?
It cost $200.
Now to dream of being
a World War I flying ace.