♪ The Simpsons ♪
-(chalk screeches)
-(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
(cries out)
(to tune of "Hooray for Hollywood")
♪ I work for Monty Burns ♪
♪ Muh-muh-muh-muh-muh-muh-muh
Monty Burns ♪
Mr. Smithers, may we
offer you a ride to work?
(chuckling)
No, thank you.
(humming)
We're from
Globex Corporation.
We'd like to talk to you about
an exciting employment
opportunity
in our nuclear division.
Flattered, but spoken for.
We're prepared to offer you
an impressive salary
plus health benefits for
you and your life partner.
The answer is no.
What's wrong with
this country?
Can't a man walk
down the street
without being
offered a job?
(sighs)
We'll have to go to the next
most senior man at the plant.
Oh, here we are.
Ten years' experience.
His name is...
Marge, I got a new job!
It's with Globex Corporation.
I get more money
plus health benefits
for me and my life partner.
And, they'll move us and give us
a nice house and liv--
-Move us?
-It's in Cypress Creek, upstate somewhere.
You took a new job
in a strange town
without discussing it
with your family?
Of course not.
I wouldn't do that.
Why not?
We have roots here, Homer.
We have friends
and family
and library cards.
Bart's lawyer is here.
But Marge,
this is a chance for me
to fulfill
my lifelong dream.
What lifelong dream?
Promise not to laugh?
I always wanted to own
the Dallas Cowboys.
(laughing)
I'm sorry, Dad.
I just find that very cute.
Homer, I don't want
to leave Springfield.
I've dug myself into
a happy little rut here
and I'm not about
to hoist myself out of it.
Just bring the rut
with you, honey.
Come on, take a look.
Uh, let's watch
something else.
Homer, you're trying to talk us
into moving to this place.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
Let's watch this.
WOMAN:
Look at this place.
Somebody ought to build
a town that works.
ANNOUNCER:
Somebody did.
It's called Cypress Creek--
a planned community designed for
the workers of the Globex Corporation.
Cypress Creek--
where dreams come true.
ANNOUNCER 2: Your dreams
may vary from those
of Globex Corporation, its
subsidiaries and shareholders.
Well, what do you
think of me
and Cypress Creek now, Marge?
It does seem nicer
than Springfield.
Yeah, did you notice how
the people weren't shoving
or knocking
each other down?
I've never been to a place
like that before.
-(cries out)
-Me neither.
Well, we could use
the extra money,
and this house
is falling apart.
All right.
(cheering)
Oh, wow! Windows.
(chuckles)
I don't think I can
afford this place.
(doorbell chimes)
Hello. I am not interested
in buying the house,
but I would like
to use your rest room,
flip through your magazines,
rearrange your carefully
shelved items,
and handle your food products
in an unsanitary manner.
Ha! Now you know
how it feels!
Thank you. Come again.
We'll never sell
this rotten dump.
A little help here.
Even if we sell the house,
we still don't come close
to paying off the mortgage.
-Hey.
Uh... Homer, ah...
about those things you borrowed
from me over the years,
you know, the TV trays,
the power sander,
the downstairs bathtub,
you going to be needing
those things in Cypress Creek?
-Yes.
-Oh, uh...
Okily dokily...
Okily dokily.
-(tires screech)
-Bye-diddly-I.
-So long.
-God bless you.
-See ya.
-Good-bye.
-Bye-bye, Homer.
-Take care.
-Adios.
-So long.
Fare thee well.
Arr. Bon voyage.
Toodle-oo.
So long.
-Bye-bye.
-Ta-ta.
-Bye, everybody.
-Bye-bye.
-Sayonara, dudes.
-So long.
-ALL: Bye-bye!
-Bye-bye, now.
-Bye.
-See ya.
-Bye-bye.
Ha-ha.
I'm gonna
miss Springfield.
This town's been
awfully good to us.
No, it hasn't, Dad.
That's why
we're leaving.
Oh, yeah.
So long, stinktown!
It says here, one of these
giant redwood trees
can provide
enough sawdust to cover
an entire day's worth
of vomit at Disneyland.
ALL:
Ooh.
Ahh.
Ohh.
Ooh.
Here we are:
15201 Maple Systems Road--
Our new home.
(whistles)
I call this room.
(knocking)
I am here to welcome you
on behalf of the President
of the Globex Corporation.
Me. Try the papayas.
They're juicy
and full of papayine.
Makes you strong
like Popeye.
Popeye, papayine.
See? Same thing.
Same... Ah, forget it.
How are you?
I'm Hank Scorpio.
Wow, my boss.
Don't call me that word.
I don't like things
that elevate me
above the other people.
I'm just like you.
Oh, sure, I come
later in the day,
I get paid a lot more
and I take longer vacations,
but I don't like
the word "boss."
-Hey, look at my feet.
-Okay.
You like those moccasins? Look in
your closet. There's a pair for you.
Don't like them? Then neither do I.
Get the hell out of here!
Ha! Ever see a guy
say good-bye to a shoe?
Yes, once.
Mr. Scorpio, this house
is almost too good for us.
I keep expecting
to get the bum's rush.
We don't have bums in our town, Marge,
and if we did, they wouldn't rush.
They'd be allowed to go
at their own pace.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm in the middle of a fun run.
See you at work tomorrow.
Although I don't really like
to call it work.
Whoa.
Okay, the oven
is cleaning itself.
The Autovac's on dirt patrol.
(beeping, whirring)
And Maggie's enjoying
her swing-a-majig.
(whimpering)
I can't believe it.
I've done all my housework,
and it's only 9:30.
Well, better go upstairs
and make sure the beds
are still made.
You will notice,
my new best friend,
that we are pretty
casual around here.
Yes, sir.
I will notice that.
Very casual, Mr. Scorpion.
Don't call me "Mr. Scorpion."
It's "Mr. Scorpio,"
but don't call me that, either.
Call me Hank.
Say, before we continue our tour,
would you mind hanging my coat
up on the wall, please?
Mm-hmm. Um, uh...
Let's see, um...
-Well, uh...
-(laughing )
Relax, Homer.
At Globex,
we don't believe in walls.
Matter of fact, I didn't even
give you my coat.
Hmm?
Wow.
Having a place like this
has always been
my dream, Homer.
What's your dream?
Uh, to work for you?
Don't do that.
My butt is for sitting,
not for kissing.
Now you tell me the truth.
What's your real dream?
Your real dream!
Um, someday, I'd... like
to own the Dallas Cowboys.
I bet people laughed at you
when you told 'em that dream.
-Yeah.
-Homer, don't give up.
They laughed at me the first time
I wore jeans with a sport coat.
I was the first wealthy man
in America to ever do that.
Now they all do it.
-Did you ever hear of Mike Milken?
-Yeah-- No.
-Hi there.
-Hey, how you doing?
Now, Homer, these gentlemen here
will be your eyes and your ears,
and should the need arise,
they'll fill in
for any other
part of your body.
Your job will be to manage
and motivate them.
Give them the benefit of your
years of experience.
Don't worry,
that won't take long.
The key to
motivation is trust.
Let me show you what I mean.
I want you to close your eyes
and fall backwards,
and I'll catch you.
That's gonna show you what
trust is all about. Ready?
-Alright.
-Three, two...
-(phone ringing )
-One second.
-Hello?
-D-ohh!
Oh, my God,
a guy's on the floor.
That was a phone call.
Don't chalk that up
to mistrust, now.
Yes? What happened?
When did that happen?
How much of it?
Oh my goodness,
I'll be right up.
Homer, I got to go upstairs.
There's a problem.
Somebody ate part
of my lunch.
I'm gonna leave
everything to you.
We're on a
tight schedule.
You keep them motivated.
Are you guys working?
Yes, sir, Mr. Simpson.
Could you, um,
work any harder than this?
Sure thing, boss.
Hey, call me Homer.
(making armpit noises)
You got a fresh sound.
It will play well
at this school.
Hey Bart, do you have
a best friend yet?
'Cause I've been looking
for someone to boss me around.
Okay, folks,
let's do it to it.
(chuckling)
Grammar, that is.
Uh, everybody write down
this sentence
and circle the nouns.
Bart, as the newest addition
to our menagerie,
you have the honors.
Um... uh...
Well, let's start
by reading the sentence.
"Two wintim
amd jawwy wirt... "
(trails off)
(armpit noise)
So, you never
learned cursive?
Um, well, I know "hell"
and "damn" and "bit--"
Cursive handwriting, script.
Do you know
the multiplication tables?
Long division?
-I know of them.
-Hmm...
You know, Bart,
I think you'd profit
from a more
remedial environment.
And I'm sure you'll feel
right at home in...
the Leg-Up Program.
(gasps)
(groans)
Guess I can't complain.
Everything's perfect here.
(ominous music playing)
So, what are you in for?
I moved here from Canada,
and they think I'm slow, eh?
I fell off the jungle gym,
and when I woke up,
I was in here.
I start fires.
Okay, now, everyone
take out your safety pencil
and a circle of paper.
This week, I hope we can finish
our work on the letter "A."
Let me get this straight.
We're behind
the rest of our class,
and we're going to catch up to them
by going slower than they are?
Cuckoo.
ALL: Cuckoo, cuckoo,
cuckoo, cuckoo...
Stop it. Stop it!
Warren! Melvin!
Gary! Dot! Gordy!
Look, lady, I'm supposed
to be in the fourth grade.
Sounds to me like someone's
got a case of "the s'pose'das."
(groans)
-(hard slap)
-Warren!
Wild flowers!
We don't have you
in Springfield.
(chittering )
Hello, Mr. Chipmunk.
You're a northern
reticulated chipmunk.
Yes, you are.
You are so reticulated.
Hi, Mrs. Owl.
You're out kind of early.
♪ La-la-la, la-la... ♪
(hooting)
Mr. Scorpio says productivity
is up two percent,
and it's all because
of my motivational techniques,
like doughnuts and the possibility
of more doughnuts to come.
I knew you'd
do well, Homer.
Sports collectibles.
Wow, a baseball made
out of Secretariat.
(gasping )
Tom Landry's hat,
and it's autographed.
"To Berman's Dry Cleaning.
Best wishes, Tom Landry."
Why don't you buy it?
I can't buy that.
Only management-type guys
with big salaries like me
can afford things like that.
(gasps)
Guys like me.
I'm a guy like me.
All right, team,
it's the fourth quarter.
The Lord gave us the atoms,
and it's up to us
to make them dance.
Hey, if Tom Landry's hat
doesn't motivate you,
then I should just
quit right now.
I'm sorry, we're just
a little tired, sir.
We've been pushing
ourselves real hard
to get the reactor on-line.
Tired, eh?
What you guys need
is hammocks.
Uh, hi, Homer.
What can I do for you?
Sir, I need to know where can I get
some business hammocks?
Hammocks?
My goodness, what an idea.
Why didn't I think of that?
Hammocks.
Homer, there's
four places.
-There's the Hammock Hut. That's on Third.
-Uh-huh.
-There's Hammocks-R-US.
-Got it.
That's on Third too.
-You got Put-Your-Butt-There.
-Mm-hmm.
-That's on Third.
-Yes.
-Swing Low, Sweet Chariot.
-Right.
Matter of fact, they're all
in the same complex.
It's the Hammock Complex
down on Third.
Oh, the Hammock District.
That's right.
Ready for the linkup,
Mr. Scorpio.
Homer, one second.
I got to take care of this.
Very important.
Be right back.
Fine.
Good afternoon, gentlemen.
This is Scorpio.
I have the doomsday device.
You have 72 hours
to deliver the gold,
or you'll face
the consequences.
And to prove I'm not
bluffing, watch this.
(explosion)
Oh, my God,
the 59th Street bridge.
Maybe it just collapsed
on its own.
We can't take that chance.
You always say that.
I want to take a chance.
Collapsed on its own?
You... You have 72 hours.
See you. Back to
the hammocks, my friend.
-Yes.
-You know there's a little place
called
Mary Ann's Hammocks.
The nice thing
about that place
is Mary Ann gets in
the hammock with you.
-(laughs) I'm just kidding.
-Oh.
-You know who invented the hammock, Homer?
-No.
That's something for you to do.
Find that out.
Any sugar around here?
Try in there, Homer.
SCORPIO:
Hi, Homer.
I'm keeping two
of my fingers crossed
that you're going
to have that nuclear generator
up to full power by tomorrow.
Yes, sir. No problemo.
Good. By the way, Homer.
What's your least favorite country?
Italy or France?
-France.
-(chuckling)
Nobody ever says Italy.
I never noticed
this office before.
Why should you?
It's mine.
Eh, you have any
sugar around here?
Sugar? Sure.
There you go.
Sorry it's not in packages.
Want some cream?
Uh... ye... no.
(ominous music playing)
♪ I like me ♪
♪ I'm as good as I can be ♪
♪ With a smile and a wave
and a happy melody ♪
♪ I'm as good as... ♪
♪ I... ♪
Hooray!
Everyone's a winner.
(groans)
(humming)
Oh, the whole forest
is blooming.
(sniffs)
(sneezes)
Excuse me.
Oh, my eyes are burning.
(loud sneezing)
(coughing)
Oh, little chipmunk friend.
I'm allergic to everything.
-(sneezes)
-(chitters)
(sneezing)
-(sneezing continues)
-(birds chirping)
(machine powering up)
Ingenious,
isn't it, Mr. Bont?
Scorpio, you're totally mad.
Heh. I wouldn't
point fingers, you jerk.
So, do you expect
me to talk?
I don't expect anything
from you,
except to die
and be a very cheap funeral.
You're going to die now.
(grunts)
Stop him!
He's supposed to die!
Nice work, Homer.
Am I proud of you.
Well...
When you go home tonight,
there's going to be
another story
on your house.
-Thank you.
-(guns firing)
I tackled a loafer
at work today.
Hey, what's with
you sad sacks?
I'm allergic
to everything here.
My nose is so stuffed up
I can't even taste Mom's
delicious boiled celery.
I've been so bored
since we moved here,
I found myself drinking
a glass of wine every day.
I know doctors say you should
drink a glass and a half,
but I just can't
drink that much.
Well, the Simpson men
are doing fine, right, Bart?
You haven't even gotten
in trouble at school.
I can't get in trouble
at school.
They put me
in the remedial class.
I'm surrounded by arsonists
and kids with mittens
pinned to their jackets
all year 'round.
Hey, Dad...
ALL: We want to go back
to Springfield.
What? We've got it great here.
And for the first time
in my life,
I'm actually good
at my job.
My team is way ahead of the weather
machine and germ warfare divisions.
It's up to you, Homer.
Whatever you decide,
that's what we'll do.
(whimpers)
WOMAN (on P.A.): "T" minus
one minute, 35 seconds.
Uh... I've got
a problem, Hank.
Oh, gee, Homer,
could it wait a sec, please?
Well, it's pretty important.
-(grunting)
-Say, what's going on?
I'm having a little
trouble with the government.
Oh, those jerks always walking
over the small businessman.
Don't get me started
about the government.
What's the problem?
Well, my family wants to
move back to Springfield.
Let them go. You'll stay here with me,
we'll go bowling.
What's bothering them?
Nothing big.
It's just a lot of little things.
Well, you can't argue
with the little things.
It's the little things
that make up life.
Homer, I'm disappointed,
but I think you need to do
what's best for your family.
Well, thanks
for everything, Hank.
WOMAN (on P.A.):
"T" minus 14 seconds.
If you need
anything, you call me.
Alright, what's the number?
I've never had to call
my own company.
Someone will tell you upstairs.
But Homer, on your way out,
if you want to kill somebody,
it would help me a lot.
(evil laughter )
Hey, Homer,
you're missing out on some fun.
Uh-oh. Sorry.
Let me just get
my girlfriend, and I'll go.
Hey, Crystal, wake up.
(doorbell ringing)
Telegram.
"Project Arcturus couldn't
have succeeded without you.
"This will get you a little
closer to that dream of yours.
"It's not the Dallas Cowboys,
but it's a start.
Drop me a line if you're on
the East Coast, Hank Scorpio."
Ah, the Denver Broncos?
I think owning the Denver
Broncos is pretty good.
-Yeah, yeah.
-Well, explain to me why it isn't.
(sighs) You just don't
understand football, Marge.
♪ Scorpio ♪
♪ He'll sting you with his
dreams of power and wealth ♪
♪ Beware of, Scorpio... ♪
♪ His twisted twin obsessions
are his plot to rule the world ♪
♪ And his employees health ♪
♪ He'll welcome you
into his lair ♪
♪ Like the nobleman
welcomes his guest ♪
♪ With free dental care ♪
♪ And a stock plan
that helps you invest ♪
♪ But beware of his
generous pensions ♪
♪ Plus three weeks
paid vacation each year ♪
♪ And on Fridays
the lunchroom ♪
♪ Serves hot dogs
and burgers and beer! ♪
♪ He loves German beer! ♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.