CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(grunting)
HOMER: D'oh!
Seymour, I'm here to tell ya
I'm returning to Scotland
and you'll never see me again.
But I have hand-picked my replacement.
Mr. Johnny Mathis.
♪ Chances are ♪
♪ I will give this hedge a trim ♪
♪ And I will kill the gophers, too ♪
Mmm. So beautiful.
(Mrs. Skinner imitating alarm)
You're late for school.
(English accent) And Friday's lunch
will be fish sticks, peas...
I'll finish those morning announcements.
-(Willie grunts)
-(clears throat)
-And lime Jell-O.
-Pathetic.
Also, Friday night is the school dance.
And that's a treat for the, uh,
popular children,
and a chance for the rest of you
to look within yourselves
and ask what's wrong.
Seymour, let me know
if you make a BM today.
Oh, my special little guy's
first school dance.
(groans) Why do I have to go
to some stupid dance?
It makes just standing around
with your friends
feel like you're a loser.
Bart, some of your biggest heroes
are dancers.
Krusty was on Dancing with the Stars
until a panel of experts
determined he wasn't a star.
(groans) Dad, help me.
(chuckles)
Son, for the rest of your life,
you're going to go
to all sorts of horrible events
just to spend time with girls.
Dances, stores, your wedding.
You don't like those things?
Oh, no. No, no, honey.
I love everything you force me do.
And sometimes if you do all that,
you get a very special night.
-(groans) And what does that get you?
-Hopefully, not a you.
♪ Not gonna make another Bart tonight ♪
♪ If I do it right,
no more Barts tonight ♪
♪ No more Barts tonight... ♪
♪ No Barts! ♪ Hmm?
-(Flanders humming)
-Hmm.
And... done. Proud of you boys.
Thanks for painting my fence,
Stupid Flanders.
Homer Simpson, reorder that border.
We've been painting since sunup.
Half the fence is mine.
Fine. Let the good Lord decide.
D'oh! Whoo-hoo! D'oh! Whoo-hoo!
D'oh! Whoo-hoo!
Now I say good day.
(chuckles) Good day, Homer.
I said good day.
(Homer groans)
Well, if it isn't the Frown Princes
of Gloomania.
What's wrong, boys?
Uncle Homer's not nice to you.
Your name's not Stupid. It's Ned.
Whoa, there, Roddy.
Someone's getting a little too familiar.
Sorry, Mr. Daddy.
(chuckles)
Time to hop aboard the...
School... Train.
School Train?
(funky tune playing)
(Otto laughing)
I'm going to die, children.
And so will you someday.
(screaming)
(sighs)
♪ ♪
-(yells)
-Thanks a lot, Bart.
That orange drink machine
was my mom's fiancé's
only source of income.
-(grunts)
-(groans)
What a relief.
This dance has turned into a fight.
Would you dance with me?
-(gasps) Where'd you come from?
-Fifth grade.
BART: Be careful, Bart.
If you take her hand now...
DEMONIC VOICE:
Your puberty has started!
Who the hell are you?
I am the puberty demon.
(cackles)
(high-pitched squeak, clears throat)
For a thousand lifetimes of man,
I have been going through changes
I don't understand.
You can join me
if you just take her hand.
I'd certainly like to help a demon,
but I...
Do it. Enter the world
of body spray, wiry hairs,
and wondering what boobs feel like.
Do you know?
Sure, sure. Of course I do.
-♪ She's up all night to the sun ♪
-Eh, why not?
♪ I'm up all night to get some ♪
♪ She's up all night for good fun ♪
♪ I'm up all night to get lucky ♪
♪ We're up all night to the sun ♪
♪ We're up all night to get some ♪
♪ We're up all night for good fun ♪
♪ We're up all night to get lucky ♪
-♪ We're up all night to get lucky ♪
-(Willie grunts)
♪ We're up all night to get lucky ♪
♪ We're up all night
to get lucky ♪
♪ We're up all night to get lucky ♪
♪ We're up all night
to get lucky ♪
♪ We're up all night to get lucky ♪
♪ We're up all night
to get lucky ♪
♪ We're up all night to get lucky ♪
-(cheering, whooping)
-Huh? (grunting)
I'll have him good as new.
I just have to get me hammers.
SKINNER: And tonight's best dancer--
Bart Simpson.
This is for you.
I'll meet you outside.
(students oohing)
Hey, look.
It's someone who does stuff.
The bullies' natural enemy.
-Nice dancing, Bart.
-Hey, knock it off!
You're a real leotard.
(bullies laughing)
That works on two levels.
Yeah. Just like the old
Springfield Galleria.
(grunts)
Do what you want to me.
Just don't touch the trophy.
(laughs) Yeah, right.
(groans)
Hi. This is for you.
Let me give you a life lesson.
This isn't your fault.
But it's the end of us forever.
(cackles)
(squeaks, coughs)
Oh, uh, hey... hey, Cassidy.
Ugh.
Sweetie, what happened?
Bullies broke my trophy.
Oh, don't worry.
When you grow up,
you're gonna have a hell of a career.
Oh, wait, you're not the girl.
You're gonna have a hell of a career.
Thank you. (giggles)
Bullying is wrong,
and I'm going to work to change it.
If I can get them to open up
another register at Kroger's,
I can do something about this.
Wha... Marge,
we don't have Kroger's money.
-(gavel slams)
-Completing our long-overdue
apologies to the witches
and their families.
Our final new business is
a proposal from Marge Simpson.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I'm about to show you
the world's filthiest word.
-(chattering)
-Oh, boy, I can't wait to see this word.
(all groan)
You know, I thought
you were gonna say...
(long bleep)
Now, Midge, uh,
thanks for coming and alls,
but, uh, since frontier days,
we've needed bullies
to steal land from Indians
and, uh, uh, punch locusts.
But not anymore.
Let's push bullying to the ground
and make it cry
and point and laugh at it.
-Yeah, yeah!
-Absolutely!
Let's pass this legislation
without any discussion whatsoever.
So moved. All in favor?
316, 317,
318, 319 to one.
Who didn't vote for it?
I didn't.
You better freaking vote for it,
or we'll bust your face,
you little troll.
(moans weakly)
The anti-bullying law
has passed without objection.
Ow.
Hey, Simpson.
Come over and get your Christmas socking.
(siren whoops)
By the unregulated power vested in us
by the hastily passed bully law,
you're under arrest.
Take 'em away, boys.
Yeah, grab that hat.
Boys, I predict you're gonna
have clear sledding from here on out.
Uh, except on those sleds.
Uh, I'm gonna need 'em as evidence.
Uh, is that a candy cane, Milhouse?
'Cause, uh, yeah.
That-that's also evidence.
Mmm, mmm.
Uh, yes, Kent, the law gives us
broad authority here.
We're not just going after
your garden-variety nurple purpler.
No, no.
We're also arresting adult bullies.
The long-trouser crowd.
And let me tell you,
arresting people
who don't think they're criminals--
it's, uh...
it's a hell of a lot easier.
Yeah. Mmm.
All you worthless writers ever do
is stare into your phones.
Why don't you text me
some freaking jokes?
A TV star criticizing his writers.
What has this world come to?
Another bully for your collection, boys.
(grunts)
I need some prison jokes. Quick.
How about "Orange is the New Blecch"?
Beautiful.
Uh, yeah. A car just cut me off.
License JDB 653.
He's a bully.
(slurping)
(ice rattles)
Oh, and the guy that filled my soda
gave me mostly ice. Bully.
Mostly ice. Dear God.
I'll never grow
a tough enough skin for this job.
Excuse me, this is madness.
The ice costs me more than the soda.
Do you realize this?
Ay, ay, ay.
What hath Mom wrought?
The police are arresting
basically anyone they want to.
Lisa, you got to learn
to trust your government.
(whispers) That's what I do.
-(electrical buzzing)
-(screams, groans)
Daddy, can we make cocoa?
Boys, I'm afraid Mr. Simpson...
borrowed our mix and our mugs.
Why don't you ask for things back?
Are you being bullied?
Now, boys, I'm just turning
the other cheek, like Jesus.
Do you think he was bullied?
(bullies laughing)
Come on, guys. Give it back.
Oh... forgive them, Father.
I raised a wuss.
Dear Lord--
Please demonstrate unto us
Uncle Homer's not a jerk.
(Homer grunting)
See you in hell, old bed.
-(snoring)
-(whistling a tune)
Oh, come on, Chief.
Why am I in here?
You're a workplace bully.
Chief, I put my name on my lunch
because you are always eating it.
Bully! Bully! Bully!
-(phone rings)
-Springfield PD. Chief speaking.
Hello? We'd like to report a bully.
Uh-huh. Uh-huh. Uh-huh!
Wow. This bully's going down!
Yeah.
-(siren wailing)
-(banging at door)
Ooh, I wonder who this could be!
-(screams)
-Homer Simpson, I'm here to charge you
with multiple counts of bullying
your neighbor, Ned Flanders.
What the... Oh, I never dreamed
that a law I had abused
could be applied to me!
-All right, time for the perp walk.
-Walk?
But I just watered up the Slip 'N Slide.
-(reporters clamoring)
-(groaning)
I have no comment at this time!
I sentence you to 90 days treatment
in our new Biff Stiffler
Bully Reeducation Center.
-Is it a school?
-More like a prison.
Phew! Thank God.
MAN: Welcome, friends.
Welcome. Welcome. No need for names.
Well, there are need for names,
or there'd be billions of people
walking around without knowing
each other, but I meant here.
I know what you're going through
because I'm a recovering bully myself.
I was bullied for years and years.
I tried to solve it in a way
that I don't suggest.
I shot a man.
But that didn't fix it.
It fixed it for him. He died.
But I then went to a lot of training.
I went into the Army,
and I was punished,
and they told me I got over it.
I don't feel it,
but I'm told I got over it,
and I have something on the wall
-that says I do.
-Ow!
Time for step one on the path to empathy,
you maggots.
Can I do yard work like the kids?
-Your work is internal.
-You mean like vacuuming?
Did you really think I meant vacuuming?
When I said "internal,"
your brain went to something
inside your house like vacuuming?
Is that what you thought?
Do you know that's why
that Dyson is a billionaire?
Something is wrong with you
when you think vacuuming.
I'm talking about inside your head.
In your head!
Oh, it's so boring in there.
Oh, is it?
And I thought it might be
like the Louvre.
Now, no more talking!
I know how this works.
You find the toughest one,
you crack that person,
and the rest of you fall in line.
You'll never crack me.
(chuckles)
Ah, you're probably right.
Just like you never heard
your mother say,
"I love you."
(sobbing)
There's not enough tissue in the world
for what I'm feeling!
(sobbing)
There, there.
The first six tissues are free.
The rest you pay for.
Use the first two again.
They don't seem very wet.
Every bully is woven
from the colorful thread
known as humiliation.
Gary, who humiliated you?
Well... (clears throat)
my father was a psychologist.
He was a big believer
in the methods of B.F. Skin-ner!
I had to go through a hamster maze
to get to my breakfast.
Which way is love, Daddy?
(voice breaking)
Which way is love?
(crying)
He made me go through a maze.
Ah. Breakthrough.
Just sit down, Gary.
Have the free potato chips.
You, we'll just heavily medicate.
I'm sorry, there's no other hope.
-Give me your money.
-Oh, beautiful.
You're just proving my point.
What about you, Homer?
Why do you hate this... Flanders?
Well, he thinks he's so perfect,
with his organized garage
and his barbecue grill
that never has crud on it.
That's very good. Keep exploring.
I'm already hating him a little bit.
Kids who love him and rub his back.
And he's got enough extra hair
for a mustache!
All I got are Archie and Wicket here.
I'm so bald.
Deeper. You've got to go deeper.
(in a deep voice) I'm so bald.
Deeper! And if you think
I mean underground,
I'm going to punch you!
Why do you hate Flanders?
Oh, everybody hates Flanders.
No, just you.
-That's right.
-(all agreeing)
He ain't no chooch.
Homer, you've got
to find the answer to this.
It's been bothering you your whole life.
Also, it's five to 11:00.
I have ten more people before noon!
Oh, can you just tell me the answer?
If I told you the answer,
then you would not have
discovered it for yourself.
Did you see that, uh,
Indiana Jones movie?
Did anybody tell him
where that thing was?
-Does this guy know?
-Well...
-Only you know!
-All right.
I hate Ned Flanders because...
(gasps) ...because he's better
than me in every way!
I think we have a breakthrough.
I was gonna say that, too.
♪ ♪
I used to be a jerk.
I never cared whose feelings I hurt
as long as it got a laugh.
I took a thumb when a pinky would do.
But we have learned our lesson,
so I hereby promise...
I promise.
-I promise.
-Te prometo.
We all promise.
ALL: To be a better human being.
Better human being.
Ugh! Once again, people.
ALL: To be a better human being.
-Better being.
-Does he have to be in this?
Well, surprisingly,
that was our best take.
Uh, question--
what will this video be used for?
Oh, in schools, by police groups.
CNN.
They're doing a lot of things now
that have nothing to do with news.
This is great.
Nothing America likes better
than someone who screws up,
goes away for a little while,
then comes back and tells everyone
how to live their lives.
Oh, I forgot to include remorse.
Eh, it's okay.
When it kicks in,
it'll be a thousand times worse.
What happened to me?
My mother told me she loved me.
Maybe I couldn't hear her because
my hand was over her mouth.
Let yourself out, please.
ANNOUNCER:
And here to throw out the first pitch,
reformed bully Homer Simpson.
And the pitch hits the umpire,
but it's not an umpire at all.
It's a returning serviceman from Iraq.
-And the crowd goes wild.
-(applause and cheering)
You're a hero.
No, you're-you're the hero. I...
No, no, you're wrong.
You're the hero.
-I... No, I just...
-I'm not.
-I-I just have a little PTSD.
-No, if you see a hero,
you're looking into a mirror, man,
because you're the hero.
Why is Mr. Simpson a hero?
Well, I suppose it's because
he used to be bad and now he's good.
BOTH: Yay?
MALE ANNOUNCER:
Jenny, the Costington's float
contains 10,001 flowers,
and work started the day after
last year's parade finished.
FEMALE ANNOUNCER:
You say that every year,
-and it's just not true.
-(male announcer chuckles)
MALE ANNOUNCER:
Well, there you go again.
Daddy, maybe someday
you'll be a hero like Mr. Simpson.
He's a hero, all right.
A hero sandwich full of baloney.
Huh. I almost said that
in front of the boys!
Time I gave that Homer
a real tongue bath!
Ooh. Glad I didn't say that, either.
Uh-huh!
Uh, wait.
What do you want me to do with this?
NED:
How about writing, "I'm sorry, Ned"?
(mutters)
What are you doing here?
Homer, sorry is not just the most
exciting board game ever devised.
It's a word I need to hear from you.
(sighs)
Fine. Sorry. We good?
No, we're not good!
You really think one little "sorry"
makes up for years of,
"Stupid, stupid, stupid, stupid Flanders"?
I'm starting to think
you don't want an autograph.
This is what I want.
I want you to understand
how you make me feel.
Homer Simpson, you made me
less of a man in my sons' eyes.
Now do you feel remorse?
Oh, my God. I'm a monster.
-Mm-hmm.
-Wait! You can't go!
I need your forgiveness!
You can't push a guy around forever, Dad.
You better take a long,
fat look in the mirror.
I know.
(Homer groaning)
Oh, driveway! Oh!
I crawled here on my knees,
all the way from my house,
to ask for your forgiveness.
Well, sir, I appreciate that,
but I don't bend that easily.
Then I'm gonna wait
right here on my knees
-till you change your mind.
-Okily-dokily.
-On my knees!
-Mm-hmm. I hear you.
-Not too comfortable.
-Nor should it be.
♪ ♪
I think he's suffered enough, Daddy.
And he seems to be sinking.
We're losing him.
"And when you stand praying,
if you hold anything against anyone,
forgive him,
so that your Father in Heaven
may forgive you your sins."
That's from that ribbon book.
Yes, it is, Homer.
And I forgive you, transgressoreeno.
Now, Ned, why don't you join us
for an all-is-forgiven brunch?
Oh, can I make my famous mimosa?
A little sparkly water
and a glass full of regular water?
Stu... pendous, Flanders.
(Homer chuckles)
(funky tune playing)
-Hey, Miss Drizzle!
-Otto! Otto!
How many tabs did you take?
(chuckles)
I took a whole sheet of Hello Kitties!
Oh, Otto!
That will have a most deleterious effect
on your brain.
The cerebrum,
the cerebellum, the medulla.
But why am I telling you about it
when we can visit
the inside of your head?
Bus, do your stuff!
(cheering)
Aah! Get it out! Get it out!
(screaming)
MAN: Mr. Foreman?
Mr. Foreman, please wake up!
Aah! Who murdered who again?
(funky tune playing)
-(crowd murmuring)
-Shh!
Subtitled by A. Vandelay