♪
Aah!
(school bell rings)
(Barney belches)
- (work whistle blows)
- Aah!
(scanner beeps)
(playing blues riff)
(tires screech)
Mm.
(tires screeching)
- (horn and toy horn honk)
- What? Whatcha...
(tires screech)
D'oh!
(grunts)
(hushed):
Who the hell are these people?
♪
Why you... (frustrated grunting)
Oh, my pâté de campagne!
My "Kick me" sign!
(tires screeching)
Oh, how could she?
Why would she?
So many feelings,
all of them anger.
Must drive them away.
Rage belongs on the road.
(tires screeching)
(growls angrily)
- (shouting gibberish)
- (meowing)
(shouting gibberish)
(tires screeching)
Where the hell's my phone?
Got to express my rage
to the person who enraged me:
my wife.
(people murmuring, shouting)
Marge, I am so, so,
so, so angry.
Anger emoji, skull emoji,
eggplant emoji,
because I hate eggplant.
Fire, fire, fire. Aah!
A fire-fire-fire hydrant!
Okay, Homer, stay calm.
Your seat belt will save you.
Wha?
Thank God I still got my airbag.
Safety first.
Hmm?
- Ah. (snoring)
- (whimpers)
Well, at least I got
shatter-proof glass.
Oh, it's shattering!
(distorted):
D'oh...!
(gasps)
I'm soaring through the air
like an angel,
or a beautiful loogie.
How very majestic
the world looks from up here.
The sky, the ocean,
Ralph.
Bart's bald mommy
is going to die.
That's her problem. (laughs)
FEMALE VOICE:
Homer? Yo, big man.
Now's not the time to chill.
What? Who the hell was that?
It's me, Maggie's
Happy Little Elf doll.
Oh, yeah.
She calls you Goobie-Woo.
Of course she does.
That's my damn name.
Okay. Sheesh, Goobie-Woo.
But how are you talking
right now?
That's a little complicated.
You see, I'm a projection
of your psyche,
and you're in the middle of
a very traumatic life event.
Traumatic? What do you mean?
I feel great.
(humming happily)
Homer. Homer, what you're
currently experiencing
is called
post-traumatic elation.
- Is that like Post Raisin Bran?
- (grunts)
Damn it, man,
you are literally in the middle
of a car accident!
What?! Oh, right.
Let me lay this out.
You and me are gonna use
this car ejection
for some self-reflection,
okay, my brother?
And that journey begins with
finding the source
of your anger.
Now, gaze into that
little piece of glass.
I need a safe-deposit box.
Want to know why?
Well, that's why I got into
banking in the first place,
for the thrilling stories.
Well, this morning,
I was on my break
- at the nuclear power plant...
- Uh-huh.
...so I went and got myself
a bag of chips.
Potato chips.
I feel like I'm at
a story slam right now.
They were so delicious
and salty and chompy,
and before long,
they were all gone.
- No.
- Almost.
Oh, there's a twist?
But then I pulled out this,
a chip that looks exactly like
John Travolta.
And that's why I need
a safe-deposit box,
to protect this treasure forever.
Oh, don't study opera staging
in Vienna, they said.
Work in a bank, they said.
Mm-hmm. Mr. Simpson,
it looks like your family
already has a safe-deposit box.
Your wife rented it out
over a decade ago.
- Wow, you've got a wife.
- Wha?
Now, I'm not supposed to
show you this,
but lucky for you right now
I'm super high.
"Last will and testament"?
Written by Clarence Bouvier,
your father-in-law.
Marge's dad left a will?
He never told me about that
in the four conversations
we ever had.
It says here he set up a trust
to pay Marge Simpson,
ooh, $1,000 a month.
A thousand dollars? What? No.
No! What?!
No! No? What?
No.
And I can confirm that
your wife has been
receiving that money every month
since her father died.
Marge has been getting
all that money for years,
and she never told me about it.
I-I don't know what to feel.
In these situations,
many of our customers
opt for extreme rage.
Well, I hate to just
follow the crowd, but...
(growling angrily)
(grumbling, muttering)
So that's why I was so mad.
And that's why
I'm even angrier now.
For all these years, Marge has
been hiding money from me.
It's a blatant act of, of, uh...
The term is
"financial infidelity."
And I can see how
you'd be angry.
Oh, thank you.
- But it's the wrong emotion
to feel.
- Damn it.
Homer, I'm gonna help you
work through this anger
so you can find peace.
Aw, work? That sounds like work.
How much time do I have?
I'd say about
point-three seconds
- judging by how fast
you're flying towards that tree.
- Aah!
Oh, my God, we're airborne.
- Whoa!
- (all scream)
I don't know which one
I'm more upset about,
that my wife has been keeping
a secret mountain of cash
from me,
or that I'm about to die
in a stupid, violent car wreck.
Don't make me choose,
Goobie-Woo.
(Homer crying out)
Homer, you're spiraling.
Of course I'm spiraling.
I'm literally flying
through the air.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Listen, I know you're feeling
all the feels right now,
but we're getting closer
to the real source of your rage.
What? I'm sorry,
I'm eating my feelings.
Bad Homer. Spit out that food,
and those feelings.
(grunts) What was Marge
spending that money on?
And why did she keep it a secret
from everybody?
LISA:
Um, not everybody, Dad.
I hate to say it,
but we've known about
Mom's secret cash
for quite some time.
Yeah, that's why I laugh myself
to sleep every night.
What? And here I've been
worried sick about
your night giggles.
Let me tell you
how we found out.
I was blowing off steam
one day...
...and I saw that Mom was
getting $100,000 a month!
LISA:
Then I explained to Bart
how decimal points work.
Then we asked Mom about it,
and she admitted
the whole thing.
So then tell me, why did she
keep the money a secret?
I don't think you can handle it.
- I can handle it.
- Okay.
The reason is...
(imitating Marge):
Your father is
an ape-faced butt monster
who eats booger sandwiches
and also sucks.
(laughs)
Why, you little
unreliable narrator!
Ow! Glass is sharp.
Oh, even my kids knew
I was being fiscally unmanned.
(normal voice):
Okay, got to go, ape face.
See you at your funeral.
We'll be the kids running around
in our nice clothes,
poignantly unaware of
the finality of death.
Oh, that tree can't
get here fast enough.
(straining)
Okay, Michael Phelps,
don't swim to your death
just yet.
Don't you want to find out
what Marge been
spending the money on?
Oh, you bet I do.
Well, that's what I thought.
Give me your best guess.
I want to give her
the benefit of the doubt,
but I can't help
but imagine the worst.
See you later. I'm off to earn
our only source of income.
He's gone. Robo-butler,
bring me a caviar hoagie.
(robotic voice):
My word. This is so expensive.
Mmm. Mmm-mmm.
You know what else
I'm paying for?
Sexy handymen doing chores
around the house.
♪ I got this feeling on the
summer day when you were gone ♪
♪ I crashed my car
into the bridge ♪
♪ I don't care ♪
♪ I love it ♪
♪ I love it, I love it... ♪
I don't know which I love more,
being rich or hiding it
from my husband.
(robotic laugh)
Let us mock him through dance.
(rapid mechanical whirring)
♪ I love it. ♪
(growling angrily)
Whew, Homer, I hesitate to ask,
but why does your brain think
that's what Marge is doing
with the money?
Because it's what I'd do.
Except the repairmen would be
my favorite rock stars:
Kiss, Bon Jovi, Men at Work,
because of
their excellent work ethic.
- (grunts)
- Stop!
Your wife is a
much better person than you are,
and she's been using the money
in a very different way.
So no robot butler?
♪ You been wasting
all your time ♪
♪ Throwing shade at Marge ♪
♪ You think behind your back
that, yeah ♪
♪ She's been living large ♪
♪ Well, I really, really hate
to burst your bubble, boo ♪
♪ All this time,
she been spending ♪
- ♪ All that cash on you ♪
- On me? No way.
I'm sure that... Huh?
♪ Homie, Homer, check your elf ♪
♪ You ain't too bright,
I'll explain the sitch ♪
♪ All them problems
you think you solved yourself ♪
♪ That was Marge, bitch ♪
♪ That was Marge,
bitch ♪
♪ The time your bar tab
was forgiven by Moe ♪
♪ That was Marge, bitch ♪
♪ That time Dr. Hibbert
reattached your big toe ♪
♪ That was Marge, bitch ♪
♪ The time you got off
of that DUI ♪
♪ That was Marge, bitch ♪
♪ I think by now
you know the reason why ♪
Goobie-Woo in da house!
- Oh, my God.
- Whoo!
All this time, I've been
thinking the worst about Marge,
but she was using the money
to save me.
Ya think?
And she only kept it a secret
to save your dumbass male pride.
♪ Well, Goobie-Goobie-Woo,
now I can clearly see ♪
♪ I've got the greatest wife
and spouse ♪
♪ That there could ever be ♪
♪ And what's more... ♪
Huh?
Holy crap,
I just flew past the tree!
♪ You're gonna live, bitch ♪
♪ You're gonna live,
bitch ♪
♪ You're gonna live, bitch ♪
♪ Yeah, I'm gonna live. ♪
- (laughs)
- Whoo!
Thank God, I don't have to
be mad at Marge anymore.
If anything, you should be mad
at Marge's dad.
- Huh?
- Oh, snap,
I shouldn't have said that.
"Oh, snap"?
What do you mean, "Oh, snap"?
Oh, snap, why not?
What do you know?
Nothing. And closure! (chuckles)
Closure-closure,
closure-closure.
Oh, no. I got to know
what Marge's dad did,
or said or rapped.
Aha, and I've got
the magical footage right here.
Don't look at it!
You've come so far.
Inner peace has almost defeated
your outer rage.
You've got to be strong, man.
So if I look at
that piece of glass,
I could change my fate
and perhaps even risk
my very soul?
Well, I'm cool with that.
What the hell?!
But, Dad,
Homer has a good heart,
and I'm going to marry him.
Oh, honey, this Simpson fellow
will never provide for you.
He has jackass written
all over him.
Marge, do you have
any turpentine?
It's not coming off.
Hmm.
His friends did that
after he fell asleep at a party.
Homer's the sweetest person
I've ever met.
Every time I look into his eyes,
I see someone who will
never stop loving me.
Oh... crap.
Look, I'm gonna leave you
something special in my will
to make sure you're okay,
because you've found
every father's worst nightmare:
true love with a true loser.
Loser? But I thought
Marge's dad liked me.
He was always warning me about
doors hitting my butt
on the way out.
How dare he emasculate me
from beyond the grave?
Uh-huh. I told you
not to look at it.
Wait, how could I remember
that talk
between Marge and her dad
if I wasn't around to see it?
You can see stuff like that
'cause you're a ghost now.
You dead.
(ghostlike):
D'oh...!
I tried to tell you,
and you didn't want to hear me.
You was eating your feelings
and carrying on.
Goobie-Woo knows what's good.
I'm gonna see this
in every dream now.
Oh, my God, I'm in heaven now.
It's so huge, so majestic.
So red.
Ooh, it's one of heaven's
goaty-footed angels.
And look at that giant fork.
Probably for eating
delicious, heavenly s'mores.
Think again, pally.
- (flesh sizzles)
- Ow!
Wait a second, I'm in hell?
But why?
Because you committed
the deadly sin of wrath
against your father-in-law.
So what? Everybody hates
everybody these days.
Plus the rest of
the seven deadly sins
all in the last half second
of your life.
♪
Whoo-hoo! I hit for the cycle!
Okay, so this is
where you check in
for your eternal punishments.
Who are they?
(lively chatter)
That's our exchange program
we have with heaven.
We send them people
condemned for sins
that aren't sins anymore.
FEMALE ANNOUNCER:
All aboard for those damned
for being gay between 5000 BC
and like ten years ago.
- It's about damn time.
- (all cheer)
Make way for Miss Thing!
FEMALE ANNOUNCER:
Now arriving,
former residents of heaven
who are now considered bad
by today's standards.
Wherefore art I in hell?
I gave the world Othello.
Yeah, and performed it
in blackface.
Get outta here.
(fierce growling)
I didn't even actually
write the plays!
Okay, Mr. Simpson,
looks like your punishment is
to be boiled alive
for all eternity
- in a lake of blood.
- All right.
Just wait over there.
Oh, there's a line?
Hey, do you mind if
I go ahead of you?
Yeah, in fact, I do mind.
Oh, for... Oh... (groaning)
Fine, take this buzzer.
When we're ready for you,
it'll electrocute you
and set your torso aflame!
I know how buzzers work.
(people screaming, crying out)
Ooh, poker.
Oh, boy, I got-a the best hand.
I'm-a gonna win.
Ha! Nice bluff, Benito.
(laughter)
Marge's dead dad!
(grunting)
You thought
I wasn't worthy of Marge.
I'll kill you
and send you to super-hell!
Hey, hey, behave yourself.
We have standards here.
Shut up, Tom Selleck!
What Marge's dad did to me
was super-sucky.
It's probably the reason
he ended up here.
Actually, he ended up here
thanks to an unrelated
check forging scheme.
Checks. Remember them?
(chuckles)
Oh, crazy.
Homer, uh, let's you and me
take a walk.
Walking?
Oh, this really is hell.
- I want to show you something.
- (man groaning)
Wow, another screen?
Yeah, this is hell.
Screens everywhere.
Mom, Dad, I'd like you
to meet Mercer.
He designs board games.
Oh, like Parker Brothers?
(laughs)
Yeah, like Parker Brothers. No.
You actually play that
mainstream corporate garbage?
You're so lucky
to be meeting me today.
Seriously, I am
so jealous of you.
Check this out.
My new game
is gonna be a huge hit.
It combines the Stratego-ness
of Stratego,
the implicit sexual tension
of Twister,
and the hard-driving whimsy
of Tic-Tac-Toe.
It's called Side-gammon.
Who's up for a game? Huh?
Oh, come on!
It's super complicated!
You'll be out
before you know it,
and you'll be humiliated!
(growls angrily) Excuse me,
I have to go yell something
into your washer-dryer.
He really is brilliant,
and he has a good heart.
- I'm going to marry him.
- (door closes)
MERCER (in other room):
I'm the Mozart of board games
and novelties!
Why, that guy's a total loser.
I don't want him to marry Lisa.
Wait, I was never as bad
as him, was I?
(chuckles)
Actually, there was a time
when I would have preferred
that guy to you.
Plus, you know what?
We got an advance copy
of Side-gammon,
- and it's not bad.
- Oh, my God.
I'm starting to see things
from another point of view.
Your point of view.
I didn't even know
other people had those.
You were just worried
about Marge,
the way I'd be worried
about Lisa.
No matter how old
and dead we get,
we just want to make sure
our little girls are okay.
- (buzzer buzzing)
- D'oh!
FEMALE ANNOUNCER:
Homer Simpson,
we are now ready
to boil you for eternity
in a lake of blood.
Wow, suddenly
that doesn't sound so good.
(angelic choir sings)
Eh, you just had
an epiphany, pally,
which means you get
to go back to your life.
It's a dumb rule, but we need
a two-thirds vote to change it.
Which is also a dumb rule.
What can I say?
Hell ain't perfect.
Homer, you're getting
another chance.
Now, get the hell out of hell
and go back to my daughter.
You heard the man.
Let's get your ass home.
(angelic choir sings)
BOTH:
Ow!
- Damn, that hurt.
- (groans)
You died and went to hell.
Ralph knows.
Whee!
Thank you, Goobie-Woo.
I learned more
tumbling through the air
than I ever did
tumbling through my life.
- (tires screech)
- (siren whoops)
- (gasps) Dad!
- Homer!
Goobie-Woo. (giggles)
Oh, Homie,
thank God you're okay.
(Homer groaning)
Homer, I have to ask you,
why did you send me
that angry text?
It doesn't matter.
I have since set aside
my own ego
and learned to savor
my many blessings.
And you, my darling,
are foremost amongst them.
I don't understand
a thing he's saying.
(shouting gibberish)
He seems to be in a lot of pain.
Can't you give him something?
Absolutely not.
No can do till we get
to the hospital.
(groaning)
(Marge sighs)
(sighs):
Ah.
I guess I can go another month
without a new purse.
♪ That's the end, bitch ♪
♪ That's the end,
bitch ♪
♪ That's the end. ♪
That's the end. (laughs)
Captioning sponsored by
20th CENTURY FOX TELEVISION
and FOX BROADCASTING COMPANY
and TOYOTA.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org
You see, I'm a projection
of your psyche,
and you're in the middle of
- a very traumatic life event.
- LISA: And cut.
Now we should move on
to the part
where your character slaps Dad.
Wait a minute,
isn't that just a sound effect?
No, it's got to be real.
Right, Lizzo?
Uh, seems a bit excessive to me,
but, hey, pshh, you're the kid.
You know what?
If you're uncomfortable,
- you don't have to do it.
- (Homer sighs)
I could do it for you.
And action!
- (grunts)
- Maybe a few more for safety?
(Homer grunting)
Whose safety? (grunts)
I don't feel safe!
- (rhythmic slapping)
- Ow. Ow.
Why, you little...
- This beat is fire.
- (Homer continues grunting)
Yo, Lisa, how 'bout
I get Sasha Flute,
you get your saxamaphone,
and we, uh, jam?
I'd love to.
- (playing Simpsons theme)
- Ow. Ow.
Ow. Stop that.
Ow. Ow. Ow.
Why, you little...
Ow.
(music ends)
Shh!