♪ The Simpsons ♪
(chalk screeches)
(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
Now, class,
I promised you
a surprise today.
Wow!
(sighing)
I knew it!
And here it is.
We're going to take a test.
-Oh!
-(class groans)
We're going to take a test.
All right! A test!
It's called the Career Aptitude
Normalizing Test--
or "CAN'T."
Some of you may discover
a wonderful vocation
you never even imagined.
Others may find out
life isn't fair.
In spite of your masters
from Bryn Mawr,
you might end up a glorified
baby-sitter
to a bunch of
dead-eyed fourth graders
while your husband runs naked
on a beach with your marriage counselor!
(clears throat)
First question--
"If I could be any animal,
I would be:
"A) A carpenter ant.
"B) A nurse shark.
Or C) A lawyer bird."
Question 60--
"I prefer the smell of:
"A) Gasoline.
"B) French fries.
Or C) Bank customers."
Well, that was
a waste of time.
Janie, school is never
Since we have 15 minutes
until recess,
please put down your pencils
and stare
at the front of the room.
Here for the tests.
(bells ringing)
(bells ringing wildly)
(electrical sputtering)
Come on, Emma.
(bells ringing)
MAN: Here's your scientifically
selected career.
-Architect!
-Mm-hmm.
-Insurance salesman.
Salmon gutter?
Military strongman!
Systems analyst, systems analyst,
systems analyst.
Systems analyst.
All right!
Homemaker?
Mm-hmm. It's like a mommy.
Police officer?
Well, I'll be jiggered.
(chuckles) If you'd like to learn more,
I could arrange for you
to ride along in a police car
for a night.
Hey! I don't need you to get me
in the back of a police car.
I really think you should
consider this.
You know, before I saw
these test results,
I had you pegged as a drifter.
Wow. A drifter.
Lousy sheriff.
Run me out of town.
He's lost my vote.
Cool.
LISA:
A homemaker!
I might as well be dead.
Lisa, it's not that bad.
So what are you gonna be, boy?
Policeman.
(choking)
Oh, that's nice, Bart.
You know, your father wanted
to be a policeman for a little while,
but they said
he was too heavy.
No, the Army said
I was too heavy.
The police said
I was too dumb.
Well, I'm going to be
a famous jazz musician.
I've got it all figured out:
I'll be unappreciated
in my own country,
but my gutsy blues stylings
will electrify the French.
I'll avoid the
horrors of drug abuse,
but I do plan to have
several torrid love affairs,
and I may or may not die young.
-I haven't decided.
-Honey, if that's what you want,
-we'll do anything we can to help.
-Wait a minute.
Isn't anybody going
to follow in my footsteps?
(crickets chirping)
(wolf howling)
Can you tell me
if I have what it takes
to be a blues musician?
Sure can.
Show me your chops.
(blues melody)
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
Cool.
So, you think
she has talent?
Sure.
Do you think she could be
a professional someday?
Oh, Lord, no.
But I'll practice every day.
Yeah, well, I'll be
frank with you, Lisa,
and when I say frank, I mean,
you know, devastating.
You've inherited
a finger condition
known as stubbiness.
It usually comes
from the father's side.
D'oh!
Stupid fingers.
You're wrong! You're wrong!
You don't need long fingers
to play the blues.
The blues come from in here.
My God, they are stubby.
(screams)
Look, I didn't steal
that copper wire.
I just thought
they were throwing it out.
Here. Take it.
Heh, no, no, sir.
We're here for your son.
He's coming
on a ride-along.
Good for you. Maybe this
will straighten the boy out.
Wow! Can I see your club?
It's called a baton,
son.
Oh. What's it for?
We club people with it.
Well! It's about time.
So you guys
like being cops?
Oh, it's great.
You get to run red lights,
park wherever you please,
hot-and-cold-running chicks.
And when you go home
at night,
you know you've made
a difference.
Hey Bart, you see
that Caddie over there?
BART:
Uh-huh.
That's Mayor Quimby's car.
Tonight, His Honor is
polling the electorate.
How would you like
a street named after you?
(whistling)
(scoffing)
I tell you.
They only come out at night.
Dear log,
this will be my last entry,
for you were a journal
of my hopes and dreams,
and now, I have none.
(cocks gun)
Do you need straight A's
to be a cop?
(hearty laughter)
Hey, fellas,
let's go shoot some bad guys.
Whoa, it doesn't quite
work that way, son.
People see movies like McBain,
and they think it's all
bang-bang, shoot-'em-up
cops and robbers.
(tires screeching)
Let's roll.
(siren wailing)
One-ocean-tango.
We're in pursuit
of a speeding individual
driving a red... car,
license number
eggplant-xerxes
crybaby-overbite-narwhal.
Oh, no.
Cops.
Whoo. They used
nylon rope this time.
It feels so smooth
against my skin--
almost sensuous.
(siren wailing)
Ooh, baby.
(screaming)
Damn boxes.
He's trapped.
-Where's our backup?
-I don't know.
Son, this is against
every regulation
but would you cover us?
BART:
Wow!
Huh?
(clicking)
(laughing)
See you in hell, punk.
(screaming)
See you in hell, punk!
(glass breaking)
(moaning)
(sirens approaching)
Man, that was close.
Good thing this alley got
so narrow in the middle.
(tires squealing)
Well, that's nice work, boys.
Looks like
you just bought yourself
a lottery ticket,
to jail.
He's unconscious,
sir.
Oh, they can
still hear things.
Sir, I know
what I want to be
when I grow up-- a cop.
Well, until then, son
I'm gonna make you
an honorary police officer.
-Eddie, give him your badge.
-Hey!
Morning, honey.
What's so good
about being stuck
in the house
behind a stove?
Lisa, I know
you're down on homemaking
but it can really
let you be creative.
See? This morning I turned
bacon, eggs, and toast
into a nice smiley face
for Bart and Homer.
What's the point?
They'll never notice.
Oh, well,
you'd be surprised.
(chomping)
-Hmm, umm, hmm...
-(belches)
Now just relax your hand.
Thank you, ma'am.
You've been most cooperative.
(sniffing)
Bad dog!
(whines)
Very bad dog!
Mom, before
you blame the dog,
I think you should take a look
at these surveillance photos.
Oh.
Oh!
(groans)
Oh, Bart!
Oh. I don't know how
that got in there.
Lisa, why aren't you
at band practice?
I quit.
Honey, right now
you're discouraged
but deep down, you know
you love the saxophone.
I think you should stay
in the band.
If you think it's so great,
why don't you join the band?
Lisa... There are a lot
of people in the world
who like to tell you
what you can't do,
but they don't always know
what they're talking about.
You know what I want to be
when I grow up?
The girl
on the oatmeal box?
(laughing)
No. I'm going to be
an astronaut.
-Women can't be astronauts.
-Why not?
They distract
the men astronauts
so they wouldn't keep
their minds on the road.
There will too be
women astronauts.
(laughing)
It's true
and we'll all live
in cities on the Moon.
So, you see,
my sisters were wrong
except about
the cities on the Moon.
I was wrong about that, so...
Well, you can see
how anyone can be wrong.
(groans)
SKINNER:
Sleek, vigilant puma--
Principal of the mountains.
Hi, Lis.
Want to quiz me
on the vowels?
Janey, I'm about ready to chuck
the whole stinkin' alphabet.
Huh?
Lisa, what
are you doing?
That's
a bad-girl bathroom.
Duh!
You want to egg
Skinner's car?
Okay.
What are you
looking at?
Nothing.
Then get out.
'Cause we're figuring out
stuff to egg.
Okay, but if you really
want to honk Skinner off
I suggest you attack
the one thing
he truly believes in.
I saw some awful things
in 'Nam,
but you really have to wonder
at the mentality
that would desecrate
a helpless puma.
(scoffs)
I never thought I'd say this
but the no-goodniks
rule this school.
WILLIE:
Get your hands off me!
God, I could really use
a half day.
Think you're big men
with your handcuffs
and blasted Tasers!
Get him out of here.
I'll get you, Bart Simpson,
if it's the last thing I do!
Now what is this all about?
Well it's quite simple,
really.
I observed our friend,
Groundskeeper Willie,
burning leaves with
a blatant disregard
for our clean air laws.
Ha! Bart Simpson
on the side
of law and order?
Has the world gone topsy-turvy?
That's right, man.
I got my first taste
of authority
and I liked it.
Hmm.
Bart, there are a lot
of trouble makers
in this school,
and, Lord knows I can't
be everywhere at once.
Go on.
Look, let's can the euphemisms, huh?
No more bull spit.
How would you like to be
a hall monitor?
Wouldn't that mean
squealing on other kids?
That's the meat of it, yes.
Hmm...
Now, Witness X
would you please tell the court
what you saw?
I'd be more than happy to.
(chuckles)
I saw Mr. Montone there
seal the late
Mr. Palaccio in an oil drum
and roll him
off the pier.
I kill you!
Ay, caramba!
I don't know.
Oh, now...
you get to wear a sash.
(gasps)
You got yourself a narc.
Hey Jimbo, keeping your nose
clean, dude? Thatta boy.
Hey, Donna,
who loves you, baby?
(yelling)
Not in my hall, bub.
I think you've had enough,
sister.
Come on,
let's keep it moving.
Pink belly! Pink belly!
Pink belly!
All right, break it up, boys.
That belly ain't going
to get any pinker.
Okay.
-Wedgie!
-(grunts)
(boys laughing)
(painfully)
Thanks, Bart.
Bart's grades are up
a little this term,
but Lisa's are way down.
Oh, we always have one good kid
and one lousy kid.
Why can't both our kids
be good?
We have three kids,
Homer.
Marge, the dog
doesn't count as a kid.
No. Maggie.
Oh, yeah.
Now take some paste
and spread it
on the construction paper.
Ralph, are you eating
your paste?
(muffled:)
No, Miss Hoover.
Good. Now sprinkle
your sparkles on your paste.
Lisa, you're not sprinkling
your sparkles.
Shove it.
(gasps)
I have never seen
a good student
take such a slide.
Lisa, what are you
rebelling against?
What do you got?
...and she goes
"Lisa told Hoover to shove it."
And I'm, like,
"No way..."
And she's like "'Fraid so."
And I'm all "Whoa!"
And she's like--
Hey, Lisa, man.
I'm, like, so impressed.
When I was in second grade,
I was all "Hi there! I'm so good."
Want a smoke?
Uh... I'll smoke it in class.
-Whoa!
Bart, you're doing
a bang-up job.
You know, before, there were
some corridors in this school
you'd just never go down.
Now I feel safe anywhere.
Every day
is a new fight, sir.
Bart, the school
is a police state.
Students are afraid
to sneeze.
I have you to thank.
Come with me.
Madre de dios!
The legends were true!
Yes, Bart, whenever a teacher
confiscates something
it ends up here.
Salacious halter tops,
complete collections
of Mad, Cracked,
and the occasional issue
of Crazy,
and this fake plastic derriere.
(laughing)
(grunts)
Now, to show my gratitude,
I want you
to help yourself
to an item of your choice.
All right!
Ooh, now you be careful
with that crossbow.
I will.
♪♪
Seymour.
This is an absence slip
signed by Nelson's mother,
and this is
Nelson's English homework.
Notice the identical
elongated loops on the D's.
Forgery!
So he didn't have leprosy.
This is a great day for me.
I thought I could never teach again.
Things have changed.
There will be no mockery
of your name, Mr. Glasscock.
Hey, Louis, watch this.
Ow! Bart, do something!
Let's go, Milhouse.
MILHOUSE: Sure, we have order--
but at what price?
Now let's correct
our homework exercises.
Lisa, what 19th century figure
was nicknamed Old Hickory?
I don't know. You?
(kids laughing)
Lisa, if you'd bothered
to do the assignment
you'd know the answer is...
The Battle of New Orleans...
I mean... Andrew Jackson.
Well, you're earning
your 18 grand a year.
(kids laughing)
(Lisa coughing)
Stupid Hoover.
Thinks she's so smart.
She wouldn't be so smart
without her teacher's edition.
(chuckling)
(distressed mumbling)
Uh, ladies and gentlemen,
the unthinkable has happened.
Some sick, twisted individual
has stolen
every teacher's edition
in this school.
What do we do?
Declare a snow day!
Does anyone know
the multiplication table?
Please, please, don't panic.
They can smell fear.
Children, I know this is
highly irregular,
but for the rest of the day,
Martin will be teaching this class.
I will? But I wouldn't
know where to begin.
Just do it, brainiac.
Have I ever told you kids
about the '60s?
(kids clamoring)
I've got to get out of here.
Calm blue ocean,
calm blue ocean.
I'm leaving the
profession again.
Oh, now Mr. Glasscock,
please reconsider.
Uh-uh.
(toilet flushing)
(whistling)
Bart, the police
haven't had any luck
finding the teacher's editions.
The dogs have picked up
the scent of books.
Send in
the battering ram.
Here we go.
We're going to have
to reorder every book.
Seymour,
I'll bet you a steak dinner
those books are still here.
All we have to do is
search every locker.
Bart, I'm not sure
random locker searches
are permitted
by the Supreme Court.
Pfft! Supreme Court.
What have they done
for us lately?
Let's move.
Hmm...
Baa!
(gasping)
(Bart gasps)
Lisa!
That's right.
It was I.
-Lis, why did you do it?
-Come on, Bart!
In your pre-fascist days,
you knew the giddy thrill
of futile rebellion.
Yeah, but even I had my limits.
You're looking
at expulsion for this.
I know! I know!
(sobbing)
(Skinner gasps)
The books!
Oh, answers! Answers!
Simpson, you've just saved
this school $120.
Who's behind
this monstrous crime?
-I am.
-(gasping)
SKINNER:
I've been so blind. In retrospect,
the signs all pointed
to a rogue hall monitor.
Sorry if I betrayed your
trust, Principal Sucker.
Now, Bart, in light of your
recent service to the school
I've decided to be lenient.
400 days detention.
400 days.
I can do that
standing on my head.
All right, 500 days.
Ooh! Big man!
600 days.
Maybe I'll just
shut my big mouth.
Let's go, Simpson.
Bart, why did you
take the blame?
'Cause I didn't want you
to wreck your life.
You got the brains and the
talent to go as far as you want.
And when you do,
I'll be right there
to borrow money.
Oh, Bart.
(saxophone playing)
Sounding good, Lis.
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.