The Simpsons
D'oh!
Hey, hey! Hey, hey!
Hey, hey! Hey, hey...
So hot. So sticky.
Marge?
I'm back here.
Ah, the old folks.
It happens every
heat wave.
Okay, people,
out of my freezer!
But we're hot
and elderly!
I'm sorry, these
are reserved for the
recently deceased.
Hmm.
Don't you go too far.
This air conditioning
is better than any
truant officer.
I'm seeing students
I haven't seen in years.
Mrs. K.
Oh, Arthur.
We're wasting more
energy than Ricky
Martin's girlfriend.
Hey-oh!
Gentlemen, our city's
sucking down the juice like
my wife at an open bar.
Mr. Burns, can your
plant handle it?
No problem.
We've siphoned off
extra power from
the orphanage.
Who are they going
to complain to?
Their parents?
But, sir, we're
at full capacity.
One more appliance
could overload the system.
Fear not.
Our town has
dodged disaster,
and I have come out
smelling like
guest-room soap.
You know what will
cool this place down?
A little touch
of winter.
Dad, no! We're trying
to conserve energy.
Lisa, if we start
conserving, the
environmentalists win!
Jingle bell,
jingle bell,
jingle bell...
Jingle bell what?
Dad, it's a blackout.
A blackout?
Oh. Every time
Santa and I get together,
it's a disaster.
Oh, no, the power's out?
We'll miss Fox's
Celebrity Boxing!
I heard tonight
they have Ed Bradley
versus Mister Ed.
It's terrible,
all the traffic
lights are out.
Driving sure
is dangerous.
Yeah, tell me about it.
I got some yuppie jerkoff
headed right for me,
yakking away
on his cell phone.
I hear that.
I got some big shot
barreling down on me.
Hey! Who are
you talking to?
Your boyfriend?
Hey, jackass!
Your voice
sounds familiar!
I don't hear an alarm.
Let's take stuff.
Whoa!
Isn't that stealing?
No, it's just looting.
Sweet. Let's go nuts.
Hot town, summer in the city
Back of my neck
getting dirty and gritty
Mannequins.
You can't buy these!
Oh! Look at all
these tube socks!
But at night
it's a different world
Go out and find a girl
Come on, come on
and dance all night
Despite the heat
it'll be all right
And, babe,
don't you know it's a pity
That the days
can't be like the nights
Oh, crap!
Kent, this city has
exploded in a fireball
of pent-up rage!
I think what the viewers
want to know, Arnie, is,
is my house okay?
You mean,
is your giant
castle okay, Kent?
Don't hate me
because I bought
at the right time, Arnie.
When's my right time, Kent?
When's my right time?
Oh, no!
They're stealing
the tire fire!
Ow! Ow!
Finally, some repression.
All right, everyone!
Disperse immediately!
We are prepared
to use force!
What, what?
We're not
prepared, Eddie?
Someone call 911.
Oh, they never come.
Thus ends
the rule of law.
Look at those looters
breaking windows,
setting fires!
They're living my dream,
and you won't
let me join them!
Please, can I
throw one little...
No.
What if I just burn down a...
Can I at least
incite further...
No.
I've caused enough trouble
already by plugging
in that Santa Claus.
No more
irresponsible behavior.
Can I have a beer?
All right.
But not the imported.
Homer?
You've got to
set limits, Marge.
No beer!
Get your T-shirts here!
"I survived the
Springfield riot!"
Remember me as a hero.
The looters stole
me glass eye!
This be a superball.
Back in my day,
we had people who
stood up to ruffians.
We called them men.
I agree with
the hideous crone!
Yeah! Hear, hear!
She's ugly!
I think I speak for myself,
Comic Book Guy and
Bumblebee Man when I say,
I blame Chief
Clancy Wiggum!
Yeah!
Yeah.
You know, it's not just
my fault. You were the ones
doing all the looting.
Oh, sure.
Blame the victims.
Throw some Nikes
at his head.
What size?
People, rest assured
the police department's
ineptitude shall not stand.
I am announcing the
formation of a
blue-ribbon committee.
A committee?
Did he say blue-ribbon?
Committees don't get
any better than that.
Man, am I appeased.
So, can we keep
the stuff we stole?
I think that's implied.
I don't care
what they say.
I won't feel safe
in this town until
we have better police.
Yeah. Wiggum
couldn't catch cooties at
Milhouse's birthday party.
Dad...
Oh! Seriously,
everyone says
your parties rock.
Homer, this is
all your fault.
If you hadn't plugged
in your dancing Santa,
none of this would
have happened.
I admit it.
I did screw up.
But I won't feel guilty
until I can put a
human face on this.
Mom! Dad!
Someone stole
my Malibu Stacy
collection!
Marge,
doesn't Lisa have
a human face?
Yes, and she's crying.
That's it!
Nobody messes
with my little girl!
I'm going to find
those dolls!
Are you gonna
call the police?
Oh! Forget it!
They couldn't catch
a cold with a
cold-catching thing.
See, when you
don't use Milhouse,
it's hard.
I love this kid.
Yes. Interesting. Okay.
All right, I've come up
with a composite sketch
of my prime suspect.
Behold!
Dad, that's Bart.
Exactly.
Look at him over there,
eating that apple.
What's he planning?
What?
Maybe we should
look for clues.
You're right.
What's this? A cap!
From The Wooly Bully.
Do you sell hats?
Yeah.
To people? People with heads?
Maybe. Sometimes.
Dude, I need a new cap.
Ah-ha!
Did you steal dolls
from my daughter?
I think they demean women!
Well, think again, son.
You're going to juvie.
But I just got
out of juvie.
Good! 'Cause
I need directions.
Well, you'll be
happy to know
Malibu Stacy's fine.
I really appreciate
what you did, Dad.
Aw.
You said you'd do
something and you
followed through on it.
Hey, you know,
stopping criminals is fun.
I felt like a big man
pushing that kid around!
Yo, empty the
register, dude.
Okay, okay,
you're the boss.
Silent alarm activated!
Oh! That's it!
No cops in sight.
If I'm gonna save that clerk,
I'm gonna have
to take the law into
my own hands again.
Cheese!
That's muy picante!
Homer, you are so brave.
If anyone deserves
to take a penny,
it is you.
Well... Well, no.
Come on, come on,
there's only one in there.
You know,
I've had a lot of jobs.
Boxer, mascot, astronaut,
imitation Krusty,
baby-proofer, trucker,
hippie, plow driver, food
critic, conceptual artist,
grease salesman, carny,
mayor, grifter,
bodyguard for the mayor,
country-western manager,
garbage commissioner,
mountain climber, farmer,
inventor, Smithers, Poochie,
celebrity assistant, power
plant worker, fortune
cookie writer, beer baron,
Kwik-E-Mart clerk,
homophobe
and missionary.
But protecting Springfield,
that gives me the
best feeling of all.
If you like protecting people,
you can make that your job.
You know, start
a security company.
Finally, a way to combine
my love of helping people
with my love of
hurting people!
Fellas, I'm starting
my own private police force.
Will you join me?
Well, who would
my partner be?
How about Lenny?
Him? No way!
You'll do as I say,
or I'll have your badges!
Once I make
and give you
your badges.
Flanders? I was
able to find your
missing leaf-blower,
belt-sander and
morning newspapers.
Well, nice work,
Inspector Find-It!
Did you catch the thief?
Who said
it was a he?
Well, I sure didn't.
Who said you did?
Nobody.
Wrong answer! Let's go!
Okely-dokely.
You're pushing your luck, pal.
Here's my commercial!
A monster!
Is this you?
If it is, don't dial 911.
Simply dial
636-555-3472.
Help me, SpringShield!
Have no fear,
SpringShield's present!
Thank you, SpringShield!
Friend?
The only friend
you need is
SpringShield.
Monster put in wallet.
That commercial
is very effective.
You know,
the old lady's apartment
was actually Lenny's.
We just used
a different duvet cover.
Well, they're
both lovely.
Hey, Officer Homer,
how'd you get
so big and strong?
Green vegetables
and homework.
Oh, shucks!
Hey-a, Officer Homer.
You look-a hungry.
I shine-a you up
a nice big pizza.
Wow! Look at Dad.
People really respect him.
Hold your heads
up high, kids.
I didn't know my chin
went that far up.
Oh, yeah,
that's the pride.
Homie, to honor
Springfield's newest hero,
I made you
your favorite dinner.
All three courses
are dessert.
Even dessert?
Dessert is three desserts.
Mr. Mayor, you've
been unflinching in your
support of Chief Wiggum.
Yes, I still believe
in our duly appointed
police force.
Behind these doors are the
finest cops ever to wriggle
into size-46 pants.
Wiggum?
Am I getting warmer?
Clancy,
you're a disgrace!
And in my blind rage,
I hereby turn over
all this town's
police duties
to Homer Simpson
and SpringShield!
Woo-hoo!
I'm Chief of Police!
Police? Uh-oh.
Oh, wait. It was
better the other way.
Now that I am the law,
I'm gonna make a lot
of changes around here.
First, I'm gonna cut
overhead by freeing Otis,
the lovable town drunk.
You can let me go,
but I'll just keep exposing
myself at the mall.
What a character.
Cool! A lie detector!
Lisa is a dork.
Dad, make him stop!
Well, according to this,
he's telling the truth.
Hurry up, boys.
We've got to get
these toy poodles
to the pet shop.
All right, Fat Tony!
Your little game is over.
Hey, how'd you find us?
One of these ferrets
is wearing a wire.
You're not a pet
and you're not a friend.
You're nothing to me.
With this latest arrest,
Springfield is
now free of crime.
Although overrun
with ferrets.
Happy days, people.
Truly happy days.
Daddy, how come
you're not at work?
I don't know.
How come you're
not at school?
My teacher says
she's tired of trying.
Yeah, well, so am I,
Ralphie. So am I.
It's Bill and Marty
on the line right now
with Springfield's
very own Fat Tony.
I wish to announce
that my associates and I
will gun down
Homer Simpson
if he has not left
town by noon tomorrow.
Wow,
that's quite a threat!
Do you have
a song request?
Radar Love.
If that thug thinks
he can run me out of town...
Oh, man, I love this song!
I've been drivin'
all night and I've got sweat
on the wheel
There's a voice in my head
that drives my heel
It's my baby callin'
on the telephone
I got some pizza and
I'm bringing it home
You all know me.
I've kept the streets safe
for you and your children.
I've tricked or treated
at many of your houses.
Last year,
I was Jar Jar Binks.
Now, who will stand
and fight with me?
I'm with you, Homer.
Shut up, Flanders.
Anyone else?
What about you,
Dr. Hibbert?
Oh! Well, I'd love
to help you, Homer,
but I have too
darn much to live for.
I just discovered
Thai food.
I'd help you,
but I have yet
to kiss a human girl.
And I've got a TiVo
full of unwatched
Dharma and Gregs.
Sorry, Homer.
I'm a coward now,
like all recovering
alcoholics.
After everything I did,
you're going to abandon me?
Homie, please,
why don't you
just leave town?
What? And let them
come after you
and the kids?
We could come with you.
In one car?
With no air conditioning?
And the little poop machine
going every 20 minutes?
I need you guys to help me!
Why'd you lock yourselves in?
Hey, why does
anyone do anything?
The point is,
what's done is done.
My Jersey muscle.
It's so good to see you.
Did you have a nice flight,
Johnny Tightlips?
I ain't sayin' nothin'.
I understand.
How is your mother?
Who says I have a mother?
Very well.
Let's do this thing.
You woke up this morning
Got yourself a gun
Mama always said
you'd be The Chosen One
She said,
"You're one in a million
"You got to burn to shine"
But you were born
under a bad sign
With a blue moon in your eyes
And you woke up this morning
And all that love had gone
Your papa never told you
about right and wrong
But you're looking good, baby
I believe you're feeling fine
Shame about it
Born under a bad sign
With a blue moon
in your eyes
So, sing it now
Woke up this morning
You got a blue moon
Got a blue moon in your eyes
Is your husband at home?
Fat Tony, how
can you do this?
Sorry, but this
is the business
we've chosen.
But you're just perpetuating
a negative Italian-American
stereotype.
I mean, you could
be a pizza man,
organ grinder,
leaning-tower maker,
and did I say
pizza man?
You are listing
my broken dreams.
I don't get it.
I finally did a job
where I wasn't lazy,
stupid, or corrupt
and now I'm going
to get killed for it.
Any last words,
Simpson?
Yeah. You can kill me,
but someone
will take my place.
And if you kill him,
someone will
take his place.
And that's pretty
much the end of it.
The town will be yours.
All right, let's do it!
Dibs on the crotch.
Oh!
He's got backup!
Somebody does care!
Johnny Tightlips,
can you see the shooter?
I see a lot of things.
You know, you could be
a little more helpful.
Oh! Homie, I'm so
glad you're alive!
Yeah, but this town
doesn't deserve me.
I'm giving this badge
to the next guy I see.
That's funny. Because
this is how I got
the job the first time.
I'm so glad this
all worked out.
Thanks for saving
my husband, Chief.
Hey, I didn't
shoot anybody.
They took my gun,
they took my badge.
Hell, they would've taken
my squad car if I hadn't
hid it under some hay.
Well, then, who shot
all the gangsters?
I must have
a guardian angel.
With a rifle.
Time to check in
on our little sweetie pie.
Oh. She's taking a nap.
Yeah, probably
dreaming about the time
she shot Mr. Burns.
She's just
like Clark Kent.
When there's
lots of excitement,
she's nowhere to be found.
Nighty-night, sweetie.
You woke up this morning
Got yourself a gun
ENGLISH - US - PSDH