CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screeching)
D’oh!
(screams)
( Bonanza theme plays)
Okay, everyone, straight
ahead is my big surprise!
(grunting, thumping)
(groaning)
Look out for the stairs.
(all moaning)
ALL:
Whoa! Ooh.
(train whistle blows)
You redid the basement!
Whoa... feel the pile
on this shag!
Whoa, baby!
Will you look
at that paneling?
I feel like I’m back
in wooden times!
Check out this pinball machine!
"Chevy Chase in Foul Play."
Pinball, eh? I’ve
always wanted to try this.
(bells dinging)
Wow, the graphics are amazing.
That ball almost seems real!
This basement is a wonderful
gift to the family.
But how could
you afford it?
Marge, we’re not going to have
to worry about money ever again,
because I’ve got a plan.
I’d like to declare
bankruptcy, please.
Mr. Simpson, do you understand
how bankruptcy works?
Yes I do. Under Chapter 13
of the fiscal code,
an individual whose debts
exceed his assets
may file for bankruptcy,
thus protecting said assets.
-That was the old
bankruptcy law.
-Huh?
Under the new law, you have to
pay your creditors everything.
What the...? But I thought
bankruptcy was the cool law!
The one that says "Dude, don’t
worry about it. I got this."
Mr. Simpson, I’m afraid
this court must appoint
a financial officer to supervise
repayment of your debts.
Hmm...
Permission to moan?
I’ll allow it.
(anguished moan)
ACCOUNTANT:
Mr. Simpson,
among the expenses
the court deems frivolous,
you throw over $1,000 a month
into local wishing wells.
Of course, you idiot,
’cause I’m wishing
for more money.
Uh-huh.
Well, you’re gonna have to make
some serious cutbacks
to your expenses.
Three subscriptions
to Vanity Fair?
I’ve got three bathrooms,
don’t I?
$500 a month
to Totalpoker.com?
Shut up! It’s an
instructional website!
Shut up!
Give it here, I’ll
find some fat we can trim.
Ah, here you go...
a giant useless
expense for something
that no one
is interested in.
(grumbling, struggling)
I don’t want to leave!
You promised me
I could die here!
No, no. This place
is too expensive.
I saw you doing a 500-piece
jigsaw puzzle in there.
(grunting)
Come on, Dad, I’m
cutting back everywhere.
To save gas, I’m
Flintstone-ing the car.
( Flintstones’ running
sound effect)
(grunting)
(straining)
Yabba...
dabba...
do...!
Ping!
-Pong!
-Ping!
Pong!
Scram, you two!
This is my bedroom now!
No way, this is our rec room!
Not anymore.
I already put my posters up.
-(Ragtime music playing)
-(Grampa chuckling)
(Flanders humming)
Hey, Mr. Flanders,
what’d you get?
Some kind of
bible garbage?
Oh, I wish!
No, these are complimentary
boxes from the shipping company.
Could a kid like me
get these boxes,
then use them for
whatever he wanted?
(laughs):
Only if he fibbed about
his name, age, and occupation
on this automated 800 number.
Why don’t you put
this box by your phone
-so you don’t call
the number by accident.
-Oh, I won’t.
(evil chuckle)
Nothing like un-tossing
a leftover salad.
It’ll be like new!
(humming)
Whoa.
What the heck are these?
Those are my medical samples!
Hands off,
you big blue Buttinski!
(groans)
Blood, bile, spinal fluid,
blood, other, phlegm,
miscellaneous ooze...
(groans)
Grampa’s driving
me crazy.
Why are you telling me?
He’s your father-in-law.
Can we at least get out of
the house for an evening?
Sure, but I think you’re
exaggerating the problem.
I’m scared.
Can I sleep across you?
(snoring)
(groans)
(doorbell chimes)
What are you doing
here, Patty or Selma?
I invited Selma here
to watch Grandpa
watch the kids.
For some reason,
she doesn’t trust him.
Maybe it’s the bang-up job
he did raising you.
He was a great Dad.
Every year he got
so mad
when Santa didn’t
bring me presents.
Um... lemon candy?
No thanks.
I brought my own.
(noisy sucking)
(noisy sucking continues)
I know what you’re wondering.
How come a single woman
with so much to offer
is alone on a Saturday night.
I assumed you were resting up
for bingo tomorrow, like me.
(dejected sigh)
My numbers don’t get
called much these days.
You’re kidding.
A sweet young thing like you?
Wow, that’s the first time
anyone’s ever
put an adjective
before calling me a thing.
You know, I was voted best
kisser in my P.O.W. camp.
Hmm...
SELMA (voice over):
Well, if he dies in my arms,
I could meet a cute paramedic.
ABE:
All right, lips,
man your kissing stations.
This is not a drill.
(klaxon blaring)
Well, here we are home early.
Yeah, and the great prices
at that new rib joint
were the surprise
of the evening.
(erotic moaning)
(gasping)
Ah! A bear
is eating my father!
I’m Selma.
Ah! A talking bear
is eating my father!
Dad, do you know what
you were kissing?
Do you? Do you?
Yeah, I know who
I was kissing,
and I also know why.
I’m a little shaky on when and
where, but I got my theories.
Well, I never, ever
want to see that again.
Ah, the hell with you.
I just might ask
that Selma girl out,
and you can’t tell me not to.
My roof, my rules!
Oh, why did I borrow
that roof from him?
So exactly what company am I
giving these free boxes to?
Uh... the name
of the company is...
Dog Incorporated.
Uh-huh.
Are you run by
dogs or for dogs?
Actually, don’t answer.
I like not knowing.
Now we just have to figure out
what to do with these boxes.
As always,
I have some ideas.
Hmm...
(laughing)
"Build a fart."
I love it.
Fort.
That’s "build a fort."
That might work, too.
I’m glad you called.
This is really going
to drive Homer crazy.
Well, actually,
the real reason I asked you
out is because I’m...
well, I’m a little sweet
on you.
Oh, listen, Abe,
the other night was fun, but...
Ah, phooey on buts.
At my age,
and with your drawbacks,
we can’t afford
to miss an opportunity.
Why don’t we just spend
some time together
and see where that takes us?
Yeah, what the hell?
Want to split a basket
of garlic bread?
Slow down, you hussy.
♪ Is she really going out
with him? ♪
♪ Is she really gonna
take him home tonight? ♪
♪ Is she really
going out with him? ♪
♪ Is she really gonna
take him home tonight? ♪
♪ Is she really going out
with him? ♪
♪ ’Cause if my eyes
don’t deceive me ♪
♪ There’s something
going wrong around here. ♪
Oh, look at Grampa and Selma
frolicking in the water.
It’s not right.
It’s like an old sea
turtle dating a suitcase
that fell out
of a plane.
Be nice, Homer.
Don’t you see how great it is
that they found each other?
Like how the parts
of a pig nobody wants combine
to make a yummy hot dog.
Oh, now you’re dragging
hot dogs into this.
Real classy, Marge.
Real classy.
Hey, Homer, that garbage
barge is complaining
about your smell.
We wrote that
joke in the water.
It wasn’t all
frolicking.
(both laughing)
(groans)
How could my Dad
go out with Selma?
Don’t those two gargoyles
know that love
is for good-looking
young people?
Well, gee,
Homer, you, uh,
ain’t exactly open-
casket material yourself.
(gasping):
Words hurt, you know.
(sobbing)
They do.
Stupid Selma and Grampa.
How dare they find happiness.
Psst! Over here.
It’s me. Patty.
Oh, great.
Who are you
in love with?
Bart?
Look, if you want to break up
your Father and Selma,
I have a plan.
But it involves you.
Okay, but I’m not
good at details.
Or the big picture.
I also show up late.
And drunk.
(whispering loudly):
I’ve got a good
feeling about this.
Lower the drawbridge!
What’s the password?
I love my sister.
(laughs)
Hey, you
little brats.
Get down from
those battlements!
Those boxes are
for shipping,
not for creating a world
of pure imagination.
Give them back.
Not till we’re bored
with them. Now, begone!
(British accent):
I shall go,
but I will return with
an army of my brethren
and together we shall
take back what is ours
and Hell will rain
down upon you!
What if we’re not here?
We will come two more times,
and then you’ll have to come
to our customer center.
(regular voice):
It’s near the airport
where the old Crown
Books used to be.
(humming)
Hello, Homer.
(shrieks):
Selma!
Relax, it’s just me, Patty.
(shrieks):
Patty!
Do you have your disguise?
Hola, I am Esteban
de la Sexface.
That means "Stephen
of the Sexface."
Okay, now let’s prepare
our mental images
so we can kiss each
other without barfing.
(moaning)
Whoa-oa-oa!
(joyfully scatting)
-Mm! Yes!
-(both moaning)
Oh, baby.
(gasps):
What the...?
Selma, how could you?!
Sorry, Abe,
we’re through.
I thought
we really had something.
What the hell
is going on here?
Dos Selmas?
Ay-yi-yi!
(gasps):
Homer!
Why would you try
to break us up?
I guess I always dreamed
that my father would
grow old alone.
Well, nerts
to both of ya!
Our love is so strong
not even a thousand crazy
schemes could tear it apart!
A thousand, eh?
I love this woman
and I’m gonna make sure
she’s in my life forever.
-I’m Patty.
-Nice to meet you.
Selma, will you marry me?
Abe...
I... uh...
Yes!
Homer, say hello
to your new ma!
(both laugh)
(screaming):
No!
("Wedding March" plays)
(all cheering)
Dad, don’t throw rice,
it makes the birds swell up!
Oh, Lisa, that’s one of those
rumors you get off the Internet.
Hey, Selma, want some rice?
(Grampa and Selma laughing)
(horn honking)
-(tires screeching)
-Pick a lane, freaks!
Nothing solves
everything forever
like a wedding.
Now to do something
I’ve been looking forward to
my whole wedding day.
(sighs):
Oh!
I’m glad I waited.
Now that we’re married,
I want to tell you
I have one strict policy--
no wife of mine
ever has to work.
Are you sure, Abe?
They offered me a
promotion at the D.M.V.
It’s longer hours, but we can
afford a place of our own.
Nonsense!
When I left Pan Am, they said
they’d always have
a job waiting for me.
Abe, there’s no more Pan Am.
Oh, I’m an old fool.
I don’t even have two
kidneys to rub together.
Oh, don’t worry, Abe.
I can provide
for both of us.
Now, we are on
our honeymoon.
I thought we were
at the circus, Lisa.
Oh, boy.
Sorry I was at
work so late.
How’d it go
with the baby?
We’re having
a great time.
I cleaned up all my best
war stories for her.
I told her how
we chased the teddy bears
into their cuddle-bunkers,
then had to tickle them out
with machine-hugs
and fun-throwers.
They say the more soldiers
you tickle,
the easier it gets.
Well, sir, it doesn’t.
Who knew guys in brown shirts
could cause so much trouble?
(whispers):
It begins.
For the Brown Empire!
(yelling)
(shouting)
(groaning, grunting)
(grunting)
(yelling)
(dragon shrieking)
Nelson, you came to help
in our hour of need.
(metallic sword ringing)
(battle cry):
Ha-ha!
(metallic clanging)
(shrieking)
(objects whistling)
(whistling sounds)
(yelling, shouting)
Yeah! We did it!
Now we can enjoy
Boxingham Palace in peace!
Want to melt it
with a hose?
Sure, I guess.
A couple of birds
pooped on it over here.
-Selma...
-Walk with me.
The new traffic
cones are held
up in Harrisburg.
Go to the costume store.
Get a hundred wizard hats
and a bucket of orange paint.
I love that!
We’ve lost the answer key
for written test number seven!
A-C-D-A-A-C-B-B-C-A!
You are what I want to be.
Selma, the
divider broke,
and the driver’s
test line is mixing
with the license
renewal line!
Hey, re-newbies,
stay on your side!
You and what line divider
is going to make me?
(sighs):
Oh!
I shaved my legs
to the knees for this?
Now to relax
with a nice cup of tea.
(laughing)
Which one of you do-hickeys
is the tea kettle?
Oh, a flapjack flipper.
I usually don’t cook,
but when you’re in love,
you do crazy things!
Now I’ll just put in a movie
to pass the time.
Let’s see. Running time
two hours.
(smoke alarm beeping)
Oh, the kettle’s whistlin’!
Ah, just the way I like it--
thick and noxious!
(exploding, alarm blaring)
Uh-oh. Better call
the fire brigade!
(squeaking)
Wow, they’re already here!
(whimpering)
So, that’s my projected
new driver’s test route.
Nice pres, Selma,
but, uh, where’s
the three-point turn
on this baby?
Um... Bailey Street?
Bailey Street?
The freshly-paved
Oh, yeah,
let’s wear that out.
(laughter,
indistinct chatter)
I’m sorry.
I-I’ve got a lot
of stress at home.
I’m wet and scared,
and the house hates me!
Selma, we don’t
have time for this.
This is the D.M.V.
We’re about
getting things done!
Abe, let’s go home.
How will we ever replace her?
Oh, I know.
Why is this so hard?
I just wanted
to marry my best gal.
I guess the
Beatles were wrong.
Love isn’t
all you need.
Abe, I hate
to admit it,
but maybe this marriage
isn’t going to work.
I guess you’re right.
Also, I didn’t realize
you liked the Beatles.
That would have caused
some problems down the line.
(sighs)
I guess I’m gonna
be alone forever.
Now, don’t be an idiot.
A sweet, young tomato like you
will definitely find someone.
Some young bruiser
who can eat corn on the cob
and not think twice about it.
You really think so?
Absolutely.
Now how about givin’
an old man one last dance?
(big band music plays)
So...
how long is Senor Homer
out of town for?
Oh, I don’t know.
He might come home any minute.
Then I must flee!
(grunts)
Where is he?
Where is he?!
I smell his
aftershave!
(groaning)
I don’t think
we’re doing this right.
Where is he?
I know he’s in here.
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Shh!
Enhanced by Fotokem