(women vocalizing)
HOMER: In my younger
and more vulnerable years,
my father gave me some advice.
He said,
"The laziest way to tell a story
is through voice-over narration."
With that in mind,
I tell the tale
of the tragic collision between
the last tycoon of the Jazz Age
and the king of a hip-hop empire.
It began with an old man
feeling like his best years
had passed him by.
(sighs)
You seem glum, sir.
How about a blood transfusion?
We have some new small batch,
single donor plasmas.
Mmm.
Better make it a double.
Hmm. My life used to be so
lively, so full of excitement.
♪♪
WOMEN: ♪ Monty! ♪
BURNS: Such shindigs
I threw at my summer estate.
In an age of shameful excess,
my parties were legendary
for their magnificent excess.
Fortunes were won and lost
at my tables.
Affairs were launched
on my dance floor
and consummated on
my floor-floor.
Sultans mingled
with Sultans of Swat.
MAN: ♪ Monty! ♪
(cheering)
BURNS:
And presiding over it all was me,
-Monogram Monty Burns.
-MAN: ♪ Monty! ♪
(groans)
Well...
what if we throw a classic shindig
at your old summer place?
Why, yes.
A beachside bacchanal
just like the Roaring Twenties.
That'll put the Cole
back in my Porter.
What fun.
Now, I have 45 close friends
who are all pretty amazing
party planners.
I'm not squandering money
on some chap to bring in
a photo booth.
I'll take care of
every detail myself.
Everything, sir?
Oh, fine.
You can fetch the ice.
Okay. How many bags?
Oh, no. None of those
pricey store-bought cubes.
Now, you head up
to Northern Canada
and get me a quarter ton
of lake ice.
Hand-sawn and tong-carried.
Risk my life
in the arctic wilderness
just to bring you some ice.
It would be an honor.
Would you like it packed in
cedar sawdust or Spanish oak?
Oh, who cares?
Ice is ice.
It says Mega Stuff
on the package,
but these are Double Stuff at best.
(licking)
Send me a free tub of Stuff
and I'll shut down my website.
Mmm.
Simpson, you seem fairly popular,
at least based on the cheers you
got at employee karaoke night.
It's not me, it's "Mustang Sally."
Mr. Burns is throwing
a little party,
and most of his invitees
are either dead or fictional.
Uh, to, uh, well,
fill out the crowd,
uh, perhaps you could, uh,
distribute these invitations
to your more, uh,
presentable friends.
I know just who to invite.
-You're not invited.
-To what?
None of your business!
All right.
MARGE:
"Your esteemed presence is requested
for an evening of
madcap magic and mischief
at Monty Burns'
Middle Hampton estate."
The card stock is so thick.
Bart, get in here
and feel this stock.
Oh, man, that's heavy.
The Springfield Hamptons?
That's on Lengthy Island,
where rich people hang out
on summer weekends.
I know all about it from
cartoons in literary magazines.
HOMER:
I'm not reading all that.
Well, now to select
the perfect guest list
of our city's sharpest wits
and glittering socialites.
(car alarms blaring,
Homer whistling)
Boy, oh, boy, a '20s shindig
at Old Man Burnsie's.
Probably gonna be
bathtubs full of shrimp
and Jacuzzis full of brisket.
Maybe I'll meet a rich bachelor
who will sweep me off my feet.
-How do I smell?
-(sniffs)
Like a wood fire put out
by dumping coffee on it.
Oh! Perfect.
Hey, everyone, hey!
I'm off-duty, so please
don't feel weird doing drugs
in front of me.
Uh, or with me.
(chuckles)
I became a cop too young.
I never lived.
I didn't live.
HOMER:
And so I entered a world of wealth.
Where mansions
are called "cottages."
And getting drunk on a boat
is called "sailing."
(all gasping)
HOMER:
Get ready for fancy.
(indistinct chatter)
I don't see any magic.
And not a hint of mischief.
Off-brand Ritz cracker?
Salt pile?
Nothing in a blanket?
Dad, did Mr. Burns cheap out?
That's impossible.
He's the richest man in town.
If I had known
this was a cash bar,
I would've gotten
wasted beforehand!
At my sister's house!
(fanfare plays)
Welcome, honored guests.
Leave your inhibitions at the door.
And write your name
on your drink cup,
you will not receive a second.
(muttering)
Now, dance the night away on
my vintage 1920s parquet floor.
The cleaning of which
is not cheap,
so be sure to don
your protective booties.
(Moe grunting)
Look, Mr. Burns, nobody loves a
party with rules more than I do.
Even I'm baffled by
the toilet payment system.
Oh, it's simple, bring the chit
from the applicable restroom
to the purser...
You might've been fun
100 years ago, Burnsie,
but now you're a cheap,
old lamewad.
And trust me,
I know cheap.
That's right,
I bought a suit,
Xeroxed it, returned it,
and wore the copy.
-(grunts)
-(guests groaning)
-Waste of my time.
-Why is everyone leaving?
Of course, no ice.
Mm, that lazy Smithers is probably
sipping hot buttered rum
in a ski chalet
overlooking Lake Louise.
(grunting frantically)
(growls)
Ah.
Uh-oh.
Aw.
(growls)
-(brays)
-(Smithers screams)
(crying)
Hey, Mr. Burns, fun party.
No one felt any pressure
to talk or laugh
or stay past 7:30.
-Super chill.
-Oh, hush.
I'm a worn-out old miser who's
forgotten the meaning of fun.
(gasps)
Great Gatsby!
What is that?
(music and chatter in distance)
Someone else is having
a party across the bay.
(chuckles)
Once I would've thought nothing
of rowing across the water
and crashing that party.
All doors would open
for Monogram Monty.
That was a long time ago.
Aw, I'll row you over.
How hard could it be?
(Homer gasping for air)
Oh, so hard.
Would it help if I whipped you?
Maybe.
Yeah, a little.
Yeah, yeah.
(grunting)
Yeah. (grunting)
♪ ♪
Oh, it's a white party.
Just the kind I used to throw.
Although we interpreted
the theme a bit differently
in those days.
♪ Aah! ♪
♪ Got a whole lot of money,
got a whole lot of money... ♪
Mm, whoever is throwing
this magnificent to-do
knows how to
enjoy their wealth.
♪ Got a whole lot of money ♪
Ooh, excessive.
Tell me, where can I find
our host?
I haven't met him.
No one has ever met him.
He doesn't exist.
Oh, he's upstairs in his office.
♪ ♪
Ooh.
Are you the host
of this incredible soiree?
I must tell you,
it's the most incandescent,
most dazzling...
My name is Jay G.
And nobody crashes my party.
Not even you nobodies.
(guns cock,
Homer and Burns gasp)
Let's go, Mr. Burns.
What did you say?
Mr. Burns and I were just leaving.
Are you Montgomery Burns,
the despised billionaire?
Well, that's what my cufflinks say.
There's something I've wanted
to tell you for a long time,
you ruthless monster.
(whimpers)
-I love you.
-(gasps)
I can't believe I'm meeting
the Monty Burns.
How do you know me?
You're the dude who wrote
The Rungs of Ruthlessness.
(chuckles) Yes, back then
they'd give a book contract
to any CEO with a power tie
and a bonsai tree.
When I was a boy,
I found a copy
left on the seat of a bus I stole.
And after I read it, I knew I'd
jacked my last courtesy shuttle.
Your book became my bible.
"Every empire needs an emblem."
See?
There you told me
to find a symbol
to represent my brand.
And there he is,
the living logo of
Golden Goose Records,
-Goosius.
-(honks)
You make me believe I can fly.
Goosius is on everything
from my cognac-flavored vodka
to the brake pads
I coproduced with Lil Wayne.
Aw, he eats the same way I do,
without swallowing.
You've flown south for
the winter with my heart.
-(honks)
-Ow!
I hope this bite never heals.
When I wrote an advice book,
I never dreamed
it would help anyone.
Everything I am I owe to you.
And a little bit
to Baz Luhrmann.
♪ When I was born,
our cupboards were barren ♪
♪ Now I'm inside
of a blue McLaren ♪
♪ Blue McLaren? ♪
♪ They all be starin' 'cause
he's a hip-hop Vanderbilt ♪
♪ I'm so established,
my life is fabulous ♪
♪ Sugar trust ♪
♪ ♪
This. This is what I thought
I'd never have again.
Well, then good news, Monty.
This is your party.
HOMER: And so was forged
the most unlikely of friendships.
A man who discovered Rick Ross
and a man who dated Betsy Ross.
The next day, my family
explored Middle Hampton.
A wonderland of boutiques
paid for by rich husbands
wanting to keep their wives busy.
Mainly second wives.
WOMEN:
♪ Hampton, ah, Hampton ♪
What kind of crazy flavors are these?
Quince jelly and pepper?
Market greens?
Bone broth brittle?
I don't know
what this place hates more,
kids or ice cream.
Really, man, a 3 Series?
I mean, what is he,
a sophomore at Exeter?
Yeah, one cup of salted caramel.
Woo-woo-woo,
scoop with the stripe, stupid.
(chuckling) I mean...
That kid just cut in line.
Are you gonna let him do that?
That's Blake Black.
His dad runs
BlackLake Investments.
So?
Richest dad rules?
Everyone knows that.
Well, I don't.
Don't misunderstand me,
Mats Wilander may have been
a decent player,
but until his inglés gets
just a little bit better,
he can coach somebody else.
Pardon me a second.
What is it,
head points, what?
Just because your father has
money doesn't mean you can cut.
Hmm, it kind of
looks like it does.
All right, I'll tell you what--
because I am a nice guy,
I am going to pay
for everyone's cones.
Is that okay?
Does that make it okay?
-Yeah!
-Yes!
No!
I would never accept ice cream
from someone whose manners
are in the bottom one percent!
(gasping)
Boom.
So, hey, hi.
Are you going to the Allens'
hot-dog-and-horseshoes
thing later?
No.
-The Forstmans' firefly thing?
-No.
The Olins' jellyfish fry thing?
I'm not going to any things at all!
But I want to, um, hang out.
What? Why?
I've never met anyone
like you before.
Anyone with, you know,
I don't know, um,
morals.
Oh. (giggles)
Well, I guess it is
a little judgy of me
to be completely
disgusted by you.
Great, I'll set something up.
Erin, are you on?
Okay, I need to bail on
the Kravises' freeze tag thing.
No, I know, I have to.
Send the big basket.
What's wrong, honey?
Lisa's got a rich boyfriend,
Dad's hanging out with
a hip-hop super producer,
and I'm stuck window-shopping
with you two fun-sucking
stink buckets.
It's not fair!
Life's not fair, kid.
Do I know you?
If life was fair,
you would know me.
But know this--
Jay G ain't all that.
-What do you mean?
-Buy a candle and I'll tell you.
-What's your cheapest one?
-$55.
No way. I could start a fire
in the woods for nothing.
HOMER: So Bart met someone
who I think comes back later.
I forget why.
Hmm. Who would have thought
two billionaire Republicans
from such different backgrounds
could end up as chums?
Is not green a more powerful
color than black or white?
The Lord picks a select few
to accumulate more money
than anyone else.
You and I bear that
sacred avarice.
Each of my enterprises
has its own G6.
What's that one?
That's for my... (chuckles)
personal horticulturalist.
(chuckling)
You know what I'm sayin'?
I don't.
You seem to get so much joy
out of your money.
I envy you.
You've given me so much, Monty.
Let me give you something back--
the freedom to live large.
A charge plate?
I've never had one of those
newfangled swipe-a-ma-jigs.
It's an Obsidian Card,
the most exclusive.
No spending limit,
no store has ever heard of it.
But they have to accept it.
Take it if you want
to roll like G.
-Don't forget to sign it.
-Oh, right.
No, no, not a felt-tip.
Oh! It'll smudge.
Okay, quick,
blow on it to dry the ink.
(both blowing)
Blake, I have to say,
this whale watch was
a very thoughtful idea.
(gasps)
Oh, it's a whole family.
But they're so far away.
Far? Babe, when you
whale watch with me,
you sit pod-side.
Fellas!
What can we do here?
This way, the whales know
we are VIPs.
Um, where's the baby?
There's supposed to be a baby.
I paid for a calf.
Does that mean anything?
Whale-copters? VIP pod-view?
This is awful!
Well, if we went on
some lame econo-watch,
we might not see blowhole one.
I mean, what are you saying?
Are you hearing yourself?
Blake, I really believed
you could change.
And you did, you became
even more horrible!
(singing)
(grunts)
These aren't VIP emotions.
This is worse than the time
I had to eat
grocery store sushi.
The shiso leaf was plastic!
(crying)
It was plastic!
JAY:
You got to buy it, M.B., it's fate.
Oh, I don't know.
$100,000 feels like
a lot of money.
You've got to splash the cash,
fling the bling, spill them bills.
It don't matter,
just splatter the batter.
Splash the cash.
(grunting)
Monogram Monty is back!
♪ I got a whole lot of money ♪
♪ A whole lot of money ♪
-♪ What you want? ♪
-♪ A whole lot of money ♪
-♪ I got ♪
-♪ A who-whole lot of money ♪
-(honks)
-♪ How much? ♪
♪ A whole lot of money ♪
♪ Whole lot ♪
-♪ What's up? ♪
-♪ Over here ♪
-♪ Over there ♪
(bell clangs)
♪ I got a whole lot of money ♪
♪ A whole lot of money ♪
-♪ What you want? ♪
-♪ A whole lot of money ♪
♪ I got it ♪
-(honking)
-♪ When the night come on ♪
♪ I already know what time it is ♪
♪ She gon' drop ♪
Now, what are you
generous folks willing to pay
for a basketball lesson
with Charles Barkley?
$10,000. $20,000. $30,000.
Do I hear $50,000?
$1 million. (whoops)
M.B., if you could only feel
what I feel right now...
AUCTIONEER:
$1 million, going once, going twice...
-$10 million!
-(crowd gasps)
Sold!
I just spent more money then I know
on something I don't even want.
And it's the greatest
feeling I've ever had!
(grunts weakly)
Still better than Shaq.
HOMER:
Mr. Burns was living the high life,
splurging on every luxury,
even the ultimate indulgence--
useless hangers-on like me.
Noice.
To think, all the years
I wasted without a posse.
Good-bye, loneliness.
We get all this stuff
just for letting Mr. Burns
beat us in mini golf.
(chuckling)
What a deal!
My whole job is to not
make eye contact with him.
I thought I'd get tired
of window-shopping
in this fancy little town,
but it ain't happening.
A chessboard
where the pieces are lipsticks!
-(gasps)
-(groans)
(gasps)
A horse show!
A protest!
Huh?
Blake, is that you?
What happened to your privilege?
-I checked it.
-(gasps)
Lisa, when you rejected me,
I knew I had to do whatever it took
to become worthy of you.
This now runs on solar power and falafel.
Now, that's sustainable!
I've dedicated my entire allowance
to Trustafarians for Horse Justice.
Here's an upside down bucket
for you to drum on.
Well, what girl could say no
to a socially conscious drum circle?
Yo, lamp dress,
I've got all access paddock
passes to the horse show.
Check out these
sweet mane combs.
I can get you up close
to the horses
for primo grooming time.
ALL:
Combing is murder!
BOY:
Primo grooming time.
HOMER:
The test of a first-rate intelligence
is the ability to hold
two opposing ideas
in the mind at the same time
and still retain the ability
to function.
Horsey, horsey,
horsey, horsey, horsey!
For her, I gave up
what meant most to me--
being a douche.
Mr. Burns, your bill came
from the Obsidian Card.
Are you sure you're not
spending too much money?
Hush, you sound like Smithers.
Where is that loafer with my ice?
(Smithers grunting,
ringtone playing)
(ringing stops)
(groaning)
-(horn honks)
-Fill her up!
And make it snappy.
My best pal and I
are going shopping
for those yachts that have
little submarines in them.
Sir, your card was declined.
(laughs)
Goulash! Absolute goulash!
It's linked
to my bank account.
I'd have to be penniless
before that card didn't work.
Well, then that means you're broke.
Broke?
(chuckles anxiously) Me?
Broke? Me?
Yes, I'm afraid I have
to destroy your card.
Good luck.
It's tempered titanium
and coated with powdered diamond.
♪ I ain't got no money ♪
MOE: Don't take it.
This car leased in someone
else's name is who I am!
My entire fortune,
spent and gone.
I splashed all my cash.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
It was your first credit card.
And I handled it as well as
a freshman at Michigan State!
Mr. Burns, I think Jay wanted
you to bankrupt yourself.
Why would you say
such a thing?
It's number one on the charts.
♪ ♪
♪ Used to be the man, Burns ♪
♪ Now you just a bad joke ♪
♪ Used to be about to die ♪
♪ Now you only dead broke ♪
♪ I gave you the card, Burns ♪
♪ And you spent your mind out ♪
♪ It was all a trap, yo ♪
♪ As you 'bout to find out ♪
Jay G is CEO of Obsidian!
-Biotch!
-(honks)
♪ Now your bank account is withering ♪
♪ Your bottom lip is quivering ♪
♪ You're Hufflepuff, I'm Slytherin ♪
♪ There's no one
doin' your Smitherin' ♪
♪ This is where your money went ♪
♪ Evict you from the one percent ♪
♪ Now watch me as my fingers tent ♪
♪ 'Cause I own you, it is excellent ♪
♪ Excellent ♪
♪ You're broke now ♪
♪ Your cash was your passion ♪
♪ Now Jay owns your ass, son ♪
(honks)
If these rhymes
are to be believed,
Jay lured me into debt
and now he owns everything.
Even my beloved nuclear plant.
Our magical friendship was a sham!
HOMER:
The loneliest moment in someone's life
is when they're watching
their whole world fall apart.
And all they can do
is stare blankly.
Oh, no, wait, he's crying now.
That's worse.
Now he's really sobbing heavy.
Oh, now he's gone to his knees
and he ripped his shirt open.
All of his buttons fell off
of his shirt.
Oh, now he's kicking his porch.
Oh, he hurt his foot
and he's hopping around.
Oh, he tripped over a dog.
(sobs)
That's way worse.
Montgomery Burns
had hit rock-bottom.
HOMER:
F. Scott Fitzgerald once wrote,
"There are no second acts
in American lives."
But he never said anything
about second parts
in American TV shows.
I should've seen it all coming.
My eyes were clouded
by the cataracts of excess.
And by an excess of cataracts.
Wait.
What happened to my posse?
Don't you worry.
A posse's loyalty is forever.
Hey, Burnsie, I didn't get
any brand-new sneakers today.
I can't be wearing
two-day-old sneakers.
Hey, if there's no more money,
we'll take our personalized
bowling balls,
fold-up bicycles, and go.
(bicycles squeaking)
(sighs)
I'm here for my hounds.
(growling)
Huh! Preposterous.
I raised those hounds from pups.
I'm the only master
they've ever known.
One word from me
and they'll rip you apart.
-Commence ripping!
-(snarling)
(sniffing)
(chuckles)
Dogs can smell power.
Sign this release legally
releasing the hounds.
If you don't, Mr. Jay G
will release the hounds.
Jay, I don't understand.
I thought we were friends.
We were going to open up
a money-losing winery together.
We can still hang out. Even
though our owners are fighting.
(honks)
Not being bitten... (cries)
hurts the most.
(sighs) Everyone's gone.
Even Smithers never bothered
to return from Canada
with my lake ice.
(alarm ringtone plays)
(grunting)
(cracking)
Good Simpson.
Faithful Simpson.
You would never go back
to the nuclear plant
that was so cruelly
taken from me.
What does your heart say?
HOMER: I looked deep into my heart,
and it said...
Uh... let me ask my wife.
I don't care if
Mr. Burns doesn't own
the nuclear plant anymore.
You still have to work there.
You have a wife, a family,
and a store to support.
You're right, you're right.
Wait. A store?
-I have a store.
-How did that happen?
Well, you spend enough
time in the Hamptons
and you have any flair at all,
you just wind up with a store.
WOMEN: ♪ What could possibly
go wrong with retail? ♪
Where should we put
the 19th century doctor's kits?
Ooh, ooh! In the window next
to the state-shaped erasers.
But I feel bad leaving
Mr. Burns. I'm all he's got.
Can't we live off the money
from your store?
Oh, God, no!
Right now I'm still
building inventory.
Luckily, the pincushion
store across the street
went out of business.
I just swooped right in
and bought up everything.
Okay.
HOMER:
With my dear wife losing her marbles,
I had to turn my back on poor,
broken Burns
and go to work at, well,
the sexiest nuclear plant on Earth.
♪ Radioactive ♪
♪ R-R-R-Radioactive ♪
Homer Simpson?
Boss wants to see you.
-♪ Booty like a power plant ♪
-WOMAN: Hey, baby.
♪ You're blowin' up my pants,
I like the way you dance ♪
JAY:
Mixtape coming soon, ladies.
♪ J-J-J-Jay's got the power! ♪
(music continues in distance)
"Rung six.
To ensure an employee's loyalty,
you must crush their
attachments to the past."
-(honks)
-(knocking on door)
You wanted to see me, Mr. G?
Relax, Homer, we're good.
When you entered my gates,
I knew you'd turn your back
on Old Man Burns.
And I respect that.
Yeah.
I ditched him, all right.
In his hour of need.
But I feel good about it.
Really good.
(honking)
Ow! Ow!
Oh... I missed that.
Because I know
you're so loyal to me,
I have a very special job for you.
Removing the last trace
of Monty Burns
from the power plant he loves.
(whimpers)
(grunts)
Don't look at me.
Stop looking at me!
(grunts)
You did good.
Here's your reward.
(gasps)
Cobbler.
I've got a granny in Atlanta
who custom bakes them
just for me.
Peach, berry, cherry,
rhubarb, pineapple.
You can't cobbler pineapple.
Yet here it is.
(crying)
Homie, what's wrong?
I've never seen such beautiful cobbler.
HOMER: But there was a hole
in me that even 1,000 pans
of hot fruit couldn't fill.
I had betrayed Mr. Burns
and felt sick about it.
Searching for an open grave
in which to barf,
I heard a horrible sound,
which I was strangely
drawn towards.
BURNS: (coughing)
♪ After the ball is over ♪
♪ After the break of dawn ♪
♪ After the dancers' leaving ♪
♪ After the stars are gone ♪
Mr. Burns, what are you
doing in this death hole?
All I have left
is my family mausoleum.
Would you like
a sip of grief soup?
I stewed it from flowers
left on graves.
I confess, I went back
to work at the plant.
Jay G seduced me with cobbler.
But after the eighth pan,
it tasted like ashes.
Ice cream got me
through three more pans,
but after that, ashes.
Well, now you have to decide,
once and for all,
where your allegiance lies.
I'm not going back to that job.
I'm gonna stay here with you
and we're going to get even
with Jay G.
And as God is my witness,
I will not tell my wife
what I'm up to.
Oh, that's good.
BURNS:
Come on, Simpson.
Give me more ideas
to get back at Jay G.
-Fill his office with balloons?
-Too soft.
Fill his office with scorpions?
Eh, I'm having a fight
with my scorpion guy.
Oh, oh, oh.
Banana in his tailpipe.
-I can't afford a banana!
-(twig snaps)
What's that?
A spy! Grab him.
Come here, spy.
What are you doing here, boy?
You're not dead. Are you?
I followed you.
I got suspicious
when you came home last night
covered in grave dirt.
Be gone, urchin.
We have work to do.
Wait, wait! He can help.
No one's better at
nasty schemes than this kid.
I mean, he's messed up.
Look at him. You got to figure
his family life's a disaster.
Why should I help Burns
now that he's broke?
I've got more money
than he does.
Would the cape and gloves
of the infamous
Gaslight Strangler
change your mind?
If you want to take down
a rapper, you got to destroy
the thing that's most important
to him-- his rep.
(whispering)
Rep means reputation.
To do that, we got to go
to the ultimate expert
on urban culture.
A white nerd.
So, in South Central
Springfield in the '90s,
there were four major
hip-hop sub-scenes.
The Good Time Mafia,
Licorice Avenue,
The Dirty, Dirty North,
and The FLTA.
The Fine Ladies Thug Army.
Fascinating.
Yes, yes, but do you have
anything we can use
against my sworn enemy, Jay G?
Before he was Jay G,
he was Jeremy Gilroy,
a founding member
of The Five Boyfriends,
a soulful R&B quintet.
Hey, I know this guy.
He tried to sell me a $55 candle!
That's Jazzy James,
the Lyrical Miracle.
He wrote all of
Jay's early hits.
But they had a falling out,
and he was never heard from again.
Then only one man can write the rap
that will ruin the rep of Jay G.
Jazzy James.
HOMER:
I told you this guy would come back.
Told you.
Yeah, I used to be Jazzy James.
The Lyrical Miracle?
My skills were empirical.
I wrote all the rhymes for
Jay G's first hip-hop record.
I didn't get a dime, because
I signed over all the rights.
-Why'd you do that?
-(groans)
All right, all right.
I'll sign!
He took my money,
stole my girl,
made me get a tattoo of
the baseball from Major League.
It broke me. I fell hard,
into scented candles.
(inhales deeply)
(exhales) Quince.
Listen, Jazzy.
We're gonna tear down Jay G
with the ultimate revenge rap.
And you're gonna write it.
-Oh... (grunts)
-(glass shatters)
I'm in.
Excellent.
-What is... rap?
-Hmm?
Hmm.
Quick, boy! Hide this thing.
(Bart grunting)
Homie, it's so sweet of you
to come visit me at my store.
But aren't you gonna get in
trouble for missing work?
You let me worry
about the nuclear plant.
The important thing
for you to do
is believe I still work there.
I can't wait to show you
the changes I've made.
We're getting a lot of foot traffic.
Three people used
the bathroom yesterday.
How much should I charge
for these handbags
made from the speaker covers
of old jukeboxes?
Five dollars.
No, no, no, no, no.
A hundred dollars!
(gasps)
It's happening. It's happening.
I love my store!
We're putting up new wallpaper.
(grunting)
Is Mom gonna be okay?
I don't know, son,
I don't know.
MAN:
Oh, it's not her, fellas.
It's the curse of
the adorable little store.
Didn't always used to be like this.
No, no.
Once, this land was
full of actual stores,
as far as the eye could see.
Then the rich people came.
They didn't need to make money,
they just needed a place for
their friends to wander into,
after spin class.
Yeah, that's progress for you.
I suppose.
HOMER:
And so, with Jazzy James on board,
Mr. Burns set out to produce
the ultimate revenge rap.
-(hip-hop beat begins playing)
-♪ Uh, listen up, suckers ♪
♪ I'm-a say how I feel ♪
♪ My dealings with Jay G
have been less than... ideal ♪
I... (sighs)
It's-it's no use. I've lost it.
I need you to rap
like your world is ending.
Like you just found out
that capital gains
are going to be taxed at the
same rate as ordinary income.
I need you to put
your entire soul into it.
Now rhyme, Jazzy, rhyme!
I got nothin'.
Just take me back to my candles.
I need my quince!
Wait, I have another idea.
I'm feelin' it! (laughs)
I'm feelin' it!
Now, almost drop me.
(whoops)
Why does this work?
♪ ♪
♪ Jay, you're a rhyme thief ♪
♪ A hip-hop perjurer ♪
♪ If my words were beef patties ♪
♪ You'd be the Hamburglar ♪
♪ My beats are the freshest ♪
♪ You reached out and stole 'em ♪
♪ Like Gollum did precious ♪
♪ Time for the truth to be paid off ♪
♪ You're a lyrical Madoff ♪
♪ So if you want to go to war, brah ♪
♪ Hit me up
and I'll write the rap for ya ♪
-Yeah!
-Whoa, it rhymed!
(laughs)
Now that's what I call
a corking revenge rap.
If anyone's hungry,
we've set up a deli platter
-in the lobby.
-I'm hungry!
For gettin' what's mine.
Oh, ain't no deli platter
ordered for a recording session
that Praline doesn't hear about.
Mm-mm.
Praline?
She's Jay G's ex-wife.
I thought you were in prison.
That's what the guards said,
but I wasn't having that.
Oh, we duckin' now?
So that's how it is?
-(chuckles) I see.
-Oh, no, he didn't.
No, he did not.
-Shut up, Miata.
-Oh.
Put that rare roast beef
in a baggie.
Mm-hmm, that one.
So, Praline, are you
with us or against us?
Jay G took
everything from me.
You best believe I'm going
to take everything from him.
Get the ham!
We're really glad
to have you.
-Thanks for your help.
-Who you thankin'?
I'm not doing this for you,
boo boo kitty.
HOMER: With an angry ex-wife
on our team,
we were unstoppable.
Praline brought in
an all-star lineup
of Jay G's enemies
to lend their hatred
to the world's
greatest diss rap.
RZA, Snoop, and Common.
♪ Yo, I want to
back-smack Jay G, son ♪
♪ He took that name
Tang Clan from me ♪
♪ And since there couldn't be two ♪
♪ I had to change
my Tang Clan to Wu ♪
♪ I seen Jay G pimp, lie, and rob ♪
♪ Took my handyman off a job ♪
♪ And when I complained ♪
♪ All he did was laugh ♪
♪ Now I got half a gazebo,
and not even the good half ♪
♪ I would never wish hate
on my brother ♪
♪ 'Cause we're all from
the same celestial mother ♪
Wait, I just remembered
Jay crashed my Jet Ski.
I hope he get food poisoning
from nachos. Peace!
Yo, Common, that was tight.
Respect, 'House.
Oh, when this track drops,
some feelings gonna get hurt.
-Obliverated.
-Indeed.
I just wish Smithers
and his ice were here
to witness my revenge.
MEN (French Canadian accents):
Fight, fight, fight.
(men shouting)
(growls, grunts)
(all gasping)
(hip-hop playing)
Prepare for the turning
of the worms.
No offense, worms.
I now drop "Choke on Diss,"
a.k.a. "Rhyme Crime,"
by Hate Squad, featuring
the Rhyme Crime All-Stars.
Why isn't it dropping?
Release the sounds!
(honks)
-(all gasping)
-Damn!
Sorry to crash your party
as a hologram, M.B.,
but I'm having a little
celebration of my own.
I just bought
the master recording
of your so-called diss rap.
Ha, no way.
Jazzy James and Hate Squad,
featuring the Rhyme Crime
All-Stars hate you!
They'd never sell out.
They would...
for money!
Sorry, Monty.
Jay G is the best producer
in the world
and you're a tone-deaf pauper
who lives in a grave.
-Ouch.
-I thought I hated him,
but now I don't.
So now I'm here.
If you can't handle
a strong female hologram,
that's on you.
Jay G and D-O-double-G.
We flipped the script.
This ultimate betrayal
is part of your spiritual journey.
Lesson one-- protect your neck.
Say good-bye to
your revenge rap forever.
'Cause it's about to drop.
(gulps, honks)
Mmm. (kisses)
Party at the power plant, y'all.
I swear on the squid beak
of Lord Cthulhu
and all his briny shoggoths,
I will get revenge on you, Jay G.
HOMER:
And so Mr. Burns beat on,
fists against the hologram,
punching back ceaselessly
into his own face.
Which new name do you like better?
Next Doorables...
(gasps)
or the Lavender Zeppelin?
I just don't know anymore.
-(door opens, bell rings)
-(gasps) A customer!
Oh, it's you.
Baby, I'm sorry.
I stayed loyal to Mr. Burns,
coproduced a failed revenge rap,
and now we've got nothing.
(gasps)
I know it's crazy,
but he needed me.
-Oh, it's okay, Homie.
-You're not mad?
Your heart told you
to stick with Mr. Burns,
and the thing I love
about you most
is you've got a heart
as big as The Ritz.
Wow, Mom, you just made an
F. Scott Fitzgerald reference.
Lisa, please,
I did graduate high school.
(sighs)
I've just hatched a plan
for the most delicious revenge.
Simpson, we must away.
Did you want to buy that?
Just looking.
We can't afford the store anymore!
Oh, thank God.
Oh! I'm free!
(grunts)
Well, before long,
another aimless soul
will open another
adorable store here.
And when they do,
Old Sam the Sign Hanger
will be ready,
with his level and his ladder.
Oh, why,
here comes one now.
-Oh, honey, isn't it darling?
-Huh? (laughs)
We finally found
the Bookmark Barn.
-(cackling)
-Oh, this is Wicker Works.
We're gonna sell
so many Yorkie sweaters.
We can use the contractor
that did Karen's store.
HOMER:
Mr. Burns' plan was so horrifying,
I could barely shut up
and go along with it.
But I was the only friend
he had left in the world
and he was whipping me so hard.
Ow, ow!
Oh, Goosius.
Daddy's got your oatmeal.
Golden raisins, just the way
you like 'em, baby.
Goosey!
(tires screech)
Where's my goose?
Why, he's right here.
Fancy a bite of roast Goosius?
You didn't!
(laughing)
Oh, I did.
Mmm.
A trifle fatty, but other than that,
excellent.
Damn, I didn't think
you had it in you, M.B.
(sobbing) Oh, man.
I don't want to live in a world
without the mascot
of my multinational empire.
(sobs)
(Goosius honking,
Homer grunting)
Stop it!
I saved your life, you stupid duck!
Simpson,
I told you to cook his goose.
I couldn't do it.
We just had our portrait done.
(honks)
Then, what did I eat?
Roast goose from
the gas station.
-Fine, then I'll kill it myself.
-(gasps)
(honking)
HOMER: The two rivals found
themselves doomed by the lusts
that drive all men-- money, power,
and the pursuit of a goose.
(groans)
(honking)
Damn it, Monty, I don't want to die.
Well, if we have to end this way,
at least it's of natural causes--
a business deal gone wrong.
(creaking)
-(shouts)
-Tell me, Jay.
Why'd you betray me?
We were kindred souls.
Brothers in avarice.
Why?
Because you told me to!
In your own last chapter.
"You will never be truly ruthless
until you destroy the one
who made you."
I had to tear you down, M.B.!
It was the final rung.
I just wanted to be ruthless,
like you.
That I inspired you to such
pure and evil greed,
that is my greatest triumph.
I am truly immortal.
We're about to die, fool.
(yelling)
Smithers, I ordered ice, not slush.
Sorry I'm late, sir.
A few of these
French Canadian bikers
got delayed at the border.
Apparently, I'm their leader now.
Smithers, Smithers, Smithers!
(chuckles)
Ow. That stings.
Oh, that one's nice.
How dare you.
Fascinating.
BOTH: Excellent.
HOMER: Mr. Burns realized
that his ruthless will to power
would beat on forever
in another man's heart.
Ah, I guess this summer's really over.
(crying)
I'm gonna miss Goosius.
Aah!
Thanks, boy.
Do you think Mr. Burns
learned anything from all this?
Could it have changed him
for the better?
You know what?
I have a feeling it did.
BURNS (over P.A.): Attention.
For the sheer joy of it,
every day will now include a
moment of musical appreciation.
♪ Music makes the whole world ♪
♪ Whole world ♪
Mm, let's not do this tomorrow.
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Go round, hey ♪
♪ Ah-ah-ha ♪
(hip-hop version
of Simpsons theme playing)
Shh!
(female group sings
Gracie Films theme)
Subtitled by Post Haste Digital