♪ The Simpsons ♪
(chalk screeches)
(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(tires screeching)
(horn honks)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
(laughing)
Why, Homer, you silly goose,
the weed whacker's just
for the edges.
-You're gonna be out here all day.
-I'm almost done.
You are a picture and a half.
(chuckles)
Well, if you're finished
by tomorrow, come on over
and strap on the feedbag.
We're gonna fire up
ol' Propane Elaine
and put the heat to the meat.
-Nummy-nummy-num!
-I'll be there!
Notty-notty-not.
"The Flanders are having
a beef-a-thon!
Incredible Nedibles!
Maudacious Vittles!"
Hmm, I think it means
he's having a barbecue.
Well, why doesn't
he just say so?
He's trying to be friendly.
You know, if you gave
Ned Flanders a chance--
Oh, here we go again.
Look, I don't care
if Ned Flanders is
the nicest guy in the world.
He's a jerk.
End of story.
Well, we can't
hold it against him
just because he has things
a little better than we do.
Excuse me? Better?
Thanks a lot, Marge.
You really put me in my place.
-Oh, Homer.
-Don't get me wrong.
It's worth feeling
three inches tall
to find out what kind
of a person you really are,
Marge Simpson,
president of the international
"We Love Flanders" Fan Club!
(both growling)
Fee, fie, foe, fum!
I smell the potatoes au gratin
of Marge Simpson.
Mm-mm-mm-mmm!
Hi, Ned.
Um... Homer sends
his apologies
but, um...
there was some important work
at the plant
that only he
could take care of.
MAN (on TV): We now return you
to exciting 15th-round action
at the Canadian Football
League draft.
And so, the Saskatchewan
Rough Riders,
who scored only four rouges
all last season, Jack...
Stupid Flanders.
Go ahead, Marge.
Have a ball.
What if they came back
and I was dead from not eating?
They'd cry their eyes out.
"We should have never gone
to the Flanders'.
"Oh, why did we go
to the Flanders' house
and leave Homer alone
with no food?"
And I'd be laughing--
laughing from my grave.
Heh, heh, heh.
(sizzling)
(barks)
What is it, boy? What?
(sniffs)
Mmm.
Barbecue.
(both panting)
Ahh.
Mmm.
Hey, everyone, I'm back.
Nice to see you. Nice to meet you.
-Hey!
-Oh!
Hey, hey, Homer!
-(muttering)
-Okay. Thanks for coming.
-You're it.
-Electricity.
No electricity.
Electricity only in freeze tag.
Okay. Now you're it!
-Hey! No tag-backs!
-Yeah, you cheater.
You lie like a fly
with a booger in its eye.
(chuckling)
The fly was funny,
and the booger
was the icing on the cake.
Friends, we love you all,
but I also have
a sinister motive
for asking you all here--
sinister being Latin
for left-handed.
(chuckling)
But enough joking.
-That was a joke?
-Shh!
As of Friday,
I'm saying toodle-loo
to the pharmaceutical game.
-Leaving? I can't believe it.
-What's he talkin' about?
No, I kid you not. Here's the noose
I had to wear for ten years.
-(oohs and ahhs)
-(applause)
What are you going to do, Ned?
Well, sir, like one out
of every nine Americans,
I'm left-handed,
and let me tell you
it ain't all peaches
and cream.
Your writing gets smeared,
Lord help you if you want to
drive a standard transmission.
-Amen to that.
-Well, sir,
I'm opening up
a one-stop store for southpaws.
Everything from
left-handed apple peelers
to left-handed zithers.
Going to call it
"The Leftorium."
-(oohs and ahhs)
-(applause)
So, Homer,
I'm dying to know.
What do you think
of The Leftorium?
It sounds like
a pretty dumb idea to me.
Well, I know it's
a little risky,
and it's going to be
a lot of hard work,
but, gosh darn it, it's going
to be a lot of fun too.
Fun? Where is this store,
Flanders?
The merry old Land of Oz?
Oh, no. The Springfield Mall.
-Oh, here, you two, make a wish.
-Nah!
-It's fun.
-No, it isn't.
Hey, you must have something
you want to wish for, Homer.
Hmm, let's see...
Nah.
Hmm...
-Hey!
-Come on, Homer.
I've got an ambition
to do some wishin'.
Keep your pants on,
Flanders!
I'm wishing as fast as I can!
Ooh!
Heh, heh, heh, heh.
Eh... too far.
Hmm...
Okay, ready.
Yes! Oh, yes!
Read it and weep!
In your face!
-I've got more chicken bone!
-What did you wish for, Homer?
No! No, no, no.
Don't say.
Otherwise,
it won't come true.
Ooh, that would be a shame.
Wouldn't it, Flanders?
(sinister laughter)
(maniacal laughter)
(choking)
(Homer coughs, exhales)
♪ They fight and fight ♪
♪ They fight
and fight and fight ♪
♪ Fight-fight-fight,
fight-fight-fight ♪
♪ The Itchy & Scratchy Show ♪
("O Sole Mio" playing)
Mmm.
(gasping)
(screaming)
♪ Dum-da-dah... ♪
Duh!
(snickering)
(laughing)
Bart!
How many hours a day
do you watch TV?
Six-- seven if there's
something good on.
Don't you think you should get a little
fresh air and maybe some exercise?
Yeah, but what are
you going to do?
Marge, TV gives so much
and asks so little.
It's a boy's best friend.
That's the problem.
Even as we speak,
millions of children
are staring at the TV,
instead of getting
some much-needed exercise.
Those children's parents should be
ashamed of themselves.
(gong sounds on TV)
Hello, I am Akira. Huah!
That didn't hurt very much
because I know the ancient art
of karate.
Karate focuses the mind
and gives one self-confidence.
People from all walks of life:
-Doctors.
-Hi-yah!
-Homemakers.
-Hu-yah!
-Landscape architects.
-Huh-yah!
-Choreographers.
-Haww.
AKIRA: High karate
at low, low prices.
I cannot tell a lie.
This is a great deal. Hohh!
-ALL: Ha!
-(gong sounds)
Hey, Mom, how about
if I learn karate?
Will that make you happy?
That sounds fine, Bart.
See, Marge, you knock TV,
and then it helps you out.
I think you owe somebody
a little apology.
(grumbles)
(cries out)
Well, if it isn't
The Leftorium.
Hey, Flanders,
how's business?
Oh, a little pokey
but things are going
to pick up.
-(crash)
-Ooh! Oh!
I am so sorry.
How much do I owe you?
Now, you put that money away.
That was an accident.
Really?
Well, thanks.
Could you validate my parking?
Absitively posolutely.
(chuckles)
So, Flanders,
have you sold anything?
Not yet, but one
of the mall security guards
took a good long look
-at a left-handed ice cream scoop.
-(scoffs)
Greetings, I am Akira,
your guide on the path
to true karate.
And this is our map,
The Art of War by Sun-Tzu.
It will teach us
our most important lesson.
We learn karate
so that we need never use it.
Um, excuse me sir.
I already know
how not to hit a guy.
Can we break out
the nunchukas?
Yes, the impetuousness
of youth.
-For now, let us read.
-Akira, my good man,
when do we break blocks
of ice with our heads?
First you must fill your head
with wisdom.
Then, you can hit ice with it.
Yo, Sensei,
can I go to the bathroom?
You can
if you believe you can.
Pay money to read books.
(scoffs)
The hell with this.
(grunting)
Come on. Touch of death!
Touch of death! Touch of death!
Touch of death.
(ghostly moaning)
(laughing)
(Homer laughing)
I'm telling you,
Flanders' store was dee-serted.
So, what do you think of your
bestest buddy now, Marge?
-(Marge grumbles)
-Dad, do you know what schadenfreude is?
No, I do not know
what schadenfreude is.
Please tell me,
because I'm dying to know.
It's a German term
for "shameful joy."
Taking pleasure
in the suffering of others.
Oh, come on, Lisa. I'm just
glad to see him fall flat on his butt.
He's usually all happy
and comfortable
and surrounded by loved ones,
and it makes me feel--
What's the opposite of that
"shameful joy" thing of yours?
Sour grapes.
Boy, those Germans have
a word for everything.
So Bart, what did you learn
in karate school today?
Yeah, come on, boy, this better
be worth my ten bucks.
Uh... I learned
the touch of death.
-Ooh, the touch of death.
-Permit me to demonstrate.
Lisa, shut your eyes.
Soon you will be at peace.
-Hey, quit it, Bart. Quit it. Hey!
-(Bart vocalizing)
Quit it! Quit it!
Quit it! Quit it! Mom!
Bart, don't use the touch
of death on your sister.
(screaming)
♪ They fought and fit ♪
♪ They fought
and fought and fit ♪
♪ Fought-fought-fought,
fit-fit-fit ♪
♪ The Itchy and Scratchy Show ♪
Uh-oh! Got to get back
to karate class.
(grunts)
-Missed a spot.
-Dopey kid.
Alright, coming through.
Outta my way. Move it or lose it.
-Step aside, lady.
-Mmm, baby.
Hey, boy.
How was class?
Today, we learned how
to rip a man's heart out
and show it to him
before he dies.
Ooh, that will learn him.
What did you swipe?
An "I Love Lefty" shot-glass.
-Left-handed pinking shears.
-Pinking shears?
Let's go to the food court
and steal some baked potatoes.
(glass shatters)
Hey, Flanders,
when are your busy hours?
Oh, I expect things to start
picking up soon.
Yeah, I think word of mouth
is starting to spread.
Hey, I hear you validate
parking tickets without purchase.
Oh, right as rain.
Or as we say around here,
"left as rain." (chuckles)
-Just stamp the ticket.
-Okay.
(gulping)
Hey, Homer, how's your
neighbor's store doing?
Lousy.
He just sits there all day.
He'd have a great job
if he didn't own the place.
(laughing)
Crummy right-handed corkscrews.
What does he sell?
Uh, well, actually, Moe, uh...
I don't know.
(chattering on TV)
-Hey, Lise, change the channel.
-You change it.
-(vocalizing)
-Okay, okay.
(gunshots and sirens on TV)
I grow weary
of this new channel.
-Change it back.
-But, Bart...
(vocalizing)
Apple... apple... apple...
Come on, candy bar.
Hey, I know you.
You're that first apple I didn't want!
That sinks it.
I'm really going
to let them have it this time.
Simpson, put that box
on Mr. Burns' desk.
Chop-chop!
(grunting)
Oh, look, Smithers
another member
of our nuclear family
with some helpful
suggestions.
And what's your name?
Homer Simpson, sir.
Simpson, eh?
Mm-hmm. I'm Monty Burns.
Ehh...
"Keep that handsome owner
out of sight.
He's distracting
the female employees."
(chuckles)
Smithers?
Got me, sir.
(chuckles)
Oh, it's a real one.
"No more apples
in the vending machine, please."
Well, that's almost a sentence.
(laughs)
-Can I leave, Mr. Burns?
-Oh, of course, and don't worry,
there will be plenty
of apples for you.
Nobody will take away
your precious apples.
But the note was
asking you to...
No, no, no!
Tell my secretary
I said you could have
a free apple.
She'll make everything all right,
I promise. (chuckles)
(grunting)
Damned infernal gizmo.
My kingdom for
a left-handed can opener!
Uh, Mr. Burns?
Come on, Homer,
tell him about the store.
I'm dying out here.
Sorry, Flanders.
Huh?
Are you sure
you're not interested?
$200 is only
the asking price.
-Sorry, Ned.
-Hey, I'm flexible.
You don't have to pay
all at once.
I'll be here all night,
if you change your mind.
Hey, Flanders,
is everything okay?
Oh, yeah, sure. Thought I'd just
get rid of some of the clutter.
See anything you like?
Oh, I get it.
It's not good enough for you,
but it's good enough for me?
Well, I wouldn't be caught
dead buying this-- Hello.
Got your eye on
the gas grill, huh?
-She's a butane beaut.
-I'll give you 20 bucks for it.
Twenty? Homer, I paid $300
for this just last year.
You were swindled, my friend.
Twenty bucks. Take it or leave it.
-Oh, Homer, be reasonable.
-Sorry!
No cash for Neddy.
Homer keep all money.
Bye-bye, Neddy. Bye-bye.
(sighs)
All right, Homer.
-$20?
-$20.
-Now I don't want it.
-What?
I changed my mind.
It was a passing fancy.
Although, perhaps if you
threw in a few lawn chairs,
maybe that tool bench,
it might rekindle my interest.
Hey, Bartely-boobely.
Care for a steakarooni?
Sounds scrum-diddley-umptious,
dear old duddely-doodely.
-(laughing) Duddely-doodely.
-(both laugh)
Homer, this is the Flanders'
entire living room set.
How much did you pay
for this?
Only 75 beans.
$75? Ned must be desperate.
I'm sure you did nothing
to discourage this,
you scavenger of human misery.
Hey! Keep your hands off
my china hutch.
♪ Let's go
to Barney's Bowl-er-ama... ♪
(doorbell ringing)
Good afternoon, sir.
I'm Chuck Ellis
from the Springfield
Collection Agency,
and I'm here to ask you
why you don't think
you need to pay your bills.
Oh, I know I need to pay them,
but there's just so many.
Does it make you feel good about
yourself to owe people money?
We've been very patient
with you, Mr. Flanders.
I know, but--
Wait a minute.
I'm Homer Simpson.
Ned Flanders lives over there.
-Oh.
-Flanders is in debt? Are you sure?
We don't make mistakes.
Damned right-handed ledgers.
-I can't write in these things.
-Why, there's a store where you--
-Hey, you said you're Homer Simpson?
-Yeah.
-See you on Thursday.
-D'oh!
Knock 'em dead, boy.
Kid's going to be
a black belt in no time.
(gasping)
(crying)
Ohh...
♪♪
Hey, check out the saxophone.
Pretty boss, but there's
something stuck on it.
Hey!
(plays sour notes)
Hey, look at me.
I'm Elvis, man!
You give that back!
That belongs to me!
If you want it,
just take it.
(boys laughing)
Okay. We're sorry.
This time we're really
going to give it to you.
Hey, stop that!
(boys laughing)
(Lisa crying)
Hey, Lise, something wrong?
Not anymore!
You punks are about to get
a taste of your own medicine.
This is my brother,
and he knows karate.
-Uh-oh.
-Oh, we're real scared.
Please don't hurt us, Bart.
What are you going to do?
Throw your diapers at us?
(laughter)
-(moaning)
-Yeah, just keep laughing.
It only makes him madder.
C'mon Bart. Start them off
with the touch of death
and go from there.
I think they've learned
their lesson already, Lise.
No, we want to see
the touch of death.
Yeah. Come on, Karate Kid,
waste me.
(group laughs)
It's funny how two wrongs
sometimes make a right.
Homer! Over here.
Flanders, I want to give you
your stuff back.
Well, there's no house
to put it in, Homer.
Not since that nice fellow
from the bank--
who was only doing his job--
came and locked it up.
You're gonna live in your car?
Oh, no. It's just
a little camp-out tonight,
then off to my sister's
apartment in Capital City.
Hey, what do you think, kids?
-The big city.
-(cheering)
(chuckles)
Say, Todd, I want to talk
to your Uncle Homer.
You're head of the car
till I get back.
Okay, Dad.
♪ Grey skies
are gonna clear up ♪
♪ Put on a happy face ♪
♪ Brush off the clouds
and cheer up ♪
♪ Put on a happy face... ♪
Oh, listen to that singing.
Those poor fools.
Homer, I'm ruined.
I know.
At times like these
I used to turn to the Bible
and find solace,
but even the good book
-can't help me now.
-Why not?
-I sold it to you for seven cents.
-Oh.
You know,
ever since that barbecue,
nothing's gone right.
It's like there's been
a curse on me.
(sobbing)
It's all my fault.
-No, it's not.
-Yes, it is.
No! You tried to warn me
about gambling
my family's future
on some pig in a poke.
I didn't listen.
Homer, you were a true friend.
-No, I was a swine.
-(both sobbing)
-Listen, Flanders.
-What?
Do you still have that store?
For two more days.
Then it becomes
Libertarian Party headquarters.
I hope they have better luck
than I did.
Flanders, you open
that store tomorrow.
Oh, Homer, there's no point.
I said do it!
Hello, Jerry? Homer Simpson.
Remember last month
when I paid back that loan?
Well, now I need you
to do a favor for me.
A left-handed corkscrew?
Oh, baby!
"Kiss me, I'm left-handed"?
(laughs)
That's a classic.
Whoa!
-Homer Simpson's on the phone.
-Tell him I went out.
He needs you
to help Ned Flanders.
Ned Flanders is in trouble?
Smithers, I'm licked.
You open this can.
Okay, but you softened
it up for me, sir.
Hold it, Smithers.
-I'll open the can.
-But, sir, how?
To the mall!
I'll explain on the way.
Hurry, Neddy, hurry.
Oh, golly, it's a miracle.
HOMER:
Come on, ya' lefties.
Oh! What did I tell you?
-(chuckles)
-Homer?
It's all here,
and it's all backwards.
That's right.
(excited voices buzzing)
Well, the worm has turned,
has it not, my tin-plated friend?
Look at you--
you who were once so proud.
Feel the wrath
of the left hand of Burns.
My life begins today.
Wow! What an icebreaker.
Left-handed ledgers.
Now, I can write
all the way to the edge.
(laughs)
Left-handed nunchukas.
Wow!
The boys at the Diners Club
will think I've gone quite mad.
Oh, I'll have that roadster
in the corner as well.
(crowd gasps)
-Yes, sir.
-Huzzah for the shopkeep.
ALL: Huzzah!
Homer, affordable tract housing
made us neighbors,
but you made us friends.
To Ned Flanders,
the richest left-handed man
in town.
-(strums)
-Everybody!
♪ Grey skies are
gonna clear up ♪
♪ Stick out that noble chin ♪
♪ Wipe off
that full-of-doubt look ♪
♪ Slap on a happy grin ♪
♪ And spread sunshine
all over the place ♪
♪ Just put on a happy face ♪
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.