Worth it.
- Totally worth it.
- Again!
Dinnertime!
Dad, are you gonna
watch the solar eclipse?
Sorry, but this is
pork chop night.
Way to go, God!
Aah! My eyes!
I told you to use
the cardboard box!
I thought you meant
for standing on.
Marge, you gonna eat
that piece of burnt gristle?
- No.
- Whoo-hoo!
Homer!
Did you pour fry pan grease
into the milk carton?
- Yes, but it's not for...
- Just a splash for my coffee.
I wanted to watch
the eclipse with you.
I can only imagine
what you've got planned
for date night tomorrow.
Date night?!
Marge, if we're still dating,
why in the world
do we have these kids?
What?
Hey!
You need to make me feel
you're as smitten with me
as you were when we met.
Marge, darling,
you mean as much to me
as the sun and the moon.
There was an eclipse of the sun
by the moon,
and you didn't even
walk outside.
Come on, Marge,
you can't be that mad.
Marge wants a date night
this Saturday.
You think you've got problems?
I'm really not liking
this new bar mix.
This Saturday? Is she crazy?
That's when we spray nitrous
in the ant farm
and watch 'em go nuts.
Yeah, here's a taste.
Stupid ants.
Maybe I could have
a date night here.
Sure. I'll make it nice.
Take the paint cans
out of the ladies' room,
just like
the Waldorf Hysteria there.
I don't know what to do.
I want it to be perfect.
I've spent so long ignoring
how she thinks and feels.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's a real crotch-22 there.
You know, Moe, a lot
of what you think you're saying,
you're not really saying.
Well, I got to admit,
I've been doing
a little of this nitrous myself.
Stupid ants.
My funny valentine
Sweet comic valentine
You make me smile
With my heart
Your looks are laughable
You didn't have to do that.
That and much, much more.
Corkage fee.
$30 dollars?
Corkage is the sum we charge
for opening the wine
you bring, sir.
30 bucks to open a box?!
I mean, nothing's too good
for this lady.
- Play the violin.
- I am just a waiter, sir.
I said play the violin.
After dinner drinks.
I feel like
Mrs. Remington Steele.
Con te partiro
Paesi
Che non ho mai...
I want you.
I want you!
And I want you. Only you.
What the...?
Sweetie, I think
you'd better see who it is.
Homer, I know it's late
and you've got your
Keep Out, Flanders sign up,
but, I'm sorry, I...
I'm feeling mighty low, sir.
- Who is it, Homie?
- It's stupid no one.
Flanders? What's wrong?
Marge, it's date night!
That's a made-up thing.
Lukewarm water.
If I close my eyes,
I can pretend
I'm at the dentist.
Afterwards, I'll grab
some Flintstone vitamins
and try to knock myself out.
Half a Bamm-Bamm should do it.
Ned, what happened?
I'm out of work.
The Leftorium is no-morium.
Hey, Ned.
I can't hack it anymore.
You want to buy
my side of the kiosk?
I'll get all the people
coming out of Sears!
But I got squat.
People are getting all
their southpaw sundries online.
All I was getting were
right-handed college students
who wanted to experiment.
Don't worry, Ned.
Homer will tell you
how to get a job at the plant.
- I will?
- Yes, you will.
- Because it's date night.
- You said that wasn't a thing.
- Let's not fight on date night.
- Oh, all right.
Call the plant and ask
for Human Resources.
Oh, thank you.
And as a reward,
you get my famous cocoa.
Now, I assume the two of you
will want a cup?
Make my next one a double.
I cannot be your head
of Human Resources
one more second, okay?
With the verbal abuse
and the physical abuse,
and the lying under oath.
And especially this!
Would you like to be
the new head of Human Resources?
To quote my pet turtle,
shell yes!
Not so fast.
You may have to give me blood
from time to time.
Yes, sir.
My blood's like my attitude.
- B-positive.
- Excellent.
Isn't this great?
We're carpooling to work.
So I can see you
in the morning, at work,
in the evening,
and in my dreams,
thanking you
for saving my life.
Look, Ned,
we're just driving together.
I don't want any iddlies,
diddlies,
neighborinos
or oopsy-doopsies.
- Okily-dokily.
- Here's another suggestion.
No talk, just music.
Oh, sure. That's why I brought
this CD of Christian favorites,
Magical Ministry Tour.
Pray, pray, heart and soul
Stick another dime
in the poor box, baby
Maybe we should talk.
Well, of course, my friend.
- Want to talk about Jesus?
- No.
- Want to talk about Ecclesiastes?
Want to talk about baby Jesus?
Pray, pray, heart and soul
Stick another dime
and I'll pray with thee
Let's crank it up to six.
You'll notice on your paycheck,
we've adjusted for desk rental
and electrical power usage.
Isn't this a power plant?
As defined by the IRS,
we are a religion.
And that is the last question
you'll ask of me.
I will break you in one day.
Now we're gonna do
a little role-playing
with Smitty and Jacqueline.
Smitty, pretend
you're greeting her.
Have a good one.
Okay, stop right there.
A good one, what?
An unspecified object
is the devil's wordplay,
so I say, come and go
with a hidely-ho!
What a wuss.
I can hear you.
Did you help this wuss
get this job?
I just told him who to call.
And you didn't put in
a good word?
- No.
- You idiot.
A recommendation from you
would've sunk him for sure.
Okay, what happens
if I touch her?
Go ahead.
Hey, good work today.
This hardly seems fair!
Your behavior is obnoxious
and offensive.
You'll be working for me
in a different capacity.
- What are you doing, Lisa?
- Making an art project.
- You color very neatly.
- Thank you.
Pride's a sin.
So is snitching to God, Rod.
I'm Todd. I think.
Homer. Homer.
Hey, hey!
Homer, you were
sleeping at work.
I had to mop up your drool.
Leave me alone.
To beef up team spirit,
I thought I'd form
a little prayer circle
at lunch.
If you pray at lunch,
aren't you interrupting
God's lunch?
Finally,
someone thinks about God.
Todd, do you have
anything else you can do?
- Can I pray for you?
- If you do it silently.
Dear Lord, let Lisa avoid
the cleansing fire foretold by
the Council of Nicaea
before they got leprosy!
- That's not silently!
- You have such great hearing.
I miss Milhouse.
I knew if I switched
from white to dark socks,
things would start happening.
You wanted to see me?
I happen to know
your father didn't die.
Look, Ned, you have to learn
the way things work around here.
People cut corners.
You have to let things slide.
Let me repeat.
Sorry, Homer,
I can't cut you any slack.
I owe it to you to help you
achieve your potential.
Maybe you could help get me
another job at the plant.
One where you don't have to
show up, like safety inspector.
But you are
the safety inspector.
Then I should really
return these things
that have fallen down my back.
They look like gummy worms,
but they're not.
I can't take it.
I can't take it!
Why can't he be like
our neighbor on the other side,
who we never see?
What's the matter, Homie?
Oh, no. No. No.
Oh, Lord, it's Homer Simpson.
I forget. Are you seven hours
ahead or behind?
Whatever. I really need
your help with Flanders.
Could you please get him fired?
I feel you. Thanks.
Oh, I reached him.
So, looking through the records,
I discovered this company has
never given anything to charity.
In fact, it looks as if
we've actually taken money
from charities.
Ned, would you mind
if I brought a few associates
into this meeting?
Well, no.
- You're fired!
- Nice boy, nice boy!
You're welcome
to keep any radiation
that seeped into your bones.
Speaking of charity,
call the orphanage, Smithers.
We have some leaks in our pipes
and need tiny hands
to plug them.
They said they wouldn't
send you any children, sir.
They have to say that.
I want to thank you, Homer.
You've been a true blue friend.
Can we talk about something fun?
I now weigh more than Fat Elvis.
Well, I know
I got one advantage you don't.
I got Homer Simpson
in my corner.
Ned,
I have a confession to make.
Now don't go
turning Catholic on me.
I can't.
I don't fit in those booths.
Don't worry about me.
I'm sure there's a job out there
for a Bob Jones University grad
who majored in teaching
and casting out demons
and who speaks fluent Aramaic.
Wish Mr. Burns
didn't send these home with you.
A word to the wise,
don't be cocky.
Don't say you can lifeguard
if you can't swim.
It'll come up, believe me.
One, two, three.
Make sure you keep at least
five Bibles between you.
Oh, don't got crazy,
Patrick Swayze.
Time to put Baby in the corner.
You can't pose for your
cover photo like that.
Much better.
Ned, would you like
to say grace?
Heavenly Father,
thank you for the blessing
of being tested, losing my wife,
losing my second wife,
losing four jobs,
and losing $23
at blackjack to Bart.
23 chips, so $2,300.
- I'll finish grace at home.
- Can you do that?
Yes, I can do that!
Oh, God, now the apologies
are gonna start.
I apologize
for my tone of voice,
and for the things I said.
And now, as penance,
I will get that skunk
out of your birdhouse.
I don't care what you say, Marge.
We got to help him!
I want to help him.
Good, good.
The ice queen begins to thaw.
Oh, Lord, give me a sign
you're still with me.
Poor Ned.
It really helps
to eat your feelings.
I've got it!
I know what job Ned can do!
Well, go tell him.
He goes to bed in five minutes.
Ned, Ned!
You should be what Jesus was!
- A carpenter?
- No.
- Fisherman?
- Foot washer?
- No.
- Wine creator?
- Water walker?
- No.
- Superstar?
- Dashboard ornament?
- No! A teacher.
I think you should be a teacher.
Like Jesus.
Lord, should I do it?
And you shall receive it.
He's looking right at us,
and he's not doing a thing!
Duffman hates Duffmankind!
Oh, yeah!
Up in the morning
and out to school
The teacher is teaching
the golden rule
American history
and practical math
You studying hard...
I promised I wouldn't cry
on his first day of school.
Let's play the frozen game.
So, rub-a-dub-dub,
30 kids and their sub.
Let's be friends, shall we?
Teacher, teacher, you must quit.
You can't teach us math or lit.
There's no mercy in the bunch.
We will make you leave by lunch.
Martin Prince?
Were you in on that poem?
Oh, they paid me.
A gig's a gig.
Well, sir, I'm not scared off.
I got two little wild things
at home.
Now, who can name
the state capitals?
A dingus.
Well, in that case, I'm
the biggest dingus in the world.
Okay, then,
let's give Mr. Flanders
a room 4F salute.
Simpson, take the kill shot.
Why me?
- Prove your loyalty.
- My loyalty to what?
To peer pressure.
Bart Simpson, I know you...
we've been fishing together,
we've gone to church together...
and if you can fire that spit
wad after our long relationship,
I don't deserve to be a teacher.
Last lesson, kids.
F is for foolish
and failure and Flanders.
You win.
Yes?
Look, what is your deal?
Do you like me?
Do you want to be like me?
Lisa, I have something
to show you.
- What?
- I made you a little house.
There's me praying.
There's you at the computer.
I made you a saxophone
out of dried macaroni,
and the crackers on the roof,
they're solar panels.
Todd, I had you all wrong.
You're a wonderful kid,
and I'm happy
to call you my pal.
So glad I have a friend.
I'm really sick of my brother.
Okay, that's enough.
What's the matter, Homer?
I think I ruined Flanders' life.
Join the club.
What are you doing here?
I come here for a G&T,
gumball and talk.
Here you go, pal.
Listen, you've got
to apologize to Flanders.
Why don't you apologize
to Flanders?
You're the one who prayed
for him to get fired.
What? He should apologize to me,
because he...
well, he...
he makes me feel so damn guilty!
All right, I'll apologize too.
What's she doing here?
Hello.
She's my designated driver.
Hey, fellas.
What brings you here?
We came to say we're sorry,
and we want you
to go back to teaching.
Oh, with all I've been through,
I've never questioned my faith
until now.
You spit-wadded
my moustache, boy.
I think you could be
a great teacher.
Almost as good as her.
Thank you, son.
Remember, if you can
teach one kid one thing,
then today will be a success.
She never gave up.
- Neither will I.
- Great.
Now, this counts
as a parent-teacher conference
and a Christmas concert.
Well, that's all well and good,
but I got to get those kids
to respect me.
Do people respect God?
No, they fear him.
It's never personal,
just business.
Just leave everything to me.
Listen up, children.
If you push hard enough
on the pudding skin, there's
a tough cup of vanilla beneath.
- Now take your seats.
- How you gonna make us?
I won't.
The good Lord will.
The scariest thing is
we don't have a class skeleton!
Truly, God is the biggest bully
of them all.
Amen.
Now, Nelson,
I'm not gonna ask you to stand
and read me a list
of state capitals,
but the good Lord
might be pleased.
Albany, Annapolis, Atlanta,
Augusta, Austin, Baton Rouge...
Does the Lord hear
the bell up there?
Yes, son, he does.
Thank you, Bart.
I knew, deep within you,
there was a good boy,
and I respectfully request
that those be
the last two pranks you pull.
You know it, man.
Wow, they're quiet.
I'm reaching them.
Edna was right.
Does that
cute school nurse
know that I'm alive?
Because last time I left
her office, I was legally dead.
I have to beat Terri
to a training bra.
I wonder how much
I can sell Maggie for.
I'm starting to think this
wheel doesn't go anywhere.