Come on, everybody.
Time for the family portrait.
(toys squeaking and rattling)
Let’s bunch together now.
Here we go.
Move it!
Perfecto.
Everybody smile.
I’m going to set
the automatic timer.
Almost ready.
Here we go.
Let’s get this show
on the road, man.
We got things
to do.
Yeah, Dad.
Okay, here we go.
Make room
for Jumbo.
-What’d you say?
-Nothing.
All right, everybody,
squeeze in real tight.
I want to get us all in
the picture this time.
Closer.
Closer!
Okay, hold still.
This is the last
picture on the roll.
Praise the Lord.
You watch your mouth,
you little smart-ass.
LISA:
Yeah, Bart.
Nothing’s going
to ruin this one.
The timer’s a-ticking.
Bart’s making
faces, Dad.
Bart!
This one’s going to be
the Simpsons at our finest.
Smile, look cheerful.
Here we go.
Why, you little...
MARGE:
Kitty cat.
Elmo.
Um... uh...
Watering can.
(gasping)
This is a nightmare.
We’re getting blown
out of the water.
Eh, what can I say?
Maggie and I share
a special bond.
School bus?
Bart and Lisa?
Bart and Lisa are
almost home from school,
and we have a dentist
appointment at 3:00.
Thanks, Maggie.
We win by forfeit.
The sweetest win
there is.
(puffing noisily)
(starter motor revving)
It won’t start.
I’ll just use Homer’s
AAA card.
American Applesauce Association?
We’re going to have to run.
There isn’t even time
to stretch my quads.
My quads!
Every stride is a nightmare!
(yodeling theme from
Raising Arizona playing)
-Whoops.
-Aww.
(nervous chuckle)
WIGGUM:
Ow!
How you holding up, Maggie?
(truck horn honking)
(screaming)
(yelling)
(horn honking)
(yodeling continues)
(yelping)
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
(squeaking, snarling)
Hey, Marge.
Oh! Ah! Oh! Oh!
(bagpipes playing)
(leprechaun speaking gibberish)
(barking)
MARGE:
We’re gonna make it.
(panting)
Marge Simpson, I just heard the
most delicious piece of gossip.
MARGE:
Tell me later!
(yelling)
Oh, hi, kids.
You’re just in time
to go to the dentist.
Dentist?
You said we were going to ride
dirt bikes around the cemetery.
Oh, Bart, you fall for
that every six months.
Hey, suckers,
check it out.
Marge is taking me
to ride dirt bikes
at the cemetery.
You’re going to the
dentist, too, Dad.
Why the cemetery, I wondered,
but my dreams were too strong.
(drill whirring)
Ah...
Mr. Simpson, have you
been flossing regularly?
Absolutely.
All the time.
I go to the floss store
and they’re like,
"Whoa, there he is again."
(nervous chuckle):
’Cause I buy
so much floss.
Let’s just get started.
Oh, my God! My gums!
They hurt so much!
I haven’t started yet.
I know, but a breeze
from the window
went in my mouth.
(sighs)
(screaming)
(screaming continues)
You butcher!
Don’t worry, sweetie.
I’m sure that man has
some special tooth problem.
HOMER:
I don’t even have
a special tooth problem!
This is just a routine checkup!
(screaming continues)
Oh, the bib is choking me!
(with normal voice):
It’s over?
(chuckles):
That wasn’t so bad.
This tape explains
oral hygiene
in a way that’s
exciting for kids.
(hip-hop style announcer):
Damn, baby got bacteria.
You want to stick it
to these whiteys?
Hey, I’m down
with OPP--
"Ongoing periodontal
problems."
Break it down.
(upbeat music playing)
MAN:
Hey, you low-life degenerates,
stop illin’ with the fillin’.
Luda-Crest.
♪ I’m the enemy of the cavity ♪
♪ Unstoppable like gravity ♪
♪ So brush with regularity ♪
♪ Or you will face calamity ♪
♪ I’ll see ya in Atlanta, GA ♪
♪ Dirty, dirty mouth, y’all. ♪
This film is against
tooth decay,
but it also kind
of glamorizes it.
Mixed signals, hmm...
This is the greatest
movie ever.
Dad, that’s Ludicrous!
I have a right to my views.
No! I mean Chris
"Ludacris" Bridges,
right here in
the dental plaza!
Hey, man,
that video was made
for a onetime only showing
in Canada, understand?
Do ya?
I’m sorry. There must have been
some sort of misunder...
Expect a letter from
Cap In The Ass Productions
and its head legal counsel,
Ms. Melissa Burlingame!
Peace out!
Here’s a free toothbrush.
Keep those teeth clean.
So you’re saying I should do
your job for you,
at home, for free.
You wish.
(humming)
WOMAN:
Okay, Principal Skinner,
I want you to relax.
Just lie completely
at ease
while I administer
the nitrous.
I shall.
(breathes deeply)
The dentist will
be here in a minute.
He’ll know exactly
what he’s doing.
Don’t resist
in any way.
(whistling)
(evil chuckle)
(humming)
Good afternoon,
Principal Stinkface.
Dr. Bart.
Let’s see...
according to your charts,
you’re due for your annual
throat scraping.
Uh-oh, I’m feeling a lot
of cooties down there.
We may need to replace a tooth.
(groans)
Now rinse.
Finally, I’m going
to take an X-ray
so lie perfectly still
for 20 minutes.
(machine buzzing)
Don’ you love that
clean mouth feeling?
Sure do.
Let’s go get ice cream.
I can’t wait to get
the freshness out
of my mouth.
I’m going to glue my mouth shut
with butterscotch.
(sighs):
Oh. Yay.
What the hell
is a fundae?
It’s a sundae
that’s fun.
I like that, but I’m on
a bit of a health kick.
So I’ll take
the low-fat vanilla--
with the following mix-ins:
Snickles, Gooey Bears,
Charlottesville Chew,
Nice ’N’ Many,
Kat Kit, Herschel’s Smooches,
Mrs. Bad Bar, and Milk Dudes.
Cup or cone?
Uh... cone!
(gasps)
(bell ringing)
♪ Celebrate good times,
come on... ♪
Congratulations.
You just purchased
the one millionth ice-cream cone
sold by this store!
Oh, my God, this is amazing!
Wait, I’m gonna be driving.
I’ll go for the cup.
-(music stops)
-BART:
Dad!
Fine, cone.
-(bell rings, music resumes)
-What’s this?!
Tonight on Smartline,
a provocative discussion
of the Middle East...
will not be featured.
Instead, we’ll be talking
to a man
who bought
an ice-cream cone.
That’s me.
Of course that has nothing
to do with the fact
that this station
and the ice-cream company
are owned
by the same corporation,
but I digress.
All right, let’s just
get through this.
Mr. Simpson,
tell us how it felt
when you bought
the fateful treat.
I’ve never been to war,
but I imagine it feels just
like your first kill.
The happiness swept me away!
(screams)
That hurt like a...
(muttered obscenities)
What’d I miss?
Kent Brockman said
a horrible swear.
Which one?
Uh,
I’ll Etch-A-Sketch it for you.
Etch... sketch...
etch... sketch...
(cries out)
Shake it! Shake it!
It won’t come off.
Where’s the hammer?
(sighs)
Earlier on this broadcast,
I said a word so vile
it should only be uttered
by Satan himself
while sitting on the toilet.
I apologize,
and will make a large donation
to charities
that fight teen cursing.
Good night.
(sighs heavily)
Hmph, people
don’t seem so mad.
Uh, excuse me, sir.
Did you see my
broadcast tonight?
Oh, God, no, I get my news
from the Internet
like every other
normal person under 70.
Farewell, dinosaur.
No one saw my show.
So, no one heard
my filthy faux pas.
My career is safe.
Well, the important
thing is
we got through
this crisis together.
That makes us
friends, right?
Uh, hey, look,
it’s the airport bus.
You should get on it.
(deflated):
Okay.
America West, please.
GRAMPA:
I can’t believe
Kent Brockman
got away with it.
Back in my day, TV stars
couldn’t say "booby,"
"tushie," "burp," "fanny burp,"
"water closet," "underpants,"
"dingle-dangle,"
"Boston marriage,"
"LBJ," "Titicaca,"
"hot dog," or "front lumps"!
I’m not sure Brockman’s
out of the woods yet.
There are a lot of religious
watchdog groups out there
keeping the world safe from
the horror of free expression.
You mean there are losers
who spend all day watching TV
looking for stuff
to complain about?
Who’d be lame enough to do that?
Okay, Smallville...
super dog licks himself.
That definitely goes
in the naughty pile.
Hmph.
60 Minutes...
Morley Safer has
questionable pants fold.
The L Word...
Used the "L" word.
And now to peruse
the local news.
The happiness
swept me away.
(screams)
Oh, that hurt like a...
(whistles, toots, chimes)
(crows)
(gasps):
God’s least favorite word
uttered on the public airwaves.
"To: Online Christian Soldiers.
Subject: Televised Super Swear."
Daddy, what are you doing?
Imploring people I never met
to pressure a government
with better things to do
to punish a man
who meant no harm
for something nobody even saw.
That’s what I’m doing.
Daddy, we think
you need a new mommy.
First things first.
The Federal Communications
Commission announced today
it will launch a full inquiry
into garbage-tongued anchorman
Kent Brockman?
In a related story, Channel Six
will demote Brockman
to... weekend weatherman?!
Dear God,
this can’t be happening.
(flat):
It’s a glorious day
here in Springfield.
Light winds, low humidity.
Now, let’s check
the five-day forecast.
What the...?!
(high-pitched):
Even the map thinks
you stink, Kent.
(laughing)
(deep voice):
In breaking news,
the FCC has just handed down
a record ten million dollar fine
against Channel Six
for Kent Brockman’s
shameful swear-nami.
(high-pitched):
Ten million dollars?!
Looks like Newshound,
the Channel Six mascot,
is gonna have to go without
his lazy-eye surgery.
(whimpers)
Sorry, boy.
No, I’m over here.
Over here!
I got a treat for you.
Oh! Now he’s gonna starve.
Proud of yourself, Kent?
(sighs heavily)
Kids, your old pal Krusty
has had to make a few cutbacks
because of a huge fine levied
against the station.
(cheering):
Yay!
That’s a bad thing.
Anyway, we can’t afford to pay
the voice actors
on Itchy and Scratchy,
so I’m doing the voices myself.
Roll it.
I’m a cat walking down
the street
swinging my arms.
Look, a lady made of dynamite!
Wait, I don’t know that yet.
How about a smooch?
Kablooey!
Here comes the mouse,
what’s-his-name.
That was me that done that.
But it ain’t enough,
so here’s this.
That’s what you get for, uh,
I don’t know,
messing with my wife.
And it goes on.
(spattered applause)
Damn that Brockman!
There are only two rules in TV:
don’t swear,
and don’t whip it out.
It’s not rocket science.
Kent, can we talk?
I’m not fired, am I?
No, no, this station
stands by its reporters.
Say, what’s that powder
in your coffee?
Is it cocaine?
No, it’s Splenda.
Spare me your slang,
pusher man.
You’re fired!
(Midnight Cowboy
harmonica theme plays)
(thunder crashing)
Haw, haw!
Your distinguished
career is over!
(groaning)
Marge, the couch is lumpy!
That’s because you’re
sitting on me, you lummox!
Kent Brockman!
I invited him to stay
with us for a few days.
His career is ruined.
And I was afraid he might
commit you-know-what-icide.
I’m sorry, Marge,
but I won’t live
under the same roof
as a member of
the liberal media.
You’ll have
to excuse him.
He’s been watching
a lot of Fox News.
Did you know that every day
Mexican gays sneak
into this country
and unplug our
brain-dead ladies?
We have to take in
Mr. Brockman.
He wouldn’t be
in this mess
if you hadn’t dumped
coffee on his lap.
Oh, sure, put down
a simple guy like me
who works hard
and plays by the rules.
Dad, you barely
go to work at all.
And you’re constantly
flouting the law.
I’m willing to change my mind
and that makes me great.
You can stay.
But you have to give us
an 8X10 for our wall
of Casual Acquaintances
Who Came to Stay For A While.
Apu sang a song.
What are you gonna do?
TV ANNOUNCER:
Can 15 strippers
run their own airline?
Find out tonight
on Fox’s newest reality hit,
Landing Strip.
Ladies, check out what I can do
with the oxygen masks.
(wild cheering)
What a great show.
Real people
with real problems.
(sighs)
(clicks)
This is Fox News
with the latest liberal outrage.
It seems liberals want
to give NASA the right
to abort space missions
whenever they feel like it.
Liberals...
I hate them so much.
One thing I’ve always wondered,
how can Fox News
be so conservative
when the Fox network
keeps airing raunchy shows?
They don’t fit together.
-(remote clicks)
-Whoo-hoo!
Liberals hate families.
-Liberals...
-(remote clicks)
Whoo-hoo!
Liberals. Whoo-hoo!
Liberals.
Whoo-hoo!
Liberals. Whoo-hoo!
Liberals.
Whoo...!
Fox deliberately runs shows
that will earn them huge fines
which are then funneled
through the FCC
straight to
the Republican party.
Everybody in the media knows it,
but no one has the guts
to say it.
Not true.
You’ve got the guts,
and I’ve got a web cam.
This time you can
tell the truth.
And swear like a lumberjack
who hacked off a leg.
Let’s do it.
-(clicks remote)
-...hoo!
Whoo-hoo?
Liberals?
Here we go.
Four, three, two...
Good evening.
Thank you for inviting me
into your laps.
Friends, the press and the
government are in bed together
in an embrace
so intimate and wrong,
they could spoon
on a twin mattress
and still have room
for Ted Koppel.
Journalists used to questions
the reasons for war
and expose abuse of power.
Now, like toothless babies,
they suckle on the sugary teat
of misinformation
and poop it into the diaper
we call the 6:00 news.
Demand more of your government.
Demand more of your press.
Fellow primate, this
is a wake-up call.
(chattering)
BROCKMAN:
Vote out your so-called
representatives.
Reject your corporate masters.
Buy nothing.
Hug your children.
Love the one you’re with.
Look at that rabble-rouser.
He’s threatening
our ill-gotten gains.
Galdarn it!
I worked hard to ill-get
those gains.
How do we stop him?
I could Dracula bite him.
(groaning)
Actually, Krusty and I’ve
been working on a plan
to take out Brockman.
You want to start?
No, why don’t you start?
Oh, but you’re
so good at starting.
You really think so?
-Oh, I know so.
Go on.
-All right.
Do you think there’s something
going on between those two?
To find out, I could
turn myself into a bat
and follow them around.
Oh, you couldn’t even get
our pizza orders right.
Every order is half this,
half that, it’s confusing!
Kent, your righteous political
commentary rocks.
Yeah, you know how many stars
out of five I gave
the YouTube of your webcast?
Five!
And I never give five.
It’s true, he never does.
Mr. Brockman,
you’re a huge hit.
Really?
How wide is the web?
-World.
-Wow.
(engine revs)
Kent, we want to offer you
your old job back
with a 50% pay increase.
Hmph.
Lisa, close your eyes
for two seconds.
(sighs):
One, two...
I held out as long as I could!
I guess there’s just no place
for truth and bravery
in today’s media.
True, but there’s room for
the truth in this household.
Do you want to hear something
really bad
Kent told me
about the Fox network?
Of course.
Gosh, Dad,
your hands are shaking.
I know.
’Cause this one’s
really, really bad.
For years now,
Fox has been...
TV ANNOUNCER:
...programming shows that
the whole family can enjoy.
(gasps):
Oh, my God!
You don’t suppose
they’re gonna start...
ANNOUNCER:
...entertaining America
with hits like House,
American Idol and
American Idol Results Show.
I’m afraid they might.
But I will not
be silenced.
The truth is...
(fanfare playing)
(whispers):
Okay.
What I was going to say was...
Shh!
(music plays)
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Enhanced by Fotokem