(theme music playing)
CHORUS: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
(whistle blows)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
(chimes)
(tires screeching)
(honking horn)
D'oh!
(tires screeching)
BART: Ice cream at church?
I'm intrigued, yet suspicious.
Wow, look at all these flavors.
"Blessed Virgin Berry,
Command-Mint, Bible-Gum."
Or if you prefer, we also have
Unitarian ice cream.
-There's nothing here.
-Exactly.
One Tower of Babel and build it to heaven.
To heaven!
Oh.
(grunting)
Christ be with you.
(groaning)
D'oh! (groans)
(clears throat) Hi.
I've created the first
intra-bovine ice-cream maker.
It makes use of all four stomachs.
The first being filled with
rock salt, then sugar, cream...
and of course, Freon so cold it burns me.
I'll have the darkety kind.
Uh, one chocolate, Mootilda.
(moos)
(gulps)
Can I have a swirl
of chocolate and vanilla?
-Huh? Uh-uh!
-Oh, nonsense. You can do it.
-(moos)
-(yelps) Ivan Reitman!
-(whining)
-Ow!
-I've never seen a brain freeze this bad.
-(whining)
Give me 50cc's of hot fudge, stat.
Hold still. You're gonna feel
a slight chocolaty sensation.
(gurgling)
(relieved sigh)
(P.A. feedback squeals)
All right, let's welcome
this evening's entertainment.
They call her the Christian Madonna...
Rachel Jordan!
(applause, whistling)
♪ Jesus loves me this I'm sure ♪
♪ I'm a groupie on his tour... ♪
-(singing continues)
-Rachel Jordan?
Isn't that the woman
you had a crush on, Ned?
(stammering)
I didn't have a "crush" on her.
-Are you blushing, Mr. Flanders?
-No, I'm not-
-Leave Ned alone.
-Thank you, Homer.
He can't admit he likes her till he's sure
she likes him back.
And there's only one way to find out.
Does... Rachel... like... Ned?
It says I have cooties.
Flanders has cooties!
(applause)
That was great. I can't believe
she found a rhyme for Hezekiah.
Hey, she's coming this way!
(gasps, clears throat)
I thought you didn't like her.
(all laugh)
-Oh!
-(gasps) Ned Flanders?
Now, where have you been
hi-diddly-hiding?
Uh-uh-uh... Oh, hey, Rachel. (chuckles)
Well, what do you know?
We both like plain vanilla
with nothin' on it.
Actually, all the toppings were gone.
(both groan)
Ants are crawling in my mouth,
and I don't care.
So, uh, where's your band?
They switched from
Christian music to regular pop.
All you do is change "Jesus" to "baby."
-Oh, how horrible.
-Uh! They'll all go to hell.
Say, how's your life going?
Ooh, she wants to know
how your life is going.
Well, my wife's passing was rough.
But I think I'm finally ready to move on.
That's great.
Maybe we could have coffee sometime.
Oh, she wants to have coffee sometime!
-I can hear her, Homer!
-He can hear you, Rachel!
(clears throat) I'd love to get together,
but tomorrow I've got lifeguard duty
at the baptismal pool.
OK. Well, maybe another time.
You know, I'd better
go check into my hotel.
Hotel? Why don't you just
stay at Ned's place?
My place? What would the neighbors think?
We're the neighbors, and we don't think.
Ned, I understand
if you feel uncomfortable.
You're still getting over your wife.
Now, wait just a Maude-gone minute, here!
I'm through livin' in the past,
and you can see for yourself.
Well, you've certainly got a theme going.
All right, I'll take the couch,
and you can have my room.
Oh, uh, could you sleep on my side?
I'm trying to preserve
Maude's indentation.
-Sorry.
-Oh, no problem!
A little starch will fix her right up.
-(shudders)
-Cold, huh?
This should keep you toasty.
How about that? It says "Maude."
(sniffs) Mmm, I love chenille. Don't you?
I don't love it. I don't hate it.
Mmm, well, good night, Maude.
I mean, Maude.
I mean, Rachel! I mean, Maude.
Oop!
(Ned humming)
(gasps, shrieks)
Oh, my God! You're trying to make me
look like your dead wife!
No, no, now, I-- I know
this is a... tad unseemly
but if you just let me even out the back-
I'm calling a cab! Good-bye, Ned!
-(door slams)
-Oh, who am I kidding?
I'm not over Maude at all.
HOMER: Yeah, maybe it was too soon.
Well? Aren't you gonna invite me in?
I sure appreciate you folks
offering to go through Maude's things.
If it were up to me,
I wouldn't throw anything away.
Oh, don't you worry.
We'll make all the hard decisions
so you don't have to.
-We can take whatever we want, right?
-Ye-- What?
Don't listen to him. You just have
a good time at the eye doctor.
Always do!
-HOMER: Say, "Bye, Mr. Flanders."
-CHILDREN: Bye, Mr. Flanders!
MARGE: Poor Ned.
He can't look anywhere
without being reminded of Maude.
Yeah, a lifetime of memories. (grunts)
Homer, don't you have any respect?
Sure. Of course I do. But life goes on.
Ashes to ashes. Turn, turn, turn.
Long live rock, and so forth.
(humming)
Don't throw this away.
It's Rod's first tooth.
You're right. We could use this
for witchcraft.
Wow. Three pairs of shoes.
Someone had a fetish.
-(music box slows, stops)
-(Homer grunting)
Man, this is taking forever.
I know how to speed things up.
(whining, grinding)
-(banging)
-Her pillow's stuck.
(gulps)
NED: Oh, my. The room looks so bare.
-Are you OK, Ned?
-Yeah, just a little shocked.
What's that? Some kind of sorting machine?
-Kinda.
-(whining, grinding)
Now for the awkward part.
-We gotta talk about money.
-(gasps)
You said we were doing
this out of friendship.
What? That doesn't sound like me.
Hey, Dad. Something didn't get,
um, "sorted."
(gasps) Maude's old sketchbook.
She was quite the little artist, you know.
Oh, eh, is that a fact?
And you think you know someone.
There's our house. A rainbow.
Oh, a white hand shaking a black hand.
"Praiseland"?
"Rides, food"? A"tithing pond"?
-LISA: It looks like an amusement park.
-NED: You're right!
Maude designed a Christian amusement park.
-Oh, it must've been her final dream.
-Hey, how about that?
Let's build it for her, Daddy.
(chuckles) Oh, that's a nice thought,
Toddy.
But to build an amusement park, you need
lots of money and manpower and turnstiles.
But Mommy wanted it.
Hmm?
But where do you put something that big?
You could fix up
the old Storytime Village.
They've been out of business
ever since that kid got his head cut off.
-That sounds perfect.
-Well, what the heck?
-Who's ready to build an amusement park?
-ALL: Yay!
Sell Storytime Village?
Why, you gotta be off your tuffet!
Well, it's been closed
for so long, and-- and l--
I thought I could turn it
into a-- a Christian theme park.
Christian, eh? Well, that's different.
Now, the thing is
I don't have a lot of money.
And what the hell good are you?
Beat it, you hippie!
-But l--
-You're right. That was harsh.
Tell you what.
Maybe I could donate
the park as a tax write-off.
(gasps) If you could do that, I'd make
this place a shining beacon for the Lord!
Ah, you are so full of it!
God's grace, that is.
It's really sickening...
there aren't more people like you.
Now get out...
your pen and we'll make it official.
Oh, bless you, sir!
(grunts) Geppetto's workshop will make
a great stable for the Nativity scene.
(grunting)
You're doing that the sucker way.
Try a little vitamin "G"!
(humming)
(gasps) Are you nuts?
Relax. It's a controlled burn. Uh-oh.
(lamb bleating)
(grunting)
Huh?
Darn teenagers with their beer bottles.
Uh, yeah. Teenagers. Huh!
(sighs)
Ned, I'm worried about you.
You've been working nonstop
for the past week.
Well, it's been a tad harder
than I thought.
But I'm not complaining,
'cause I work for a sweet, sweet boss.
You're our foreman, Maude.
She's still bossing you around
from beyond the grave? Can they do that?
No, I don't mind, but my greenback stack's
gettin' kind of slack.
How about asking the community
for donations?
(chuckles) I'm not very good
at begging people for stuff.
I am. I'd be glad to spearhead
the entire begging initiative.
-Oh, thanks, Homer.
-No problem.
I'll need a sack and something sharp.
Well, I guess I could
donate these costumes.
They're from my Last Supper
pie-throwing sketch.
(Wiggum grunts)
You can have these,
uh, fireworks I confiscated.
Some Chinese people claimed they were
celebrating New Year's in February.
(laughs) Oh, yeah. Those guys
and their crazy scams.
(both laugh)
Good food, though.
This sawdust'll soak up the puke
from the roller coaster.
That's Willie's special blend.
(sniffing)
Do I detect a hint of cinnamon?
Oh, I'll never tell.
Praiseland amusement park
has its grand opening today.
We now go live to its founder,
Mr. Nedward Flanders.
Oh, morning, Kent.
Our volunteers have done an amazing job
-getting the park ready here.
-(chuckles)
We're gonna show Springfield
that faith and devotion
-are the wildest thrill rides of all.
-(babbles, gasps)
All right. I hear the mayor's arriving
for the ribbon cutting.
It is with great pride that I dedicate
this new school,
sports arena or attraction.
(crowd cheering)
Well, Maude, your dream
has finally come true.
(children shouting, laughing)
Halt! Who dares to disturb King David?
Silence! You have invaded the chamber
where I wrote all of my 150 psalms.
-(all gasp)
-I hope you enjoy hearing them all.
Number one. "Blessed is the man
who does not walk
in the council of the wicked."
What do you hit 'em with?
-There's no mallet.
-You can stop Satan with your faith.
My face? You callin' me ugly?
No, no, no, no. I think you're beautiful.
-Oh, that's it!
-(shrieks)
Ooh, what can I get you, little Christian?
How about a Noah's Ark of jellies?
Oh, are there two of every flavor?
-Nope. They're all the same-- plain.
-Oh.
How about a Maude mask?
(as Maude) I'm Maude. God is super!
Can I sit in the car?
-Let's both sit in the car.
-Bye-bye.
A Bible park without beer? (scoffs)
Now I've seen everything!
And this candy is sub-par.
Any religion that embraces carob is, uh,
not for Carl Carlson.
Oh! Hey, get out of the way,
pal. You're blocking the exit.
Oh, you want me to stamp
your hand so you can get back in?
Don't you dare!
-Bye, everybody!
-What a rip-off!
It ain't even worth torching.
Whoa! Where's everyone going?
What's wrong?
This place is the height of tedium.
Yar! She blows!
(gasps)
(sighs)
Oh, Maude, I turned your dream
of a Christian amusement park
into a bemusement park.
-(gasps) Don't say that, Ned!
-It is!
It's a bemusement park!
I'm sorry, sweetheart. Oh, please,
don't look at me like that!
(gasps)
-(all gasp)
-It's a miracle!
-(all exclaiming)
-It's almost like she's alive again.
What's that, floating mask?
Y-You want me to shoot everyone?
(all exclaiming)
Nah, I'm just screwin' with ya.
It's a miracle.
ALL: Oh!
-(all exclaiming)
-This is fantastic.
I've never been so close
to rubbing my eyes in disbelief.
Oh, what the heck! Huh? Huh?
I think it's a sign from God
that we should all go nuts! Whoa-hoa!
-What the-
-(grunting)
Ah! What is wrong with you?
-Go get that!
-Yes, ma'am.
Well, looks like our phenomenon
is actually a phenome-not!
(chuckles) Because when you look
at it rationally--
(gibberish) Hakala makta towhoo abowhoo.
Hakala makta towhoo abowhoo.
-(all exclaiming)
-He's speaking in tongues!
Oh, knock it off, Seymour!
Go find that boy with my purse!
-Oh! It was incredible! I saw heaven!
--(all gasp)
But it wasn't clouds
and angels playing harps
like at the end of so many
Three Stooges shorts.
It was a golden elementary school
with a teacher's lounge that stretched
as far as the eye could see.
-And no one was ever tardy.
-Was I there?
No! It was heaven, my vision of heaven.
(crowd murmuring)
Oh, truly this was the will of Maude.
Hey, I want the Maude statue
to give me a vision!
CROWD: Yeah!
WIGGUM: Yeah! I want to hallucinate, too!
I'm sorry. The ticket price doesn't cover
visions, miracles or other godly hoo-ha.
Yeah, folks. The power of Christ
compels you to give Ned an extra 10 bucks.
(chattering, shouting)
Homer, no! I can't exploit
a divine manifestation.
Oh, why not? Everybody's doin' it.
You could give the money to the orphanage.
I hear they need a new wall.
(whimpering) Three is not enough.
(coughing, gagging)
(chattering)
(humming)
Maude, it's Disco Stu.
Lay some heaven on me, foxy dead chick.
Ooh! (grunting)
(disco music playing)
Ah, Disco Stu. Right this way.
But, hey, Saint Peter, you just said,
like, you was full.
-DISCO STU: Oh, yeah!
-Ah, geez.
-(music continues)
-Ah! Ooh! Ah!
-Whoa, Frank Sinatra!
-For me, this is hell. You dig, pally?
Ah, ah!
(grunting)
-Who's next?
-That would be me. Thank you, sonny.
(grunting)
(alarm blaring)
My chair! It's... got a mind of its own!
-Help me, Mr. Spock!
-Shazbot! My captain is in peril.
(shouting)
You saved the captain's life.
I want to make out with you.
And so do Catwoman and Agent 99.
-(purrs)
-(kisses)
Oh!
How come everybody's
having visions, Daddy?
Oh, there's no explaining
God's will, Roddy.
That's like explaining
how an airplane flies.
Stupid grill! Why won't you light?
The gas is on full blast.
You better stick your head in
and see what's goin' on.
Good idea.
No, Dad! I think
there's a leak in the line!
Leak in the line?
(hissing)
(gibberish)
Oh, no! This isn't a divine miracle.
Everyone's just gettin'
goofy from the gas.
(gibberish)
Uh-Uh, folks, I just discovered,
eh, something about this statue that,
uh, may disappoint you.
You see-
What is it, Mr. Flanders?
Is something wrong with the miracle?
Will there still be money
for the orphans? (wheezing)
(coughing)
Hello, gas company?
How poisonous is your gas?
Wow. Bu-- Eh-- But I'm talking about,
you know, outdoors
with plenty of ventilation.
That-- How could that be worse?
OK, permanent brain damage
or just temporary?
I see.
I gotta close Praiseland down.
Someone could get hurt.
(sighs)
"Could" get hurt. "Could."
There's a chance they won't.
Ned, Praiseland has
touched an entire town...
with its inspiring message
and toxic super freak-outs!
Look at those smiling faces.
Rich laughing with poor.
Bullies breaking bread with nerds.
Orphans lighting candles
over a leaking gas line.
Lighting candles?
-(gasping)
-(groaning)
TOGETHER: No-o-o!
(scream, groan)
I can't feel my legs.
I taste blood.
(Ned and Homer sigh)
-(all gasp)
-Adults attacking orphans?
I don't think Maude Flanders
would approve of that.
Absolutely not!
-Never!
-No friggin' way!
Yeah. This place is more like "Crazeland."
-CROWD: Huh?
-Instead of "Praiseland."
-CROWD: Oh!
-I see.
It's a play on words.
May the Lord have mercy
on your gas-sniffin', orphan-beatin' soul!
-Christ be with you!
-(horn honking)
Hey, Ned!
I just read about your park
in that horrible AAA magazine.
Ooh, Ned, look who's here.
It's that girl you don't like.
Not! (laughing)
Hey, your hair's grown back real nice.
It's a wig. And let's never
speak of it again.
So what happened here?
How about I explain it to you
over a cup of coffee?
That is if you're willing
to give me another shot.
Are you sure you want to do this, Ned?
I'm sure.
-So how about a movie tomorrow night?
-Sounds great.
I think Ned is gonna be all right.
(disco music playing)
♪ Get dancin', dancin', dance ♪
♪ Dance ♪
MAN: Keep movin'.
♪ Here come DJ Disco Tex ♪
♪ Truckin' with his Sex-O-Lettes ♪
♪ Get dancin', dancin', dance ♪
♪ Guaranteed to rock the boat ♪
♪ Machine-gun rap and locomote ♪
♪ Get dancin', dancin', dance ♪
MAN: Come on, baby. Come out there
and dance to your song.
Turn yourself on.
(speaking Spanish)
Over Hollywood-- America needs you!
We need you to go dance!
We need you to get together
and boogie-woogie- woogie-boogie!
-(murmuring)
-Shh!
(orphan girl coughing, wheezing)
Captioned by
Visual Data Media Services