CHORUS: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(theme music playing)
(bell ringing)
(whistle blows)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
(tires screeching)
(clanks)
(honking horn)
(tires screeching)
-D'oh! (screams)
-(tires screeching)
ALL: (screaming)
♪ O'er the land of the free ♪
♪ And the home ♪
♪ Home of the brave ♪
♪ Oh, America's
The home of the brave ♪
♪ The brave,
America the brave ♪
♪ The brave ♪
♪ Home of the brave ♪
Thank you, Springfield!
I love you! Peace!
CONROY:
Thank you, Cyndi Lauper.
Just a reminder, folks. We do
have a baseball game today.
-MAN: All right.
-(chuckles)
I am Dennis Conroy,
and here come your Isotopes!
-CROWD: (booing)
-(all gasping)
Let's welcome two new additions
to the team,
Smash Diggins
and Fishbone Walker.
Lucky for us,
they were sent down
from the Majors
for drug violations.
(crowd cheering)
Oh, stupid Isotopes.
Hurry up and lose
so we can get out of here!
Why do you hate
the Isotopes so much, Dad?
Because I loved them once
and they broke my heart.
Let that be a lesson
to you, sweetie.
Never love anything.
-Even you?
-Especially me.
But you've got to support
the team, Dad.
They're already threatening
to move to Moose Jaw.
That's right.
Like my mother always said,
"You've got to stick it out
even if you picked a loser..."
-Hmm.
-"...to the bitter end."
CONROY:
First pitch of the game.
(screams)
That's a rotator cuff.
His career is over.
I'm going to warm up the car.
But there's only been
one pitch.
And it sucked.
CONROY: Bases loaded,
two outs, bottom of the ninth,
and it's do or die.
HOMER (singing):
♪ Hitler is a jerk ♪
♪ Mussolini ♪
That'll bring up Babe Ruth IV.
'Course, he's no Babe Ruth III,
but the franchise
is very excited
about this illegitimate
great grand bambino!
And... what's this?
He's pointing
to the right field bleachers,
probably at a dying little boy.
-Mom, am I dying?
-No, of course not.
-Is he, Mom? You can tell me.
-No.
CONROY: Now he's pointing
to the ground.
Is he indicating a bunt?
Yes, he's bunting!
(crowd booing)
MARGE: Good hustle, kid!
HOMER (singing):
♪ No, it doesn't work ♪
So who won? The losers?
No, they lost.
(chuckling) Losers.
But only by two points,
and they didn't resort
to stealing bases
like the other team,
so it's kind of a moral
victory.
With a little middle relief,
they might even
make the playoffs!
You'll be
in your cold, cold grave
before that ever happens.
Homer, would you please
stop talking
about the childrens' graves?
(loud chatter, cheering)
-MAN: Whoo!
-(grunts)
What's the hubbub?
Did Moe finally
blow his brains out?
Quiet! We're watching
the Isotopes!
Shut it off. They're losers.
Where you been?
The Isotopes are on fire.
Yeah. That sniper
at the all-star game
was a blessing in disguise.
Now we're
in the championship game.
Championship? Hmm.
Whoo! 'Topes rule!
Well, here's a die-hard fan.
Sir, your beloved Isotopes
are about to make history.
Any thoughts?
Ah! It's a great team, Kent.
They never gave up hope.
I want to thank Jesus
and say "Hi"
to my special lady, Marge.
We did it, baby! Whoo! Whoo!
The inspiring words of a fan
who'll always root, root,
root for the home team,
even if they lose this game.
They lost? Those losers!
No, no, no.
The game's not over.
Whoo! Not over! Whoo!
There you have it. Whoo!
(all cheering)
CONROY:
Bottom of the ninth, two outs.
It all comes down to this.
And here's the pitch.
Humping Hesus.
He got all of that one.
It's going... going... going.
Our technical director today
was Stan Kadlubowski.
It's out of here! 'Topes win!
-(all cheering)
-Isotopes! Come on!
(cheering continues)
(sighs)
Nobody touched my rumaki.
Whoo! Rumaki!
-(honking)
-Yay!
Isotopes! Whoo!
(grunts)
-Isotopes.
-(grunts)
MAN: Isotopes.
You know what
I'm sayin' to you, baby?
Hey, a baseball field.
Batter up.
-(all yelling)
-MAN: Go, baby! Steal second!
I think I'm going to puke!
-Hey, who's on first?
-Touchdown!
BARNEY: Slide!
(tires screeching)
-HOMER: Safe!
-(all cheering)
(cheering continues)
Hey, Carl. Isotopes!
(all groaning, grunting)
(drunkenly)
♪ We are the champions ♪
♪ You got mud on your face
Big disgrace ♪
-(screams)
-Whoop! Careful.
(munching)
Wow! You look
really hungover, Dad.
What did you do last night?
Last night? Uh, um...
Hmm, huh. Hello, Big Maggie.
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Someone trashed the school.
What the dilly-yo?
Where this morning,
the three "Rs" stand for
"rowdiness, ransacking
and irresponsibility."
-Any suspects, chief?
-None.
That's why we're
jumping to the conclusion
that this was the work
of no-good, punk kids.
Kids?
Therefore,
effective immediately,
I am imposing a curfew.
Any kid caught on the street
after dark will be shot,
or returned to their parents
as the situation may warrant.
-(gasps) Curfew?
-Whoa!
Serves you little punks right.
So, maybe next time,
you'll think before--
Oh, my God!
Look what those rotten kids
did to my car! (crying)
The cops can't just
slap a curfew on us.
-We have rights.
-Sure, you do.
You have the right
to remain silent.
(both laughing)
That was cold-blooded, Marge.
-Yeah.
-But it's not fair.
Adults always blame kids
for everything.
Well, if kids are so innocent,
why is everything bad
named after them?
Acting childish, kidnapping,
child abuse.
What about adultery?
Not until you're older, son.
(children giggling)
Okay, go deep!
Ice cream truck!
Hey, quit pushing!
I was here first!
Get out of my way!
(soft tune playing)
(exclaiming)
-(siren wailing)
-(tires screeching)
Achtung, babies!
Curfew is in effect.
Return to your homes,
immediately.
(screaming)
All right,
let's see some IDs, boys.
Huh. You two scofflaws
are violating curfew.
I'm taking you downtown.
Oh, uh, sorry to disturb you,
Dr. Hibbert.
(deep voice)
Not at all, officer.
(laughing like Hibbert)
Hah! What a beautiful night.
Fireflies, full moon.
And here we are, locked inside.
Kids, the carnival's in town
for one night only.
And they've got cotton candy
and hats with feathers.
And there's no lines
because all the stupid kids
have curfew, so...
Oh, right. Sorry.
(giggling)
-Hmm.
-(sighs)
Why don't you kids play
one of your old board games?
When was the last time
you played Citizenship?
-BART: Energy Shortage.
-LISA: Hippo in the House?
MARGE: Ooh! The Game of Lent.
Oh, can't we just go to bed?
It's only 5:30.
Fine. We'll play
Hippo in the House .
Oh, the hippo's missing.
(both groaning)
You think that's bad?
I had to talk
to my mom all night.
She's got problems.
Scary problems.
Adults blow.
Yeah. Just look at them
over there.
Smoking their cigarettes.
Drinking their coffee.
Scratching their big butts.
Your metabolism will change
someday, too, young man.
(mutters, clears throat)
That ought to show
little Timmy and Tammy scumbag
who's in charge around here.
Gee, chief,
all those gears and motors
must have cost a fortune.
Well, you got to spend money
to make money, Lou.
Uh-huh.
(yawning) You want to
hold it for a while?
Nah.
MARGE: (humming)
Marge. Kite.
Hey, there is one thing
we could do.
-(music playing on TV)
-(gasps) Lise, no. It's prime time!
You robbed me of my manhood.
That's petty theft.
(audience exclaiming)
Don't go there.
(audience laughing, applauding)
Don't Go There
will be right back.
-Oh, no. It won't.
-Wait, there's a commercial.
(spooky music plays)
-Ah, oh... yeah.
-Whoa.
MALE NARRATOR:
40 years ago,
a film appeared
that was so shocking,
so terrifying, it was sealed
in a concrete vault
deep beneath the earth.
But even the new management
of Sony/TriStar
could not contain the pure evil
of The Bloodening.
(woman screaming)
Milhouse, do you see
what's on channel six?
Uh, yeah,
it-it's really something.
(gasps)
MALE NARRATOR:
A registered nurse trained
in the treatment of terror
will be on duty
during the showing of...
The Bloodening.
(evil laughter)
(normal voice) Now playing
at the Springfield drive-in...
after dark.
Milhouse, spread the word.
We're seeing this movie,
tonight.
That's right.
We're breaking curfew.
(both grunting)
Come on.
(grunting)
-Breaking curfew, Mom!
-WOMAN: We're out of skoal!
Due to the likelihood of
fear-induced heart attacks,
we're offering all patrons
million-dollar life insurance policies.
Life insurance? Hmm.
Will I be able to borrow
against the equity?
Uh, I don't know, sir.
It comes free with the popcorn.
Is that air-popped?
MAN: Skinner!
-We're losing valuable make-out time.
-WOMAN: (groans)
(grunts)
-Little help.
-Sure.
(grunts)
-(groans)
-(grunts)
-Lisa.
-Nelson.
CHORUS (singing):
♪ Let's all go to the lobby ♪
♪ To get ourselves some drinks ♪
Get off of my moor,
you mischievous weans.
Actually, we'd prefer to stay.
You're thinking about
hurting us.
(groans)
Now you're thinking,
"How did they know
what I was thinking?"
Now you're thinking,
"I hope that's shepherd's pie
in my knickers."
(groans)
(screaming)
-Wow!
-They showed him.
Man, I never liked Shakespeare
until now.
Right, you little blighters.
We've had quite enough
of your evil mischief.
But you're the one
who's been bad.
You've been sneaking puddings.
But-but, how did you know?
We know all your secrets.
-And you pilfered the poor box.
-(gasps)
And, doctor, we know that you
and the bootblack
have been rogering the fishwife
in the crumpet shop.
-(blows raspberry)
-(gasps)
-Lies! How dare you!
-Get them! Quickly!
We can't have that.
(gasps)
(grunts)
-Take that, you suckers!
-Way to go!
In your face, fishwife.
(thud)
Enjoying the movie, kids?
ALL: (screaming)
Listen up, punks.
The moral of the story is,
the adults always win.
(yells)
Stop crying out loud, Eddie,
you scared the hell out of me.
Sorry, chief. (evil chuckle)
KIDS: (groaning)
CLANCY WIGGUM: Don't forget
to clean under the jowls.
That spot is club med
for mildew.
And let this be
a lesson to you.
Kids never learn. (grunts)
(tires screeching)
(all coughing, retching)
Oh, that is it.
I'm tired of being
pushed around by grownups.
It's time to fight back!
ALL: Yeah! Fight back!
Man, if we had eye power
like those kids in that movie,
we could read the adults' mind
and tell their secrets,
and make them pitchfork
each other and junk.
(laughing, cheering)
Wait! We don't need
supernatural powers.
-We already know their secrets.
-She's right.
Homer's done a ton of crap
that never made the papers.
My mom shoplifts all the time,
stuff she doesn't even need.
My dad gets in car accidents
on purpose.
Great. This is all gold.
MILHOUSE: We got to spread
this stuff around.
Let's put it on the Internet.
BART:
No, we have to reach people
whose opinions actually matter,
and I think I know how.
Why don't we just...
(chatter)
Attention,
hemline and midriff monitors.
-(tapping)
-Um.
-(squeaky sound)
-(gasps)
Willie, get my Windex.
(snoring)
(cat meows)
200 channels,
and nothing but cats.
So, Marge,
ready for another episode
of Don't Go There?
I'm tired of that show,
but I've been hearing
good things about Talk to the Hand.
Tom Shales says the writing
snaps, crackles, and pops.
Okay, whatever takes
my mind off my life.
(theme music playing)
♪ Talk to the hand, they say... ♪
Hey, look what I found.
Grandpa's old radio.
Oh, wouldn't it be grand
to gather round
and have a listen?
Well, turn something on.
I'm starting to think.
(big band music)
(rock music)
FRANKLIN ROOSEVELT:
A date which will live...
in infamy.
Good evening, adults.
We interrupt this broadcast
to bring you
a very special presentation.
Tonight's program is entitled...
KIDS: We Know All Your Secrets.
Boring.
Go back to that "infamy" guy.
BART: Constable Wiggum
likes to act tough.
But he also likes
to walk the beat
in control-top pantyhose.
(gasping)
Heh-heh! Well, heh,
it's not like that's a crime.
I'm afraid it is, chief.
-Um.
-(handcuffs ratcheting)
BART:
And Schoolmistress Krabapple
has been stealing supplies
from the school cafeteria.
(gasps) Edna, how could you?
Don't get up.
I'll bus my own tray.
BART: And now we come
to Mr. Homer Simpson.
(gasps)
Did you know, he likes to eat
out of the Flanders' garbage?
Oh, no. Homer.
I have a problem.
Tune in tomorrow and every day
until the curfew is lifted
because we'll be revealing
embarrassing secrets about
Springfield's other adults.
Well, at least
they've already done me.
And we have plenty more
on Homer Simpson.
D'oh!
I've called this meeting
to determine
what to do
about those blabbermouth kids
and their creepy
English accents.
Hey, shut up, Mayor.
They're telling secrets again.
ALL: (gasp)
Oh, I hope they don't reveal
this is a comb-over.
LISA (over radio):
Our top secret tonight,
Gay divorcee Luanne Van Houten
has been cheating
on her boyfriend, Pyro...
-CROWD: (gasp)
-...with his best friend, Gyro.
How many times
have I fought beside you, Gyro?
And this is how you repay me?
(both grunting)
Pyro, Gyro, settle down.
Can't we shut down
that infernal transmitter?
-Can't we just blow it up?
-You go ahead, girlfriend.
(chattering)
-Settle down, people.
-(gavel banging)
As we speak,
Chief Wiggum is tracking down
those little squealers
using the latest
in crime-fighting technology.
Ah, I got nothing.
How about you, frinky?
I have captured the signal,
and am presently
triangulating the vectors
and compressing the data down
in order to express it
as a function of my hand.
They're over there.
And guess
who's been practicing medicine
without a license?
(gulps)
That's right. Homer Simpson.
Freeze, you little shock jocks.
(guns cocking)
Brilliant.
They transduced
amplitude modulation
via the concavity of that over-sized
beverage conveyance.
I mean,
that is some clever goyvin.
All right, you kids,
come down now.
We promise, we won't kill you.
Speak for yourself.
Bart, get down here!
I'm going to spank you
back to the Stone Age.
You can't make us come down.
You adults are always
giving us orders.
Well, you kids
are always disobeying them.
Well, adults treat kids
like children.
Kids treat adults
like cash machines.
-Adults! Adults! Adults!
-Kids! Kids! Kids!
(singing) ♪ Kids, you've had your fun
♪ Now we've had our fill ♪
♪ Yeah, you're only here
'Cause Marge forgot her pill ♪
(sneers)
♪ Kids, you're all just ♪
♪ Scandalizing,
vandalizing punks ♪
♪ Channel-hoppin',
Ritalin-poppin' monkeys ♪
But please don't quit
the fan club.
♪ Kids, I can nag and nag ♪
♪ Till my hair turns blue ♪
♪ Kids, you bum my smokes
And don't say thank you ♪
♪ Why can't you be
like we are? ♪
♪ Oh, what a bunch of brats ♪
♪ We ought to drown you
just like cats ♪
(cat meows)
♪ Adults, you run our lives ♪
♪ Like you're Colonel Klink ♪
♪ Adults, you strut around
like your farts don't stink ♪
♪ Adults, you're such a
drooling, snoring ♪
♪ Boozing, boring bunch ♪
♪ Surly, meanie,
Three-martini lunchers ♪
I just ate a thumbtack.
♪ Adults, they're always
telling us to-- ♪
Shut your traps!
♪ Eh, we're fed up
with all of you whippersnaps ♪
♪ We're tryin' to get
some sleep here ♪
♪ It's almost 6:15 ♪
♪ What's the matter with ♪
♪ Don't you treat us like ♪
♪ Can't you just lay off ♪
♪ We're sick of all of you ♪
ADULTS: ♪ Kids...
to... day... ♪
We're going to teach
all you rugrats a lesson.
Oh, yeah? (blows raspberry)
What can you old people
do to us?
-Yeah, you old fogies.
-Buzz off, you old buzzards.
(chatter)
...iron you.
This is Kent Brockman
reporting from my own home
in accordance
with a new curfew
for anyone under 70.
-(growls) I can't believe that passed.
-(Homer speaking inaudibly)
I warned you guys that seniors
always vote in record numbers.
The controversial measure
passed by a single vote.
Um, you really
should have voted, Homer.
Pfft. It wouldn't have made
a difference.
Lights out, you punk kids!
Yay! We took back the night!
MAN: Hey, fellas!
Hey, you wanna stop
with the kicking?
My pills are in that can.
Good gravy.
I don't kick your things.
When you're trying
to breathe on the machine,
do I go up and kick it?
Oh, now, look at that.
It went down the sewer.
You're happy?
I'm gonna sue now.
Now it's time for the lawyers.
(theme music playing)
Shh.
MAN: Don't tell me to shush,
you stupid lady!
Captioned by
Visual Data Media Services