CHORUS:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
(playing the blues)
(playing out of tune)
(honking horn)
D'oh!
(screams)
MARGE: (humming)
ANNOUNCER:
The start of television's
Mid-season, is just 200 exciting
seconds away.
-Door?
-Locked.
-Phone?
-Unplugged.
Dog? Cat?
-Taped and corked.
-Perfect.
ANNOUNCER: It's
America's funniest tornadoes.
(Bart and Homer laughing)
ANNOUNCER: And at 09:30,
All in the family 1999.
Oh, geez, there they got me
living with an African American.
A Semite American
and a woman American, there.
And I'm glad, I love yous all.
I love everybody.
I wish I'd saved my money
from the first show.
Oh, I can't wait.
Look, Marge,
I had a scorecard printed up
at that all-night scorecard place.
Isn't mid-season
just a dumping ground
for second-rate shows
that weren't good enough
for the fall schedule?
You're thinking
of all the other years.
This year's shows are classics.
There's The Laughter Family,
that's animated.
Networks like animation
'cause they don't have to pay
the actors squat.
(imitation Ned)
Plus, they can replace them
and no one can tell
the diddley-ifference.
ANNOUNCER: And now, mid-season
kicks off with Admiral Baby.
Yee-hee-hee!
We're taking the entire
sixth fleet to Candy Island?
Those are the Admiral's orders.
(gurgles)
(loud canned laughter)
(groans)
It's hard to believe
someone that young
could have risen
to the rank of Admiral.
Gee, I never thought
I'd say this about a TV show.
But this is kind of stupid.
Hey, Police Cops.
That sounds like
a lethal combination.
Let's get this bank
back to our hideout
and we'll break into it later.
It's the cops.
Worse. The police cops.
(yells)
(grunting)
(screams)
-This isn't bad.
-"Isn't bad"?
Tell me one thing mankind's
ever done that's any better.
The renaissance.
This is better.
Let's book 'em and roll.
And that's the end
of that chapter.
You men saved my bank.
I'd like to donate $40
to charity in your honor.
But I don't know your names.
Lance Coffman.
Simpson,
detective Homer Simpson.
(gasping)
He's named like my name!
GIRLS: (giggling)
(chuckles)
I don't get it, Homer.
You're a millionaire
and you've got all
the babes you want.
Why aren't you living it up
in your palace in Europe?
Well, let's just say I hate crime.
(groans)
(grunts)
Arrest that guy.
And that's the end of that chapter.
Wow, they've captured
my personality perfectly.
Did you see the way
daddy caught that bullet?
That's not really you, dad.
He's just a fictional character
who happens to have
the same name.
Don't confuse daddy, Lisa.
Homer, it's just a coincidence.
Like that guy named
Anthony Michael Hall
who stole your car stereo.
Right. Coincidence.
(telephone rings)
Another person wants
to congratulate you
for having a famous name.
Hello.
Yes, this is
the original Homer Simpson.
Who's this?
The Debbie Pinson
who was the homecoming queen
in high school?
Yes, I'm still available.
No, he's not.
Marge, that was Debbie Pinson!
Debbie Pinson!
No dating.
Ohhh!
Hey, Homer, Homer, check it out.
Bottom of page 12.
"Local man has same name.
A TV character has
the same name as Springfield
resident Homer Simpson."
Hey, you're famous.
"And that's the end
of that chapter."
(all exclaim)
Mr. Simpson, sir,
can I get your autograph?
All right. What's the name?
Homer, we've worked together
for ten years.
It's "Carl."
You only wrote my name.
Um, I wanted yours.
Take it or leave it... Carl.
So, uh, what kind of adventure
you going to be involved
in tonight, Homer?
Mm, who knows?
Maybe I'll have to foil
an assassination
or stop a peace conference.
So they really based that
Homer Simpson character on you,
huh?
Yep, right down to the scarf.
-(crowd gasping)
-MOE: Ooh, there it is.
Nice beating, Lance.
Especially around the eyes.
It...
Say, where's your partner?
Where's Homer Simpson?
HOMER SIMPSON: Coming, Chief!
Whoa! Whoa!
Now what have you done, Simpson?
I was supervising
the "Guns for Toys" program.
It's "Toys for Guns".
Now you tell me.
Oh, Simpson!
(all laughing)
Hey, what's going on?
That guy's not Homer Simpson.
He's fat and stupid.
Hey, it looks like they
changed the character
into a bumbling sidekick.
No. No, he can't be.
I know,
maybe he's just acting stupid
to infiltrate a gang
of international idiots.
Yeah, that's got to be it.
You destroyed that drug shipment?
Yes, indeed-y.
That was my insulin.
Uh-oh, spaghettio's!
CHIEF: Simpson!
Hey, Homer,
that character's you all over.
Come on, Homer, act all stupid
like you do on TV.
Yeah, come on, dum-dum,
do something unintelligent there.
(all laughing)
Shut up! I'm not your clown!
Don't diminish me!
Gentlemen, I bid you fare--
(groans)
(all laughing)
(groaning)
-(yells)
-(car screeches and crashes)
HOMER: Ow!
(groans)
Geez, what an exit.
Oh, man, what's he going
to do for an encore?
Woo...
I don't think he'll be doing
no encores for a while.
(laughs)
I can't understand what happened.
Why did they change
Homer Simpson's character
from cool to stupid?
The first episode
was just a pilot, dad.
Producers fiddle with shows
all the time.
They change characters,
drop others
and push some
into the background.
Your character provides
the comic relief, like, oh...
Marlon Brando in Apocalypse Now.
Wish I hadn't bought
a hundred of these.
LENNY (whispering):
Get ready, everybody.
He's about to do something stupid.
Well, I'm sorry
to disappoint you, gentlemen
but you seem to have me
confused with a character
in a fictional show.
Now, if you'll excuse me
my fondue is just about...
D'oh!
(laughing)
LENNY: There goes Albany.
Uh-oh, spaghettio's!
Oh, man.
(horn honking)
OTTO: Whoa,
it's that Homer Simpson dude.
Ha-ha!
People are laughing at me, Marge.
Let's get out of here.
Forget the baby's medicine.
But her forehead's on fire.
Fine. I'll be in the car...
driving home.
Well, if it isn't
that stupid cop from TV.
Ah, yeah, that got it.
That's Homer Simpson.
(all clamoring)
WOMAN: Let's crowd him.
Your catchphrase is hysterical.
Please say it clearly
for my answering machine tape.
(weakly)
Uh-oh, spaghettio's.
Worst reading ever.
How about an autograph?
-Picture, mister?
-Can I have your shoes?
Come on, people. Enough is enough!
Oh, it's never enough
not for them.
Once they get a taste of you
they want more and more and more!
That reminds me.
Do you mind if my nephew
kicks you in the belly?
Okay.
(groans)
Oh, the flash didn't go off!
You got another one in you, Josh?
The whole town's laughing at me.
Even that cat out there.
Bart, kill that cat.
BART: Okay.
And that big yellow flower.
Homer, your growing insanity
is starting to worry me.
Why don't you talk
to the producers of the show?
Maybe they'll make
your character suave again.
Hmm... I guess I could.
But while I'm gone
keep an eye on that weird
looking kid down there.
-Bart?
-Yeah, "Bart."
Uh, so I just want to know
how come
you made your Homer Simpson
character so--?
Stupid?
Well, I can assure you
it happened organically.
It better have.
The 13 of us began
with a singular vision...
"Titanic meets Frasier."
But then we found out that ABC
had a similar project in development
with Annie Potts and Jeremy Piven.
-Who's Jeremy Piven?
-We don't know.
But it scared the hell out of us.
So we slapped together
a cop show instead.
-Police Cops.
-No.
Actually It was called
Badge Patrol.
But the network idiots
didn't want a show
about high-tech badges
that shoot laser beams.
So we asked ourselves
"who's behind the badge?"
-Police...
-Cops...
Police Cops.
Yeah, but why does
the Homer Simpson character
have to be so stupid?
Oh, he's not stupid.
He's a street-smart
fish out of water
in a world he never made.
I'm begging you. I'm a human being.
Let me have my dignity back.
ALL: Mm-hmm.
D'oh!
Let me down, Chief.
I'm begging you!
I'm a human being.
Let me have my dignity back.
Yow!
Now he's stupid and whiny.
That does it.
There's only one thing I can do.
Your honor, I'd like to sue
the producers of Police Cops
for $20 million for improper use
of my name.
Court finds in favor
of Police Cops.
Next case.
(mumbling)
Then I'd like
to legally change my name.
What name would you prefer?
Any of these will be fine.
Hmm, "Hercules Rockefeller.
Rembrandt Q. Einstein.
Handsome B. Wonderful"?
I'm going to give you the only name
you spelled correctly.
From this day forward,
your name shall be...
"Max Power"?
Dynamic, isn't it?
I love it, Max.
You changed your name
without consulting me?
That's the way
Max Power is, Marge.
Decisive, uncompromising and rude.
Oh, wait a minute.
The family name is
my legacy to you.
I got it from my father,
and he got it from his father
and he traded a mule for it.
And that mule went on
to save spring break.
But this will be so confusing.
The mailman
won't know what to do.
Did you think of the mailman
at all before you did this?
Yes, briefly.
And what about the tattoo
on my you-know-what?
Oh, honey, they have acids
that can burn that off.
But I fell in love
with Homer Simpson.
I don't want to snuggle
with Max Power.
Nobody snuggles with Max Power.
You strap yourself in
and feel the Gs!
Oh, Lord.
And it doesn't stop
in the bedroom. Oh, no.
I'm taking charge.
Kids, there's three
ways to do things...
The right way, the wrong way
and the Max Power way.
Isn't that the wrong way?
Yeah, but faster.
D'oh!
We should really put that
in the corner.
(Gold Finger melody)
♪ Max Power ♪
♪ He's the man whose name ♪
♪ You'd love to touch ♪
♪ But you mustn't touch ♪
♪ His name sounds good
in your ear ♪
♪ But when you say it
you mustn't fear ♪
♪ 'Cause his name can be said ♪
♪ By anyone... ♪
Ah! Max Power.
How's every little thing?
You remembered my name!
Well, who could forget the name
of a magnetic individual
like you?
Keep up the good work, Max.
"Mr. Power."
Yes, of course."Mr. Power."
So I want the monogram
to read "M-A-X-P-O-W..."
Sir, traditionally,
a monogram is just initials.
Max Power doesn't abbreviate.
Each letter is as important
as the one that preceded it.
Maybe more important...
No, as important.
(sighing)
Very well.
And if you got enough room
add exclamation points
and a pirate flag.
The man knows what he likes.
Just taking care of business.
If you don't, who will, huh?
Trent Steel.
Homer Sim... Uh, Max Power.
Ooh, hey! Great name!
Yeah, isn't it?
I got it off a hair dryer.
(chuckling) I like a man
who can poke fun at himself.
Ooh, hey, my 01:00 canceled.
Have you had any lunch?
Yeah, but I usually have
three or four.
So where to eat? You like Thai?
Tie good. You like shirt?
Marge, this is Thai food.
From now on, I want it
morning, noon and night.
When did you start
liking Thai food?
When Trent Steel bought me some.
Who's Trent Steel?
He's Max Power's
oldest and dearest friend.
What's this wrapped
in a banana leaf?
(sniffing)
Mmm... smells like mint.
-Oh, I spit my gum in there.
-Eeww.
Where'd you meet
this Trent Steel... Moe's?
No way. This guy's a winner.
He has a company
that makes computers.
Or a computer
that makes companies.
Anyway, you wouldn't understand.
Well, I guess your new name
is really opening doors for you.
For all of us... look.
"You are invited
to a garden party this Saturday."
This is our chance to rub elbows
with Springfield's young,
hip, power couples
like me and Debbie Pinson.
(grunting)
Wow! Look at this place.
The house number
is spelled out with letters.
Get used to it, honey.
From now one,
we'll be spelling everything
with letters.
Did you wish me to destroy
this machine for you?
Nah. Just park it.
Very well.
And I counted the pennies
in the ashtray!
(music playing)
Oh, look!
It's Woody Harrelson!
(laughing) I can't believe those pants
are made entirely out of hemp.
And there's Ed Begley, Jr!
...and this one solar collector
can gather enough energy
to run this colorful pinwheel.
Wait... wait, I got it, I got it.
Very nice, Ed.
Your inventions
continue to impress me
and the entire nation.
Marge... President Clinton.
Oh, my Lord!
I feel like Cinderella!
Me, too. Let's sing
the Cinderella song.
Eh, maybe later.
(gulping)
Uh-oh. Here comes Lorne Michaels.
Pretend you don't see him.
Ah, Max Power.
Trent said I absolutely must
meet you. This is fabulous--
(loudly) Anyway, Marge...
How do you feel
about the economy?
(Homer laughing)
So I said if this
is the house of pancakes
how come I can't eat the walls?
(others laughing)
Oh, you are too much, Max.
I thought I knew
all the players in Springfield.
Where have you been
hiding yourself?
Well, I spend a lot of time
on the couch.
(chuckling)
Tell me about it.
Haven't we all?
I know you don't think
you're good enough for me,
but believe me... you are.
Hell, I've done it with pigs...
(chuckling)
Real no-foolin' pigs.
Are you sure it's a federal law
that I have to dance with you?
You know, I'd change that law
if I could, Marge,
but... I can't.
(whispering)
Aw, shoot.
Quebec's got the bomb.
Well, I got to go
but, look, if you're ever
near the white house
there's a tool-shed out back.
I'm in there most of the day.
(clicking tongue)
Attention, please. Attention.
Um, I just want to say how
thrilled I am with this turnout.
I'm proud to share my home
with Springfield's
best and brightest.
Hey, no problem.
We've all been blessed
with privilege and success.
Whoo! Privilege!
Uh, but with privilege
comes grave responsibility.
(spitting)
What?!
We all have to give
something back
to the world that's been
so good to us.
Give something back?
Boo! Get a haircut!
I'm talking, of course,
about our endangered forests.
(murmuring agreement)
What's happening in the forest?
We have to protect them
because trees can't protect
themselves...
Except, of course,
the Mexican fighting trees.
Somebody buy this guy a tree
so he'll shut up.
Can we let
the wanton destruction
of our nation's forests continue?
ALL: No!
If a tree falls in the forest,
will you make a sound?
ALL: Yes!
To the protest bus!
(all cheering)
Hey, stop shoving!
I'm Max Power.
(sobbing)
What's going on, Trent?
Where are you taking me?
We're going to try and save
some beautiful redwoods.
(screaming)
Aren't you coming, Ed?
I prefer a vehicle
that doesn't hurt mother Earth.
It's a go-cart powered by my
own sense of self-satisfaction.
Oh, this is the worst party ever.
I don't know...
Remember that new year's
eve at Lenny's?
He didn't even have a clock.
Oh, Marge,
I thought it would be fun
to be on Springfield's "A" list,
but these people are nuts.
You can't blame them
for having a social conscience.
Sure you can.
Bunch of no-good do-gooders.
Hang in there, Max.
Saving the environment
is a hard, grueling job.
That's what I am saying.
See, Marge? This guy gets it.
(siren blaring)
All right,
what's going on here?
We can't allow you to destroy
these beautiful trees
which have the same
rights you have.
Man, I have really had it
with you tree-huggers.
(chuckling)
"Tree-huggers".
Something funny, nature boy?
No. I just thought it was
cute when you called them--
Yeah, all right, Max Power.
Eddie, swab this joker's eyes
with mace.
"Swab"?
I thought it was a spray.
-Okay, she's second.
-Hmm?
(nervous sobbing)
Don't give them the satisfaction
of screaming, Max.
-It'll only burn for--
-(Homer screaming)
Hey, hold still.
Keep running, Max!
I can't lose him!
Help him out, Lou.
Uh, you better call
for backup, Chief.
Just leave me alone!
Go swab Begley. He likes it.
Slow down, punk!
Uh-oh.
I'm free! Whoo-hoo!
(screech)
Oh, no...
(rumbling)
(siren blares and fades)
Mmm, what a tragedy.
That car was just two days away
from retirement.
(all gasping)
This is terrible.
Uh, so, Trent...
where's the party bus
headed now?
What?
Well, I'm glad you
changed your name back
to Homer Simpson.
Yes... I learned
you got to be yourself.
-Good night, honey.
-Good night.
(click)
Oh, I almost forgot--
While I was at the courthouse
I had them change your name.
To what?
Chesty LaRue.
Chesty LaRue?
Just try it for two weeks.
If you're not
completely satisfied
you can be Busty St. Claire.
I don't want to be Chesty LaRue
or Busty St. Claire.
-Fine. Hooty McBoob it is.
-Good night, Homer.
HOMER: Sleep tight, Hooty.
MARGE: Let go of those.
HOMER: Heh-heh-heh...
(theme music playing)
Shh.
Captioned by
Visual Data Media Services