(Futurama theme plays)
♪ Two... two, three... ♪
Ooh. Wiggle in.
-Get comfortable.
-(Marge yells)
Hey, a couch is a couch.
-(Homer grunts)
-Ooh, yeah.
(sexy lounge music playing)
(Hedonismbot chuckling)
-(Homer moaning)
-Yes, there, you see?
-Oh, yeah!
-(giggles)
-(laughing)
-Oh-ho-ho-ho!
That's so...
HOMER:
Whoo-hoo!
SKINNER:
Uh, students,
each one of you
has been assigned
the mandatory honor of contributing
to the Springfield time capsule,
where your arcana will lie dormant
until the 31st century.
And...
(grunts)
By the time you finish talking,
we're gonna be
opening this damn capsule.
Right. Time capsule.
Nelson, give me something.
I brought a picture of my dad.
He's still at large...
(voice breaks)
in my heart!
I brought
my lucky rabbit's foot.
I can have good luck without it.
(gasps)
Ow!
Wish we could put this moment
in the time capsule.
Consider it done.
Uh, how about you, Bart?
Let me guess-- you forgot
to bring something.
I'm offended you think I forgot.
Let's see.
Ta-da!
Listen, boy, this is the only legacy
you'll ever leave.
Better make this count.
(blows nose)
(gasps)
My sandwich!
(devious chuckle)
And so a thousand years from now
this capsule will be opened
by some future Mayor Quimby.
(crowd cheers)
That-- That could be anyone's ooze.
(truck beeping)
(grunts)
There.
And now,
to help secure the jazz vote,
Lisa Simpson
will play her saxophone.
♪ ♪
(thunder crashes)
Even God hates jazz.
(thunder rumbling)
KENT BROCKMAN:
A mysterious electrical storm
is currently wreaking havoc
with our studio.
But I'm not one of those
brainless dolts
who mindlessly
reads a teleprompter-er...
error 401 backslash backslash
colon reset C-drive
shutting down.
-(electrical zapping)
-(male screaming)
-(crash)
-(grunts)
-What the hell was that?
-Probably just another piece
of America's space junk
falling out of orbit.
Remember when this country
didn't suck?
'Cause I don't.
(thunder crashing)
(loud glugging in distance)
(loud belch)
-(glass shatters)
-(gasps)
Homer,
I think there's someone downstairs.
Relax, Marge.
It's probably just Homer
coming home late from Moe's.
Hmm.
Ooh, the eyes in that picture
are following me!
Uh, that's a mirror.
Isn't all great art kind of a mirror?
(door creaks)
(deep belching nearby)
We'd better send the dog down.
Come on, here's your chance
to protect us, boy.
-(whining)
-Come on...
-(growls)
-Aah!
Stupid dog.
(growling)
Ow!
(clattering in distance)
MALE VOICE:
Ow.
We'll have to set a trap, Bait--
I mean, Bart.
HOMER:
All set.
When he starts gnawing at you,
I'll whack him with this broom.
(gasps)
Hmm.
Ooh! (chuckles)
Don't drink my loved ones!
Oh! Bite my shiny metal ass!
A robot!
With a catchphrase!
Hey, Homer, you gonna kiss him
or kill him?
-(grunts)
-(yells)
All right! Tether-boy!
-(grunting)
(yelling)
(chuckles)
Okay, so, what are you?
Must be a secret
government project.
Whoa, what do I look like, a narc?
My name is Bender,
and I come from...
the future!
Prove it. What happens
to Homer Simpson in the future?
I don't know. You die?
Oh... my... God.
He's telling the truth.
I have to take you
to our civic leaders.
(deep belch)
Hey, hibachi head,
how are you gonna pay for that?
Uh, let me just transfer some, uh,
electronic hyper-credits
into your register here.
Ding-da-ding-ding-ding-ding-
ding-ding!
Ooh, and, uh, another round
for my friends!
Ding-da-ding-ding-da-ding-ding.
(others cheer)
(chuckles)
Hey, this blade rummy is all right.
He's a big spender,
plus he fixed the jukebox.
(quietly)
I think they had a thing going.
FEMALE VOICE:
♪ Oh, baby, what you done to me... ♪
(needle scratches record)
I hate it when they get quiet.
Listen, uh,
I know you're a robot
and incapable of emotion...
(sobbing)
It's true.
I'm empty inside!
(sobbing loudly)
Uh, look, I just want to ask,
can we be friends?
BENDER:
Ooh.
You're the only guy I know
with less hair than me.
Sure.
That's why I came to your time--
for all you know.
OTHERS:
For all we know!
(chuckling)
D'oh!
(mechanical whirring)
A, uh, strike!
A totally legitimate strike!
Yeah!
(chuckles)
Hey, uh, what's the robot version
of bro-mance?
Ro-mance.
You future guys have a word
for everything... pal.
(both snoring)
You know,
they look a little similar.
Yeah.
Like the guy who designed Bender
just took a drawing of Dad
and stuck an antenna on it.
A little lazy, if you ask me.
Regardless,
I see no reason to believe
that Bender is from the future.
Robotic technology today
is very advanced.
Oh, really?
Can your modern-day robots
do this?
("The Stars and Stripes Forever" playing)
It's not my birthday--
although Maggie's is pretty soon.
I can't do "Maggie."
The Gs look like sixes.
This is the robot who claims
to be from the future.
Can your present-day robots
do this?
(babbling)
Uh, no, no, they cannot.
Not sure why they'd want to--
gorbid.
Now, why are you here?
What is your mission,
uh, so to speak?
I don't remember.
Man, this guy doesn't
ask permission--
he just goes right in you.
Eh... aha!
Bender's mission protocol
is definitely intact.
It just requires a delicate procedure
known as "unplug and re-plug."
(chuckles, mumbles)
Because that fixes everything.
-(whirring)
-I remember why I'm here!
To kill Homer Simpson!
-(gasps)
-(singsongy) My ears are burning.
(singsongy)
Not yet, but they will be.
(yelps)
A boxing glove!
But we bowled together.
Oh, I can't do it.
What stopped you, Bender,
Asimov's Three Laws of Robotics?
You think robots care what some
hack science fiction writer thinks?
I killed Isaac Asimov
on the way over here.
Well, Isaac somebody.
What the...?
My ass is about to project something.
(loud whisper)
You don't have to announce it.
Just do it quietly and blame the dog.
Bender,
we've just regained contact.
Have you killed Homer Simpson?
Uh, yep.
Killed him good.
If Homer's dead,
why are the creatures he begat
still here
and multiplying out of control?
(all chattering angrily)
What the...?
You lied to me, Bender!
Homer Simpson's still alive!
Come on, Bender, stabbity-stabbity.
Wait! Stop!
Why must you kill my dad?
Especially when cheeseburgers
are doing the work for you.
Homer Simpson
must be eliminated immediately.
The creatures destroying
New New York have his DNA.
The monsters are stealing
our office supplies!
That's inexcusable!
Gah!
Um...
Hello, robot.
Looks like everyone gets
a turn to say something.
This concludes my turn.
We sent Bender back in time
to kill Homer
before the monsters
could evolve from him.
Apparently,
this was too heartless a task for a robot.
Leela, can you handle it?
In a New New York minute minute.
(explosion)
-(grunts)
-Ow!
(chuckles)
Ow!
Right in my language center!
(jittery gibberish)
Professor,
y-you're a fellow man of science.
Maybe if we teamed up,
we could, uh, figure something out.
Okay. Eh, but remember,
to me you're incredibly stupid.
Oh, and the annoying girl may be helpful.
Meanwhile, Leela,
take Homer and explore this time period.
Find out why people would ever pay
for "freemium games."
I'll explain.
Okay, it starts free, right?
Then you visit your friend's game,
and he's got this awesome
candy mansion...
Get a load of those freaks!
And you're like, "99 cents?!
You bet I'd like one!"
And that's why I owe
Clash of Candies $20,000.
Here we are.
Marge,
I'd like you to meet Leela and Fry.
MARGE: Oh, don't mention her eye.
Don't mention her eye.
LEELA: Don't mention her hair.
Don't mention her hair.
I... am so pleased to meet you.
Nice to be hair.
-(laughs)
-(soft grumble)
Oh, Lord.
(professors mumbling)
Professor Farnsworth,
I'm dying to know how you got here.
-Was it a time machine?
-Little girl,
time machines
are physical impossibilities.
We teleported through a singularity
that I quantum entangled to Bender
under the guise of fixing his collar.
Yes,
but how did Bender get here?
-With a time machine.
-But you just said that...
-(bell dings)
-Sample's ready!
(snores)
Kill all humans.
Start with Flanders.
(snores)
Good news, everyone!
That means it's bad.
The human DNA in the creatures
was only half Homer's.
The other half came from...
someone else.
Oh, so we can kill that person instead.
Maybe they're evil and deserve it.
Or have one of those annoying voices
that gets on everybody's nerves,
with the adding
extra noises for no reason.
Myveen.
Bloingy.
And the other person is...
HOMER:
Oh, who's that?
-It's me.
-(gasps)
Wait a minute.
We don't have to kill you.
Oh, well, that's better.
We just have to kill all your children.
-(exclaims)
-Or just one of them.
If you can figure out which
one sired the killer rabbits.
(whistling)
(rattling)
We interrupt this hologram
to bring you an important bulletin.
The horrific creatures
destroying New New York
have begun metamorphosing.
(laughs)
(muffled screaming)
(grunting)
(all growling)
(man gasping)
Eat my shorts!
¡Ay, caramba!
(laughs)
What a surprise.
It's Bart.
Wow,
I'm doing the same jokes
a thousand years later.
¡Ay, caramba!
But how did a mere boy
destroy the future?
Well...
Let this be a lesson.
Never throw meaningless crap
in a time capsule.
That's it! All we have to do
is dig up the time capsule.
And bury Bart in the hole.
I thought people in the future
would be more full of peace and love.
Like in Epcot Center.
In our time,
Epcot Center is a work farm for the weak.
Oh, but it's not as crowded
as the slave labor camps
at Universal Studios.
(grumbles)
(tires screeching)
HOMER:
We're here.
(chuckles)
My bowling buddy.
GROUNDSKEEPER WILLIE:
Hey!
You can't dig that up
for a thousand years.
Plus, I wrote my name there.
See?
(rattling)
Shmayday!
(gasps) They got Scruffy!
Nope.
They just got my mustache.
But a life without a mustache
ain't worth livin'.
FARNSWORTH:
No!
That generator powers the portal.
If they destroy it, we'll be...
(exclaims)
(grunts)
...sucked back into the future.
Okay, head count.
One, two, three... (gasps)
Where's Maggie?
Well, little meatbag,
it looks like it's just you and me.
Stuck in a terrible past
where I know the result
of every horse race ever!
To the track!
-I want that.
-Well, you can't have it.
(glass breaking)
Why, you little...
Dad, it's me.
Prove it.
When's your birthday?
February 23rd.
Ha! February has no 23rd.
-You... (grunts)
-(grunting)
Yes, it does.
Can you please just get us
out of this lousy future?
Actually, of all probable futures,
this is the worst.
It is, 'cause my baby's not in it.
Motherly love.
Why did we outlaw that?
Madam, our mechanical friend
Bender is your portal home.
But we can't use him until
the generator is repaired.
Homer works at a nuclear plant.
He can help us get home.
Oh, are you good at your job?
I was voted employee of the month
as an April Fools' Day joke.
Why, you little...
Great.
You and Fry
can bumble around together
while the rest of us
give up and make peace
with our various deities.
As for me, I'm an atheist.
Oh, nobody's father, who art nowhere,
I know you can't hear me,
completely ignore this prayer.
Nothing art thou and nothing
will thou ever be.
Jesus was just a man.
ALL:
Amen.
Well, I shall stay here
for the decadence.
There's no debauchery
like end-of-the-world debauchery.
Your lips, my lips, apocalypse, ooh!
I can't believe
you're all giving up without a fight.
Lisa,
we're just a package delivery service.
And not a very good one.
The only way to handle
the creatures
is to do what we do to each year's
Super Bowl losers:
shoot them into space.
But we'd have to round them up first.
Let me take care of that.
If there's one thing I know how to do,
it's manipulate Barts.
You're nuts.
I've got a will of iron.
(deep humming)
(mumbles)
Okay, let's get going.
(drooling)
Dad, we have beer in our time.
Hey, I haven't had a drink
in a thousand years.
(horse neighs)
(gasps)
There's a horse called Bender's Bounty.
But my memory says
he died during the race.
That can't be true.
ANNOUNCER:
And way, way, way back is Bender's Bounty.
Damn it!
Oh, Chief, it looks like a robot
killing horses over there.
Oh, a 608...
Lou, can't you just
let me enjoy my day off?
W-Why are you dressed
in your uniform, then?
'Cause they're the only clothes
that fit me.
You happy? Happy?
Attention, goblins.
Madison Cube Garden
is filled with Butterfinger bars.
And people are laying fingers
all over them!
(cackling, grunting)
They're evolving. Wow.
That's a first for you, Bart.
Will you shut up?
-(gentle melody plays)
-(grunting)
Uh, did I remind you
to strap yourselves in?
(all cheering)
You realize you're cheering the death
of millions of my children.
(all cheering)
Wow, it's working.
I guess the instructions were in English.
What the...?!
Whoa!
Hey, here's a souvenir photo
of you guys coming out of my chest.
Aw, I will treasure this forever.
Lie detected.
Oh, my sweet baby.
Oh, feels like you have a full diaper.
Ooh, um, I'll change her.
(whispers)
Here's your cut.
Nice knowing you, meatbags.
Have fun turning to dust.
Wait, wait, wait.
You're the portal.
How are you
gonna get to the future?
The old-fashioned way.
Good night, friend.
You'll always have a special place
here with us.
(grunting)
Thanks, pal.
(eerie music playing)
Look at this mess.
It would have disintegrated upon entry
if someone hadn't turned off
the atmosphere last night.
I like it cold when I'm sleeping.
Besides, these horrible
Earth creatures are delicious.
The Johnsons will be here
for dinner any minute.
What happened
to the handsome man I married?
-I ate him, remember?
-Here they are.
Uh, hmm...
Hope we're not interrupting anything.
(burps)
I can't take any more.
(sobbing)
I-I can't take it.
Well, perhaps the one of you
that is female should go console her.
(Futurama theme plays)
♪ Two... two, three... ♪
HOMER:
♪ Simpsons in the future ♪
♪ Space jokes flying through town ♪
♪ What are those tubes? ♪
♪ I wonder what ♪
♪ Ice cream's like now ♪
♪ Maybe it's hot ♪
♪ Or some new temperature
they invented ♪
That's it, we're done.
(The Simpsons theme plays)
-(crowd murmuring)
-Shh!
Subtitled by Jimmy Boots