♪ The Simpsons ♪
(chalk screeches)
(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(tires screeching)
(horn honks)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
MAN:
Live from beautiful Laughlin, Nevada.
It's the Miss American
Girl Pageant.
Brought to you by
Meryl Streep's Versatility.
Smell like Streep for cheap.
I'm your host
Troy McClure, and now
here come the ladies.
♪ We learned
the truth at 17 ♪
♪ That love was meant
for beauty queens ♪
TROY: Like Miss South Dakota.
Miss North Carolina.
Miss Indiana.
-Miss Alaska.
-Kids, I won't be home tonight,
so I'm leaving you some low-cal
microwavable TV dinners.
Okay.
I'm auditioning for a play.
It's a musical version
of "A Streetcar Named Desire."
Isn't that exciting?
TROY: If you ask me,
they're all winners.
We'll be cutting
our first 40 contestants
right after this.
TROY: Let's take
a minute to meet
our distinguished
panel of judges.
Skin care consultant
Rowena.
Syndicated columnist
William F. George.
Token black panelist
Dredrick Tatum
and Mr. Boswell,
the man behind those infamous
worst-dressed lists.
Mr. Boswell,
can you give us
a sneak peek
at this year's list?
Memo to Goldie Hawn:
cheerleading try-outs
were 30 years ago.
-Let's grow up, shall we?
-(laughing)
(laughs)
He's such a bitch.
I haven't been in a play
since high school,
and I thought it would be a good chance
to meet some other adults.
Sounds interesting.
You know, I spend all day
alone with Maggie,
and sometimes it's like
I don't even exist.
-Sounds interesting.
-(groans)
It's time to name our five
finalists, starting with
Miss Montana.
A beaut from Butte.
Miss South Carolina.
Nothing could be finer.
Miss Delaware.
Gee, uh...
good for her.
♪ La-la-la-la-la-la ♪
Marge, keep it down
in there.
Homer, my audition
is in half--
Hey, look, it's last year's
winner, Debra Del Smallwood!
Tonight, my reign
as Miss American Girl
comes to an end,
and I'd like to apologize
one last time
for my unfortunate remarks
at the United Nations.
(playing Dance of
the Sugar Plum Fairies)
Maggie, cut that racket!
And where exactly
are you going?
I'm auditioning
for a play.
Well, this is the first
I've heard about it.
I told you
several times.
It's a musical version of
"A Streetcar Named--"
Excuse me, Marge.
I think that if you
had told me, I would remember.
I mean, I'm not an idiot.
-Well, I thought I told you--
-Kids, back me up.
-He's right, Mom.
-Sorry.
Match point,
Homer.
I'm sorry,
honey.
That's okay.
We're none of us perfect.
(people warming up
their voices, piano)
♪ Me-may-mow-mo-moo ♪
Well, howdy do,
neighbor.
Hi, Ned, I didn't know
you were an actor.
Oh, Indeedily doodily.
I've even been
in "Streetcar" once before.
I played Blanche Dubois.
Mm-hmm.
Just part of the fun of
going to an all-male school.
Hello, I am Llewelyn Sinclair.
I have directed three plays
in my career,
and I have had
three heart attacks.
That's how much I care.
I'm planning for a fourth.
Maybe I should have taken
a nice calligraphy class.
Oh, forget about it, that
Mr. Takahashi's a lunatic.
-Quiet!
-Sorry.
I am not an easy man
to work for.
While directing
"Hats Off to Chanukah,"
I reduced more than one
cast member to tears.
Did I expect too much
from fourth graders?
The review, "Play Enjoyed
By All" speaks for itself.
Hmm.
Those auditioning
for the role of Stanley,
take off
your shirts.
Take off your shirts!
Deshabillez votre chemises.
Schnell, schnell, schnell!
Uh-uh.
Nope.
Try joining a gym.
Oh, ye Gods!
Hey, man, if you like that,
you should see my butt.
You, you're my Stanley.
Hotdiggity.
How about that, Marge?
Little old Stanley me.
(softly)
Stella.
(louder)
Stella! Heh heh heh.
♪ Hey, look me over-- ♪
-Next.
-♪ Won't you come home Bill Bai-- ♪
Next.
♪ There's got to be a-- ♪
-Next.
-♪ Lah-- ♪
Thank you for nothing.
You're all terrible.
What you ladies don't
understand is that Blanche
is a delicate flower
being trampled
by an uncouth lout.
(sighs)
Forget it.
Just strike the sets.
Clear the stage.
This production is--
Homie, I didn't get the part.
You were right,
outside interests are stupid.
Wait a minute.
(groans)
I'll come home right away.
All right, I'll pick up
a bucket of fried chicken
extra skin.
Rolls,
chocolate cream parfait--
(gasps)
Stop bothering my Blanche!
I play an aging
southern beauty
who's driven to insanity
by her brutish
brother-in-law Stanley.
Wow! My mother, the actress.
I feel like
Lucie Arnaz-Luckinbill.
Are there any jive-talking
robots in this play?
Hmm, I don't think so.
Bart, don't ask
stupid questions.
Is there any
frontal nudity?
No, Homer.
My name
is Helen Lovejoy,
and I'll be playing Stella.
I am Apu Nahasapeemapetilon.
I play Steve.
My name is Otto.
I'm playing Pablo.
Lionel Hutz, attorney at law.
I'm filing a class-action
suit against the director
on behalf of everyone
who was cut from the play.
I also play Mitch.
I'm Marge Simpson.
I'll be playing Blanche.
I made some peanut butter
brownies for everyone.
Well, would anyone else
like a bite of banality?
I would.
-Stanley...
-Yeah.
you're-you're pulsing
with animal lust.
You take Blanche and you
fling her roughly to the bed.
Roger-dodger.
(grunts)
(growls)
Aw! Isn't that cute?
Me without a camera.
Here, my sister runs
a day-care center.
Hmm. I guess a few weeks
wouldn't hurt her.
MARGE: Maggie is allergic
to strained pears
and she likes a bottle of
warm milk before nap time.
A bottle?
(laughs)
Mrs. Simpson, do you know
what a baby's saying
when she reaches
for a bottle?
Ba-ba?
She's saying, "I am a leech."
Our aim here is to develop
the bottle within.
That sounds awfully harsh.
Mrs. Simpson, I don't like
to toot my own horn,
but we're the only
day-care center in town
that's not currently under
investigation by the state.
Oh.
Well, be a good girl,
Maggie.
I'm sorry, Maggie.
We don't allow these here.
♪ You're a dame,
and I'm a fella ♪
♪ Stanley, stop,
or I'll tell Stella ♪
Passion,
Mrs. Simpson!
Anger.
This man disgusts you.
♪ All I want
is one embrace ♪
♪ I'll twist this bottle
in your face ♪
(grunting softly)
(laughs)
Here, Marge, let me.
Hate to be
an Armchair Blanche,
but I always
gave it one of these.
(chuckles) There, there's
the old face shredder.
-Oh.
-Mrs. Simpson, if you set out
to push the bile
to the tip of my throat,
mission accomplished.
I'm, uh...
I'm gonna crawl into bed
with a bottle of amaretto.
Good day.
HOMER: Easy, easy.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
-D'oh!
-Seven-ten split.
Homer, can you run
some lines with me?
Make Bart do it.
It will just take a sec.
Gutter ball.
D'oh!
You see, Marge?
While you're off in
your own little world,
you forgot that other people
have problems too.
(sighs)
(theme music from
"The Great Escape" playing)
(crashing)
(thuds)
Don't like to nap, eh?
We have a place
for babies like you.
The box!
(theme music from
"The Great Escape" playing)
All right, let amateur night
in Dixie commence.
I'm sorry, Llewelyn.
I just-- I just don't see
why Blanche should
shove a broken bottle
in Stanley's face.
Couldn't she just
take his abuse
with gentle
good humor?
Marge, your ride's here.
Homer, it will just be
a few minutes more.
♪ You're a dame,
and I'm a fella ♪
♪ Stanley, stop,
or I'll tell Stella ♪
LLEWELYN:
Marge, Marge...
I'm asking
for white-hot rage,
and you're giving me
a hissy fit.
Marge, can I get some change
for the candy machine?
Oh, here!
(coins clinking)
Hey, there's some
quarters in here.
I just don't see what's
so bad about Stanley.
(angry grunting)
-Stanley is thoughtless, violent and loud.
-(Homer grunting loudly)
Marge, every second
you spend with this man,
he is crushing
your fragile spirit.
You can't let
that happen.
(Homer yelling)
Woo-hoo!
Come to papa.
Marge, I'll be out in the car.
♪ All I want
is one embrace ♪
(horn honking)
HOMER:
Marge, move it or lose it.
(angrily)
♪ I'll twist this bottle in your face ♪
(grunts)
Alleluia! I have done it again.
Ned, you're supposed
to overpower her.
I'm trying, I'm trying.
(both grunting)
Salt me.
(Bad Southern accent)
Here you are, Homer.
What the--
Why are you talking like that?
The play's tomorrow night.
I've got to stay
in character.
(Southern drawl)
Hey Mom, would it help
-if I talked like this too?
-It might.
(British accent) And I'll talk like this.
Bob's your uncle, mate.
That really
doesn't help, Bart.
Big Daddy, would y'all mind
passing a little ol' biscuit?
(British accent) Can I slog off school
tomorrow? Got a pain in me gulliver.
I'm living in a cuckoo clock.
Ooh!
See ya' later kids.
I've got to go rehearse
with Ned.
But Marge,
What about dessert?
For God sakes, you can pull
the lid off your own can of pudding!
Fine! I will!
(screaming)
Oh, no, my pudding
is trapped forever.
So I can open my own
can of pudding, can I?
Shows what you know, Marge.
Marge!
Hey, Marge!
Keep yelling, you big ape.
(chuckles) Aren't you being
a little hard on old Homie?
Oh, forget about him.
Let's rehearse
the bottle scene.
Oh-ho, let's not
and say we did, hmm?
(reading quietly)
So, what time
does this play start?
Why, are you going?
Well, I got to go, don't I?
I'm sure you
won't enjoy it.
There's nothing about
bowling in the play.
Oh, wait, there is.
Probably not much of it.
Why can't you be a
little more supportive?
'Cause I don't care, okay?
I can't fake an
interest in this,
and I'm an expert
at faking an interest
in your kooky projects.
What kooky projects?
You know, the painting class,
the first aid course,
the whole Lamaze thing.
Why didn't you tell me
you felt this way?
You know I would never do
anything to hurt your feelings.
Good night.
(snoring)
(groaning)
Playing nicely, little humans?
Good, good.
Hello, Maggie.
Poor little dullard.
(theme from
"The Great Escape" plays)
KRUSTY DOLL: Hey, kids!
I'm flame-retardant. (laughing)
(gasps)
DOLL: If I break, buy a new one.
(laughing)
(glass shatters)
(babies clamoring)
HOMER:
Maggie, time to go to the-- (screams)
(echoing sucking sounds)
(echoing sucking
sounds continues)
HOMER (shivering):
Oh.... babies.
Perhaps we are all
a little mad,
we who don the cap and bells,
and tread beneath
the proscenium arch.
But tonight,
you will all be transformed
from dead-eyed suburbanites
into white-hot grease fires
of pure entertainment!
Except you.
You're not working out.
I'll be playing
your part.
Drag!
♪ Long before the Superdome ♪
♪ Where the Saints
of football play ♪
♪ Lived a city that
the damned call home ♪
♪ Hear their
hellish roundelay ♪
♪ New Orleans ♪
♪ Home of pirates,
drunks, and whores ♪
♪ New Orleans ♪
♪ Tacky, overpriced
souvenir stores ♪
♪ If you want to go to hell,
you should take a trip ♪
♪ To the Sodom and Gomorrah
on the Mississip ♪
♪ New Orleans ♪
♪ Stinking, rotten, vomity,
vile, New Orleans ♪
♪ Putrid, brackish,
maggoty, foul ♪
♪ New Orleans ♪
♪ Crummy, lousy,
wretched and rank ♪
♪ New Orleans ♪
ACTRESS:
What's the matter, honey? Are ya' lost?
MARGE:
I'm looking for my sister, Stella.
LISA:
It's Mom!
Huh?
My name is Blanche Dubois.
♪ I thought my life would
be a Mardi Gras ♪
♪ A never-ending party ♪
Ha!
♪ I'm a faded Southern dame
without a dime ♪
I'm collecting
for The Evening Star.
Come here.
I want to kiss you
just once,
softly and sweetly
on your mouth.
♪ I am just
a simple paper boy ♪
♪ No romance do I seek ♪
♪ I just wanted 40 cents ♪
♪ For my deliveries
last week ♪
♪ Will this
bewitching floozy ♪
♪ Seduce this
humble newsy ♪
♪ Oh, what's
a paper boy to ♪
♪ Do? ♪
Whoo-hoo!
Stella!
♪ Can't you hear me yell-a ♪
♪ You're puttin' me
through hell-a ♪
♪ Stella ♪
Stella!
(Marge moaning, shouting)
Cool, she can fly.
I think it's supposed to
symbolize her descent into madness.
(moaning, shouting continue)
Whoever you are,
I have always depended
on the kindness of strangers.
♪ You can always depend
on the kindness of strangers ♪
♪ To buck up your spirits
and shield you from dangers ♪
♪ Now, here's a tip from
Blanche you won't regret ♪
♪ A stranger's just a friend
you haven't met ♪
♪ You haven't met ♪
♪ Streetcar! ♪
(applause)
-LISA: Yay!
-(Bart whistles)
♪♪
Ahh!
BOTH: Yay!
Mwah! Mwah!
You people out there,
you are the stars!
Cool!
Hey, look at me!
I'm Blanche Dubois.
Mom!
Oof!
Way to go, Mom.
Everybody
was cheering for you.
Almost everybody.
Kids, wait in the car.
I want to talk to your mother
about this play thing.
(British accent) Looking for a spot
of fun with the Missus, eh Gov'nor?
Shut up, boy.
Marge, you were terrific.
Oh, come on, Homer.
By the end,
you were so bored,
you could barely keep
your selfish head up.
I wasn't bored.
I was sad.
It really got to me
how that lady, uh, um...
You know which one I mean.
You played her.
Blanche.
Yeah, how Blanche was sad,
and how that guy, Stanley,
should have been nice to her.
Yeah, go on.
I mean,
it made me feel bad.
The poor thing ends up
being hauled to the nut house,
when all she needed
was for that big slob
to show her some respect.
At least,
that's what I thought.
I have a history of missing
the point of stuff like this.
No, Homer,
you got it just right.
Hey, you know,
I'm a lot like that guy.
-Really?
-Yeah,
like when I pick my teeth
with the mail and stuff.
Well, maybe just a little.
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.