♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
Well, sir, it has been an
uneventful week in Badger Falls,
where the women are robust,
the men are pink-cheeked,
and the children are
pink-cheeked and robust.
(laughing)
What the hell's so funny?
(inhales)
At the Apple Biscuit Cafe,
where the smiles are free,
don't you know,
Sven Inqvist studied
the menu,
and finally, he ordered
the same thing he has every day.
(laughter)
Maybe it's the TV.
Stupid TV. Be more funny!
(grunts)
Well, sir, I think
it is time
to turn this pledge drive
over to Troy McClure.
I can't keep up
this pace forever.
(deep sigh)
Hi, I'm Troy McClure.
You might remember me
from such telethons as
"Out With Gout '88"
and "Let's Save
Tony Orlando's House."
Folks, do you realize
without your support,
public television
can't afford to bring you
such award-winning shows as
"Edward The Penitent"?
I'm really, really,
really sorry.
I'm afraid sorry doesn't
cut it with this pope.
Oh-ho.
-(phone ringing)
-What the hell?
Oh, we got a call.
(chuckles) Some idiot
actually called in.
-Hello. What's your name?
-Marge Simpson.
-(screams)
-I'd like to pledge $30.
Oh, thank you.
Marge, it's public TV.
They never have anything good.
Where are the Geraldos?
Where are the Eubankses-ses?
They need our support.
Besides, they gave me
two tickets to the ballet.
-The ballet? Whoo-hoo!
-You like ballet?
Marjorie, please.
I enjoy all the meats of
our cultural stew.
Ahh, ballet.
Hee-hee-hee. All right.
Whoo-hoo! Yea!
(laughing)
Yeah!
♪♪ (humming with
calliope music)
(humming continues)
-(doorbell rings)
-(humming continues)
-Hello, Ruth.
-Hi, Marge.
I was wondering if you had
a power sander I could borrow.
-Homer?
-Nope.
-(whirring)
-That's one right there.
All right.
But remember, it's mine.
That's what ballet is?
(groans)
You promised.
You can't back out like when
you volunteered
for that army experiment
to avoid dinner at my sisters'.
Mr. Simpson, you do realize
this may result in
hair loss, giddiness
and the loss of equilibrium?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Just give me the serum.
(chuckles)
It was worth it.
-(thudding)
-(Homer giggling)
Hey, Homer, you wanna get
a beer on the way home?
I can't. I gotta take my wife
to the ballet.
(chuckles) Gonna go see
the bear in the little car, huh?
Hmm?
Mmm, invisible cola.
Mmm.
(chuckles)
Time to stick it to the man.
Hey, hey.
Careful there, Homer.
I heard somebody lost
an arm in there once.
(scoffs) That's just
an old wives' tale.
(grunting, straining)
(grunting)
Just a little more--
(grunts)
Got it.
(screams)
I'm stuck.
Help me.
-He's done for!
-Let's get outta here!
(both yelling)
(grunting)
(grunts)
Must... get to ballet.
Promised Marge.
(grunts)
HOMER: Hello?
Can I get some help?
Snack-related mishap.
(grunting)
Mmm. Candy.
-(phone rings)
-Hello?
Marge, this may be
hard to believe,
but I'm trapped inside
two vending machines.
(loud sigh)
Sure, Homer.
Trapped in vending machines.
Okay.
Would you two
like to go to the ballet?
-(snorts) That's girl stuff.
-(doorbell rings)
Thanks, Marge.
When my husband left,
he took all our power tools,
along with the car,
my youth, my faith in mankind.
Well, see ya.
Mmm. Hey, wait!
♪♪ (classical)
♪♪ (continues)
Vyachepov's loins
oughta be outlawed.
(giggling)
(scoffs)
Far too much dancing,
not nearly enough prancing.
A little mincing
would be nice.
(all gasp)
-(glass shattering)
-(buzzer buzzes)
(applause)
Well, thank you
for a lovely time.
You're not going home
already, are you?
It's almost 9:30.
(laughs) Yeah, right.
We better turn in.
(laughs)
Oh, you were serious.
Oh, I'm gonna have these things
on my arms forever.
♪♪ ("Wedding March")
(guests cheering)
-Candy and sodas for all.
-(cheering)
Mmm, convenient.
Homer, this-- this is
never easy to say.
I'm gonna have to
saw your arms off.
-They'll grow back, right?
-Oh, yeah.
-Whew.
-(whirring)
Homer, are you just
holding on to the can?
-Your point being?
-(men laughing)
I envy you and Homer.
Thank you.
Why?
If you ever met my ex-husband,
you'd understand.
All he ever did was eat,
sleep and drink beer.
Your point being?
And to top it off,
he's been stiffing me
on child support for
the last four months.
(groans)
Well, you were unlucky.
But there are
a lot of good men out there.
Hey, can I throw up
in your bathroom?
-I'll buy something.
-(shudders)
Marge, I know you
didn't believe me
about the vending machines.
That's why I had
the firemen write me a note.
"Mrs. Simpson: While we were
rescuing your husband,
a lumberyard burned down."
D'oh! Lumber has
a million uses.
I'm disappointed in you,
but it turns out
I had a wonderful time
with Ruth Powers.
In fact, we're going out again
tomorrow night.
Marge, that's twice.
I think you're spending entirely
too much time with this woman.
Homer, please.
You know it's hard
for me to make friends.
(laughs) Oh, Marge, we should
do this every Thursday.
Marge, I got sprayed by
this skunk.
-(hissing)
-Oh, look. It's doing it again.
(all screaming)
Marge, you can't go out
on Saturday.
That's our special night.
What's so special
about it?
What's so--
Oh, I don't know.
A little show called
"Dr. Quinn, Medicine Woman"?
(groans)
-Where're you going?
-I don't know.
-When will you be home?
-I'm not sure.
-Where're you going?
-You already asked me that.
Will you bring me
back something?
(horn honks)
Don't wait up.
How can you do this, Marge?
How can you desert
your children?
-Have a blast, Mom.
-Rock the Casbah.
Man's best friend indeed.
Whoa.
You look... nice.
Tonight has nothing
to do with nice.
Tonight's all about...
♪ Sunshine, lollipops
and rainbows ev-- ♪
Oh. Sorry, Marge.
Wrong tape.
♪ Welcome to the jungle
we got fun and games ♪
-♪ We got everything... ♪
-(Marge screams)
I can't believe
your mother went out
to have fun without me.
Don't worry.
You'll feel better once we put
your hair up in curlers
and give you a makeover,
Homina.
(high-pitched voice)
Oh, that would be delight--
(normal voice)
Quiet, boy.
There's nothing to feel
ashamed of here.
Women have a right to
a night out. Right, Lisa?
Sure, Dad.
(imitates whip cracking)
That's it!
I'm calling my buddies.
Marge is not the only one
who can have a girls' night out.
Oh, no can do, Homer.
I'm watching the game.
Shave up not down,
you idiot.
Ooh, sounds delish.
Let me just toss
some jeans on and--
Wait a minute.
Who is this?
-(phone ringing)
-Well, howdilly dodilly-do.
-(line clicks, dial tone)
-Hello?
Hello? Hellodilly-odilly?
Fine. I can have
a great time all by myself.
Hey, Dad, I think state
and federal laws
require us to have a babysitter.
(chuckles) Oh, Lisa.
Haven't you seen "Home Alone"?
If some burglars come,
it'll be a very humorous
and entertaining situation.
You're absolutely right, Homer.
We don't need a babysitter.
Wait a second.
Hmm...
You kids do need a babysitter.
Blast that infernal card.
Don't give that card to me.
-Here you go-- No!
-(doorbell rings)
Mr. Simpson, I was just
going through your garbage,
and I couldn't help
overhearing that
you need a babysitter.
Of course, being
a highly skilled attorney,
my fee is $175 an hour.
We pay eight dollars
for the night,
and you can take two popsicles
out of the freezer.
-Three.
-Two.
Okay, two, and I get to
keep this old birdcage.
-Done.
-Still got it.
MARGE: Oh, I've heard a lot
about Shot Kickers.
♪♪ (country)
(grunts) How come
no one else's chair is doing this?
Hey, baby.
Feel like getting lucky?
I am lucky.
I have a husband
and three wonderful children.
Thank you very much.
Listen, baby.
I always get what I want.
-I said no.
-Oh, did ya?
Oh, I completely misunderstood.
Please accept our apologies.
Sometimes you gotta go
where everybody knows your name.
Hey, guys!
(fan squeaking)
Moe, get the darts.
I wanna play.
No. We're phasing out
the games.
People drink less when
they're having fun.
Oh.
Oh, sure. Like lawyers work
in big skyscrapers
and have secretaries.
Look at him.
He's wearing a belt.
That's Hollywood for you.
MARGE: Ooh, I've never been
to an underground club.
♪♪ (dance)
Don't you think
your hair is a bit much?
Hey, Mrs. Simpson,
you should try one of these
smart drinks. (laughs)
Oh, wow.
I've wasted my life.
Would you, uh,
care to dance?
Mayor Quimby!
What are you doing here?
I'm here with my nephews.
Oh, that's nice.
Ooh, jet. Whoo-hoo!
It's Garrett Morris's birthday.
Hmph.
This is not
a library.
This is not a Kwik-E-Mart.
What was it
you wanted to show me?
-This.
-(gasps)
You're not gonna hunt me
for sport, are you?
(chuckles)
Relax, Marge.
I'd never turn
a gun on a human being.
My husband,
on the other hand.
(gunshots)
-Come on. You try it.
-No. I couldn't.
Yeah. Just breathe slowly
and squeeze the--
(gunshots)
I hit it! I hit it!
My cans.
My precious antique cans.
Aw, look what
you done to 'em.
Well, it's getting late.
Maybe we should call it
a night.
It's only midnight.
Come on. I know a place.
Whoa.
Beautiful, huh?
Homer and I used to
come up here on dates.
Homer, stop that.
It's just a weather station.
(grunts) Come on, Marge.
It's fun to smash things.
(laughs)
I smashed it good.
You got real "purdy" hair.
You know, Marge,
of all the places
we've been tonight,
I think I like
this one the best.
Mmm. Me too.
Look, you can see
our houses.
MARGE: There's an awful lot
of black smoke
coming from my chimney.
Mr. Hutz, why are you burning
all your personal papers?
As of this moment,
Lionel Hutz no longer exists.
Say hello to Miguel Sanchez.
Mmm, maybe we should
call it a night.
Okay. I should get home
to my daughter
before that naked talk show
comes on.
(starts engine)
Ah, young love.
The old make-out place.
Hey, a new weather station!
I'll bash it good.
Oh...
It's just no fun
without Marge.
Ah, there's nothing like
moonshine from your own still.
Oh, Simpson.
What are you doing here?
My wife's having
a girls' night out.
Ah, just get one of those
inflatable women.
But make sure it's
a woman though.
'Cause one time I--
(stammering)
Come on. I'll, uh--
I'll give you a ride home.
(groans)
I miss you, Marge.
Huh.
Their left taillight's
a little smaller than
their right one.
-I better pull 'em over.
-(siren wails)
-I think they want us to stop.
-Fat chance.
-This car's stolen.
-Stolen?
-(revs engine)
-(Marge screams)
Looks like we got ourselves
an old-fashioned car chase.
♪♪ (pop)
♪ Sunshine, lollipops ♪
♪ And rainbows, everything ♪
♪ That's wonderful is what
I feel when we're together ♪
♪ Brighter than a lucky penny
when you're near ♪
♪ The rain clouds disappear
dear and I feel so fine... ♪
(siren wails)
Ruth, is there something
you wanna tell me?
Remember when I said
my ex-husband was behind
on his child support?
Mm-hmm.
Well, to even things up,
I kind of stole his car.
Didn't you realize
all you had to do was
report him to the police?
Marge, you're the levelheaded
friend I never had.
(groans)
We're in pursuit
of two female suspects.
One is wearing
a green dress, pearls,
and has a lot of blue hair.
A lot of blue hair?
(giggles) What a freak.
-(car hits bump)
-Ooh!
(screams)
It's Marge!
She's become a crazed criminal
just because I didn't
take her to the ballet.
That's exactly
how Dillinger got started.
Really?
I don't wanna be
a wet blanket,
but maybe you should
give yourself up.
Marge, it's a matter
of principle.
I just can't let
that deadbeat win again.
You're with me, aren't ya?
(thinking) I should say something
reassuring yet noncommittal.
(groans)
Look, Marge,
there's no reason
for you to get
dragged into this.
Once we lose the cops,
I'll let you out.
Well, I don't think
they're gonna be
that easy to lose.
These are professional
lawmen and--
Oh, my God!
It just disappeared.
It's a ghost car!
-(tires screech)
-(grunts)
There are ghost cars all over
these highways, you know.
-Hold me.
-Only if you hold me.
(coyote howling)
(shuddering)
You can call
a cab in there.
Well... bye.
I'm sorry about all this.
But you gotta admit,
we did have some fun.
Yeah. Everything before
the high-speed chase
was just lovely.
Hey. You're
a good friend, Marge.
Mmm.
(coin clatters)
This cross-country flight
from the law would be hell
if we didn't stick together.
Hey. Friends stick together.
It's amazing how through
all this adversity,
we managed
to stick together.
If there's one thing
decent folk do,
it's stick together.
I hate it when
the waffles stick together.
Sticking together
is what good waffles do.
(groans)
(siren wailing)
Thanks, kid.
Marge, what are you doing?
Ruth, I've done a lot
of thinking,
and I really
consider you a friend.
And an important part
of friendship is--
-(tires screech)
-(Marge screams)
-(siren blaring)
-You stupid kid!
You know that drives away
all my business.
See you tomorrow, loser.
(sizzling)
Mmm, engine-block eggs.
If we can keep these down,
we'll be sitting pretty.
-That's them!
-Quiet. I can't hear the eggs.
(snoring)
(grunts)
Hey, it's morning,
and Mom and Dad
aren't home yet.
Don't worry.
Mr. Hutz is still here
to take care of us.
Don't touch my stuff!
Hey. This isn't
the Y.M.C.A.
Dispatch,
this is Chief Wiggum
back in pursuit
of the rebelling women.
MAN (on radio): All right.
Your current location?
Oh. Uh, I'm, uh--
I'm on a road.
Looks to be asphalt.
Um, aw, geez.
Trees, shrubs.
I'm directly under
the Earth's sun... now.
MAN (on TV):
We now interrupt this program
for a special bulletin.
We've just received word of
a high-speed desert chase.
The suspects have been
identified as Ruth Powers
and Marge Simpson
of Springfield.
-(gasps)
-Cool.
I always knew someday
Mom would violently rise up
and cast off the shackles
of our male oppressors.
Eh, shut your yap.
At the risk of
editorializing,
these women are guilty
and must be dealt with in
a harsh and brutal fashion.
Otherwise, their behavior
could incite other women,
leading to anarchy
of biblical proportions.
It's in Revelations,
people!
(sirens blaring)
Look. We're only two miles
from the state line.
We're gonna make it.
We're gonna be okay.
My God! That must be
every policeman in Springfield.
That's it. I give up.
A single mother
can't win in a man's world.
Ruth, that's a lot of hooey.
It's not over
until it's over.
I'm sorry.
I should've asked first.
No, Marge. You did it.
We really are gonna make it now.
Oh, no!
They're headed right for
the Grand Chasm.
Oh, my God! They're gonna
drive right into it
just to teach us men a lesson.
And it's all my fault!
Marge. Marge!
-Homer?
-Look, Marge.
I'm sorry I haven't been
a better husband.
I'm sorry about the time
I tried to make gravy
in the bathtub.
I'm sorry I used
your wedding dress
to wax the car.
And I'm sorry--
Oh, well, let's just say
I'm sorry for the whole
marriage up to this point.
You're right.
I am lucky to have him.
But, please, Marge,
don't drive into that chasm!
BOTH: Chasm?
(tires screech)
(Homer and Wiggum screaming)
(thud)
Ha! And to think
those idiot environmentalists
were protesting this landfill.
Solid waste.
I could kiss you.
(loud kiss)
Yech.
(kiss)
Ew!
Ugh!
(kiss) Ooh, I think
this was pizza.
MAN: Ruth Powers was tried in
Springfield Superior Court.
The judge dismissed
her ex-husband's auto theft charges
and forced him to pay
all back child support.
Mr. Powers blamed
the outcome on his lawyer,
one Lionel Hutz.
Lionel Hutz,
A.K.A. Miguel Sanchez,
A.K.A. Dr. Nguyen Van Thoc,
was paid eight dollars for
his 32 hours of babysitting.
He was glad to get it.
Marge Simpson
was charged with
a violation of penal code
section 618a,
wanton destruction
of precious antique cans.
She was ordered to pay
50 cents to replace the cans
and $2,000
in punitive damages
and mental anguish.
Homer Simpson was
remanded to the custody of
the United States Army
Neurochemical Research Center
at Fort Meade, Maryland,
for extensive testing.
Whoo-hoo!
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.