Welcome back, sir.
Oh, Artemis,
you wouldn't believe
what my customers
unloaded on me tonight.
Crappy marriages, crappy jobs,
crappy sports teams.
My ears are killin' me.
That's why the Confidential
is here,
to share your burden.
Just give me the usual, huh?
As if we served anything else.
To the Confidential,
the one bar where they listen
to the listeners.
Come on. We got to get a seat
in the front row.
If anything flies off the stage,
I want to be in the Stain Zone.
I'm sorry, Krusty,
but there's no way
we can seat this audience until
we round up all the escaped,
you‐know‐whats.
Tough luck, kids.
The show's canceled.
I'm going down to the deli
to drown my sorrows in tongue.
What about this upside‐down
exclamation mark show?
Upside down is funny.
Desde Downtown Springfield,
es ¡Noches con Abejorrito!
¡Y ahora El Hombre Abejorro!
¡No se duerman,
o les voy a picar!
Milhouse, you know Spanish.
What did he say?
Oh, it's a cultural thing.
You wouldn't get it. Estúpido.
Y luego, había un escorpión
en mis pantalones.
Pantalones.
¡Una visita de mi primito!
Eso significa
que es tiempo de jugar...
¡No... Te... 'splotes!
Presentado por la Monja Humilde,
la horchata más divina.
Hermanas,
traigame unos concursantes.
¡Ay, caramba!
It's a game. They fill
your mouth with horchata,
and if you don't laugh,
you win a prize!
¡O, Bebito Abuelito!
¿Cuáles son las vacas
más perezosas?
¡Las vacaciones!
¡Nuestro ganador!
Pick your prize!
Grandpa Baby, this is the
easiest choice I've ever made.
Look what I won
on Spanish Krusty!
Oh, my God.
That is not
just any crystal skull.
It's Calavera Gritando!
That tequila's so authentic
that it inspired George Clooney
to make his own
semi‐authentic tequila.
Wait, my skull is full of booze?
That's why it has a screw cap.
Bart, you've got
to give it to me.
I've always wanted to drink
something fancy enough
to come in a bottle
that doesn't look like a bottle.
Nah. I think I'm gonna save it.
For high school.
Come on. Gimme that!
Bart won that skull
full of tequila.
He can do
whatever he wants with it,
except drink the tequila.
Sorry, Homer. Game, set, skull.
Coming up now,
we got a special dedication
to Homer S. from his son Bart.
I like how there are no lyrics
to upset me.
Tequila
Isn't that your dad?
No.
I may not speak Spanish,
but I know when an imaginary
talking skull is mocking me.
Gentlemen,
I give you Calavera Gritando!
Whoa, a crystal skull.
Like from my least favorite
Indiana Jones movie
and most favorite
Shia LaBeouf movie.
Okay, this booze is so classy,
I'm finally breaking out
my commemorative Iran
hostage crisis shot glasses.
Look at these guys.
Now, those were hostages.
Hey, Moe, why don't you pour
yourself one for a change?
Me? Nah, nah, that's okay.
The pouring
is enough of a thrill.
Come on. You're
always on that side of the bar.
At least come over here
and take a load off.
Well, maybe it
wouldn't hurt none.
So this is sittin'.
You know, Moe, all these years,
we've never seen you drink.
Well, you know, a bartender
ain't supposed to drink
with his regulars.
It's frowned upon.
By whom?
Not some secret society
that I go to every night
after closing time,
if that's what you're thinking.
Look, I'm just the schlub
that pours the booze.
That's all.
Moe, you're not just
our bartender.
You're our friend.
Friend? You mean that?
Well, maybe it's just
my relaxed butt cheeks talking,
but down the hatch!
I haven't had anything
this expensive in my mouth
since my dad's gun.
Yeah. Go, Moe.
- Go, Moe.
- Now you got it.
I think you're pretty cool too,
skull.
Oh, my head.
Oh, what a hangover.
Ah, that's actually
a little better.
Oh, no.
Oh, no! Last night's
all coming back to me.
Let's go show the world
how much fun it is
when drunk guys do stuff
in public!
Baba‐boo!
Excuse me, could you move?
My husband and I would like
to sit on this bench
and comment on how the elephant
seals are living the life.
It's the only joke
in our entire marriage.
Oh, that's not what I hear.
The real joke is that you two
haven't pushed
the ole twin beds together
since before the election.
Of Obama.
To the Senate!
How'd you know
about their sexless marriage?
Oh, Mrs. Lovejoy blabbed
about it to her bartender,
who then told me.
Hey, wait,
you bartenders tell each other
the stuff we say
in drunken confidence?
Oh, we sure do.
Look what else I know.
You file your taxes
as one person.
You sell all your pets
each time you go on vacation.
Hey, you're two‐timing us
by also being the mayor
of another town.
I swear,
Greenview means nothing to me.
Hey, I love hot goss
as much as the next guy,
but maybe
you shouldn't be spilling
- people's secrets.
- Secrets.
You mean like you not asking
anyone out on a date in years
because you're ashamed
of your wet spaghetti arms?
What woman
could feel held by these?
Or how you keep yammering about
your million‐dollar invention?
File the patent already,
you coward.
Or how 'bout Barney over here?
Always going on about
how much you love your mother,
but you haven't visited her
in years.
She still thinks
I work at Autozone.
I can't tell her they fired me
for huffing floormat cleaner!
Moe, you've officially gone
from fun drunk to mean drunk.
You judging me?
You're the one who said
you're so scared
of being a lousy father
and husband
that you hide out at the bar
instead of going home
and actually tryin'.
You're worse than a mean drunk.
You're an honest drunk!
No! You guys are the drunks.
I am just wasted.
Baba‐boo.
Okay, Moe.
You did what no bartender
ever should've done.
But maybe, just maybe,
they won't find out.
The Confidential.
They found out.
All right there, Kristof.
Time for me to answer
for my sins.
Lead the way.
Frickin' Kristof.
Yeah, so, I...
I got your rat.
Look, I know I screwed up,
but that...
Since time immemorial,
bartenders have been
the cornerstone of civilization,
an eternal guild of listeners.
And so a paradox...
for to whom could bartenders
confide their secrets?
Thus was born the Confidential,
a hidden society of those
who listen to the listeners.
But this institution
will crumble to dust
if we do not obey
its first and only law...
A bartender keeps his secrets!
Look, Artemis, I know
I shouldn't have got wasted
and blabbed the unblabbable.
It's just, for once, I wanted
to have a drink with my friends.
A bartender has no friends!
Mr. Szyslak, your tab is closed.
Surrender your key, sir.
Well, them's the rules, I guess.
It was nice being part
of a place
that was bigger than me
and also super weird.
What the...
The penalty for your offense is
far greater than mere expulsion.
Your friends,
your regulars are to be...
cut off.
Cut off?! No.
No, that's too horrible.
You can't do that to them!
You did this to them.
They have
until the clock strikes...
happy hour.
Tick, tock, Mr. Szyslak.
Tick, tock.
Guys, you're all in danger!
You...
Oh, sorry. I've never been
in your office before.
Any office, for that matter.
Yeesh. Now I get why
you all drink so much.
You've got a lot of nerve
coming here,
after what you said last night.
I know, I know,
but this is serious, okay?
Some very scary people are mad
for all that drunken blabbing
I did,
so you're being... cut off!
So what? You already lost us
as customers.
No, no, you don't get it.
Cut off.
There isn't much time,
but I'm gonna keep
being cagey about it.
Oh, wait a minute.
Where's Barney?
Barney doesn't work here.
Really?
Seems like he would.
Yeah, that would lead
to some good stories, all right.
Hurry, call him. Call him!
Fine.
Well, if it isn't
the meanest drunk in town.
Barn, it's happy hour.
You got to lock your doors
and windows right away!
During the best time of day
for ocean breezes?
- Look out for the dapper gentleman!
- No dice.
Damn vampire bats!
What the hell was that?
He's been injected
with Antibooze...
a drug that makes it
so he can never drink again.
Antibooze?
That stuff isn't real.
Oh, it's real, and
the side effects are horrible,
unthinkable!
It starts with
a skull‐splitting headache.
Then you got
your firehose sweating.
Rhinoceros pox.
And finally, hurricane vomiting.
He's been cut off.
And now they're coming for you.
If they catch ya, you can
never touch alcohol again.
No! No!
Wait. What about rum cakes
and other boozy desserts?
Never again.
No!
Run faster. Every bartender in
town is coming after youse guys.
All because I couldn't
keep my drunken trap shut!
Well, how many bartenders
could there be in Springfield?
How many people in this town are
miserable at work and at home?
Oh, my God.
You guys, get out of here!
I'll hold 'em off... with this.
He's like a ninja
with that crotch rag.
That disgusting towel is a blur!
This is no way to live.
Hunted.
Hunted like dinosaurs.
What are we supposed to do now?
If you ever want to drink again,
all you can do is get
on the next bus out of town
and never stop running.
Sounds like a plan.
Those poor bastards.
I must keen for them.
Forget it, Homer.
They're non‐drinkers now.
Marge, pack what you need
and choose one kid.
We're leaving
Springfield forever.
That's ridiculous, Homie.
Look who dropped by for dinner.
Hello, Homer.
Dad, Dr. Hibbert was just
telling us
how he worked his way
through medical school.
I think you'd be interested
to hear how I did it.
- I would?
- Bartending.
Who wants mushroom caps?
I'm so sorry, Homer.
And Midge, your husband
can never drink again,
and it's all because of me.
Good morning, family.
You sure I can't make you
some oatmeal with blueberries?
Not today, honey.
I promised to pick up coffee
for everyone on my team
to celebrate our record numbers.
You are so much more of a
go‐getter since your promotion.
I love this new, sober you.
And I love any version of you.
Get a room!
Bart, I haven't forgotten about
your skateboard competition.
And don't worry, Lisa.
It'll be over in plenty of time
for me to be front
and center at your recital.
Well, off to the salt mines.
Well, this is a coincidence.
I haven't seen you guys
since, you know.
Geez, it would've had
to have been the syringings?
Yeah, finally got in shape.
Not drinking all day every day
really freed up a lot of time
for me to work out.
And as soon as I filed my
patent, my start‐up got funded.
Soon, everyone in America
will have their own personal
body‐hair‐shaving mini robot.
That's you?
I love my Groomba!
And I got my job back
at Autozone,
so I could finally face my ma.
He holds the big arrow
that says Autozone.
Yeah, I guess
we're all doing pretty well.
You know who I heard ain't?
A certain bartender.
You won't believe
how low he's sunk.
It would be nice
to laugh at someone
living their lowest moment.
I asked for the ham
in my omelet to be diced.
This ham is clearly cubed.
Yes, ma'am.
Right away, ma'am.
You flipped my omelet too high
in the air,
and it got cold on the descent.
My mistake, sir.
I'm sorry, sir.
I wanted to see him low,
but not eggs‐on‐demand low.
I bet he doesn't even have
a shotgun under that bar.
Get out of here.
You can't see me like this.
Slingin' eggs in a well‐lit,
non‐dank environment.
I can't believe I'm saying this.
We're all saying it.
Even though
we can never drink again,
we still want you
as our bartender.
You... You mean it?
- Yeah.
- We do.
From now on, you can spray
your own pans, America!
There you go, fellas.
Bottoms up.
To Moe, our friend.
Nah, nah, guys.
I'm something better.
Your bartender.
Who knew
you could drink water in a bar?
It's still watered down.
Good one, Moe.
Well, I have never seen
such a perfect distillation
of the human spirit.
A cocktail of humility
and self‐sacrifice
with a dash of un‐bitters.
Whoa, Artemis.
What are you doing here?
Such loyalty to a bartender
deserves a reward.
The antidote to Antibooze.
Now, think carefully, chaps.
Once injected, you will lose
all the benefits of sobriety.
Go away, Ma.
I'm sorry. I can't go back.
Sobriety has made me the man
I never thought I'd be.
Now I'm going home to my family.
Hey, Bart, isn't that
your stupid crystal skull?
Wasn't stupid.
It was my best friend.