No, sweetie.
That's a deadly glass ball
that we hang
where babies can get it.
See? Deadly glass ball?
Todd Flanders?
How'd that get on our tree?
Christmas is no time
to think about your neighbors.
It's a very interesting story.
A Christmas story
of failing and redemption.
Isn't that
every Christmas story?
A Christmas story of your
father's failing and redemption.
Isn't that every Homer story?
This one also has a secret room,
and it's set
six years in the past.
Oh, thank God
it's not the horrible present.
What year did it happen?
Oh, you know the year.
The Oscar went to an overrated
movie that nobody remembers,
Tom Brady won the Super Bowl
and a public figure
had to apologize
for saying something stupid.
- Oh, that one.
- That year.
Oh, yeah.
Remember it well.
Okay. So, Homer and I
were going
to the office Christmas party.
I had just lost
my last adult tooth,
- which they say is worth thousands.
- Grampa.
- This is my story.
- Fine.
We were getting ready...
Listen, before we go,
I want to ask you a favor.
Don't drink at the office party.
But then
it just becomes a meeting.
I'm serious. I don't want you
embarrassing yourself at work.
All right. I'll just drink soda.
- Water is healthier.
- Not in this town.
Kids, get the hot dogs!
Homer, that's not safe.
Marge, it's natural gas.
Marge. Marge,
Marge, Marge, Marge.
- When will you ever settle down?
- What the...?
Hey, Marge,
want to rub shoulders?
Cover yourself up
and quit hitting on my wife.
Oh, so now she's your wife.
I've never been at a party
where I'm sober
and everyone else is drunk.
This is a nightmare.
I know how you feel, pal.
I haven't had a drink
in four years.
You're so boring.
He's right. I am boring.
We should give Homer
a little help
enjoying the party.
So, if you're all partying,
who's running the plant?
We got a dog that barks
when a light goes red.
Ah, it's nice to get close
to the workers once a year.
- Are you enjoying your holiday?
- I was just watching
this fantastic movie,
It's a Wonderful Life.
A tribute to
my favorite character,
the conniving, evil banker
who ruins Christmas Eve.
I presume it ends
with Jimmy Stewart's suicide.
Attention! Attention!
I've arranged for some of
the latest hip music to be sung.
Hark, the herald angels sing
Good old Monty is our king
He's a mean old crocodile
Worse than jock itch
by a mile
I can't wait
till Burnsy dies
Watching vultures
eat his eyes
Not so fast.
Release the hounds!
On, Slasher! On, Gasher!
On, Mangey and Nips 'Em!
On, Stalker! On, Vicious!
On, Rabid and Rips 'Em!
Good night, Mr. Burns.
Die! Die! Die!
And cool me whiskey.
Good King Wenceslas
looked out
Homer, we've got to go.
Come on, can't I finish
filling my pants with shrimp?
I don't know what happened.
What happened
is what happens every time.
You got drunk,
and you made a fool of yourself.
I don't want you coming home
until I know you've changed.
Good night.
Aren't you gonna get out?
No, just drive me around
in circles, please.
Oh, sorry. You have to order
an Uber Sad for that.
There, there. Prices
are always surging at Christmas.
Where do I go? Where do I go?
Hey.
You got to bowl or go home.
Skate or go home.
Go home or go home.
Isn't a church
supposed to offer sanctuary?
I'll tell you what.
Quote one Bible verse,
and I'll let you in.
There once was a man
from Judaea
who said to my wife,
if I pay ya...
And no.
Please.
I have nowhere to go.
Well, there is one person
that takes the homeless,
lost dogs,
even grocery bags
carried off by the wind.
I don't know
how to put this.
Come on in, my brother.
You too.
Look, Maude. God blessed us
with another mouth to feed.
More like a sinkhole
that likes french fries.
Oh, now, Maude, Jesus said,
love your neighbor
even though he never seemed
to live next to anyone.
Please, Ned. I'm due any day.
Maude, when I look
in that man's face, I see Jesus.
When you look at everything,
you see Jesus.
I bet you're seeing Jesus
right now.
I love you so much.
Put him in your man cave.
Man cave?
My Son of Man cave.
The Wi‐Fi password is
sinners burn in hell.
The second S is a dollar sign.
The first L is a one.
The E in sinners is a three,
but the E in hell
is an E for eternity.
I'll just use
my data plan like an animal.
You ate the Christmas ham.
And it wasn't even cooked.
Wait, wait.
You were saving that?
It was still in the plastic.
That was plastic?
I know it's tough, Marge,
but you're doing
the right thing.
Just like I raised him.
Punish, punish, punish.
And after it's much too late,
love.
It's not just this one thing.
It's a pattern
of constant disappointment.
You must see it.
You live with us temporarily.
What do you mean, temporarily?
Nothing. Nothing, nothing.
Have a good night.
Oh, I can't take this place.
Even my peripheral vision
is betraying me.
So, wife threw you out, eh?
- Yeah.
- We've got a nice, warm bed for you
in the lake of eternal flame!
A house by the lake?
I could get some writing done.
In the lake.
Oh, thank God.
Any excuse not to write.
Kill me.
Hey, hey, kids.
Especially the little ones.
Here's an all‐new
Itchy & Scratchy.
Parental discretion advised.
But if they were around,
you wouldn't be watching.
Where's Daddy?
He won't be back
for a while.
It's okay. I love Bart.
I love Bart.
I love Bart. I love Bart.
And I love Lisa.
I love you,
I love you, I love you.
Oh, that's wonderful.
We can still have
a nice Christmas,
- even without your...
- Daddy's back.
Daddy's back.
Look at that hat.
He must be a millionaire.
Okay, it's time to go to bed.
We'll have fun tomorrow.
See? Even without Daddy,
it's Christmas at the mall.
Please give something.
I'm about to be the first person
ever dishonorably discharged
by the Salvation Army.
That was a real beard.
Can I get these
for me and Daddy?
I'm not sure Daddy will be back
by Christmas.
Ooh, I smell marital problems.
A salesman's dream.
Little boy,
if she doesn't buy it,
she doesn't love you.
Really? And do you have
a happy homelife?
Why, ye... No.
Aw, poor fella.
I know what'll cheer him up.
Homer, would you like
to say grace?
I'd rather just eat.
No grace?
Then I'm gonna let
my hair grow natural.
Homer, please.
Honor the Lord
until we're all bored.
Dear God, how you doing?
I know your son's
birthday's coming up.
Oh, with his mother, you say?
Oh, that's too bad.
Now, Homer, in this house,
grace is personal, pious,
and at least 500 words.
Fine.
Thank You, O Lord,
for my wonderful home,
which I'm not in.
And my beautiful family,
which I can't see.
I mean,
Flanders is great and all,
but even you must think
he's kind of a jackass.
What's a jackass?
It's a silly person, Roddy.
Daddy, you're a jackass.
Sheesh.
The mouth on that kid.
Ned, that man has got to go.
Maude, you know we can't
turn away someone in need
right before Christmas.
You're right.
I forgot my Christian values.
Could you please get our guest
some Christmas candy?
Absotively.
Get the hell out.
Where'd he go?
Can't be a rapture, I know that.
- Yep.
- Scram!
I have no luck.
Just keep bringing me drinks
until I pass out
under this table.
Also, you have tables?
Why aren't you home with Midge?
I've been kicked out.
I have no place to go.
Oh, you poor guy.
Let's take a walk.
Finally.
If only I could get back
in there tonight.
Well, actually,
there is a way.
What are you talking about?
There's a tiny little room
above your garage
that you've never noticed.
Until Marge forgives you,
you can hide out in there.
Have you ever stayed up there?
I haven't, but I did rent
it out to a nice Irish family.
Oh, Ma, this is the best place
we've ever lived.
We only have to clean
Moe's bar for seven years,
and then we get
our passports back.
God bless Bart.
God bless Mommy.
God bless Santa.
Santa bless God.
And especially God bless Daddy.
God, I don't know
if you could do this,
but I want a different father.
I'm home.
So cozy. Ooh, cheese!
Rat trap!
Ooh, more cheese.
Ooh, rat trap!
Cheese!
At least I haven't seen
any spiders.
Cool. Now that I'm a bachelor
again, my hair is coming back.
Hey, Lenny.
Yeah, I'm doing okay.
You're living the life
you always dreamed of,
not being able to stand.
I'm so lonely I made a Marge
from insulation.
Mommy?
Bart and I decided we'll give up
all our toys for Christmas
if Daddy can come back.
But I'll need double
on my birthday.
Take it or leave it.
What's happened to you?
I'm becoming a jerk
because I have no dad.
So you'll be better
if he comes back?
Maybe not, but you won't get
all the blame.
Well, I want him back too.
I want him back,
but I need your father
to do one great thing.
One thing to show
that all the nonsense
I put up with has a point.
Now, we're going to go
to midnight mass
without your father.
Aw, missing church.
This is the saddest
I've ever been happy.
One thing. One gesture.
I know!
I'll do the thing that Christmas
is really all about!
Make cookies.
Dad made cookies!
How many did you eat?
Most but not all.
Oh, that's wonderful!
No forgiveness, no cookies,
and I burned the good drapes
so we'll have to get
corncob curtains.
I need a miracle,
but those never happen
at Christmas.
Contraction!
Oh, if only that pregnant woman
would stop that racket
so I could think.
You could deliver the baby.
Wait, who are you?
I'm your brain.
How come I haven't heard
from you before?
Your stomach gets all the blood.
You shut up about that!
I know where you live.
Oh, the baby's coming.
Oh, where's your father?
He's delivering
Christmas turkeys to the poor.
That selfish jerk.
Did somebody order
an unlikely hero?
Maude, let's get you
to the hospital.
No.
It's too late.
Then I'll deliver this baby
myself.
How are you gonna do that?
The same way I learned
what the top ten bass solos
through history are...
Through YouTube.
Oh, there's always a commercial.
There will be a time,
mark my words,
where the monkey attempts
to eat your face.
If you've done
everything correctly,
your mother‐to‐be
is calm and peaceful.
Shut up.
You know nothing.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to get angry.
That's okay.
Of course it's okay!
Could you do me a favor?
Anything.
Pretend to be Ned.
Okay.
Oodily doodily.
No clownin',
that baby's crownin'.
You're almost out of labor,
neighbor.
No, no. The real Ned.
I'm a left‐handed weirdo
with a cop mustache.
No. No, no, no.
I mean the quiet,
wonderful man I married.
All right.
To help you deliver this baby,
I'll make
the ultimate sacrifice.
I'll act like a weenie.
Maude, I know I'll love heaven
because you've made one for me
on Earth.
Let's bring another angel
into this world.
Perfectly normal.
Eight fingers and eight toes.
How long have you been here?
Long enough to see
the man I married
is heroic and wise
and capable and brave.
- And...
- Give me my baby!
I guess it is mostly yours.
Here.
Homie, you did great.
Oh, Maude.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay, Neddy.
I was in good hands.
I redeemed myself at Christmas,
like the Grinch,
the Die Hard guy
and Scrooged.
In honor of today,
we're gonna name our son Homer.
Todd Homer Flanders.
Todd's middle name is Homer?
Yep. And for similar reasons,
Maggie's middle name is Lenny.
But that's a story
for the next Arbor Day.
Well, I want to see
your secret room.
Oh‐oh‐oh, not so fast, boy.
First you have to tell me
one of your secrets.
Okay. Not saying why,
but you might want to get
a new toothbrush.
You too, son.
You too.
And I found out something else
about the day you were born.
What?
You were born
with a full set of teeth.
And here they are!
Where are my dentures?!
I got a hot date tonight,
and I want to show off
by eatin' chicken.
What am I doin' up there?
You think the kids can hear?
No, no, everything up here
is totally soundproof.
Well, don't let me stop youse.
What?
What are you lookin' at?