(whimpering)
Heh.
♪ The Simpsons 25x13 ♪
The Man Who Grew Too Much
Original Air Date on March 9, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
NARRATOR: Neptune...
eighth planet from the sun.
A mystery now, we hope to have
close-up photos from Voyager 2
in 1989.
We do have them!
They're my home screen!
Miss Hoover, once again,
the lesson plan I prepared
would have covered this
topic much better.
But I can see...
(rumbling)
(whimpers)
Miss Hoover?
It's Tuesday, Lisa.
Taco Tuesday.
(rumbling continues)
(shudders)
Huh?
(bell rings)
ALL:
Taco Tuesday! Taco Tuesday!
Taco Tuesday!
(quietly chanting):
Taco Tuesday, Taco Tuesday...
(rumbling)
Oh, no. I'm about to become
another moppin' statistic.
There's only room
for one of us, Ethel.
(music from Titanic playing)
(kids laughing)
(grunting, yelling)
(grunting)
(crunching)
Bart, that's
your sixth taco.
You know, Whitman says, "If anything
is sacred, the human body is sacred."
(mouth full):
Fascinating.
Congratulations, boys.
You made it through
another Taco Tuesday.
Back in the bucket
till next week.
Won't those
vegetables go bad?
Nope. They're genetically
modified to stay fresh.
Just don't ask how
old the Jell-O is.
Ew.
Overreactor.org warns that over half of
the vegetables sold in this country are
genetically modified organisms
whose effect on humans is...
unknown.
Whoa! Mom, you
made me overswipe!
Your parents' credit card
has been charged $20.
(laughs)
(gasps)
I have to get
to the church.
Helen Lovejoy is posting the
spring volunteer sign-up sheet.
In five minutes, every
good task will be taken.
(tires screech)
Dang it!
Jasper Beardley!
You'll never make it!
(low mumbling)
(Marge murmuring, smacking lips)
No!
(low mumbling)
(frustrated grunt)
♪
(revving engine)
Ooh... (groans)
(low mumbling)
(groans)
(mumbling)
Oh!
What the hell
is this thing?
(signal light clicking)
Bake sale... taken.
Candle snuffing... taken.
Baby shusher, miscellaneous
choir support.
Everything's taken!
All that's left is...
Teen abstinence
counseling.
You get to pass out
abstinence pledges
and make sure the kids sign
their John Han-bleeps.
(Marge grumbles)
But, Ned, saying
nay is your thing.
Not this month.
(chuckles)
Edna signed us up
for a tango class.
It was the only way I could
avert... (sighs) wine-tasting.
Look, I'm really not comfortable
talking about S-E-X with K-I-D-S.
Language.
Oh, it's not that hard.
Just tell them
that God wants them to ignore everything
in their bodies that God is making happen.
We took the pledge!
We won't have sex
until we're married!
To each other!
(both humming a tune)
Mm, their skipping lessons
are really paying off.
MARGE:
Hello. Hello.
(nervous laugh)
I'm-I'm Marge Simpson, and
I'm here to talk about a...
a-a wonderful,
beautiful thing.
Speaking of beautiful things,
tongue me, babe.
(both grunting)
(gasps)
How many of you are here
for the free cookies?
Because we've discontinued that.
(angry chatter)
- I'm out of here.
- Forget you!
One of our brightest and most meddlesome
students called this meeting... somehow...
to discuss an urgent
menu matter. Lisa?
Our school cafeteria
is serving GMOs...
genetically
modified organisms.
- (people gasping) - Now, in order
to thoroughly explore the issue,
I'd like to play the first video
that came up in my Web browser
when I typed in "GMO" plus
"danger" plus "question mark."
Hear, hear!
♪
MALE NARRATOR: If there's one thing
scientists love, it's money.
Money, money, money.
And that's been true of scientists
ever since caveman times.
We need look no further back
than the ancient Mayans,
who crossbred
plants and animals
in an unholy experiment
in what is now a resort
that charges $30 a
night to valet park.
Once you're there,
they've gotcha.
(all gasp)
The Mayans didn't listen...
to themselves.
Yet today, we toy with our fate
by using retroviruses
to create these so-called
"super foods."
Are we doomed to
repeat an event
- (snaps fingers)
- that destroyed all human life?
The answer is
in your mouth!
(narrator laughing maniacally)
Um, that video seemed a
little unscientific.
My name is Jenny McCarthy,
and I endorse this tirade.
Oh, my God, it's worse
than I thought.
Everybody wait here while I
do some actual research.
Nobody form any opinions
while I'm gone.
Well, hurry, we have
no minds of our own.
♪
I say we do not categorically ban
genetically modified organisms.
ALL (gasping):
What?!
Well, GMOs are resistant to
pests, disease and drought.
It's just possible that GMOs
can actually end world hunger.
I say, let's get these GMOs
inside our children pronto!
Way ahead of you!
(people whooping, shouting)
I'm eating
the food of the future.
(robotically):
Beep, boop. What is love?
Boop, beep, boop.
Lisa, I'd like to thank you for
mollifying these land apes.
We'd like you and your family to visit
us at the Monsarno research campus.
Ooh, campus! Do you have a statue of the
founder I can stick a funny hat on?
Go, go, go!
(giggling)
WOMAN: Simpsons, we're trying to change
the world one molecule at a time.
Sounds like that
would take a while.
Ooh, you're right.
Everyone, three
molecules at a time.
(others grumbling) Oh, you
got to be kidding me!
(exasperated sigh)
I'll be home late, honey.
Yeah. Three molecules now.
Well, it's nice
to see for once
a corporation that does good
work and cares about people.
Yes, Lisa, we finally put to bed the silly
notion that our company is in any way evil.
Now, say hello to our
chief scientist.
(door creaks)
(all scream)
SIMPSONS:
Sideshow Bob!
Dr. Sideshow Bob.
Real doctor or PhD?
PhD.
All right, I'll leave you and Bob in
this locked room to get reacquainted.
(bolt clacks)
Simpsons, there's
no need for alarm.
That's not for
you to suck!
Now... where was I?
Right. Uh, no need to worry.
I'm still technically shawshanking
it at Springfield Penitentiary.
This is getting boring. Either murder
us or tell us how you got here.
Very well.
The inanity of the vanity
license plate puns
was slowly driving me mad.
So when Monsarno Labs asked
for experimental subjects,
I... gladly volunteered.
My job was to make
sure the experiments
wouldn't be too painful
for the test monkeys.
(zapping)
(screaming)
(flame whooshes)
I don't know what
we're doing here.
Uh, we'll pick it
up after lunch.
(quiet chattering)
(zapping)
(Sideshow Bob screaming)
I wrote up my results and
went from subject...
to scientist.
BART (laughs):
Look at me!
I'm Sideshow Bob!
(shrieks)
Sideshow Bob!
Foolish boy! That's
phosphoric acid!
A mere sip would have dissolved a hole in
your stomach the size of a silver dollar.
Yakety, yakety, yak.
"The spotted hawk accuses me,
he complains of my gab."
"I too am not a bit tamed,
I too am untranslatable."
Walt Whitman.
Leaves of Grass.
Very good.
Lisa, you always were
the one rose petal floating atop
the cesspool that is the Simpsons.
- HOMER: Well!
- BART: That's mean.
(clack, creaking)
(giggles): Oh...
If you're done, our chief scientist
has to get back to work.
Our corn on the cob has
become self-aware.
Wait! Wait! Won't
you visit me again?
Let me show you I really am
trying to make a better world.
Lisa, we can talk
Walt Whitman.
And, Homer, I think
you'd enjoy the company
of the campus' lazy,
overfed squirrels.
"Overfed"? I don't
know this word.
♪
(crickets chirping)
(Marge chomping, grunting)
Visit me, Lisa. We can discuss
poetry, fine art, and...
and if we must, jazz.
Mom, can I visit
Sideshow Bob?
Why would you want to do that?
He's tried to kill us!
You. He tried
to kill you.
And I refuse to concede a mind that
thinks so much like mine can be all bad.
Don't you think the parts that
aren't evil are a little, mm...
pretentious?
Absolutely. We're talking
about Lisa, right?
- Shut up!
- You shut up!
This is the pinnacle of
conversation around here!
Fine, I'll take you.
They have this cool psych class
at the campus I sat in on.
(whispers): Uh, that was
a sexual harassment seminar.
It doesn't matter...
I'm taking it pass-fail.
Blowing off steam in the
crafts room, Marge?
No! I'm not giving up
on reaching those kids,
and I might just have
a secret weapon.
Mm-hmm. Is it
finger puppets?
Maybe!
Well, we haven't had finger
puppets in this church
since Reverend Brogan
was arrested.
But I suppose enough
time has passed.
And that's why Nancy No is the most
popular girl in Promiseville High.
Mm. I prefer the modern
thinking of Yolanda Yes.
And I think I'd have a
shot with Mabel Maybe.
(laughter)
I'm so tired of those
kids sniggering.
Uh-oh. It's Horndog Hank.
Well, Nancy knows how
to keep him away.
(material creaking)
Darn it, they're stuck.
(Marge groans)
(Marge sighs)
Um, can I take one of
those girl puppets home?
I won't do nothin' to it.
Oh!
♪ You say modified tomato
♪ I say modified tomahto
♪ I say engineered potato,
you say engineered potahto ♪
- ♪ Potato!
- ♪ Potahto!
- ♪ Tomato!
- ♪ Tomahto!
BOTH:
♪ Let's splice some DNA!
(laughs)
(chuckles)
That is my first
non-evil laugh in years.
Bob,
there's one thing I got to know.
Are you plotting revenge?
I don't plot
revenge anymore.
It's like love. If it
happens, it happens.
Now, how about
those s'mores?
(creak, whoosh)
Dad! You already ate
all the chocolate bars.
That's why I got to get the
marshmallows down fast.
(crickets chirping)
I like how they cut them down
from 140 characters
to a more manageable
20 characters.
Oh, another
seminar tomorrow.
I just wish I could connect
with those teenagers,
since it seems like
we'll never have any.
(chuckling):
Oh, Marge,
teens can't control
their urges.
It's why there's never
been a teenage president.
Are you saying I'm
wasting my time?
No. I'm saying you're
wasting everyone's time.
But it's a church thing,
so that's a given.
Oh. Well, then maybe I need to
give those kids a better example.
Good night!
Shut your eyes.
They're too bright.
HOMER: Sorry.
(birds singing)
Kids, today,
we have a very special guest...
my husband.
I brought Homer here
to show that we can,
and have, abstained
for two whole days.
Two days? That's all?
That means, three days ago, the two
of you made the blob with two backs!
Listen, you punks,
if you can't handle the image
of our naked bodies
in the tender
act of a-oo-ga,
you should never have come to
the basement of this holy place.
Ugh! He's
touching her!
They're practically
doin' it here!
Ugh!
(sexy purring)
(both moaning)
I'll sign the pledge!
Just get your fat heaving
buttocks out of my head!
Never!
(tires squeak)
All right, Bob, you've created 5,000
patents, so... one hour of freedom.
But remember, your every move will
be watched by these unarmed docents.
That block's gonna
need its own ticket.
I have a family
membership.
Well, if that's
your kid, kiss it.
(groans)
Mmm.
(makes loud kissing sound)
(wheels squeaking)
What next?
Proto-Cubists?
(with French accent):
The Pointillists?
Or the alleged art of
Itchy and Scratchy?
Ooh, ooh, I like the
Impressionists.
The boy bands of
the art world.
But for you, Lisa, I shall face
the Renoir with sangfroid.
Warmer. Calder.
Warmer. Warmer. Calder.
Calder. Calder!
That's using your
$300,000 M.F.A.
To the Calder mobile!
Ugh!
Bob, you saved me!
But how did you
get the strength?
Calder's work in this period
was marked by heavy use
of sheet metal painted
to look deceptively airy.
Well put.
Thank you. (laughs)
Answer the question.
Well... there is something
I should have told you.
You see, it occurred to me that if I can
genetically modify fruits and vegetables,
why can't I modify... me?!
You've been
changing your DNA?!
Well, at first, just a
peptide here and there.
Carrot for my presbyopia,
Brahma bull for strength,
and a touch of corn for
highlights on my hair.
So... how strong are you?
(wind whipping)
Figurines.
Get your porcelain
figurines.
Now, how about those
Impressionists?
I... but we sang
Gershwin together!
Well, rhapsody in boo-hoo.
Do you know why we came
to the museum today?
Well, I thought it was
because it was Tote Bag Day.
Well, that was part of it, but
the biggest part was that!
Washington's backbone,
Einstein's eyebrows.
Florence Nightingale's tenacity, though
I'll have to clip around her moral fiber.
(gasps)
You're going to take DNA from these
historical figures and add it to your own!
I shall be the wisest
and strongest maniac
ever to bring the blessings
of dictatorship to the world!
BART:
Jig's up, Bob!
Return the spear to
the Homo erectus.
(laughing):
Homo erectus?
Where has that word
been all my life?
Now, Bart, I promised
I wouldn't hurt you.
- You did that for me?
- More for Mom, but yes.
But beware, I have DNA in me from
Ophiocordyceps unilateralis,
better known as...
zombie ant fungus!
And we're scared of
that because...?
What I am saying is,
I could be tipped
into a murderous rage by
the slightest provocation.
Could you take a picture
of me with my family?
Mm-hmm.
Oh, would you take
another for safety?
Oh, I think my eyes
were shut in that one.
(groaning)
Now, can you take one
with my husband's camera?
They're all ugly because
you're in them!
- Oh.
- (children cry)
Taste Praxiteles of Athens!
(yelling)
(moos)
(panting)
(phone rings)
Uh, Chief, we got a report
of a disturbance at the Met.
We got bigger
problems, Lou.
Horny teens who should
be out having bad sex,
but instead somebody made them take an
abstinence pledge, by the looks of it.
I don't get it. There are taboos about
premarital sex in the Middle East,
and you don't see those
people getting all violent.
(panting)
You can't escape me!
I've got grasshopper thighs
and the sonar of a killer whale!
(making whale sounds)
(loud panting)
(gasping)
Uh, Bob, you can't kill us
without a little singing, right?
A little singing?
If there's one thing he did not have to
genetically enhance, it's his voice.
♪ Non piu andrai,
farfallone amoroso... ♪
(tires screeching)
How dare you torture my
children with Mozart!
Ah, you know Mozart?
I call all music Mozart!
We're here to stop you with the help
of the teenage abstinence class!
If you defeat this madman, I'll
release you from your pledge
and teach you other fun
ways not to get pregnant.
I think I might be
pregnant already.
Well, that's one of 'em.
(all grunting and yelling)
(groaning)
Python jaw... unhinge!
Aah!
I don't want to die in
some old dude's mouth!
(sobbing)
Bob, would you
look at yourself?!
(mumbles)
To quote Whitman,
"This is what you shall do:
"Love the earth
and sun and animals,
despise riches, stand up
for the stupid and crazy..."
(mumbles)
Who am I kidding?
My only exit...
is a final one.
- What?! No!
- Farewell, Simpsons.
And, Lisa, when
you're older,
write an autobiographical novel
trashing the rest of them.
How veiled?
Thinly!
(wind whipping, grunting)
(chicken clucking sound)
Now, don't worry.
Your friend will always be
part of our drinking water.
(water gurgling)
Oh, right, I gave
myself gills.
(water gurgling)
(groaning)
(tango music playing)
I told you, the only
dancing I like is square.
Hey, I let you pay for those
boys' skipping lessons.
Okay.
♪
Ooh! Ned! Ha!
Sure do miss that laugh.
Ha, ha! I miss her, too.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
Shh!