-CHOIR: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
-MILHOUSE: Whee!
Uh-oh!
(exclaiming)
(school bell ringing)
(Barney belches)
-(whistle blows)
-(yells)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
D'oh!
(tires screeching)
(grunts)
(fanfare plays)
(dramatic music playing)
Hey. How ya doin' there?
(both grunting)
(murmuring angrily)
(grunting furiously)
(humming)
(gasps)
(squawks)
Ah.
(irritated murmurs)
(gibbering)
(reluctantly agreeing noise)
Ook.
(grunting)
Ow.
I brought fried chicken!
-Biscuit!
-First dibs!
Homer, you have to do more.
Ook?!
I'm getting tired of your ooks.
I can't do this alone.
Where's your chore list?
Oh, I'm taking care of that!
It's laminated.
And to make sure I do it...
Hmm?
(groans)
I've never seen this.
It must've been left
by some previous owner.
Holy moly!
A valuable antique car!
This is the find of a lifetime!
Oh, it's a stick.
(grunting)
(engine starts)
Dad, shouldn't we see
who owns the car?
Now, sweetie,
according to the ancient law of trover,
abandoned property passes
to the subsequent landowner.
Man, ever since you watched
Medieval Tomb Robbers
on the History Channel,
everything with you
is trover, trover, trover.
Boy, either show me a writ of replevin
or pipe down.
♪ ♪
(tires screech)
♪ Chubby dude in a tiny car ♪
♪ Making friends both near and far ♪
♪ In this little town
he's a shooting star ♪
♪ That's a chubby dude ♪
♪ In a tiny car ♪
♪ From Shelbyville to Zanzibar ♪
♪ It doesn't matter where you are ♪
♪ There's not a thing that can com-par ♪
♪ To a chubby dude in a tiny car ♪
Aw, the needle's on "E."
Uh, I got something
that works as gasoline.
(bell dinging)
♪ ♪
(honks jauntily)
-Daddy's home!
Hello, children.
For you, daughter,
a little ragdoll.
For you, son, a Florida orange.
You know, there's something
truly amazing about you, Dad.
Everything's an adventure.
You go to clean the garage,
and you find a classic car.
Yes, fortune favors the bald.
Now for the best part:
sharing my great day with your mom.
(hums, spits)
Well, if it isn't my favorite gal
in my favorite room.
I'm glad you had a good day.
You don't sound glad.
I'm not glad.
But you said you were glad.
You need to read between the lines.
Why?
There's just white space there.
(sighs deeply)
(voice breaking)
I'm sorry, Homie.
Your life is full of fun surprises.
My life sucks.
(sobbing)
HOMER: Uh-oh. Tissues?
(sniffs)
Oh...
Well, would it help
if I rubbed your back?
Huh? Eh? Uh?
Your hands smell like steering wheel.
(sniffs)
Hmm.
Poor Marge.
What do I do?
Help me, universe!
(doorbell rings)
-Jay Leno?
-Hiya!
I was just passing
in my 1973 Citroen DS Pallas
when I saw that classic Morgan
with the original wood dash interior.
Man, I-I'd like to buy it.
You'll have to pay cash
with no questions asked.
How much you want?
I said no questions!
Don't worry,
this car is a piece of art,
going where it will be admired.
To my secret underground
car depository!
(groaning)
(sighs)
It's time for me to do
what I do best:
prolong this marriage.
You wanted a good surprise,
Marge?
You've got it.
We are going on the trip
of our lives.
Really? Where?
(doorbell rings)
I'll be right back.
Let your imagination run wild.
Hey, Homer.
-And you are...?
-Jay Leno.
Hey, do you still have that money
I gave you for the car?
Sure do.
Well, uh,
I'm gonna need it back.
But I just promised my wife...
Homer,
I've collected hundreds of antique cars
on the theory that they don't
make 'em like they used to.
Well, I just bought this new Toyota.
Turns out it's much better.
I can go to the store
and make it all the way back.
It doesn't break down once.
-Imagine that? Geez.
-Yeah.
Here's your money back.
Can I have my car?
Unfortunately, when I went to register it,
it wasn't your car.
So the-the police took it.
♪ Chubby cop in a tiny car ♪
♪ Going to the nearest cop bar... ♪
-Well, see ya.
-(car lock beeps)
Unbelievable! It opens from here.
(laughs)
The age we live in!
I've decided where I want to go.
Um, ooh, the trolley at the mall?
No, Paris!
The most romantic city in the world.
(groans)
Paris?
What am I gonna do?
(beeps)
A travel agent!
Oh, thank God you're not obsolete yet.
And a good morning to you, sir.
Here's the problem.
I've disappointed my wife
so many times,
I can't do it once more.
I see.
So I have to take her
and our three kids to Paris.
But here's the challenge:
I have no money.
Uh, let me see what I can do.
Anything coming up?
No, it's not plugged in.
The noise helps me think.
All right.
There is a way...
but it is a tad risky.
Would you consider
being a casual courier?
You mean not like the fancy guys
that ride the bicycles...
Let me explain.
The mob--
I mean, the courier company--
will pay airfare and hotel,
and all you have to do
is deliver a package.
But... you cannot look
inside the package.
Sure. For Marge, I will make
the supreme sacrifice
of not doing something.
(humming)
That's the "package."
What package?
The package you're delivering.
Ooh.
And the clients
have asked me once more
to remind you not to look inside.
Hey, buddy,
I didn't start doing this yesterday!
I started doing it right now.
Uh... the package?
Hmm.
Paris! I can't believe it!
Homer Simpson,
just when I think you have
nothing left to offer,
you whisk me to the birthplace
of existentialism.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
it's an 11-hour flight,
and I have to visit the "Louvre."
(chuckles)
(Marge humming)
(annoyed chatter)
MAN:
Can't see the movie now.
HOMER:
Everything's great.
Absolutely great.
Yet, there's something
in that briefcase,
and it could get us in trouble.
My mind's running wild.
And you're not supposed
to run on an airplane.
Oh, that's it,
I have to open the briefcase.
(shrieks)
(hiss)
Oh, what a cute, blue sna...
(muffled grunts)
(hyperventilating)
Okay.
(thinking) First thing, I gotta figure out
if it can breathe in there.
D'oh!
Hmm. Better try the other eye.
Okay, maybe the first eye again.
What the...?
I found it.
It's an Amazon Blue Constrictor.
Ooh, it's a very rare
and endangered species.
Oh, the trip of a lifetime.
(sighs)
(whispering)
I can't break her heart.
Well, you can't let anything bad
happen to that snake.
I promise.
And you have to promise
to preserve
another endangered species...
my marriage.
I promise.
Oh, for the first time,
a snake has ruined paradise.
I'll get the luggage.
Marge, you and the kids grab a cab.
A Parisian cab.
(French accent)
Taxi. Taxi.
(giggles)
Taxi.
Are you casual courier
Homer Simpson?
I am.
Here is your money.
Finally. I've been
here for two minutes.
Listen, what's gonna happen
to, uh, the package?
Oh, it will have a fine home.
A wonderful home.
As the belt around the waist
of a well-dressed woman.
I am not gonna let you
hurt that snake!
You have to say "Lisa, catch"
before you throw it.
-Come on.
-(grunts)
Where did they go?
Maybe we shouldn't have stopped
for that seven-course meal.
Oh, maybe we should just
have six, like peasants!
So, back home we call this
the tire fire.
♪ ♪
Man, look at those gargoyles.
That's from back when religions still knew
how to scare the crap out of you.
Homie, I have to ask.
Why are you carrying
that briefcase?
I just brought a little work.
You don't even bring
your work to work.
(grunts)
I'm sorry.
I just want this family
to have one trip that's great.
Not like Australia or Brazil,
Japan, London,
China,
that World's Fair Bart drove to,
that place with
the underground jockeys...
So, Dad, what are you
gonna do with the snake?
...Itchy and Scratchy Land,
outer space...
Lisa, I've come to understand
a snake's natural habitat
is not a briefcase.
So I'm going to set him free.
Oh, may I suggest
the gardens of the Louvre?
-They're filled with delicious rats.
-(man screams)
Whoo-hoo!
It's a shame Lisa and your father
had that errand
and couldn't join us.
But on the upside...
more pâté please!
Vraiment?
You want more pâté?
Yes, before my cruelty-free daughter
shows up.
Perhaps madam would like
to order from our
extra cruelty menu.
We have coq au vin made
from an old rooster
who was kicked to death
in front of his wife and children.
Very nice.
On second thought,
I'll just have a salad.
Ah, très bien.
Gilles, gouge the eyes out
of some new potatoes!
Ugh, I can't stand to look
at this anymore.
Bart, can you ditch this
in the alley for me?
(glass clattering)
(clamoring)
Hmm.
Starving models.
Well, Bart Simpson never met
a beautiful woman
he couldn't prank.
Dad, I love being on a caper
in France with you.
Well, this is gonna be a snap.
All we need is to get our tickets
from this automatic
French ticket dispenser.
(grunting)
(female voice speaking French)
Shut up. Shut up. Shut up!
FEMALE VOICE:
Votre billet.
Dad, you just bought
a ticket to Argenteuil.
Prochain client, s'il vous plaît.
Stop speaking French,
damn you!
MALE VOICE (speaking German):
Die Maschine nicht zu schlagen!
Yes, sir.
(upbeat runway music plays)
Here, skinny, skinny.
Here, skinny,
skinny.
(models grunting)
BART:
I've never been happier.
Okay, you're free.
Now, remember to respect
this ecosystem.
Come on, go.
You'll be a snake that lives in Paris.
It's a children's book that writes itself.
UGOLIN:
Not so fast!
(gasps)
How did you find us?
All tourists come to the Louvre.
Hey, it's got great paintings.
Oh, yeah? Name two.
Uh... uh...
Uh...
Don't patronize us!
You make belts from snakes.
We treat our high-fashion animals
in the most humane manner.
(gasps)
You're monsters.
True, but that is just
a part of who we are.
We are also poets.
Communists.
Experts on mustard.
They're gone!
If we want to be criminals,
we should keep
a better eye on people.
-It's really not that hard.
-Do not worry.
There is one surefire way
to find the Americans.
Marco!
HOMER (far off):
Polo!
I say, "Marco!"
HOMER (closer):
Polo!
LISA:
Dad, control yourself.
HOMER:
I got it.
Marco!
HOMER:
Polo! Oh, he tricked me.
(fading)
Marco! Marco! Marco! Marco!
Polo!
Now what are we gonna do
with the snake?
We'll just have
to keep him with us.
(gasps)
What is it, Lisa?
Do you see a Burger King?
We're at rue des Lombards,
home of the three most famous
jazz clubs in Paris.
What do you think, Dad?
Just pull the rope, please.
(playing jazz)
How old are you?
Eight.
Très bien.
(crowd gasps)
We need a doctor!
And someone who can
play saxophone!
Oh, which is which?!
I'll show you.
LISA:
I've never been happier.
♪ ♪
(sighs)
Plastered in Paris.
There is no better feeling.
(sighing)
(moaning)
Marge, there's something
I need to tell you.
That briefcase.
I knew it was trouble.
Yes, this is my Battle of Essling.
Unless Napoleon had a more
famous defeat I'm not aware of.
(gasps)
I've been smuggling this snake
this whole trip.
But it was the only way
I could pay for it,
and you wanted to go so badly.
And besides, those French crooks
couldn't catch anybody.
-There they are!
-No, no bridge!
We'll have to board
a Bateau Mouche.
A little champagne,
some dancing, and then...
(groans)
They're gone again!
This joie de vivre is killing us.
HOMER:
Man, I never thought I'd be so glad
to get back to our own
arrondissement.
(French accent)
Ooh-la-la-la-la.
You have despoiled
our supermodels,
let an American perform
with a French combo,
and stolen
these poor gentlemen's snake.
Well, I guess this is the point
that comes in every vacation
where I say... run! Run!
(sighs)
Okay, don't run.
Better cuff this one.
No snake!
What's on the desk?
Just a few dozen urgent messages
from someone called "Grampa."
This one says the cat
is eating his toast.
I have no time
for cats and toast.
Search the room.
(French accent) We have searched
their room from armoire to bidet, huh?
No snake.
Maybe we were wrong about you.
Let's see if the police
dogs can do anything.
(yipping)
I keep telling you
they are worthless.
But they're so damn cute.
(yipping)
All right, Simpsons,
I apologize.
As for you,
set the dogs on them.
(yipping)
Prepare to have
your ankles nipped!
(yipping)
I just want to say
that before we came,
our family was falling apart
like your European Union.
But just a few days
in your wonderful country,
and now we're better than ever.
All is forgiven, my friends.
Enjoy la douce France.
And now something we should have done
the moment we met you.
Come on,
you guys kiss like grandmas.
Get in there.
I don't know how we did it,
but we finally
lucked into a great vacation.
In Paris,
a lady makes her own luck.
♪ ♪
Now my favorite part of each trip.
The gifts I brought back
for my friends.
For Carl,
a French Coca-Cola.
Ah, très chic.
For Lenny, a miniature
Empire State Building.
-We had a layover in New York.
-Wow.
And for Moe, a belt made
out of a blue snake.
Artificial, I think.
Thank you.
Ook.
-(crowd murmuring)
-Shh!
Subtitled by B. Everdene