D'oh!
(tires screeching)
(grunts)
ANNOUNCER: Welcome
to Super Bowl XLVIII
between the Seattle Seahawks
and the Denver Broncos.
The field is a frozen tundra,
(Bart laughing)
- imported at great expense
from Alaska. - Hmm?
Hmm?!
Huh...?
(shrieks)
(gasps)
Oh!
(screams)
(screams, jabbers)
Whoo-hoo.
(whimpers)
(sobs)
(Homer continues
whimpering, sobbing)
(electricity buzzes,
Homer screams and whimpers)
(Homer screams,
electricity crackles)
ANNOUNCER: And the game
comes down to this one play...
- (Homer screaming)
- a final field goal.
The kick is up, it hits
the crossbar and...
(power humming off)
HOMER:
D'oh!
(Homer slurps beer,
then whoops)
♪ The Simpsons 25x11 ♪
Specs and the City
Original Air Date on January 26, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
(to tune of "Silver Bells"):
♪ Glowing rods, glowing rods
♪ It's making me
♪ Weak and dizzy...
Uh, rumor has it they're about to
give out the company Christmas gifts.
Who told you that?
I got an in.
The VP of Personnel is
doing my girlfriend.
Ooh, look at you,
Mr. Connected.
I hope it's better than
last year's lousy gift.
CARL:
Yeah, what a rip.
Ugh. Remember this gift?
The executive stress ball.
BURNS' VOICE: One more
squeeze and you're fired.
(gasps) Now I feel
more stressed than ever.
Gah! (gags)
BURNS' VOICE (muffled):
Excellent. Excellent. Excellent.
Uh, you don't look
so excellent to me.
(retches)
Ho, ho, humbug.
Santa Claus approaches
to judge and punish.
Wow! A good gift
for once.
Oogle Goggles.
Augmented reality glasses.
You wear them like eyeglasses,
but inside the lens,
you see information about the
people and places around you.
Ooh, finally I'm not a slave
to my stupid human eyeballs.
(gasping in wonder)
HOMER:
Ooh!
Whoa.
(high-pitched gibbering)
(smug chuckling)
- Glasses, call Lenny.
- Ooh, I'm getting a call.
Answer call. Hello?
Lenny, it's me, Homer.
Hm. I always thought
it was "Simp-sen."
Really? Don't you ever
look up at the sky?
(theme song playing)
Always wondered
what that was.
Sir, I'm concerned about
your sudden generosity.
The doctor said to bring you in right
away if you display kindness or warmth.
Oh, don't worry. This
Santa still has claws.
As of now, each of those nuclear
nitwits is wearing a video camera.
With a direct feed to me.
(gasps) You're
spying on them?
Smithers, how much did this company
lose to office supply theft last year?
$7,043.
Yes, well, no more of that.
Thanks to this $26 million
surveillance system.
Beware, rabbits. I spy
with my transplanted eyes.
Oh, and I forgot to show
you the best feature.
Each of these buttons
represents an employee.
When I press it,
he or she dies.
(scoffs) What's wrong
with this thing?
(grunts in frustration)
Now, remember kids, the school says
you must have a valentine card
for everyone in your class.
How does this mean anything when
everyone's forced to do it?
What did I say about pointing out
the meaninglessness of things?
Not to.
Well, no way I'm giving
a valentine to Nelson.
He's a bully, and I
do not love him.
Jesus says to love
your enemies.
That's because Jesus
knows one day,
he gets to look his enemies
in the eye and say
"It was me who
sent you to Hell."
Bart, your school requires
you to give everyone
a valentine card in an
envelope with a fun sticker.
Your teacher put out
an e-mail alert.
With a video attachment.
MAN:
Welcome to Firstline. Tonight,
"Valentine's Day:
Always A Massacre."
At this school, children
may give valentines
to whomever they choose.
Danny is unpopular,
due to rumors he sleeps in the
raw with his ma and his pa.
Human young are born with the
ability to count valentines,
and Danny realizes
he's been snubbed.
Past generations of children
were used to rejection.
But today's kids, raised in
a climate of video games
and instant messaging,
are fragile weirdos.
LYMAN:
On February 15, 2:00am,
after checking the
mailbox one last time,
Danny nearly died
from an overdose
of little candy hearts.
Many of history's monsters
never received a valentine.
Attila the Hun, Mao Tse-tung,
and me, Will Lyman.
This is Firstline.
Fine, Nelson gets
a valentine.
An old one from the box.
Perfect. Bad movie, bad
pun, even bad paper stock.
(Homer laughing)
(giggles)
What's so funny?
I'm watching videos of
idiots wearing these glasses
and not paying attention
to the world around them.
Look at these jerks.
(man screams)
Ow!
I don't understand what's
so great about these
state of the art,
solar-powered, computo-glasses.
I'll let you try them on, right after I
decide if these videos are Funny Or Die.
Funny, funny, die, die,
funny, funny but
the guy died.
Oh.
Now, a simple Sunday drive will reveal
the hidden wonders of our hometown.
Hmm...
(grunting with effort)
Whoo-hoo!
D'oh!
Springfield City Hall was built for the
Spencer Tracy movie Meet Me At City Hall.
It was just a flat wall with
nothing behind it for 30 years.
Dad, Bart's on my
side of the seat.
Dad, Lisa's my little sister.
(both grunting)
The rearview mirror was invented
in 1911, for just this reason.
Interesting. When was the
term "shut up" invented?
As early as 1859, shut up
was used to shut up...
Homie, I think the kids
are just hungry.
Glasses, direct me to the
nicest restaurant I can afford.
FEMALE ELECTRONIC VOICE:
Accessing soup kitchens.
What, you... Oh, that's
it, I'm taking you off.
Aah! Reality.
JEREMY:
Oh! Sorry, sir!
Okay, let's see
what we got here.
Ugh, oh! Ooh.
Eh.
- Oh.
- (Homer giggles)
HOMER:
Mm-hmm. Squeeze here.
Rotate there.
Pause for sweet talk.
Oh, glasses, you're
so wonderful.
Huh? A-Are you using your
glasses for snuggling?
But the avatar looks
just like you.
I'm afraid wives don't make passes
at husbands in those glasses.
Glasses, find me a great
gift for my wife.
(whispers):
Under five dollars.
MARGE:
I heard that!
Glasses, take me two
minutes back in time.
Oh... (grumbles)
- Marge.
- Mm.
- About the glasses.
- Mm!
- I'm really sorry, and...
- Mm, mm, mm.
Here's your breakfast.
Only five pancakes?
- You're trying to kill me.
- Well, I'm not happy with you.
Look, honey, I know these glasses
are a radical new technology
and should be worn
in moderation.
Isn't that right, glasses?
FEMALE ELECTRONIC VOICE:
Yes, just like I told you.
Anyway, I'm giving them up.
To whoever dares take them.
(Lisa and Bart gasp)
Yoink.
Aw, come on, Mom.
For once, I'm
grabbing the goody.
So the rumors are true.
Moms can want things.
Hmm.
Hmm...
Nicely done, Lewis.
A Transformer that
transforms into a heart?
I love it!
Mm. This Hershey's
Kiss is melted.
Not good.
My mom left it on
the dashboard!
My mom...!
I'll have yours now, Simpson.
In Ga'hoole, we would
break his frickin' knees.
No. No Valentine
for you, Nelson.
Excuse me?
I'll give a Valentine to a loser,
I'll give a Valentine to a dork,
I'll even give a
Valentine to a girl,
but I won't give a
Valentine to a bully!
Here's what's gonna happen.
You have one week to make me the
best Valentine any kid ever got.
And what if I don't?
Simpson, there's gonna be
a heart in my hand,
either paper or yours.
- Hey, everybody.
- That's strange.
I-I'm hearing a voice, but
I'm not seeing a user icon.
Carl, it's me.
I'm here.
Really here!
Hey, Homer. A lot of
information about you.
Let me just page through it.
Oh! Stop! Hey! What?
Oh, no one can live in a
non-augmented reality.
I need another
pair of glasses.
Charlie, your move
in Muppet Chess.
Gonzo to Fozzie Seven.
Aw! That's Kermit-mate.
Wocka wocka!
Oh, why is it the recipe
card you need is always
the one Homer writes
his cocktail ideas on?
Maybe these bleep-bloop
glasses can help.
Okay, Marge Simpson
entering the Matrix,
for a brownie recipe.
FEMALE ELECTRONIC VOICE:
Here are my top-rated recipes.
Ooh. So many choices, Maggie.
(beeping)
HOMER:
Um, Mr. Burns, sir?
Can I get another
pair of glasses?
Maybe two pair? One
for the beach house?
Can I also get a beach house?
Two beach houses.
Huh? Monitors?!
What the...?
Burns gave us those glasses
so he could spy on us!
This is a violation
of our human rights.
Okay, so let's see what we can see.
(cracks knuckles)
Solitaire, top hats on eBay,
Angry Birds fan fiction,
guy doing really easy crossword puzzle,
Lenny doing Carl's clown makeup...
someone's actually working?
Maggie?!
Who's Mommy's little girl?
Genealogy.org says you are!
You are!
(Maggie giggles)
(chuckles):
Aw...
Wait a minute. Since Marge
is wearing my glasses,
I can see everything
she sees!
Uh-uh, I shouldn't
watch this.
MARGE:
Such a good baby.
You deserve some ice cream.
Wait a minute... Marge said
we were out of ice cream.
(Marge humming happily)
Ooh!
(Marge chuckles)
(gasps)
Oh!
What else is Marge
hiding from me?
(doorbell rings)
MARGE: Maggie, he's here!
Oh, is she having an affair?
Thanks for asking
me to lunch.
Oh, why isn't she
having an affair?!
What about a Valentine that
says: "Bully, for you"?
Hmm, interesting.
"Interesting" means "no."
(snaps fingers)
- Milhouse, you're a genius!
- I am? What did I say?
(groans):
Oh, nothing.
On TV when a guy
says something lame,
another guy says he's a genius,
and then he has an idea.
I thought it might
work for me.
Well, you called me a genius.
That means a lot.
Oh, I hate this
stupid holiday!
The only thing you
can do is screw it up.
(gasps)
That's it! Bart,
you're a genius!
Well, if you keep throwing the
word around, it means nothing.
- Who are you?
- Mr. Burns!
Oh. I'm so sorry, Mr. Burns.
I won't bother you again.
HOMER: Marge, that's a
"Compact Only" space.
(Marge grunts)
(chuckles): Well... who
knew you were such a rebel?
Now let's learn more about
my wife's secret life.
Secrets which can
only be good.
Hi, Marge. Dr. Carlock
is ready for you.
MARGE:
Thank you.
So, Marge, how have you been?
MARGE (sighs):
Okay, I guess.
Marge is in therapy?!
MARGE:
Oh, I hate when I come here
and the first word out
of my mouth is "Homer."
But here we go, again.
(sighs)
Homer was converting our
dollars to "yu-ros."
Not the money, the sandwich.
And has there been any
improvement in Homer's drinking?
MARGE: Well, he's down
to two beers in the shower.
They're pale ales! Please!
Well, maybe if you just concentrate
on one problem, like his temper.
MARGE: Oh, everything in the
newspaper makes him mad.
Not Marmaduke!
Never Marmaduke!
Marmaduke was horrible today!
Also, Marge is in therapy,
and she didn't even tell me.
Whoa. She has crossed a line.
How did you find out?
Spied on her with
a hidden camera.
She thinks I'm selfish. She thinks I
don't spend enough time with the kids.
Well, that's crazy.
Come on.
You work your butt off in
a radioactive hellhole,
and what do you get? Not
one lousy superpower.
I guess the only choice
is to come clean with her
and tell her what I
know, and how I know.
Whoa, whoa! Bad idea. No, no.
Chicks do not like finding
out they're being spied on.
I speak from loooooong...
experience.
No, you got to make it seem like
you found out by accident there.
Um... ooh!
Next week you schedule an appointment
with the therapist after hers,
and then you bump into Midge
in the waiting room there.
Moe, that's great!
(chuckles):
How do you get your ideas?
Pretty much all my friends
are divorced guys.
Hello, Homie!
Dinner's almost ready.
Pork chops with my
secret seasoning.
Yeah, you do like your
secrets, don't you, Marge?
Don't lose your cool, Homer.
The building block of a
marriage is long silence.
Hey, where'd she go?
Good, good, you held
your tongue there.
Because... hey,
where'd you go?
Doesn't anybody want
me to give 'em advice?
Okay there, Fido, when you
see that squirrel outside,
at first you play it
cool, you understand?
(barks twice)
"I fear you"?
This is what Valentine's
Day means to you?!
This is what it means
to everyone.
How can you be forced
to say "I love you"?
People only give Valentines
because they're scared
of what would happen
if they didn't.
"Nelson, you frighten me so,
"The psycho-est bully I know,
"You're a sociopath
in need of a bath,
I'm sure you'll wind
up on death row."
(sniffing)
Mmm! You can really
smell the fear on this.
I rubbed it on Milhouse.
Simpson, you just touched
my heart's butt.
Why are you hugging yourself?
Why are you hugging
yourself?!
If Nelson doesn't do something
bully-ish in two seconds,
I'm gonna wedgie him.
Nelson doesn't
wear underwear.
Wow. Always
one step ahead.
Uh, I'm here to check
in for the 3:00.
Please fill out these
forms, Mr. Fakinami.
No, it's "Fake Name."
I'll just call you Elias.
That's "Alias."
Duh. Hm!
HOMER:
Finally.
Time for the big bump-into.
Same time next week, Marge?
Oh, absolutely.
These sessions keep
me on an even keel.
Dr. Carlock is like my
Wednesday reset button.
HOMER:
Wednesday?
(pleasant classical music
playing)
♪
Okay, she's always in a
good mood after therapy.
(sad, minor-key music playing)
♪
(Marge hums happily)
Oh, my God.
Marge needs this.
It lights her way through the
dark path of marriage to me.
Come on in, Mr. Fakinami.
No need. Everything's fine.
I'm sorry, but there are no
cancellations within 24 hours.
(chuckles): Well, as long as
I'm paying for the time...
Ow! Where'd you
learn to cut hair?
(nervous chuckle)
You know, you have
some anger issues.
More snip, less lip.
Oh, I forgot to
tell you, Homie,
I bumped into Helen Lovejoy
today, and guess what?
I don't need to know, Marge. You
deserve to have your secrets.
It's not a secret.
It's a funny story.
Okay, Marge, but
first, well...
I have something
I need to tell you.
Something I did you might be
mad about, and rightly so.
Oh, I bet my story's
more interesting.
Whoo-hoo! I tried!
- Okay.
- Okay,
so, Helen Lovejoy
told me that
she made her famous snickerdoodle
Bundt cake for the church sale,
and she put in salt
instead of sugar!
(laughs)
Yeah? And...?
That's it. That
was the story.
- Where's that cake now?
- It got sold.
- Who bought it?
- Dr. Hibbert.
- Excuse me. I have to make a call.
- Don't take too long.
Okay, Hibbert's in surgery,
but they're having him paged.
(both moaning passionately)
HOMER:
Wait, something's wrong.
(grunts)
That's better.
Oh, dear God.
Hi, Ralph. Um, I just
wanted to tell you,
there was a tooth in the
Valentine you gave me.
Plant it and you'll
grow a new Ralph.
I don't need a new Ralph.
I like the old one.
Happy Valentine's Day.
Well, better get ready
for St. Patrick's!
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
Shh!