(theme music playing)
CHORUS: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
(whistle blows)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
(jazzy solo)
(chimes)
(tires screeching)
(honking horn)
D'oh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
Welcome
to the Springfield YMCA.
Tonight you can sample
all of our classes for free.
and if you find one you like,
you can pay
the membership fee and enroll.
(laughter)
(laughs) I know. We'll never see
any of you again.
-(assenting)
-HOMER: You got that right.
(ball bouncing)
Alley-oop.
Three to one.
Ooh, this is a high-scoring affair.
Yeah? Well, it's your turn
to get the ball out of the peach basket.
(muttering) I'll get a ball out
of your peach basket one of these days.
Welcome to gymnastics.
I am Coach Lugash.
I came to this country in '83
by cartwheeling over Berlin Wall.
(giggles)
-No giggling! It weakens the haunches!
-(students gasp)
What a little angel.
How old are you?
-Eight.
-Eight? Too old! Go home, Grandma!
I am sorry, little girl.
Lugash must go next door
to anger management class.
Worthless anger
management class!
I hate it so much!
I spit on it!
Yo, boy, this class is tight.
You go from "sloppa"
to "proppa."
Cool.
-(gasps)
-Welcome to my etiquette class:
-The Proper Young Man.
-But the black man said--
Are you accusing my husband
of misleading you? Good gracious!
I should bust a cap
in your ass!
Mmm, I'll pick, uh, Carl.
Lenny and Carl.
I kinda like the sound of that.
My turn, huh? Let's see.
Pick me! Pick me!
I got hoop dreams, Coach!
I got 'em bad!
-OK. Homer!
-Yes!
Losers! Losers, losers, l--
-You said "Homer," right?
-Mm-hmm.
Losers!
I'll take Professor Frink.
Ah, you won't regret it,
my good man.
What with the passing,
and the dribbling...
and my shoes
made of the flubber!
And away I go!
It's frightening.
Ow, that was painful.
Oh, the flubber is burning my feet!
Now before we begin...
fitness buff Rainier Wolfcastle
would like to say a few words
about the Springfield YMCA.
(grunts) Oh, hello.
I have purchased
the Springfield YMCA.
I plan to tear it down and turn the land
into a nature preserve...
where I will hunt
the deadliest game of all... man!
Now let's play ball!
Ooh, and Lenny is taking off!
-(grunts)
-That's a foul.
I am taking the ball
and going home.
Hey! Hey, that's not your ball!
(rifle clicks)
The chase begins.
(gasps)
Whoo! You da man, Carl!
I believe you can fly!
Boy, I am so sick of everyone assuming
I'm good at basketball
because I'm African-American.
(grunts)
(chanting)
Go, Carl. Go, Carl.
It's my birthday.
Three-peat!
You got mail, baby!
-(shrieks)
-(groans)
Willie tickles the twine
for two! Oy! Oy!
OK, guys. I got a secret play I've been
saving for the Olympics...
or possibly the Final Four.
And it goes something
like this.
(quietly) All right, Skinner,
I want you to block out Carl.
Moe, you can take
Professor Frink.
Homer, you take
Groundskeeper Willie.
No way am I taking
Yes, you are.
Are you a team player or not?
Oh, my goodness,
an untied shoelace.
I'll just get down on one knee
and re-tie that.
(grunts)
Eat my dust, mortals!
(groans) I'm OK.
-(metal squeaks)
-(gasp)
(groans)
Homer, I'm afraid
you've torn out
your anterior
cruciate ligament.
-Did you say "anterior"?
-Yes.
(screaming)
Now how did this happen?
Maybe a little morphine
would refresh my memory.
(chuckles, moans with pleasure)
I don't know.
I'm still a little hazy.
Ga! Oh, yeah.
Now I remember it like
it was yesterday.
It happened today.
Hey, man,
you're harshing my buzz.
Anyway, it all started
when I was--
(straining)
You go, Homer.
-(grunt) Whoosh!
-(crowd cheers)
Ow! Jetson!
We've got to
get you into surgery.
Maybe a little morphine
would get me there quicker.
(sighs)
(moans)
So many times we've
seen our father go under the knife.
One more and I get
a free hysterectomy.
Now, Homer, you'll have a full recovery
from your spinal cord injury.
-What spinal cord injury?
-Oh, he fell off the gurney.
But it will take plenty of time and rehab
before you can go back to work.
Miss work? But my life would be nothing
without the nucleon plant.
Oh, you're also responsible
for this hefty hospital bill.
You shouldn't have
ordered all those
hospital haircuts
and porno films.
But Doctor Screwlittle
sounded like a delightful romp.
But you don't have to
worry about the bill.
We've never welshed on a--
Look, a bear!
Run!
-(snapping)
-Ow.
(growling)
Now, Homer, I want you
to stay off that leg for two weeks.
Two weeks?
What am I supposed to do?
Just sit on my ass and watch TV?
That ain't my style, man.
Now, Homer, there are people
right through that door
that have it much
worse than you.
(sniff) No, they don't.
Mmm, everyone's
having fun but me.
-(humming)
-Boingy, boingy, boingy, boingy, boingy.
Mrs. Simpson,
can Homer come out and play?
No, Homer won't be able to play
for a long time.
(groans)
Would you make me some Jell-O?
You shoo,
Barney Gumble.
(sighs) Well, I can still hang out
with you guys.
Sorry. I got a baseball game
in 15 minutes.
And I've got a rally
for Take Back the Afternoon.
(chuckles)
So, the tables have turned!
Now you're the shut-in,
-and I'm the hip young dude!
-(cracking noise)
(gasps)
There goes my wagging finger.
I'm so bored!
Aw, come on. There's lots of ways
to pass the time.
Hitch up your pants,
air whittle.
♪ Di dee di di dee di di ♪
Make friends
with a Chinese man.
Uh, Mr. Simpson, you weren't
supposed to leave the home.
-Thank you, Ping-Pong.
-My name is Craig.
Sure, it is.
This place is so boring.
I got to do something to keep
from going crazy.
I know. I'll breed the pets...
to each other. (evil laugh)
-(meows)
-(whines)
-(yelps)
-(meows)
Soon I will have
a miracle hybrid
with the loyalty of a cat
and the cleanliness of a dog!
("Let's Get It On" plays)
♪ Let's get it on ♪
-(barking)
-(yowling)
-(dog whines)
-No. That's not how you do it! (gasps)
-(yowls)
-Quitters!
-(dog yelping)
-Hey, Homer.
Oh, it feels so good to talk
to another human being!
Stupid Flanders.
Hey, Homer, I need
to ask you a favor.
My babysitter canceled, and I got tickets
to a Christian rock concert.
(laughs) It's gonna be
one wholesome evening.
So, you think Marge could take care of
Rowdy Roddy and Typhoon Todd?
Well, Marge isn't here. She had
to identify a body at the morgue.
That's not my Uncle Lou.
And this man's not dead.
That's what I've been
trying to tell you!
-That's just gas escaping.
-(cries)
Would you mind watching the kids?
I'm kinda in a pickle here.
Well, they would
keep me company.
And this pickle you're offering
only sweetens the deal.
(cheering on TV)
(grunts)
Mr. Simpson, can we have another
jelly and candy sandwich?
Sure. Knock yourselves out.
-And call me Homer.
-(boys gasp)
Daddy said it's rude to call
grown-ups by their first name.
-Daddy's not here, is he?
-(all laugh)
(cheering on TV)
Now, my good man,
what do you like to play?
-Pokémon!
-Pokémon? Pokémon?
With the pokey and the man...
and the... (blabbering)
...the guy comes
out of the (blabbering)
-(all laugh)
-That is the darnedest thing.
So did you boys
have a good time?
Yeah. Mr. Simpson
was really funny.
He told us how the world
keeps screwing him over.
(laughs) Yeah. Well,
how was the concert?
Well, sir, I've never heard a preacher use
the "M-F" word so many times.
Anyway, thanks again.
Hey, it was fun.
My kids are sick of all my stories.
But they just can't
get enough of me.
Can Mr. Simpson
watch us every day?
(laughs) Oh, Roddy,
he's not running a day care center.
Don't tell me
what I'm not doing.
So you are running
a day care center?
Oh, you'd like that,
wouldn't you?
Oh, I sure would. It would give the boys
a place to go after school.
Then I'll do it,
just to see the look on your face.
That's the one.
♪ This world is whistles
and missiles ♪
♪ Bones and trombones ♪
Why did you put
my name on the sign?
It's just a legal thing
to protect me.
Is your knee
really gross under there?
-See for yourself.
-Ew!
-Can I touch it?
-Sure. Go for the gusto.
(whimpers)
It's healing over my hand.
-It knows you're afraid.
-(doorbell rings)
-(chattering)
-Hello.
I would like to take
advantage of your baby prison.
-We're calling it day care.
-Yes, whatever. Just take them!
Aw, aren't they sweet?
-Any medical things I should know about?
-APU: Yes, probably!
Why, Homer, your surgical incision
is completely healed.
I owe it all to my rewarding work
with children.
And not picking at it.
Ah, yes, how is your
day care center doing?
Wonderful!
Being with those kids gives me a high
only morphine can top.
-You got any?
-(chuckles) Always with the morphine.
(chuckles) Mmm.
Peekaboo! Peekaboo!
Dad's been doing that
for two hours!
I've never seen the baby
get tired of it before the adult.
-(chuckles) Peek... a... boo!
-(whines)
Uncle Homer, will you sing
that crazy song we love?
(chuckles) OK.
♪ Is that all there is? ♪
♪ If that's all there is,
my friend ♪
♪ Then let's keep dancing... ♪
(laughs)
I can't remember the last time
Dad sang us a torch song.
Yeah!
Hey, Homer, I thought you were
only gonna do this day care thing
till your knee was better.
Yes. But then I discovered
the joys of raising children.
-What about us?
-Don't worry, honey.
You'll have children
of your own someday.
Then you'll know my joy.
Hey, Bart, your dad gave me
this temp tattoo.
It's so cool!
(making motorcycle noises)
You have the "bestest" dad.
He read me
a story about Chinese food.
You haven't seen the real Homer.
It's all burping and neglect.
I think we know your dad
a little bit better than you do, Bart.
Is that my jacket?
-He said it looked better on me!
-(groans)
♪ If you're happy
and you know it ♪
♪ Say a swear... ♪
-Boobs!
-Hiney!
Mitten!
(all laugh)
They're always laughing.
Laughing at nothing.
How come parents are always
nicer to other kids
than they are
to their own?
I guess Dad just
takes us for granted.
Well, don't worry.
This'll give his heartstrings
a much-needed plucking.
(laughs)
Huh?
Aw, what a beautiful frame.
Perfect for my day care permit.
Sweet.
Mm-hmm.
(both groan)
Hang on, everybody!
Three... two... one, blast off!
(screaming and laughing)
That was "tree-mendous!"
(chuckles) Where's Ralph?
I almost died!
Homer, this man
is from the Good Guy Awards.
We honor people who make
life better for the community.
Like you with your
day care center.
-I contributed by not objecting too much.
-Aw, that's my girl.
Anyway, this film crew will shoot some
behind-the-scenes footage
of your amazing work.
-Is there a snack table?
-It's already set up.
(giggles) (chomping)
Don't film this!
Uh, excuse me.
This is a hot set. No visitors.
-It's my room.
-Well, if you want, you can sit on this.
(grumbling)
Teamsters are sleeping
in my room.
MAN:
We're just resting our eyes.
'Cause the thing is,
there are no bad kids.
Ow! You stepped on my arm!
Sorry. Daddy thought
you were a pile of cable.
Tell me about
the Homer Cares Program.
My kids wear these hearts
to remind them they are always loved.
Aww. Did you make 'em yourself?
Yes. Through the magic of caring.
Night will come soon.
There's gotta be a way
to get back at Dad.
Well, I've been cutting
the felt kind of crooked.
No. We've gotta show the world
what Dad's really like.
Then everything
will be back to normal.
(sinister laughing)
Back to normal.
BOTH: (laughing)
♪ I'm a nice guy
I'm a hell of a guy ♪
♪ And tonight
we honor you ♪
-Stop the music! Stop it!
-(music stops)
One more line, and we have to pay
for the song!
-Now, is anyone here from Springfield?
-You know we are!
Oh, tough crowd.
(laughs)
So what's in the news?
Oh, right.
The bus disaster-- very sad.
Now our first award
is for biggest people pleaser.
You can walk all over
these doormats. (laughs)
-And the nominees are...
-(drumrolls)
Ned Flanders,
Principal Seymour Skinner...
and Mother Teresa Junior.
And the winner is...
Principal Skinner!
-(grunts)
-(growls)
(chuckles) Now I'm told
there's a glitch in our Internet webcast.
So all of you out there, type Control,
backslash, semicolon, Alt, dot, Escape,
and you'll be fine.
-(grunts) Ah, perfect.
-(beeps)
Hey, hey. Hey, hey.
We'd like to thank our sponsor,
Hansen's Hypno-Coins.
If you can find a sturdier
hypno-coin,
-you buy it.
-(applause)
Now, every year we find
one Good Samaritan so deserving
that not recognizing him
would make Santa Claus himself
vomit with rage.
(groans)
Who writes this stuff?
(chimp chitters)
(growls)
This year's winner of The Saint Who Walks
Among Us Award...
Please let me win this, Lord,
'cause if you don't--
KRUSTY:
...Homer Simpson!
-Yes!
-(cheering and applause)
All my love has come back
in trophy form.
Now let's take a look
at Homer's wonderful work.
MAN (narrating): It looks like
any other home in America.
But this is the house
that love built.
KIDS: (grunting)
-(engine hums)
-(tires screech)
(laughs)
MAN (narrating): His scabby red knee
became an infectious beacon of hope.
Aww.
MAN (narrating): I guess you could sum up
Homer in two words:
-BART: Big phony!
-(gasp)
This is the real Homer Simpson-
-A beer-drinking meanie!
-(sniffs)
(groans)
Huh?
-And he gambles like crazy.
-(laughs)
-I'll call.
-Three nines.
Oh! I almost had a straight!
Come to new papa.
-(gasping, murmuring)
-Hey, what's the deal?
We just spliced in some home movies.
What do you think?
Well, I'd rather reserve
judgment until l-- Oh, my God!
-I'll mace you good!
-(screams)
-(gasps)
-That is completely taken out of context!
-Why you little--
-(both screaming)
Our children aren't safe
with that monster!
Yeah, keep away from him, Milhouse!
You too, Ralphie.
You're out of that day care center.
Oh! My polite indignation
knows no bounds!
(grunts) No! No!
No one is taking
my kids from me!
(grunts)
Run, children, run!
MAN: Come back here
with my young'un!
The term "soccer mom"
is thrown around all too often these days.
But the nominees in our next category...
-(chattering)
-Where are we going?
Uh, for frosty chocolate
milk shakes! (insane laugh)
Frosty chocolate milk shakes!
(tires screeching)
An award ceremony erupted
in kidnapping tonight,
as alleged "Good Guy" Homer Simpson
absconded with several children
in a stolen paddy wagon.
Now let's go to Arnie Pie
in the Sky.
-(sirens wailing)
-ARNIE: I can see them right below me.
I'm gonna try to nail the driver
with one of my shoes.
Arnie, please leave this
to the police.
I'm sick of being a reporter.
I want to make the news!
Arnie, this is not the time!
You're not the time, Kent!
You're not the time!
Where are we going, Mr. Simpson?
I'll tell you where we're not going.
-Jail!
-Then you better turn.
-Uh-oh! Aaah!
-(tires screech)
(groaning)
ARNIE: He's jumping
out of the car, Kent!
He's trying to climb
over the fence!
Now he's realizing
he's too fat.
-He's digging a hole like a dog.
-(Homer sobbing)
Now he's given up on that
and he's running back and forth.
He's climbing into a pipe
and he seems to be stuck.
His legs are dangling
in a comical fashion.
Oh, it's the saddest thing
I've ever seen.
KENT: Arnie, Arnie,
how are the children?
ARNIE: I can't see through metal, Kent!
All right, Fatty.
Out of the pipe!
Why did you rat me out, kids?
Was it because I showered love on those
other children while ignoring you?
-Yep.
-Pretty much.
Well, I learned my lesson.
From now on, you two are the only kids
I'll care about.
Oh, and Maggie.
Now let's all enjoy
the snack table while we still have it.
The teamsters said
they'd pick it up by 5:00.
Yeah. That'll happen.
(all laugh)
HOMER: Teamsters.
(theme music playing)
-BILL COSBY: Pokémon? Pokémon?
-Shh.
With the pokey and the man...
and the... (blabbering)
where if a guy
comes out of... (blabbering)
Captioned by
Visual Data Media Services