♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
(whistle blowing)
(beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screeching)
Ah, the morning horoscope.
"Today will be a day like
every other day." D'oh!
It just gets
worse and worse.
♪♪ (whistling "Simpsons" theme)
Bart, I've asked you not
to whistle that annoying tune.
-Jawohl, mein mommandant.
-Why are you so happy?
Yeah. You kids gotta go to school.
I gotta go to work.
The only one who
has it easy is Marge.
(grunting)
We're having
a field trip today.
Ah, Lise, won't it be great
to cast off the shackles
of the soul-crushing hellhole that
is Springfield Elementary?
Oh! I'm sorry.
I forgot.
Your class isn't going.
You're right, Bart.
School is for losers.
"And that's how I cured
all disease, ended war,
"And reunited the entire cast
of TV's Facts of Life,
including longtime
holdout Tootie."
Ohh! Sounds like another
Pulitzer for me to polish.
Hush, field trip boy!
Impaled on my Nobel Peace Prize.
How ironic.
Yo! Lise! Lise!
-Come back, Lise! Come back!
-Why?
I'm so much happier here.
And now, Principal Skinner
will tell us
where we'll be going
on this year's field trip.
-Thank you, Edna, everyone.
-(clears throat)
Now, class, I wonder who among
you can tell me what this is?
Oh! Not the box factory
again, Seymour.
(all groaning)
This may well prove
fascinating.
I know.
I'll just do like Lisa
and escape into fantasy.
Class, instead of going
to the box factory today,
we'll be going
to the box factory.
Damn TV!
You've ruined my imagination,
just like you've ruined
my ability to--
to, um-- uh--
Oh, well.
♪♪ (cartoon plays)
♪ Fifty-six boxes of bottles
of beer on the wall ♪
♪ Fifty-six boxes
of bottles of beer ♪
♪ You take one down
and pass it around ♪
♪ Fifty-five boxes of bottles
of beer on the wall ♪
(gasps)
(laughter, chattering)
(all groaning)
(tires screeching)
Ho!
MAN: The story of how
two brothers and five other men
parlayed a small business loan into
a thriving paper goods concern
is a long
and interesting one.
And here it is.
It all began
with the filing
of form 637/A--
the application for
a small business or farm--
Many interesting and important things
have been put into boxes over the years.
Textiles, other boxes,
even children's candy.
Do any of these boxes
have candy in 'em?
-No.
-Will they ever?
No. We only make boxes
to ship nails.
Any other questions?
When will we be able to
see a finished box, sir?
Oh, we don't assemble them here.
That's done in Flint, Michigan.
Have any of your workers
ever had their hands cut off
-by the machinery?
-No.
And then the hand started crawling around
and tried to strangle everybody?
-No, that has never happened.
-Any popped eyeballs?
I'm not sure what kind
of factory you're thinking of.
We just make boxes here.
This room is the most
popular part of our tour.
It's just like the other rooms.
Yes, but with
one important difference.
Oh. We took that out.
Yes, it is just like the other rooms.
-What's that building over there?
-That's just a TV studio
where they film Krusty the Clown and
other non-box-related programs.
Since it has nothing to do with boxes,
I'll just shut these blinds.
-(all groaning)
-Oh, man.
Now, here's my office.
If you'll direct your eyes to the floor,
you'll see a yellow line.
Follow it. It will lead you around
my desk and back out the door.
SKINNER:
Mm-hmm.
Mmm. Mm-hmm.
I gotta get out of here.
Aha!
The perfect escape.
(grunts)
Hmm.
Oh!
Ah! Do you work here,
little boy?
-Yeah.
-Well, then, go right in, sir.
-Bart!
-(chattering, shouting)
I'll handle this.
Simpson, I'm giving you until
the count of three to come out.
One! Two! Three!
-I've done all I can do.
-We'd better call his parents.
-(phone ringing)
-Just a minute!
-Don't hang up!
-(dial tone)
(groaning)
No answer at home.
I'll call his father.
-(ringing)
-Just a minute! Don't hang up!
Y'ello? You'll have to speak up.
I'm wearing a towel.
(crowd chattering)
Somebody need a script?
-Action!
-Ay, ay, ay! No me gusta!
(sighs, British accent) I'm sorry. I'm
really not comfortable with this, Ethan.
-What's the matter, luv?
It's just-- It's-it's the same,
old, tired gags, isn't it?
I mean, let's give
the audience some credit.
-How about a giant mousetrap?
-I love it!
-Action!
-Ay, ay, ay! No me gusta!
Ay, es grande!
What do you mean,
you lost him?
He might have fallen into
one of these machines!
Oh, my God!
That's his lucky red hat!
He's a box!
My boy's a box!
Damn you! A box!
♪♪ (humming)
-I said I wanted a Danish!
-I'm sorry.
-All the Danishes are gone.
-They're not gone.
-You're gone!
-Uh-oh.
(muttering)
"Tragic news tonight.
120 dead
in a tidal wave
in Kuala la-la--"
"Pur--"
"Kuala Lum-pur--"
-France.
-Yoink!
Yoink?
-(gasps)
-Ah, heck.
Now, where am I gonna
get a Danish?
-Here's a Danish, Krusty.
-Gimme, gimme, gimme!
(munching)
Now, that's Danish.
Where'd you get it?
I stole it
from Kent Brockman.
Great! Uh,
he didn't touch it, did he?
No.
Good job, kid.
What's your name?
I'm Bart Simpson.
I saved you from jail.
Oh, I--
I reunited you with
your estranged father.
Uh, I don't, uh--
I saved your career, man!
Remember your comeback special?
Yeah, well, what have
you done for me lately?
-I got you that Danish.
-And I'll never forget it.
Hey, kid.
Wow! A big clown hankie.
It's a towel, you yutz!
I want you to wash it.
You're my new assistant.
Cool!
Yeah, I know I'm on.
But I don't care.
I don't read the news
until I get my Danish.
Go ahead.
Try to find a replacement. Aah!
A powerful tidal wave in Kuala Lumpur
has killed 120 people.
Ay, Chihuahua!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Marge, I have some horrible,
bone-chilling news!
-(gasps) What is it?
-Hi, Homer.
-Oh, nothing.
-Hey.
That's my lucky red hat
sittin' on top
of a double-corrugated,
eight-fold, 14-gauge box.
Oh, it sounds like you really learned
something on your field trip.
Think you'd be interested
in a career as a box maker?
Well, that'll always be
the dream.
But for now, I got a job
in the show business.
From now on, I'll be helping
Krusty the Clown after school.
Mmm, I don't know, Bart.
You're only 10.
I've got a weekend job helping the poor,
and I'm only eight.
(scoffs) That's not a job.
It's a waste of time.
What can poor people pay you?
Nothin'!
What satisfaction do you get
from helping them? None!
Who wants to help poor people anyway?
Nobody!
So, anyway, can I, Mom?
-Can I take the job?
-Well--
Why not? I remember my first
after-school job.
I was in a band.
Hello, everybody. I'm Archie Bell,
and I'm also the Drells.
We got a new song called "Tighten Up,"
and this is the music you tighten up with.
(groaning, muttering)
Hey, whatsa matter, you?
You crazy kid,
you chasing away my business.
-Buzz off, Giuseppe.
-Pepe, go for the face!
-(screeching)
-(screaming)
-♪♪ (continues)
-Help! Aah!
Yes, son. You can have
an electric guitar
just like your old man.
Dad, I'm asking if
I can get a job.
Gig, son. When you're a musician,
a job is called a gig.
Wow. Being in show business
is like a dream.
We're really lucky,
aren't we?
-I wish I was dead.
-Don't listen to him, kid.
This is a dream factory.
The birthplace
of magic and enchantment.
Now I need you
to go clean out my toilet.
Right in here, boy.
If it-- Ooh!
I don't know what
I was thinking last night.
This'll take you
a couple hours.
I'm tellin' ya.
I do work on the Krusty show.
-Look at the credits.
-Bye-bye, kids!
-(chuckling)
-(children cheering)
I'm Kent Brockman.
On the 11:00 news tonight,
a certain kind of soft drink
has been found to be lethal.
We won't tell you which one
until after sports
and the weather with
funny Sonny Storm.
There's my name, right there--
Bart Simpson.
Looks more like
"Brad Storch."
No, it says, "Betty."
-"Betty Symington."
-(grunts)
That's for taking credit
for other people's work.
Oh!
It's okay, son. Who cares
what a bunch of fourth-graders think?
You're doing what you want to do with
your life. Nothin' else matters.
Thanks, Dad.
That's great advice.
Yep. Well, that's what
got me where I am today.
-Oh.
-There, there.
-Would you sign my picture, Krusty?
-Sure, kid. Get in line.
(groaning)
-I love you, Krusty!
-Over there.
-Okay, kids, open your books to page 60--
-(cell phone ringing)
Yes, Krusty?
Bart, I need to get your fingerprints
on a candlestick.
Meet me in the conservatory
chop-chop.
Don't worry.
Everything's gonna be all right.
Oh!
I wish I was dead.
Aah! There's cheese
in this sandwich!
Surely you know
I'm lactose intolerant!
-Sorry.
-Sorry?
Do you know how sick this is
going to make me? (groans)
Oh, boy. Come stand next
to the bathroom door.
I want to yell at you some more.
(groans)
Why, you little
rapscallion--
-Oh, show business sucks. I'm outta here.
-(shouting continues)
The most hideous child
I have ever witnessed!
Bart! I need to use you
in a sketch.
-You want me to be on the show?
-It's just one line.
-Mel's supposed to say it, but he's dead.
-Dead?
Or sick.
I don't know. I forget.
Anyway, all you gotta do is say,
"I am waiting for a bus."
Then I hit you with pies for five minutes.
Got that?
-"I am waiting for a bus."
-Makes me laugh. Let's go.
-(buzzer sounds)
-(applause)
♪♪ (vaudeville)
I am waiting for a--
Whoa!
-Ooh!
-Aah!
-I didn't do it.
-(laughter, applause)
(cheering, hooting)
Oh, man. It's a miracle
we got through that one.
Remind me never to let you
on stage again, kid.
Some people got it,
some people don't.
And you, my young friend,
do not have--
Hold on. I wanna finish
this thought outside.
-It's that kid!
-(cheering)
It's the "I didn't do it" guy!
He's mine! I own him and all
the subsidiary rights!
♪♪
Why, this rickety ladder
in front of this door
is the perfect place
for this priceless Ming vase.
Eh? Eh?
I didn't do it.
(laughter, applause)
Thank you.
And now,
the I Didn't Do It Dancers!
♪♪ (dance)
Don't move, dude.
This is totally a gun.
-(alarm sounding)
-I didn't do it.
-(both laughing)
-And then the boy says the thing--
-(gasps)
-Honey!
(gasps)
Joe, how could you?
I, uh, didn't do it.
(all laughing)
Help! Help!
This is the third time
that this building has burned down
because someone
has been smokin' in bed.
TOGETHER:
I didn't do it.
(all laughing)
Help me!
This biography of Bart
came out awfully quickly.
-It's not even about him.
-Sure it is. Look at the cover.
But inside,
it's mostly about Ross Perot,
and the last two chapters are excerpts
from the Oliver North trial.
Ah, Oliver North.
He was just poured into that uniform.
(groaning)
♪♪ ("U Can't Touch This")
I didn't do it.
(grunts)
Hey, proper.
(excited chattering)
I have to pay
to see my own grandson!
That's the democrats for ya!
See the boy! Five dollars! Or call him
24 hours a day on Bartchat.
BARNEY (on phone):
Bartchat.
-Are you Bart?
-Sure, I am.
-I didn't do nothin'.
-Uh, isn't it, "I didn't do it"?
Yeah, whatever.
(belches)
Um, I never thought I'd say this,
but shouldn't we be learning something?
Say the line, Bart.
(groans softly)
I didn't do it.
ALL: Yay!
Come on, Lisa.
Say somethin' funny.
-Like what?
-Oh, somethin' stupid like Bart would say.
Bucka bucka, or woozle wozzle.
Somethin' like that.
Forget it, Dad.
If I ever become famous,
I want it to be for something worthwhile,
not because of some obnoxious fad.
-Obnoxious fad?
-Ah, don't worry, son.
You know, they said
the same thing about Urkel.
That little snot boy.
I'd like to smack that kid!
What the hell
are you reading books for?
I'm doing
the Conan O'Brien Show,
and I wanna have some intelligent stuff
to talk about.
Don't forget to say,
"I didn't do it."
Dad, there's more to me
than just a catchphrase.
-How do you figure, boy?
-Watch the Conan O'Brien Show. You'll see.
All right. But after Leno,
I'm all laughed out, you know.
♪♪ (theme)
You know, Conan,
I have a lot to say.
I'm not just a one-line wonder.
Did you know
that a section of rain forest the size
of Kansas is burned every single--
-Just do the line.
-I didn't do it.
(laughter, applause)
(chuckling)
Great material.
-We'll be right back.
-♪♪ (theme)
-Sit perfectly still. Only I may dance.
-(groaning)
"Just do the line."
(exhales)
What's gonna happen to me?
MALE ANNOUNCER: And now,
it's time for Match Game 2034,
with Billy Crystal.
-Hey!
-Farrah Fawcett-Majors- O'Neal-Varney.
-(grunts)
-The "I Didn't Do It" Boy.
-Ventriloquist Loni Anderson.
-Ooh!
-Spike Lee.
-(groans)
-And the always lovely
and vivacious head
of Kitty Carlisle.
Hi, everybody!
Let's start the game!
-(hisses)
-Aah!
-(yelling)
(knocking on door)
MARGE: Bart, it's time
to get ready for the show.
No!
-Where's that little punk?
-(orchestra tuning)
We go on in 10 minutes.
Oh, the tension.
Somebody! Walk on my back!
ALL:
Huh?
-(crowd clamoring)
-Ow! Oh-- Ow!
One at a time!
No Teamsters!
Honey, I know you feel
a little silly
saying the same four words over
and over, but you shouldn't.
You're making people happy,
and that's a very hard thing to do.
You're right, Mom.
I shouldn't let this bother me.
I'm in television now.
It's my job to be repetitive.
My job.
Repetitiveness is my job.
I am gonna go out there tonight and give
the best performance of my life.
The best performance
of your life?
of my life.
Where is that lousy
little pisher?
Bart! Mwah!
-♪♪ (theme)
-And now, boys and girls,
here he is, the boy that says the words
you've been longing to hear
like the salivating dogs
that you are, Bart Simpson!
♪♪ (fanfare)
I didn't do it.
-(weak chuckle)
-(clears throat)
-I didn't do it.
-(cricket chirping)
(muttering)
I don't know.
Woozle wozzle?
-What the--
-(all muttering)
That's what passes for entertainment
these days? Woozle wozzle?
ANNOUNCER:
Ladies and gentlemen, the clown show
has been put on hiatus
for retooling.
-What happened?
-Oh, don't worry about that.
You're just finished,
that's all.
-Finished?
-It happens all the time.
That's show business for you.
One day, you're the most
important guy who ever lived.
The next day,
you're some schmo
-working in a box factory.
-I heard that!
Boy, show business
is kind of cruel, isn't it?
(latch locking)
(groaning)
RADIO DEEJAY:
And that was "Kung Fu Fighting."
Say, speaking of one-trick ponies,
whatever happened to that
"I didn't do it" kid?
DEEJAY 2: Boy, did that
get old fast. Whoa!
You know, if you wanna last
in this business, you gotta stay fresh.
-(honking horn)
-(silly sound effects)
(grunts)
I saved these for you, Bart.
You'll always have them
to remind you of the time
when you were the whole world's
special little guy.
-Thanks, Mom.
-And now you can go back to just being you
instead of a one-dimensional character
with a silly catchphrase.
-D'oh!
-Ay, caramba!
-(groaning)
-(sucking)
-Hidilly-ho!
-(belches)
-Ha-ha!
-Excellent.
If anyone wants me,
I'll be in my room.
HOMER: What kind
of catchphrase is that?
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.