CHORUS SINGS:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
(grunts)
Hmm-mm...
Doot-doot, doot-doot.
(ringing)
(shrieks, gulps)
MARGE:
♪ You like potato ♪
HOMER:
♪ And you like po-tah-to ♪
-♪ You like tomato ♪
-♪ And you like to-mah-to ♪
-♪ Potato ♪
-♪ Po-tah-to ♪
-♪ Tomato ♪
-♪ To-mah-to ♪
♪ Let's call the whole
thing off...ically on ♪
♪ And toast Valerie
and Dave ♪
♪ Togasaki-Rothman! ♪
(cheering, applause)
You guys will be the hit
of Cousin Valerie's
wedding reception!
Can I just ask,
who the hell says po-tah-to?
Songwriters who are stuck.
Homie, I'm still
a little nervous
about performing in front
of all those people.
Don't worry, sweetie.
With me at your side,
our toast will do just
what it's supposed to:
steal focus from the bride.
(chortling, snickering)
Why is everyone staring
at static?
We don't have one of those
digital conversion gizmos.
(Yiddish accent):
I miss the History Channel,
damn it!
How else would I know
what I lived through?
Maybe I should go out
and get you guys a converter.
Aw, that's sweet!
Here's all the money we would've
given to televangelists.
Wow! How long has
the TV been out?
'Bout ten minutes.
Fore!
Oh, I feel like
I'm mashing the tufty
on the links at St. Andrew's!
Sir, your cheeks
are ruddy!
Did you eat a sugar cube
when I wasn't watching?
No, it's all thanks
to this self-powered
experience approximater!
I've never seen
Mr. Burns this happy.
(face crackling)
Just think what that game could
do for Grampa and his friends!
(soldiers screaming)
Wait, I'm shooting
at Nazis?
That's not
how I remember it.
HOMER:
See you at 5:00
on the dot.
Phone kisses!
(singsongy):
♪ Homer's got a girlfriend! ♪
She's not my girlfriend.
She's a girl who I married,
who used to be my friend.
Hey, what's
your fortune say?
"You will enjoy the
company of others."
Wow! That's exactly what
I'm enjoying right now!
-Spooky.
-Mine says,
"Something you lost
will soon turn up."
(gasps)
My faith in the Lord.
It came back!
"Today is your lucky day."
Yeah, pfft!
Hey, Homer, if I was you,
I wouldn't be so quick
to say "pfft."
Yeah, these cookies are
on the up-and-up now,
according to the only
honest newspaper:
the Beijing Daily Worker.
See?
If it's your lucky day,
you'd be a fool not to
take advantage of it.
Hey, any part of a cookie
you can't eat
is just a waste of time.
(screams)
-(happy shriek)
-What incredible
good luck!
Just as the cookie foretold.
Hmm! Maybe this is my lucky day.
A disc?!
Please be compact.
Please be compact!
Whoo-hoo!
Here we go.
♪ Ooh, what a lucky man ♪
-♪ He was ♪
-HOMER: ♪ I is! ♪
(mimicking synthesizer)
♪ Boo-weee-boo-weee-wee,
doo-doo-dee-dee-doo-doo ♪
doo-doo-dee-dee-doo-doo... ♪
Huh?!
Holy moly!
If it's your lucky day,
you'd be a fool not to
take advantage of it.
There's no time!
I need you
for the wedding toast!
My hair!
(screams)
Now let's get
that ticket.
Come on, line, move!
Maybe it'll speed
up if I make
"Oh, can you believe
this" noises.
Oh. Oh.
Oh, for goodness sakes!
Oh!
Oh! (grunts)
APU: Mm-hmm.
Thank you. Come again.
Who is next?
Oh. Hello.
Hmm...
Yo no creía en fortunas,
pero entonces me salió
una galleta...
Sí, sí.
...que decía que hoy
era mi día dichoso.
Primero no lo creí,
pero entonces me caí
contra la máquina de
dulces, ay, ay, ay!
-(Marge groans)
-And now,
Valerie and Dave will
deliver their own vows,
because my vows, apparently,
weren't good enough.
Show me how
it's done, Dave.
"Valerie,
even though you're
a Starbucks girl,
and I'm a Seattle's
Best guy,
I know we can focus on the
things we have in common--
like Mad Men,
season two!"
(all chuckle and coo)
I give it a year.
Homer! Where are you?
I'm almost there.
I can see the church steeple
in the distance.
Uh-oh! Here comes a train.
(mimicking chugging)
-(mimicking whistle)
-(mimicking clanging)
(train sounds continue)
(chugging, whistling,
clanging continue)
HOMER (imitating conductor):
Tickets, please.
Hey, where's your ticket?
(imitating man):
Leave me alone!
(imitating conductor):
Why you little...
(imitating man):
No, don't do it, sir!
He's strangling me!
I'm gonna choke!
Good evening, Mr. Homer,
how can I...?
No time to pretend
we're friends!
Lotto me!
"1-6-17-22-24-35."
I did it! I'm gonna make it!
♪ You like potato... ♪
♪ You like tomato... ♪
(all murmuring, groaning)
♪ Potato... ♪
♪ Tomato... ♪
♪ Let's call
the whole thing... ♪
(sobbing)
I'm a-comin', Marge!
Let him go, Lou.
Someone going that fast
has no time for a ticket.
(clears throat,
microphone feedback squeals)
Okay, who's ready
for a wedding-themed
knock-knock joke?
Whoa!
Start the joke!
Um, knock-knock?
-Who's there?
-I don't know.
Did I hear "lettuce"?
-Not from me, you didn't.
-(grunts)
Lettuce who?
I don't know!
(all booing)
Don't drag your kid into this!
Lettuce...
congratulate the new couple.
Why won't she stop?!
(sobbing)
There, there.
There, there, sweetie.
(tires squealing)
I'm gonna make it!
-(phone ringing)
-I'm gonna make it!
I didn't make it?
(screaming)
Here I am, about to start
my new life in Springfield!
(Homer screaming)
(chuckles)
What an idiot!
This is the perfect time
for my catchphrase:
"Soon you will be mi..."
(screaming)
(crash, Homer grunts)
(heart monitor beeping)
Homie?
Homie, can you hear me?
Oh, thank God,
you're okay!
(sighs)
I'm alive!
And surrounded by the
people I love the most in the--
Could you scooch over a bit?
Our top story:
Last night's big lotto winner
has still not come forward.
Once again, those numbers are:
1-6-17-22-24 and 35.
HOMER:
A million dollars!
Now I'm really glad
I didn't die!
The mysterious winner
purchased the ticket
at 7:07 last night.
7:07?
That's exactly the moment
I was furious at you
for missing our toast.
And now I'm the one
who has to ask:
Can you forgive me?
Oh, I'll try.
Wait!
If I tell Marge I won,
she'll know I was
buying the ticket
when I was supposed
to be onstage with her.
Oh, I'm rich and I can't
even tell my own wife!
(rapid beeping)
Calm down, Homer.
Calm down.
(steady beeping)
(flatline tone)
Wow, I do look pretty
calm down there.
(shrieks)
(mumbling)
(chuckling)
Ladies and gentlemen,
the Orchard Avenue Kwik-E-Mart,
birthplace of the yardstick
on the doorframe
that tells you how tall
your robber was,
is proud to announce
its latest lotto victor.
Mr. Barney Gumble!
Mm-hmm!
That's right!
I bought the winning ticket!
And now I can buy back
all the blood I sold!
Mm-hmm!
(chuckles)
Actually, after taxes,
the amount you will
receive is...
This money will go to partially
cover the cost of a study
to decide what to do
with the money.
(all cheering)
Barn, thanks for picking
up the money for me.
(chuckles)
Now, what should I buy first?
Hitler's baseball?
A mirror that gives me advice?
My advice is to buy
Hitler's baseball.
Wait a minute, Homer!
You can't spend
any of that money
or Marge will
know you lied.
Oh, yeah.
Marge, what are you doing?
(sighing):
The laundry.
The machine's on the fritz,
and we can't afford
the $400 to fix it.
(groans)
Here I am a millionaire,
and I can't even help the woman
who gave birth to me.
Why don't you just buy things
your family needs,
and leave them where
they'll find them?
Oh, Barney,
that's brilliant!
Just for that,
you can help yourself
to anything from this tree.
That's not the
money tree.
I know.
It's where I hide
my adult magazines.
Ooh...!
Oh, wow!
All right, it's all hooked up.
(all murmuring, grumbling)
This isn't normal TV.
It's a video game
that encourages
activity and exercise.
(all grunting)
Please, at least
try the tennis game.
Hmm...
My puppet-- with this
wand I control it how--
by jumping?
You use the wand
like a tennis racket
to hit an invisible ball.
(chuckles)
Look at me!
I'm big Bill Tilden!
I think I'm looking
at a poop later.
Hey!
(grunting, laughing)
Catch, boy!
Oops, the Frisbee went
into the bushes.
Why don't you go find it?
You threw it, you go find it.
Why, you little...
(grunts)
-(thud)
-Ow!
There's a big box in here!
A box? No way!
A new washing machine?
No way!
That's just what we need!
But how are going
to get it home?
You, go rent us a truck.
Ow!
(Mendelssohn's Fourth Symphony,
First Movement playing)
(playing sour notes)
(Fourth Symphony continues)
(music crescendos)
(Fourth Symphony,
First Movement ends)
And now, Marge's
secret benefactor
is going to get her the luxury
she's always dreamed of:
a toaster wide enough
for bagels.
I'll just take out a little
money from my "local branch."
(grunts)
Hmm... Not as much money
as there used to be.
-Homer?
What are you doing?
-Huh?
Why... I'm just...
(bone cracks, Home screams)
(wailing):
Ow...!
(crying):
Yow...!
Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh!
There's money
in this tree.
What the hell is going on?
Lenny... and Carl--
A fortune cookie...
and then I ran into
the candy machine,
and I-I found an Emerson,
Lake, and Palmer...
(mumbling):
And there was a...
♪ Ooh-wee, bah-doo, bah-doo,
bah-doo, bah-doo, bah-doo... ♪
♪ Bah-doo... ♪
(groans)
Okay, let me get this straight:
You got all this moola,
legitimately,
but you're too scared
to do anything fun
with it?
Son, if I was interested
in fun,
I would've run away the
day you were born.
Look, man, you've got to enjoy
yourself a little.
You work hard, or at least
you're out of the house a lot.
You're right.
I have been acting
like Telethon Jerry Lewis
when I should've been acting
like rest-of-the-year
Jerry Lewis.
Will you teach me how
to put myself first?
And how!
MOE:
Not so fast!
(gasps)
Don't forget my cut.
Uh... your cut of what?
I don't know.
I just go around saying that,
in the hope it'll be applicable.
I'll be on my way now.
(hums happily)
On my way...
("Viva La Vida" by Coldplay
playing)
-♪ Oh... ♪
-BART: Wait!
I have to go to the bathroom!
So, where are you from, Homer?
Here.
(slurps loudly)
Mm-hmm!
♪ Oh... ♪
Wait!
Yes, Homer?
Do you think you could
use someone like me
in your band?
Yeah, come on up.
You can play the tambourine.
I said someone like me,
I didn't say me.
♪ Oh, o-oh... ♪
PILOT:
Here we go, folks,
the ultimate zero gravity
experience!
(giggles)
Look at me!
I'm flying,
like Superman's dog!
Race you to the cockpit!
(both belching)
(grunts)
I'm gonna call you
Benson and Hedges
'cause you're
gettin' smoked!
Lisa, thanks
to your new whatsis,
we're as fit as fiddles.
Nurse!
Another round of waters
in your finest paper cups!
(grunts)
I'm gonna need a little
Ben Gay for this shoulder.
I'd like a fresh pair
of socks tomorrow.
A matching pair.
I want to put salt
on things!
Tell me what my name is!
Take away my
roommate!
He's dead!
PILOT:
Folks, it's time
for our final run.
No way!
I want to go a million
more times!
Sorry, boy.
You have school tomorrow.
Rich kids don't
need school!
When I grow up, you can
buy an apartment building
and make me the super.
With that attitude,
you'll never super
in one of my buildings!
Boy, I am through
spoiling you.
First thing tomorrow,
you're going back
to the rotten life
you've always enjoyed.
Oh, yeah?
If you don't keep
splashing the cash,
I'm gonna tell Mom that
it's thanks to you
she made the first bad
wedding toast ever.
(gasps)
Blackmail your father
in space, will you?!
(Homer yells angrily
then screams in fear)
D'oh!
(Bart laughing)
Oh... D'oh!
D'oh!
(manically laughing)
(all moaning)
Why is the TV
back on?
What happened
to the video game?
Oh, the video game.
You'd think it'd be
dishwasher safe,
but it wasn't.
LISA:
Why would you put it
in the dishwasher?
(gasps)
You ruined it on purpose.
You want the old folks
to be zombies,
because it makes
your jobs easier!
Ooh, excuse us.
We tried to make the worst
job in the world easier.
Well, I agree it's not the most
pleasant job in the world...
Don't forget the low pay and
the constant presence of death.
Well, you still should have
let them have their fun!
They should've had their fun
before they got here.
(groans)
Who's ready for panini?
Up-- that's
my chair, boy.
No problem.
I'll just sit here,
closer to Mom's ear.
Mom, how do you think we really
got that panini press?
I thought the government
sent it to us
as part of the
stimulus package.
At least that's what
the letter said.
Well, actually, Mom...
Uh! On second
thought, boy,
why don't you
take my chair?
So, Bart, how's your big school
presentation coming along?
Oh, great, now that
Dad's gonna star in it.
I agreed to no
such thing!
Mom...
-Where and what time?
-Homeroom, 8:00 a.m.
-Never!
-Mom...
(sighs)
What do I wear?
Behold, Neanderthal man,
our ugliest, stupidest ancestor.
(kids laugh)
Come on, missing link,
put on a show.
(growling)
(all laugh)
-Make a fire!
-(grunting)
-Be scared of the fire!
-(yelps)
-Evolve! Evolve!
-(grunting)
Get religious
about a bird you see!
(chittering)
Sprain your ankle and know
it's a death sentence!
(groaning)
(laughs)
(panting)
Very good, Bart.
Can I get extra credit for
a caveman break dance?
Of course.
(groans)
(singing gibberish
with a hip-hop rhythm)
Homer, I need you to rickshaw
me to soccer practice.
(groans)
Fine.
Let me just get
my harness pads.
No time.
(gasping)
Boy, this has gone too far!
I quit!
Soon as I finish
these oats.
Hey, hey, hey.
Let's not get crazy.
If you quit, I'm telling
Mom everything.
Not if I tell her first.
(moans)
Now how am I supposed to
get to soccer practice?
Hey, Milhouse, want a turn
pulling my rickshaw?
Okay, but just 'cause
I'm your best friend,
don't be afraid
to use that whip.
Okay, I'm taking off
the blindfold.
Surprised?
Well, I kind of got a clue
when I heard that
"ballooning safety" video.
Marge, soaring above the
forgiving beauty of nature,
I have something
to confess.
Um... I wasn't there
for that wedding toast
because I was buying
a lottery ticket.
You were what?!
You have a right to be angry.
Furious!
And even though that ticket
won a million dollars...
We've got a million dollars?!
Screw the toast!
Uh, yes, well, um...
taxes took out a lot,
I spent a ton on those
things for the family,
and, um, I didn't know
you could rent a balloon.
(sighs)
So we're right back
where we used to be.
Yes, but I have one more
thing to show you.
MARGE:
Oh... my... God!
Marge, those groves
of cherry blossoms
will bloom every year,
to remind the world
of the sweetest,
most forgiving woman
who ever lived.
Am I off the hook?
♪ You like potato ♪
♪ And you like po-tah-to ♪
♪ You like tomato ♪
♪ And you like to-mah-to ♪
BOTH:
♪ So if you go for oysters ♪
♪ And I go for ersters ♪
♪ I'll order oysters ♪
♪ And cancel the ersters ♪
♪ For we know we need
each other, so we ♪
♪ Better call
the calling off off ♪
♪ Let's call
the whole thing off! ♪
-DRIVER: Soon you will be m--
-Shh!
Enhanced by Fotokem