Okay, children,
everyone pick an instrument.
Doesn't matter which one.
Everyone's gonna be bad.
Who cares? I'm union.
I told you,
I am not playing an instrument.
You're playing an instrument.
Mom, music is made by computers,
not rusty metal you put
in your mouth.
Look, your mom thinks
that forcing you to do music
in school will somehow make you
into a different person
than we all know you are,
which it won't, so just do it,
or I'll cut all your shorts
into skirts.
Fine.
What about this stupid thing?
Why don't you try this clarinet?
It's like the recorder,
but cooler.
What about this hobo guitar?
At least he was wearing
a tuxedo.
Now can we get out of here?
The Wi-Fi sucks,
and I'm trying to click through
this slideshow of celebrities
who let themselves go.
Word is that number four
is insane.
And here's the form which says
you're responsible
for the instrument.
So, if I break the violin,
Homer has to pay?
The school is lending
your son an instrument
that's worth $430.
Violin, you and me are gonna
make beautiful music together.
Bart? Bart?
$430 violin?
If the beer's in a frosted mug,
you're not an alcoholic,
you're an aficionado.
Hello, Father.
Thank you for
taking responsibility
for this lovely instrument.
I trust you find its music...
soothing.
Come on, dude,
just leave me alone.
I'm a good man.
I've got kids!
You're right,
I've been too hard on you.
Here you go. Catch.
You. You.
I took you into my home,
and you've stolen everything
from me.
You know what this is?
It's me playing
the world's smallest violin.
I'm free. I'm free.
I'm finally free!
Where are you going?
To do to my brain what I just
did to your dreams for our son.
Chug, chug, chug!
The little engine that could
get me wasted.
Yeah, everyone loves
the ol' Disorient Express.
Moe's Tavern. Moe speaking.
What? You have
the nerve to call me?
Why don't you delete my number
from your phone,
then put the phone in a sock,
and then beat yourself
in the head
till your face looks like
motor lodge buffet eggs!
Yeah, another prank call, huh?
Who was it this time?
Anita Manbone?
Ivan Talickya?
Ooh, ooh, I got one.
John Rootbeer.
It wasn't no prankster.
It was someone I know
all too well.
- Oh, who?
- Shut your stinkin' face-hole!
That's who it was, okay?!
Bar's closed!
Everybody get out! Get out!
Oh, stupid drunk breath.
Oh, stupid drunk dog!
Guess I'll have to order
a ride on my smartphone.
Get in.
No mints?
I should've just called Uber.
Hey. What's with Moe?
It's too late for the cockfights
and too early
for the rat fights.
He's been extra psycho
since he got that phone call.
I just want to...
Oh, it sounds like that time
you lit the barbecue
with a possum inside.
Maybe we should follow him.
You're the sober one.
Call me, will you?
Oh, I'll meet you, all right.
I'll meet you good.
I'll kill you.
I'll kill you, you dirty mug!
You've got to stop them.
Let me go, huh?
I'm one loafer smack away
from tearing off
his whole hair system!
Why are you fighting
with an old man?
Because this old man...
is my old man.
Morty Szyslak.
Nice to meet you.
You mean nothing to me.
All you are is a rotten old
rib roast covered in cologne.
You ungrateful punk.
You're not worthy to walk
through a cloud of my scent.
I never should've called you.
On that we agree.
The saddest thing in the world
is seeing a family broken apart.
Drunk dog.
Oh, I ain't seen
my pops for years.
After he called,
I weakened and went to meet him.
But one sniff of
Eau de Sportcoat,
and my shoe was in my hand.
How could you go so long
without seeing your own father?
Seriously, how'd you do it?
It sounds amazing.
Yeah, well, let me explain.
You know how the world
sees me as a...
- Human toilet brush?
- Bingo.
Well, I'm the white sheep
of my family.
They're involved
in a very evil business.
- Illegal drugs?
- No, worse.
- Prescription drugs?
- Oh, well, not that bad.
The Szyslaks are
mattress salesmen.
I know, I know.
They're like mortgage brokers
without the moral code.
Charging people 1,200 bucks
for what's essentially
a big bag of hay.
Growing up, it was me, my dad
and my brother and sister.
We were the biggest
mattress chain in town,
mainly thanks
to our local TV ads.
How does it...?
There it is.
Here ye, hear ye!
I declare the best deals
in all the land!
No credit...
No problem!
So come on down
to Mattress King,
at any one of our many
convenient locations.
We'll have you sleeping
on a new mattress to...
Knight!
- And cut.
- Great work, kids.
Everyone gets an onion.
But there was another
reason for our success,
as I was about to learn.
Son, your voice is finally
gravelly enough
for you to learn what it takes
to survive in the sleep biz.
Bedbugs?!
These are Hungarian
mattress gnashers.
The only way to get rid of them
is to walk away from your house
naked and start a new life.
You're gonna
sabotage our rivals?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
You are.
You want to be a sandman,
a slumber jack, a yawn jockey?
This is what it takes.
It's the Szyslak way.
They were
the competition, sure,
but they were a family too.
I couldn't ruin them.
You should be proud.
You did a good deed.
Yeah, well, that good deed
ruin't my life.
That family I took pity on,
they doused
our mattresses with bedbugs.
The Szyslak empire was ruin't.
Soon, we were down
to just a few locations.
My pops never said
how disappointed he was,
but he let me know
in his own way,
by kicking me out
and turning my room
into a home gym he never used.
My brother and sister took
my place in my father's heart.
The only connection I had
with Pops was LinkedIn.
That's worse than nothing.
Why do you think your dad
reached around to you
after all these years?
I don't care.
I don't care so much!
Moe, you will never have peace
until you make up
with your father.
Honey, I need you to hear this.
Sticking your nose in Moe's
horrible life will end badly.
Homer, what's your
favorite movie?
Fast & Furious 6.
And what's the theme
of that movie?
Cars.
What's the other theme?
Family.
She's right, Moe.
You got to give your cars
a second chance.
- Is that your family's mattress store?
- No.
Is that your family's
mattress store?
- No.
- Is that your family's mattress store?
No!
Geez, I never noticed
how many mattress stores
there are.
Yeah, you never do
till you're shopping for one.
Then they're
freakin' everywhere.
That mattress looked perfectly
fine when it was delivered.
It's not my fault
you flipped it over!
Mr. Szyslak,
I've brought someone here
who still cares for you.
Hey there, Pops.
I'm sorry about
shoe-slapping your face and all.
Well, maybe I had it coming.
You hittin' that?
Can I say I am?
That must be
Moe's brother and sister.
They don't look ugly like Moe,
but I'm still feeling the ugly.
That one's eating
Chinese food with scissors.
Hey, what's Ugly Do-Right
doing here?
He ain't no mattress man.
I will never forgive you for
what you made Dad did to you.
Oh, so we're doing the what
I done made Dad did thing?
Because I can did this
all day long!
Shut up, you box springs!
I'm the one what reached around
to this cesspool
of disappointment.
You know, to make amends.
- Amends?!
There's no reason
for this to come to shoes!
I want you all
to come to our house
for a family forgiveness dinner.
We'll be there.
Can I bring
a bottle of something?
That would be lovely.
You want oxy or Demerol?
Okay, the brother here,
the father there, Moe here...
No. No good.
You know,
when this all ends horribly,
it's gonna be pretty hard
not to say I told you so.
Just don't say it.
You've never been married,
have you, Lisa?
When you love someone very much,
the toughest thing
is not to rub their face
in their horrible screw-ups.
So, okay, here's a fun game.
Everyone take turns
saying something nice
about a person
they're related to.
I'll start.
Lisa has lovely penmanship.
Thank you, Mom.
Me? Well, it's...
admirable how my stupid father
reached around to this traitor!
I'm impressed
that you better shut up
and make nice with the traitor!
I like that Bart...
Bart is... He...
Can I do two Lisas?
- Dinner fight!
- Yeah, whatcha gonna do? Whatcha gonna do?
Homer! Go to phase two.
It was the sale before Christmas,
and all through the store...
All the deals were amazing
on twin sets and more!
Mattress night
Low, low price
No payments due, but...
Am I the only one
feeling all oniony
about the way things used to be?
We were dressed
as stinkin' reindeer,
but we were really
a stinkin' family.
Oh, I miss you frigs.
Marge, thank you for
reaching around to my family.
I got something
to tell all of youse.
I'm retiring.
Sleepy is the head
that wears the mattress crown.
That's right,
my springs have sprung.
To my son,
I give a store.
To my daughter,
Well, good dinner, everyone.
I'll see youse at the funeral
of whoever dies first.
And to my oldest son,
I give a store.
Wha...?
I buried this dream so deep,
no amount of self-harm
could ever carve it out.
Oh, the smell
of foam off-gassing.
When I cross this threshold,
I begin a new life!
This is the first time
that I've ever been carried
into a store.
Look at me now,
Lady Foot Locker!
Look at me now.
Hey, everyone.
Hey, thanks for coming out.
If anybody wants
a glass of wine,
they're on the memory foam.
Hot dang.
My goodness.
Okay, okay, all right,
shut your, shut your faces.
The commercial that me and
my brother and sister all made
is about to air now.
I cannot tell a lie.
It's good to be back
in the mattress biz.
Sleep softly
and carry a big discount!
And now we're freeing
the savings!
So rush-more to Mattress King
Slumber Super Stores,
as we all welcome our big
brother Moe back to the family!
And remember,
at Moe's location,
every mattress
had someone die on it.
Dead-o's on my mattresses?
Hey, hey, somebody messed
with our commercial.
Who died on Moe's mattresses?
Shut-ins. Fat people.
And inmates! Inmates! Inmates!
No, no, it's all lies!
Come back!
My mattresses are brand-new!
Made in the finest
Filipino sweatshops
by the cutest kids you ever saw!
That's a gross a-mattress!
They betrayed me.
Stabbed me right in the hump.
Sorry, big brother.
We saw an opportunity to knock
you out of the family business,
and we took it.
It's the Szyslak way.
But I brought them together.
How could things end so badly?
Don't say I told you so.
- Don't say I told you so.
- Maybe I shouldn't have gotten involved.
Don't say I told you so.
Why didn't somebody warn me?
I told...
When my pop finds out
I got played for a chump,
he'll wish he never reached
around to me in the first place.
Moe, I'm so sorry.
For the first time,
I'm going to offer you
platonic physical comfort.
I just can't
go through with it.
It's all right.
You got closer than most.
But I have to believe
it's not too late
to reach around and fix things
with your family.
No, no, no.
I tried things the Marge way.
Now I'm gonna do this
the Szyslak way.
No. No!
That's right, me and my family,
we're going
to the mattresses, baby!
I better go with him.
To make sure I see it.
Oh, my God.
What happened?
We cut 'em up good.
They ain't so pretty no more!
All this was just
revenge appetizers!
Tonight is the main course.
And I'm serving it up
family style.
There's only one man
who can stop this.
Sir, this shirt depicts
an octopus sportfishing
and drinking a mai tai.
It's the bestseller in our
Retired Blowhard collection.
Oh, yeah.
I can see myself
watching golf in this.
Mr. Szyslak Sr.,
you've got to do something!
Your children are
tearing each other apart!
No, no. I'm retired now.
Let them work out
their own little tiffs.
Does this look like a tiff?
Free mattresses?!
The time for leisure wear
is over.
Mahalo, sir.
Moe's in there, and I've never
seen him this angry before,
not even when he lost
that angriest man contest.
He's crazy!
He's gonna do it!
He's really gonna do it!
I'm up here, Pops.
I'm playing with
my little brother and sister.
Just like old times.
Hungarian mattress gnashers!
If he releases those bugs,
all our mattresses are ruined!
Not mine. My mattresses
are safe and sound.
All my enemies gnashed!
It's the Szyslak way!
Morty! Do something!
Do it! Smash that jar!
Take what's rightfully yours!
- Wait, what?
- You wanted him to dooze this?
He's finally man enough
to finish the job,
just like he should've
all those years ago.
Do it, son!
Everything will be yours!
Do it for your king!
Do it for your king.
I can't do it.
Wha...?!
Sorry, Pops.
I guess I'll never live
the Szyslak way.
Oh, Moe, you're a good man.
And these soulless mattress
jackals don't deserve you.
I never thought I'd say this,
but some families
just don't belong together.
Yeah, yeah, I'll kill ya!
Physical contact.
I told you so!
Hey, this is Moe S.
from the Mattress King.
Give me a call at 555-0146.
For a limited time only,
the Mattress King's got
queen mattress sets for $99
and king sets for $129.
Are you okay?
Oh, yeah. I'm fine.
That's what I was afraid
was gonna...
That's what I was
afraid was gonna happen
- with that damn thing.
- You all right?
- Oh, I'm fine.
- You sure?
Messed up my guitar though.
No, I'm fine.
- You sure you're...
- No, I'm fine.
Try your arm and stuff.
- He's wearing leather.
- Oh, okay.
- Did you get it on film?
- Yeah.
All right. All right!