♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
ANNOUNCER:
Live, from the famous
Brown Sands
of Public Beach, Delaware,
it's the...
Oh... Saturday afternoon TV
is so boring.
-ANNOUNCER: Bikini girls.
-Hmm?
-Dune buggies.
-All right!
-Daredevil surfers.
-(gasps)
Ordinarily, this beach
would be swarming with them,
but not today-- Oh, no!
They've all been cleared out
to make way for
painstaking sand preparation.
That's right, Dick.
You know, this year,
everyone's a-buzz
about one thing:
the absence
of Mark Rodkin.
Oh, wait. There he is.
(deep yawn)
Marge, I'm bored.
Why don't you
read something?
Because I'm trying
to reduce my boredom.
Well, you could hand out
these flyers
for the neighborhood
rummage sale.
You'd get some fresh air
and exercise.
Eh, I'll do it anyway.
Come on, boy. We're going
to see the neighbors.
Good old Evergreen Terrace...
the swankiest street
in the classiest part
of Pressboard Estates.
If you love it so much,
why are you always littering?
It's easier. Duh.
♪ The dream police ♪
♪ They live inside of my bed ♪
♪ They come to me in my head ♪
♪ The dream police ♪
♪ They're going
to direct me now ♪
♪ Oh, no... ♪
Howdy, neighbor.
May I spray you with the hose
in a playful fashion?
Eh... spray the boy.
(choking)
Well, ready for
the big rummage sale?
Oh, yes, indeed.
I've got nothing but time
until they fix that
malfunctioning Squishee machine.
HOMER:
Hey, I never noticed this place.
Dad, it's right across
the street from us.
That fancy house
will never sell.
Nobody who could afford it
would want to live in
this neighborhood.
Hey, what's wrong
with this neighborhood?
Big shot! Too good to buy
a house here, snobby?
Who are you
talking to, Homer?
The guy who
doesn't live there.
Can we get rid
of this Ayatollah t-shirt?
Khomeini died years ago.
But, Marge,
it works on any Ayatollah.
Ayatollah Nakhbadeh,
Ayatollah Zahedi...
even as we speak,
Ayatollah Razmara
and his cadre of fanatics
are consolidating their power.
I don't care who's
consolidating their power.
Well, we don't need this.
But, Marge, that's the
Rhinestone Nights fashion gun.
I need it to rhinestone up
my old clothing.
Who's Disco Stu?
I wanted to write disco stud,
but I ran out of space.
Not that Disco Stu didn't get
his share of the action.
So if you're looking for
a half bag of charcoal briquettes
or an artificial
Christmas tree-- trunk only--
come on over
to the Hibbard table, pronto.
Well, sir, looks like we got
some nice items
here at table Glick.
Like this... what the
heckaroonie is this, Mrs. Glick?
It is a candy dish, Ned. $90.
Uh-huh. Well, I, uh...
I guess you could put
a lot of nice things in there.
No! Just candy, Ned. $90.
Well, looks like
somebody sold something today.
Are you interested
in that motorized tie rack,
Principal Skinner?
(motor whirring)
Hmm... it's
awfully loud.
Well, you can always
take the motor out
and use it
as an ordinary tie rack.
But now the ties
are motionless
and those in back are
virtually inaccessible.
Well, it's a moot point,
as I have only one
tie to begin with.
I believe I'll pass.
Have you sold
that tie rack yet?
-No.
-I'll take it.
Now, folks,
nothing spells fun
like rhinestones
on a dungaree jacket.
Stu, you should
buy that.
Hey, Disco Stu
doesn't advertise.
Uh... hey, Ned, let me
help you with that.
Hey, everybody! Who thinks
Flanders should shut up?
(all yelling in agreement)
So, anyone here from
Evergreen Terrace?
(applause and cheering)
I think this is
the best neighborhood in town.
Anybody agree with me?
(cheering)
You're the king, Homer!
King of the neighborhood.
Say, that Ayatollah
thinks he's better than America.
Is he right?
(booing)
MAN:
Yes.
Well, for only five dollars,
you can sock it to him in style.
Right here!
And for the man
who has everything,
a tie rack motor.
I'll take that.
(jazzy up-tempo music playing)
♪ Hey, big spender ♪
♪ Dig this blender ♪
♪ Rainbow suspenders ♪
♪ Hey, big spender ♪
ALL:
♪ We surrender ♪
♪ Spend ♪
♪ Some dough at table three ♪
(cheering and applause)
(truck horn honks)
(all murmuring)
Thank you, neighbors, thank you.
Now, let's give it up
for table five.
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ Table five, table five ♪
♪ Table five ♪
♪ Table five, table five... ♪
Hey, what's the big deal?
It's just
some new guy moving in.
(clears throat)
Disco Stu likes disco music.
(electronic feedback)
Hi there, neighbors.
I'm... George Bush.
Former President George Bush?
(murmurs of recognition)
HOMER: Okay, let's give it up
for the new guy.
Now let's all turn around
and pay attention to me again.
Hello?
Wow! A former President
living right across the street.
Oh! Why did he have
to move in on my territory?
Look at him.
Thinks just because
he led the free world
he can act like a big shot.
Stupid President.
Why couldn't he just stay
in his own state?
Actually, this is one
of the nine states
where Mr. Bush
claims residency, Dad.
I wouldn't have
voted for him
but it's nice to have a
celebrity in the neighborhood.
Wait a minute.
If Lisa didn't vote for him
and I didn't vote for him...
You didn't vote
for anybody.
I voted for Prell to go back
to the old glass bottle.
After that,
I became deeply cynical.
And your business
here, Mr. Flanders?
Well, sir,
I'm welcoming the Bushes
on behalf of the
Neighborhood Association.
Never mind
about that, Ray.
Just give them a quick pass
with the metal detector
and let them on in.
Hey, Bar!
The neighbors are here.
Howdily-doodily there,
President Bush
or should I say
President neighbor?
I'm Ned Flanders and this
is Maude, Rod and Todd.
Well, howdily-doodily
yourself there, Ned.
This is my wife, Barbara.
Call her Bar.
Would you like some lemonade?
-Tip-top-notch!
-Okily-dokily.
Thankily-dankily.
Greatalicious!
Scrumpdiddlerific!
BOTH: Fine and dandy
like sour candy.
Bar's a whiz
with cold drinks
aren't you, Bar?
Don't understand
lemonade myself.
Not my forte.
What brings you
to Springfield?
Well, George and I
just wanted to be
private citizens again...
go where nobody cared
about politics.
So we found the town
with the lowest voter
turnout in America.
Just happy to be here
among good, average people
with no particular
hopes or dreams.
But, Mr. President,
we're not all good people.
There's one little boy
you should watch out for.
He's a bad,
bad little boy.
(laughing nervously)
Now, Todd,
don't scare the President.
(panting)
Huh... look at those phonies,
sucking up to Bush.
(whimpering)
(barking)
I guess you might say he's
barking up the wrong Bush.
HOMER'S BRAIN:
There it is, Homer.
The cleverest thing you'll
ever say and nobody heard it.
D'oh!
Ah!
Just going to relax
with my U.S. News and World
whatnot.
Oh, good.
They're roasting the new guy.
(imitating Dennis the Menace)
Hello... Mr. Bush!
George...
this is a neighborhood
boy, Bart Simpson.
He came over
to say hi.
(quietly)
Hello.
Hi! Hey, what's this?
My electric card shuffler.
Don't go near the--
Now, I told you.
Oh... those cards
were from Air Force One
and they only give you
so many packs.
Oh, George,
boys will be boys.
Bart's just being friendly.
Why don't you get off that sofa
and show Bart your photos?
Oh, he'll gunk
them all up.
His hands are probably covered
with mud and cookies.
Well...
(muttering)
Probably stole a napkin.
Who's that, George?
That's me with
Charlton Heston. He was...
Who's that, George?
Now see, you
wouldn't know him.
That's Bob Mosbacher,
He was Secretary of...
That's a dumb name.
Who's that, George?
Maybe he thinks Bart
is a dumb name.
How many times were
you President, George?
Just once.
Bar, isn't it time
for dinner yet?
I'm making rice.
It'll be a while.
Did your
Secret Service goons
ever whack anybody,
George?
You know, in my day,
little boys didn't call their
elders by their first names.
Yeah, well, welcome
to the 20th century, George.
(muttering) I'll kick you right out of
the 20th century, you little...
(tires screeching)
Oh, man! I only got one minute
till they stop serving
those breakfast balls. D'oh!
Let's see now.
What do you folks
have here, huh?
Hmm, a Krusty Burger.
That doesn't sound
too appetizing.
What kind of stew
do you have today?
Uh, we don't have stew.
(honking)
Sir, why don't you just
have the cheeseburger?
Oh, that's really more
of a weekend thing, Ray.
Hey, jerk!
Move your fanny!
That guy is louder
than World War II.
Ray, go see what
the rhubarb is, will you?
(honking)
Sir, could you
pop your hood?
(horn braying)
Hey! My taxes paid
for that horn.
Why, hello, Mrs. Bush.
Hi, Bart.
Mr. Bush is
upstairs napping.
You know, your husband's
awful grumpy.
Oh, that's just his way.
He really likes you.
You know, it's time
for him to get up
and work on his memoirs.
Why don't you
go wake him?
(horn sounding)
What? What the--
Great Scott, don't touch that.
That's the alpenhorn
Helmut Kohl gave me.
Where'd you get
those pajamas?
They're presidential pajamas.
You have to be president,
and you're not president.
Yes, I am.
No, you're not! Bar!
Hey, where's your candy?
We don't have any.
Now, go away.
George!
Older people don't eat
much candy, Bart
but I could bake you
some cookies if you like.
(muttering) Can't remember the last time
she made cookies for me.
-What's that?
-Oh, nothing.
HOMER:
All right.
His story checks out.
Marge, would you love me
more if I were President?
'Cause I'll do it
if it'll make you happy.
Homie, as long
as you keep
the car full of gas,
I'm happy.
Well, she can always
depend on that.
-(typing)
-And since I'd achieved
all my goals as President
in one term
there was no need for a second.
Hmm... good memoirs.
Good, not great.
Now, let's look
at that old outboard.
Soup that baby up,
rattle a few windows
down in Kennebunkport
next May.
Hello... Mr. Bush!
What you doing?
Don't upset the desk there.
Careful! Don't want
to horse around with...
Hey, cool! What does this do?
Now don't you pull that cord,
young man!
(engine revving)
GEORGE: Now look what you did.
Whoops! Hey!
Bar, my motor's gone loco!
Oh! The birdhouse.
My prize orchids!
Oh, no!
Not the memoirs.
Don't even
think about it.
Not gonna happen.
(groans)
(engine stops)
Whoa, man.
Whoa, nothing.
I'm going to do something
your Daddy should
have done a long time ago.
Now go home and think about
what you've done, young man.
He spanked you?
You? Bart Simpson?
I begged him to stop
but he said it was
for the good of the nation.
Big deal.
When I was a pup,
we got spanked by Presidents
till the cows came home.
Grover Cleveland spanked me
on two non-consecutive
occasions.
Grampa, I know in your day,
spanking was common
but Homer and I
just don't believe
in that kind of punishment.
And that's why your no-good
kids are running wild!
First, Bush invades
my home turf,
then he takes my pals,
then he makes fun
of the way I talk... probably.
Now he steals my right
to raise a disobedient,
smart-alecky son!
Well, that's it!
Hey, Bush!
Get out here!
Excuse me, sir.
Where are you going?
I'm going to punch
George Bush in the face.
Okay. Is he expecting you?
You owe me
an apology.
Hey, you owe me
If you were
any kind of a father
you'd have disciplined
that boy a long time ago.
You want to step back, sir?
-You're trampling the flowers.
-Ooh!
Hiding behind your goons,
eh, Bush?
Oh!
Well, you are a wimp!
Wimp... am I?
Agent Johnson?
Agent Heintz?
You men, stand down.
All right, mister.
You want trouble,
you're going to get trouble.
Oh, I want trouble, all right.
Then you're going
to get trouble.
No, you're going
Oh, that's good, that's good
'cause I want trouble.
Then we're agreed
there'll be trouble.
Oh, yeah,
lots of trouble.
-Trouble, it is.
-For you.
-For... D'oh!
-(door slams)
(chuckles)
This is gonna be sweet.
200 bottle rockets,
and George Bush
doing toe-touches
by an open window.
BART: If you get one
up his butt,
it's a million points.
(sizzling)
(whistling)
(booming)
BARBARA:
Why don't you just
say you're
sorry, George?
Because I'm right.
Oh, no.
I'm going to fix
their wagon good.
I've pulled some pranks
in my time.
(rattling)
DR. HIBBERT:
Uh, I don't understand.
Are you saying you and
Barbara are bad neighbors?
No, that's not Bar
and me, it's them.
Who? Maude and me?
No, the man
and his boy.
You know, the...
the boy is named Bart.
I don't know the
name of the man.
Bar, what's the
name of the man?
I'm not getting
involved, George.
Look, just never mind.
I thought the banner
was pretty
straightforward
but... guess I'll
just take it down.
BARBARA:
George...
it's time to
get dressed.
Nuh-uh. I'm not
going outside today,
not with those
neighbors.
Staying right here till
my speech to the Elks Club.
(knocking)
HOMER:
Yoo-hoo.
Who is it?
HOMER: It's your sons,
George Bush, Jr. and Jeb Bush.
Come outside, Dad.
Oh, good.
Bar, the boys are out
in the front yard.
They'll help me
think of a plan
to get those
Simpsons.
Oh, George, is that all
you ever think about?
The boys probably just want a
letter of recommendation.
Boys? Where
you going?
Okay, son, give him the glue.
(Homer grunting)
(Homer and Bart laughing)
HOMER:
Hey, looking good!
GEORGE:
And that's why I will continue
to oppose teen alcoholism
in all its forms.
Now, are there any questions?
Keeping in mind that I already
explained about my hair.
(mumbling)
Oh, yeah, that's right.
(engine revving)
(tires squealing)
(mud splattering)
President Bush is
driving on our lawn.
He must be lost.
He's not lost.
Looks like we're
experiencing
some blow-back from
the wig offensive.
It's time to hit
him where he lives.
His house?
Bingo.
So I thought to myself
'what would God do
in this situation?'
(buzzing)
(snickering)
Locusts...
They'll drive him nuts.
It's all in the Bible, son.
It's the prankster's Bible.
(engine revving)
Hmm. Can't decide if this'll
be considered feisty or crazy.
Hey! Hey, what the..?
Ohh, if he thinks George Bush
will stay out of the sewer
he doesn't know George Bush.
Hey, turkeys, behind you.
For the last time, Bush,
apologize for spanking my boy.
Never.
You make him apologize
for destroying my memoirs.
You didn't tell me you
destroyed his memoirs.
Never!
Yay, Dad!
I really feel awful
about your lawn, Marge.
George can be
so stubborn
when he thinks
he's right.
Well, Homer too.
They're so much alike.
Too bad they got off
on the wrong foot.
It's just like
the Noriega thing.
Now, he and George are
the best of friends.
(both panting)
Here's a little something
we learned in C.I.A.
(buzzing)
Get him, boys.
(doorbell ringing)
Hello?
(buzzing)
I'll ruin you like
a Japanese banquet.
I'll take your
head, and...
Gorbachev.
(nervous chuckling)
What are you
doing here?
I just dropped by with present
for warming of house.
Instead, find you
grappling with local oaf.
Oh, brought some of
your commie friends
to help you
fight dirty, eh?
But, Mikhail, he put
a wig on my head,
my memoirs...
BARBARA: George...
this is the last straw.
You apologize
to Homer right now.
But, Bar, we can't
show any weakness
in front of
the Russians.
George.
Yes, dear.
(speaking Russian)
(laughing)
Okay.
I'm sorry I spanked
your boy, Homer.
Woo hoo!
In your face, Bush!
Now, apologize
for the tax hike.
It's a shame it didn't
work out, Marge
but George just felt
this neighborhood
brought out the worst
in him, and...
(honking)
Oh, my.
Well, so long.
Bye-bye.
Hi.
Pleased to meet you.
I just moved in.
My name is Jerry Ford.
(gasping)
Former President Gerald Ford?
Put her there.
I'm Homer Simpson.
Say, Homer,
do you like football?
Do I ever?
Do you like nachos?
Yes, Mr. Ford.
Well...
why don't you come over
and watch the game
and we'll have nachos
and then, some beer.
Oohh..
Jerry, I think
you and I
are going to
get along just...
-D'oh!
♪♪
Shh.
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.