(SINGING) The Simpsons
D'oh!
(SCREAMS)
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
ALL: (SCREAM)
ANNOUNCER: We now return to
"Blacula Meets Black Dracula."
(DISCO MUSIC PLAYING)
I'm turning this
disco into a hockey rink.
You mean a honky rink.
(SCREAMING)
You know, Black Dracula is now
a Congressman from Virginia.
(HUMMING)
Bart, where did
you get those?
There's an open
house next door.
They're giving out cookies
and business cards.
Check it out.
I'm a business jerk.
(GRUNTING)
Marge, I don't want
to buy this house.
I'd have to live
next door to myself.
(LOUD MUSIC PLAYING)
Turn that down.
Screw you.
(GRUNTS)
Relax.
We're just looky-loos.
We're only here
to compare our lifestyle
to our neighbors'.
Come on, Marge.
It's not fair to
compare us to
an American household.
(GASPS)
It's so beautiful and modern.
Ooh.
A sub-zero fridge.
A slightly colder fridge?
In my lifetime? Amazing.
This is the kitchen
I've always wanted.
(GASPS) Ooh,
a bread-maker maker.
(WHIRRING)
And check this out.
A walk-in microwave.
Hey,
Marge, can you press "stop"
when my popcorn's done?
Uh-oh.
(HUMMING)
Hmm.
(GASPS)
(GROANS)
Homie, when I married you,
I knew we wouldn't
live in luxury.
And I kept that vow.
(BOTH GASP)
But seeing that kitchen today
made me wish we had something
a little better for ourselves.
I'll build you
a new kitchen, sweetie.
Oh, Homie,
that's so thoughtful.
But maybe we should hire
a professional contractor.
A contractor?
Those guys are
the biggest crooks around.
They charge for
materials and labor.
Pick one, jerks.
(HUMMING)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANING)
Man, that hurt.
Now to do
the exact same thing again.
(GROANING)
Maybe you should
turn off the power.
All right.
(GRUNTING)
Don't demolish along the way.
HOMER: Fine.
Easy. Easy.
Playdude magazines?
Have you been hiding
bosom rags from me?
Trying to. (CHUCKLES)
These magazines are from
before we were married.
Maybe you should
throw them away.
But I need them
for the articles.
Mmm. The articles, eh?
So, you wouldn't mind
if I cut out all
the erotic nudes?
Of course not.
Why would I want to look
at a nude woman I'm
not even married to?
I mean, l wouldn't even know
how she could improve me.
Hmm.
"I'm not wearing any clothes,
"so why don't
I just splay myself
on a pool table?"
(GRUNTS)
Steady. Steady.
Okay, here's your
precious articles.
Thanks, Marge.
I can't wait
to read about...
"Sport Fishing
With Sonny Jurgensen."
(SOBBING)
(GRUNTS)
What man would want you now?
Whoa! Playdudes!
Let the blossoming
of Milhouse begin.
I gotta be honest.
I don't see what all
the hubbub is about.
Hey. The lady in
this picture is hot.
She can calamine
my hives anytime.
That's Congresswoman
Bella Abzug.
MILHOUSE: Ciao, Bella.
The grownups in this magazine
are pretty cool.
BART: I could make the tree
house look like this.
Then we could have orgies,
whatever they are.
We'll be Playdude Playmates.
BOTH:
We are Playdude Playmates.
There it is,
nice and smooth.
I'd like to see
your boyfriend,
the contractor,
do a better job.
I think you used
too much plaster.
(SNORTS)
Now you tell me.
I never stopped
telling you.
So, that's what
that white noise was.
I'm calling a contractor.
Thanks for taking the job.
I'm sorry my husband
is being so difficult.
Get lost, crook.
That's all right,
Mrs. Simpson.
Many husbands feel emasculated
when their wife must turn
to a professional
to satisfy her
remodeling needs.
Why don't you just kiss her?
I'm gay.
But I have a subcontractor
that does that
sort of thing for me.
I like to kiss.
(KISSING)
Now, don't you worry.
Your kitchen will be
done in three weeks.
When Virginia Woolf
wrote, "Every woman
needs a room of one's own,"
She must have been
talking about the kitchen.
What's the first
thing you're gonna make
in your new kitchen?
How about
cooking up some money
because this stupid
kitchen cost $100,000.
(CRYING)
I was thinking
of chicken wings.
Those are good, too.
Same old stuff.
Meatloaf,
casserole, tuna loaf,
loaferole, cassaloaf...
Marge Simpson's
Wasabi Buffalo Wings?
Ooh. An Eastern
twist on a Western
New York favorite.
(ALL MOANING)
These wings are going
straight to my thighs
and I say bon voyage.
What do you think,
Thomas Pynchon?
(MUNCHING)
These wings are V-licious.
I'll put this recipe in the
Gravity's Rainbow Cookbook
right next to
the Frying of Latke 49.
I agree with my
fellow Cornell alumnus.
Huzzah for Marge.
ALL: Huzzah.
And how about a huzzah
for my husband who paid
for our new kitchen?
Never
Marge, you know, I thought
I was Springfield's
wing-ding king.
But you make
my chicken look like
cock-a-diddily doo doo.
Great stuff, Ned.
You know, I was gonna enter
this here Ovenfresh Bakeoff.
But up against you,
I wouldn't have
a Hindu's chance in heaven.
If you win,
Ovenfresh Industries
will make you
the new face
of Auntie Ovenfresh.
Come on, Marge.
It's either you or...
I guess it would be a hoot
to have my face on everything.
Oh, Mrs. Simpson,
you must pursue your dreams,
like my old dream
of coming to America
and starting a family.
Or my new dream of
ditching my family
and sneaking back
to India in disguise.
Apu? Never heard of him.
My name is Steve Barnes.
(JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING)
So, when do they
start singing?
Well, the Playdude
Advisor says
this music will
get a stewardess
to give you a layover.
I hope it's in Omaha.
My grammy lives there.
MARGE: Bart, can you come
in here for a second?
Your mother is
about to show us
her new recipe.
Outta sight.
Lay it on me, Mama.
In the Ovenfresh Bakeoff,
clever presentation
is as important as taste.
So, I'm entering
my dessert dogs.
It's deep-fried cookie dough
with meringue buns,
cherry ketchup,
and caramel mustard.
Mmm!
It's dessert
but it's hot dogs,
so it's good for you.
Marge, I don't
want to freak you out,
but I think I love you.
Oh, I hope the
Ovenfresh Bakeoff likes
them as much as you do.
Mmm.
Mom, a letter from
Ovenfresh Industries.
Well, open it.
Open it. Open it.
"Thank you for applying
to the Ovenfresh Bakeoff.
"Every year many
wonderful cooks
fail to qualify.
(SIGHS)
"But screw them, you're in.
Congratulations."
Oh, my God.
Someone somewhere
says I'm better
than someone else.
I'm proud of you, honey.
(CRYING)
Sorry, Ralphie.
The bakeoff
rejected your recipe.
I want to be in the bakeoff.
There, there.
I think your
grilled crayon sandwich
was delicious.
You only had
a pretend bite.
No. I'm eating it, look.
Mmm.
Can you taste
the thumbtacks?
Aw, crap.
I'm here live at the annual
Ovenfresh Bakeoff
brought to you by
the Ovenfresh Flour
family of products.
Including...
(JOURNALIST READING)
Quetzalcoatl's choice,
the favorite
from Zihuatanejo
to Popocatépetl.
Ha-ha!
Bart looks different today.
Aw, Nelson, your debonair
wit reminds me of
a young Mort Sahl.
Guh?
Listen up,
ring-a-ding-dingers.
I'm throwing
a little sip 'n' quip
at the Playdude Tree House.
Saturday night at
the top of the ladder.
Be there or be square.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
I want to be a triangle.
You're not invited.
It's gonna be weird cooking
without your tipsy father
grabbing me from behind.
But I think I'm up to it.
Welcome to
the Ovenfresh Bakeoff.
I'm Billy Bouillon Cube.
Follow me to
your oven station.
Why thank you, Billy.
Don't look at
my human eyes.
Oh, don't mind Billy.
His oven light's on
but nothing's cooking.
(CHUCKLES)
So, what you making, Marge?
Well, Stuart,
I'm making a dessert
that looks like
a hotdog but it isn't.
You're making a tasty fake?
(CHUCKLES)
That is so '90s.
Why don't we all
move to Seattle
and use slow modems?
(ALL LAUGH)
(SCOFFS) Yo, Marge.
Your recipe, she is pathetic.
She is not.
(JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING)
Great licks, man.
Great licks.
Yo, Bart.
There's no room
left in the grotto.
Who's that adult?
Hey, it wouldn't
be a Playdude party
without James Caan.
So, I'm trying to
talk with Miss November
and Charlie Callas over here
is blocking my action with...
(INDISTINCT)
Turns out he's
choking on a peanut.
Well, punch to the gut
cleared that right up.
(KIDS LAUGHING)
Hey, Bart.
Me and Mrs. Krabappel,
we're gonna go
play some backgammon,
if you know what I mean.
I don't. But I hope you win.
Oh, he's gonna win.
Some guys like
a challenge, not me.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Before we begin,
let us introduce
Auntie Ovenfresh 1954.
Ribbons and trophies
are no comfort
on your deathbed.
Auntie Ovenfresh.
(CHUCKLING)
And now, chefs.
Start your kitchens.
(GASPS)
Huh?
Fish scales?
Stop.
You're tainting my entry.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
It was, how you say,
done with malice
aforethought, yes?
You did it on purpose?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
My English,
she's not so good.
I was, how you say,
ruining your
food so I win, yes?
(SIGHS)
Why is everyone
at this bakeoff
such a meanie-bo-beanie?
These muffin-huffin'
batter biddies
can smell weakness
a mile away.
Weakness named Marge.
Why can't everyone
just play fair and...
Did you just dunk your hair
in my mixing bowl?
You're weak. Weak.
Listen here, Simpson.
Your son has been exposing
our kids to adult themes,
unabashed dictionaries
and the lesser short fiction
of John Cheever.
Adult themes?
What are you talking about?
My Roddy told a joke
about an octopus
and a set of bagpipes.
And the punch line
implied that they fornicated.
Ralphie wants
to go on the pill.
Stupid Bart.
(CHUCKUNG)
Bagpipes getting
down with an octopus,
that's classic.
Hot bananas
coming through. Oops.
(GASPS)
My dessert.
(PANTING FRANTICALLY)
(SOBBING)
Come on, Mom.
You still have
20 minutes left.
You can fix it.
You're right. If I can
feed a family of five
on $12 a week,
I can do anything.
You feed us on $12 a week?
I stretch your
father's meatloaf
with sawdust.
Attention, contestants.
Baking time is over.
The judging will
commence in one hour.
If your dish is not
in the judging room
by the time this metal door
hits the ground,
your entry will
not be official
and will be
eaten by the janitor.
(BUZZING)
Hurry, Mom.
Oh! I guess I was
the last one.
AGNES: Damn it.
These other
dishes look so pretty.
And those cheaters
blackened my sugar wieners.
I'd like to give
those Betty Crookeds
a taste of their own medicine.
Yes, medicine.
(MARGE READING)
(SINISTER LAUGH)
Ugh.
Even the Pope
couldn't forgive this pizza.
And he's letting
a lot of things
slide these days.
Don't worry. There's
plenty for all of you.
Now who's laughing? Huh?
Huh? (LAUGHING)
Me. I'm laughing.
(LAUGHS)
I can't believe
my mom would cheat.
Hi, sweetie.
Is Morn winning?
Oh, she'll win the contest,
but she'll lose her soul.
But she'll still
win the contest?
And lose her soul.
But win the contest?
Yes.
Whoo-hoo! If Marge
becomes Auntie Ovenfresh,
we'll meet all
the food personalities.
Look. It's Mister Cashew,
the Koobler Dwarves,
Snip, Krinkle, and Poof.
Twinkle the Kidd,
I love you.
Whoa, easy there, partner.
(GROANING)
Uh-oh.
You killed him.
He was my world.
ALL: (CHANTING)
Blood for cream.
It's always difficult
to pick two finalists.
But this year it was easy.
All the other
dishes made us vomit.
(RETCHING)
Our two remaining dishes are
Blackened Dessert Dogs
by Marge Simpson
And Armadillo à la Road
by Brandine and
no last name given .
That's an entry?
I thought it was garbage .
Just 'cause it was cooked
In a garbage can don't
make it garbage .
(CHUCKLING)
"Canned and frozen juices
are more popular
than ever these days.
"But most bachelors
we know would
"prefer to squeeze
their own tomatoes."
(LAUGHING)
Bachelors are
always squeezing stuff.
Would you excuse us, Milton?
It's Milhouse.
Yeah, and your father's
no house. Now, scram.
(GROANS)
Maybe I was a little
hard on him. Oh, well.
Bart, I know
a father has no right to
pry into the life of
his 10-year-old son.
But what's going
on up here?
I'm just spreading
the Playdude philosophy.
Hi-fi's, Norman Mailer,
getting some.
Uh, um...
What do you think "some" is?
Uh,
toys?
(SIGHS) I thought I'd
never have to do this,
but it's time to tell
you the facts of life.
Do you know what a boob is?
Oh, yeah.
Good. That'll save
us some time. Okay.
Why do you think your mother
and I sleep in the same bed?
Because we're poor?
Exactly.
And we're poor
because we have kids.
And the biological
method by which
children are created
by a man and a woman is...
(BART SCREAMS)
BART: Then the man...
(KIDS SCREAM)
BART AND MILLHOUSE:
Then the woman...
(KIDS SCREAM)
(KIDS SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING)
Well, it's better
they hear it from me now
than from their parents
when they're old enough.
Congratulations, Mom.
You seem to have
a prescription for success.
What a kind yet oddly
ominous thing to say.
Now, I've gotta get
ready for the finals.
Don't forget your
secret ingredient.
Cheating.
Well, it's not my fault.
Lisa, the people
in this bakeoff are stinkers
who pushed me
and pushed me like
the pushy-wushies they are.
Mom, if I don't
have you to look up to,
I don't have anyone.
Look, I'll be a winner
with feet of clay
like Mickey Mantle.
Everyone loves the Mick.
I don't want Mickey Mantle.
I want my mom.
Hey, plenty of kids
are gonna look up to me
when I'm Auntie
whatever it is.
Right now, people just know me
as the wife of a guy
who doesn't go to work.
Can't you understand
that I need this?
(SIGHS)
I guess Dad has
to be my hero now.
Not if you knew
what he's been doing.
(SHUDDERS)
Welcome to the final battle
of the Ovenfresh Challenge.
Ooh, she's already
ahead of me.
Mm, mm, mm, mm, mm.
Well, I didn't come
this far not to cheat.
Huh?
(MARGE READING)
That's clever and devastating.
(GROANS)
Stop the competition.
(ALL GASP)
I don't deserve to win.
I sabotaged all
the other entries.
(GASPING)
Looks like me and Marge
are both going to hell.
That's where
I'll make my move.
Then I won with my festive
Holiday Alco-Hog.
(RETCHING)
Huh! I thought it was dead.
Mmm.
Thanks, honey,
for saving me from myself.
And, Marge, you'll always be
the best chef in our house.
(SIGHS) BFD.
I've had your
scrambled eggs, Homer.
The secret
ingredient is whiskey.
Hey, it keeps the kids quiet.
Hey, look.
The new Ovenfresh Flour bag.
Ah, that could've been me.
CLETUS: Aw,
I wish it had've been.
(SOBS)
Now that Brandine's famous,
she done run off
with James Caan.
But don't you worry.
I'm gonna fix his wagon.
A tollbooth?
I hate these things.
That's it. Next time I fly.