CHOIR: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
HOMER: Oh-hoo-hoo!
Pork chops with gravy!
Wait... but today's not
Pork Chop Tuesday.
Or Gravy Thursday!
I also set up some mirrors
so you could watch
hockey fights while you eat.
HOMER: Whoo-hoo!
Oh, I love Canadian-on-Canadian violence.
Oh, baby, this is so great!
Thank you so much.
I'm just happy you're happy.
Wait a minute, that's not something
people really feel.
What's going on?
Well, I do have a favor.
Patty and Selma came home early
from their vacation,
but the cleaners still haven't
gotten all the black mold
out of their apartment.
(deep roar)
So they need a place to stay. Here.
-(shrieks)
-Paris was a bust.
They wouldn't even let us
see the Mona Lisa.
They kept yelling, "La Joconde!
Her smile will die!"
No, Marge, no!
You can't invite a couple of Riddlers
to stay in the Bat Cave!
You ate the food
and looked in the mirrors.
They're staying!
(gruff chuckling)
(inhaling, exhaling loudly)
(Bart and Lisa coughing)
Hmm.
Oh, honey,
one teensy problem with this plan.
I'm a teensy bit concerned
about them smoking around the children.
You know, their lungs are so teensy.
Mwah! Mwah!
Hmm. He has a point.
No, no.
No, no, we don't have to smoke.
We can stop whenever we want.
See?
(both grunt)
Okay, how about this--
if you catch us smoking in the house,
even one time,
you can throw us out on the street.
You know what?
I trust them not to smoke.
And if you trust them,
I trust them, too.
(devious chuckle)
Safety first!
Screw this.
We'll just go outside.
Nature is God's ashtray.
(hums)
(thunder crashes)
Bad news, bears.
Forecast calls for nothing but rain.
(both groan)
(grunting)
(glass shatters)
(humming)
(sighs)
Here we go.
Problem solved.
Electric cigarettes.
(loud inhaling)
Choke on our harmless fumes.
Hmm?
Well, if you fall asleep with them,
will you even burn to death?
-BOTH: Uh-uh.
-Oh.
(loud, rapid inhaling and exhaling)
They call these cigarettes?
They don't stain my fingers,
my hair smells like hair,
and what do I stub out
in my scrambled eggs?
Sure, it's got the nicotine,
but where's the tar?
Where's the stab from every breath
that reminds me I'm alive?
No smoke detector! Let's roll!
(both grunt)
Wait, wait.
Turn on the faucet
so no one'll get suspicious.
(explosion)
(smoke detectors beeping)
Aha! I gotcha!
-(beeping stops)
-You can't resist smoking in the house
any more than I can resist
drinking in the car.
-What happened?
-I don't know.
The water caught on fire.
(gasps)
And now I banish you from paradise.
I'm glad I never bothered to learn
which one of you is which.
Please, show some compassion
for two good people
who just can't stop smoking.
Hmm... hmm.
I know just the place.
-(tires screech)
-(coughing)
(both sniffing)
Oh! (shudders)
Tobacco!
(both chuckling excitedly)
(loud inhaling, exhaling)
Who needs Paris?
This is our City of Lights!
♪ ♪
Flaming tap water.
I saw something about that
in a documentary.
Sad. Sad.
Sad. Sad. Sad. Sad.
Sad. Sad. Sad.
Cute. (gasps) This one!
MALE NARRATOR:
In this rural community,
hydraulic fracturing, or fracking,
was greeted as a windfall.
(crowd cheering)
By pumping high-pressure liquid
into underground shale deposits,
fracking releases natural gas,
but can lead to devastating
environmental consequences.
(whooshes)
Yep, used to be you could try
burning your water all day
and nothing would happen.
Henry, did you remember
to turn off the Slip 'N Slide?
(children laughing)
-(explosion)
-(screaming)
Well, I... reckon not.
I think someone is fracking
under our neighborhood.
And I know who.
It's you, Mr. Texan.
Oil wasn't enough--
now you're going after
our natural gas.
Aw, now,
ain't nothing natural about gas.
If you can't dance in it,
I ain't drilling for it.
I don't do this for the money,
it's the dancing.
It's always been the dancing.
(whooping and laughing)
-(both sigh)
-All right!
BART: Oh, man.
He made us watch him dance
for three hours,
and he really only has one move.
If someone was fracking
in our neighborhood,
wouldn't we know it?
Maybe a satellite picture
will give us a clue.
Hmm, this is clearly a fracking site.
How are they keeping people away?
(wind whistling)
-Aw, it's a terrific sport--
-Shh!
This whole building is just a facade
for a drilling operation.
Indeed it is.
Evergreen Terrace is built atop
a massive shale deposit.
Think of it--
all that poor natural gas
trapped underneath
your shanties and lean-tos.
Smithers, give these two brats
what they deserve
for sticking their noses
in my business.
(both groan)
(Lisa groans)
Stopping Mr. Burns may be beyond
the power of an eight-year-old girl
with a book report due on
Beezus and Ramona,
but I know someone who can help--
the first female
Speaker of the State Assembly,
a politician
who would never ignore
a fellow environmentalist in need,
my hero, Maxine Lombard.
(gasps)
Charge the electric limo--
we're going to Springfield.
What about your cool-down period?
What about it?!
Lisa! Motorcade!
Assemblywoman Lombard!
You got my e-mails!
I'll go anywhere, anytime,
to defend our precious Bay Area values.
(gasps) Terrible!
Just shocking.
Does anybody have a baby
we can hold near the flames?
I guess I do.
(sighs)
I'm gonna hit this Mr. Burns
with a politician's
most powerful weapon--
an invitation to a committee hearing.
Mr. Burns, do you admit
that you illegally pump
toxic chemicals into the groundwater
below Evergreen Terrace?
(indistinct whispering)
I... don't recall.
Mr. Burns!
Have you no regard
for the life and health
of your fellow human beings?
(indistinct whispering)
I... don't recall.
You can't drill underneath people's homes
without their permission.
As chairwoman
of this Committee on Energy,
Natural Resources,
and Blimp Safety,
your fracking operation
is hereby shut down.
(groans)
I demand to see that
capitalism-castrating suffragette
this instant!
You haven't bested me.
I will find a way to shatter that shale.
What makes men like you
think you can do
whatever you want to our planet?
Maybe the planet wants a strong man
to take her by the hand and lead her.
You don't know
what the planet wants.
Oh, and I suppose you do?
The planet wants to be
protected and nourished
and maybe even...
Kissed.
(both moan)
Mwah!
♪ ♪
Wait a minute,
I'm not having a stroke, am I?
No. Am I?
-I don't think so.
-Oh, good.
♪ ♪
(both gasp)
-You!
-Me?
(Burns shudders)
This was all a mistake--
an impulsive...
-Reckless...
-...knee-buckling...
-...spat-snapping...
-...Spanx-shredding mistake.
-(sighs) Oh, it was great.
-(chuckles) Best I've ever had.
And that includes...
Nellie Taft.
So, Monty, shall we find a way
to continue this...
purely passionate affair?
But you're a softhearted liberal!
And you're a hard-hearted capitalist.
Enemies by day, lovers by night.
MAXINE: Mmm... mwah!
Now, get out of my office.
As soon as I collect my things.
Uh, derringer, sword cane,
derringer cane, sword derringer--
all right, it's all here.
If I want to resume fracking,
I have to buy the mineral rights
for every single parcel of land
in Evergreen Terrace.
To win people over,
I'll need a salesman
whose folksy facade
masks a deep gusher of greed.
Hmm?
(chuckles)
Congratulations, Simpson!
You're now my chief
energy innovation marketing officer.
Whoo-hoo!
All you've got to do is sell fracking
to your friends and neighbors.
Whoo-hoo?
I don't know, "fracking" is
one of those scary Lisa words.
Bah! Fracking produces
enough clean natural gas
to make America independent
of sheiks, caliphs, and...
Scandinavians.
Not to mention,
it doesn't create any of that awful
worker-mutating nuclear waste.
Homer, game starts in an hour.
-Don't forget to set your fantasy lineup.
-Thanks, Charlie.
Maybe fracking isn't so bad.
Then say yes to this raise,
this promotion,
and this flannel shirt, which says--
"I'm not screwing you over."
I'm not screwing you over.
No, uh,
(crying)
I'm so proud of you, Papa.
Some folks will tell you
that fracking's no good,
but what they don't tell you is,
hydraulic fracturing creates jobs.
And all those new workers
are gonna want
to spend their earnings
buying what you're selling-- beer.
Authentic Italian food.
Useless left-handed crap.
Magical nonsense.
Expensive toys for grown-ups
they don't open or play with.
Pornography and nachos.
High-quality
Spanish-language programming.
High-quality methamphetamines.
Laundry, homework, pranks,
poop, poop, and poop.
But our water was on fire.
How could you sell fracking
for Mr. Burns?
'Cause I've never gotten
a promotion before.
Once I thought I had,
but it turned out
to be a beautifully-worded firing,
-so judge me all you want.
-I am judging you.
-Good. Judge away.
-Judge, judge, judge.
-Don't care. Don't care.
-Judge, judge...
Pumping frack cash.
It's a gas cash... blast?
Residents of Evergreen Terrace
are undecided
whether to sell
their mineral rights to Mr. Burns.
Mr. Burns is a vampire,
sucking the lifeblood of this town
and lining his coffin with cash.
Oh, Maxine, no one insults me
in a sound bite the way you do.
Oh, Monty,
you're such a sexy little Nosferatu.
Same time tomorrow night?
(chuckles)
I'll bring the oxygen.
-(quietly) Better bring two tanks.
-Hmm?
And so, we see a clear correlation
between industrial hydro compounds
and water table contamination
well outside the...
margin of error.
Mr. Simpson, rebuttal?
(clears throat)
Everyone who signs over
their mineral rights
to Mr. Burns gets $5,000.
5,000 smackers?!
Money is like a job
you don't even have to do!
-(dance music playing)
-(cheering)
-Ay, dinero.
-Signing Stu.
(laughter)
Yeah!
I think my arguments
were more cogent-- bo-hyvik.
What?!
Cogent-- bo-hyvik!
(bird caws)
Mr. Burns, we did it!
Everyone in the neighborhood
sold us their gas rights!
Hmm.
Excellent.
No, no. It's excellent. It's excellent.
Uh, maybe you can help me, Simpson.
You've had a relationship
or two in your life.
(laughing) Well... one.
I have embarked
on a "beneficial friendship"
with a woman with whom
I have nothing in common.
Her opinions are abhorrent to me,
but the passion.
Well, look at these racy texts
she sends me.
(rhythmic clicking)
Oh, baby.
How long can I sustain
this high-wire act
of loathing and lust?
Well, I'm no Carl
when it comes to this stuff,
but I ain't no Lenny, neither.
And I would say...
no matter how much you try
to keep things casual,
someone always gets hurt.
Hmm.
Well, then I must harden my heart
against such an outcome.
I appreciate the counsel, Simpson.
Now, please trap-door yourself out.
Glad I could be of help!
(indistinct chatter)
Do you have the signed gas leases?
Hold on. This feels light.
Ah.
One of these deeds
is missing a signature.
The gas rights transfer form
for 742 Evergreen Terrace
was never signed by...
Marge Simpson.
(gasps)
Marge, why didn't you sign?
Our water was on fire!
I'm sorry, but the law states
that unless every single resident
sells their rights,
Burns can't frack drop one!
ALL: Oh!
Oh, I was counting on that money
to pay for my other calf implant.
MOE: Yuck.
I already felt the pride
of energy independence.
(overlapping crowd chatter)
Marge Simpson,
I'm as mad at you
as you usually are at me!
-(gasps)
-Hmm!
(indistinct chatter)
(wind whistling)
Cheer up, Monty.
All you lost was money,
but what you get is... me.
(cracking)
All I lost was money?
Let me make one thing
perfectly clear.
Our dalliance meant nothing to me!
You were but a sprig of parsley
garnishing my beefsteak.
Now I cast you aside
for the busboys to gnaw upon.
Considered this ill-conceived
affair terminated!
(gasps)
(chuckles)
I played this just perfectly.
HOMER: Oh, yeah, great.
Great, Marge, great work.
Thanks to you, Springfield will never
be a natural gas boomtown,
and like all boomtowns,
it would have lasted forever.
Oh... our water was on fire.
Oh! Was on fire. Was!
I finally got a job I was good at,
and now I have to give it up!
(grunts)
So, you've come begging
not to be fired?
Smithers,
turn my back on this man!
Maximum huff!
Wait, Mr. Burns.
I'm here to man up.
It was all my wife's fault!
(sighs heavily)
Sometimes I think she and I
have nothing in common!
Nothing in common, eh?
Tell me more.
Marge likes sushi.
I like gum that squirts in your mouth.
She's into romantic comedies.
I like movies where there's only
one day a year when murder is legal.
Yup, Marge and I see the world
in totally different ways.
Hmm. Different, exactly.
That's why I had to give my woman
the old heave-ho.
So, you don't miss
that politics lady at all?
Not for one Chinese second.
And I'm sure
she's forgotten all about me.
(both gasp)
HOMER: Killdozers.
Whatever are you doing, man?!
We're tearing down this place
and putting up a recycling center,
slash Native American history museum,
slash condor sanctuary.
(screeches)
Hmm. A project this bloated
and ill thought out
could only be the work
of an angry liberal.
(gasps) Maxine!
My ex is using the thing
I hate most against me--
big government.
(grunts)
-(chatter)
-(camera shutters clicking)
Stop this ribbon cutting!
This is private property!
What's the matter, Mr. Burns?
Never heard of eminent domain?
You're just doing this
to get back at me for dumping you!
That is ridiculous.
(gasps)
The Antonin Scalia bedroom!
It's a National Public Radio
broadcast center now.
Who are you?
I'm Robert Siegel,
and this is All Things Considered.
(theme music playing)
-(groaning)
-Stop laying about, you!
There's work to be done!
(weakly) Or Gravy Thursday.
If that woman thinks
she's been scorned now,
she ain't seen nothing yet!
(clacking)
It's fracking time.
(squeaking)
(whooshing)
(rumbling)
(groaning)
(Bart groaning)
(grunts)
(groans)
Is one of the side effects
of fracking earthquakes?
(voice shaking) Yes!
What are you doing?
You're destroying this neighborhood.
Just like you destroyed my mansion.
I don't know what I ever saw in you,
you planet-ruining monster!
Likewise, you planet-saving succubus!
(metallic rattling)
Homer, turn off that horrible machine!
You don't know anything
about hydraulic fracturing!
You've just been brainwashed
by liberal TV shows
who use fracking
as an easy bad guy,
but it can save this country!
Our... water... was...
on... fire!
Wait.
I finally get what you're saying.
Fracking is great,
but the only place it should ever happen
is in other people's towns!
Hmm.
(grunting)
(grunting nervously)
You always do the right thing...
sort of.
What is he doing?
He was furious at that woman,
now he's embracing her.
He told me himself
they had nothing in common.
Nothing except passion.
-Mm.
-(cracking)
(hearts beating)
I was a fool
to break up with you, Maxine.
I'm sorry I turned your home
into a liberal paradise.
You think we could make us work?
I don't know.
We're pretty different.
But we've got passion,
and as long as we've got that,
our lives will never get boring.
Mmm.
Oh, there's free jazz on Saturdays
at the art museum.
Now they say omega-3 pills
are bad for you.
My sister's dog had puppies.
What kind?
What kind of what?
What kind of dog
does your sister have?
I don't know.
What color drawer pulls
did you want?
Nickel or brushed nickel?
Oh, I wish we'd bought
the more expensive theater tickets.
I'll never see anything in row BB.
There's a sale on lawn furniture
at the Lawns Plus.
Why are all cars black or gray now?
It's like if you see a red one,
it's a big deal.
I'm thinking about
wearing a watch again.
-(crowd murmuring)
-Shh!
Subtitled by B. Everdene