♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
(engine sputters)
Hey, what gives?
You said you wanted to live
in a world without zinc, Jimmy.
Well, now your car
has no battery.
But I promised Betty
I'd pick her up by six.
I better give her a call.
(yawning)
(stuck dial tone)
Sorry, Jimmy.
Without zinc
for the rotary mechanism
there are no telephones.
Dear God.
What have I done?
(clicking)
Think again, Jimmy.
You see, the firing pin
in your gun was made of...
yup... zinc.
Come back, zinc.
Come back!
Come back.
Zinc, come back.
Zinc!
Zinc, zinc!
What?
Oh, it was all a dream.
Thank goodness I still live
in a world of telephones
car batteries, handguns,
and many things
made of zinc.
Gross! He's picking his nose.
(students laughing)
-Hmph!
-(bell ringing)
If anyone wants to learn
more about zinc,
they're welcome to stay.
We can talk about anything.
I'll do your homework
for you.
(groans)
"Chef Lonely Heart's
Soup for One."
One scratch and win,
Apu.
Mrs. Krabappel,
I haven't seen you
since we doubled
our prices.
Still teaching?
Let's see.
One more day at least.
(engine sputtering)
Bingo, bango,
sugar in the gas tank.
Your ex-husband
strikes again.
Mm...
Hmm?
A personal ad?
Why not?
It might be fun.
Kind of a lark.
(phone ringing)
Come on, come on.
Answer the phone.
I need a man!
(loud talking)
Ow, my eyeball!
(laughter)
Enough, people.
People?
All right.
You know, I can wait
just as long as you.
(noise continues)
Knock it off!
Now, boys and girls,
let's welcome
our very special guest,
Ted Carpenter from
the Twirl King Yo-yo Company.
(smattering of applause)
Kids, this is a yo-yo.
Kind of dull, huh?
Not much competition
for a video game...
or is it?
Presenting
the Twirl King Champions!
Mr. Amazing!
Sparkle!
She's beautiful.
Zero gravity!
The Cobra!
These guys must be millionaires.
I'll bet they get
all kinds of girls.
I question the educational
value of this assembly.
Hey, it will be one of
their few pleasant memories
when they're pumping gas
for a living.
♪ This is the dawning
of the age of Aquarius ♪
♪ Age of Aquarius ♪
♪ Aquarius... ♪
(cheering)
Now, for our next stunt,
what do you say
-we get your principal up here?
-No.
(cheering)
Careful now.... Ohh!
That one grazed my ear.
Don't move.
-You could really get hurt.
-Oh.
How much do those yo-yo's cost?
I don't care.
(kids shouting good-byes)
Wow!
Thanks, Sparkle.
Wait...
This isn't you.
That's the old Sparkle.
All right, get your
worthless butts in the van.
We got three more schools to do.
C'mon, let's go, go, go!
(shouting good-byes)
That's your trick?
No. Here's my trick.
Hoowah!
(laughing)
(gasping)
-Whoa!
Thank you.
Marge, come here.
Can you believe it?
Pretty soon, I'll be able
to quit my job
and live off the boy.
What? Name me one person
who's gotten rich
by doing yo-yo tricks.
(thinking)
Donald Trump? No.
Arnold Palmer? No.
Bill Cosby? No.
D'oh!
"After two months at sea,
the Pilgrims were running out
of food and water."
Yes, Nelson?
Did they have any yo-yos?
No, they did not have yo-yos.
"When they landed
at Plymouth Rock,
they were greeted by
the friendly Wompanog Indians."
Did the Indians have yo-yos?
No, they did not have yo-yos!
That's it!
I am sick and tired
of talking about yo-yos.
From now on, I will not
accept any book report
science projects, dioramas,
or anything else on yo-yos,
or yo-yo related topics.
Am I making myself
clear?
Yo.
(laughs)
Hey, Bart,
got any new tricks
for us today?
Just one.
A little something I call
"Plucking the Pickle."
I build up a little steam,
and...
(gasps)
I didn't do it.
Don't worry
about your wee fish, lass.
They're going to a better place.
(toilet flushing)
Bart, that's one month's
detention.
Mrs. Krabappel, we're all upset
by the untimely deaths
of Stinky and Wrinkles
but life goes on.
So, if I could just have
my yo-yo back...
Bart, if I were you,
and you were me,
would you give back
the yo-yo?
Here you go...
just kidding.
Just kidding.
(chuckling)
Well, would you?
Absolutely.
P-hih!
What's eating you,
woman?
Your personal ad said
you wanted a man.
You got yourself
a hum-dinger.
I don't know.
I guess I expected
something different
from your photo.
Don't let my age fool you.
Just because there's a little
snow on the roof...
I forget how the rest
of that goes.
One month's detention.
She'll pay for this.
Yup, there's your problem.
Someone jammed
a Malibu Stacy head down here.
Edna, happy hour
in the teacher's lounge.
Just a sec.
Hmm.
Huh?
"One plus one equals two?"
"Write Edna K. Box 402."
Hmm.
Dear Edna...
I never answered
a personal ad before
but I found yours irresistible.
My name is...
SEXY MALE VOICE:
Woodrow.
I like holding hands
and dinner by candlelight
and oh, yes,
I really hate yo-yos.
Oh, Woodrow!
(yeowling)
Maybe we should
let the dog in.
Marge, dogs love the outdoors.
(whimpering)
MARGE:
I think he needs a doghouse.
Yeah, but what
are ya' gonna do?
I bet we could buy
a nice doghouse for $50.
Marge, you're a tool
of the doghouse makers.
I am not.
Yes, you are.
You've been brainwashed
by all those doghouse
commercials on TV.
I know. I'll build
him a doghouse.
Oh, I don't know.
Don't worry.
I just drew up
a little blueprint.
Let me walk you through it.
This is a door.
He goes through that--
This is a roof.
And this happy character here
is the Sun.
He shines down
on the house, see?
How was detention
today, dear?
Oh, not bad.
I'm starting to get
the hang of the floor-waxer.
Yes!
MRS. KRABAPPEL:
Dear Woodrow,
I must admit I'm intrigued.
You're not like
the other men I've met.
Yeah, I'm the 28th president
of the United States.
But I've had some bad
experiences with these ads.
So, I'd like to learn more about you,
please write back soon.
Here's a photo that will
get your pencil moving.
You've got a date
with the Xerox machine.
(grunting and groaning)
Stupid lumber.
Damn it!
D'oh! I--
Oh, the hell with this!
A fellow came in to the store today,
asked for change for a dollar.
Well, sir, I gave him three
quarters by mistake.
Took me the whole afternoon
to track him down.
Todd, would you like
some mixed vegetables?
Hell no.
(gasping)
What did you say?
I said, I don't want
any damn vegetables.
All right, that's it, young man!
No Bible stories for you
tonight.
(crying)
Weren't you
a little hard on him?
Well, you knew
I had a temper
when you married me.
Ned Flanders
is on the phone.
Oh, if this is about
that stupid quarter again, I...
Hello, Ned.
Sorry to bother you, Reverend Lovejoy,
but I'm kind of in a tizzy...
Our son Todd just told us
he didn't want to eat
his "damn vegetables."
Well, you know
kids and vegetables.
What was it, asparagus?
No, no, Reverend.
The point is he said a bad word.
Oh. Oh, right.
Well, kids usually pick
these things up from someplace.
Find out who's doing it
and uh, direct them to the Bible.
Where in the Bible?
-Uh... page 900.
-But, Rev--
Damn Flanders.
Hey, Lis,
a moment of your time.
Yeah?
Suppose I was writing
a second letter to a girl
and I already used up
my "A" material.
What should I say?
Ooh, could it be
there's a special someone
you're not
telling me about?
Oh please!
-Is it Teri?
-No.
-Is it Sheri?
-No!
Is it that girl
with the lazy eye patch?
No!
Is it that exchange student
Mix-pa?
No! It's not for me.
It's... homework.
Sure it is.
Hey, Bart,
let's do some homework.
(kissing)
(groans)
Golly, Sergeant Carter,
I can't fix your Jeep,
but maybe this
will make it up to you.
(deep baritone)
♪ Galveston, oh, Galveston... ♪
Is this all he watches?
He used to watch
"Davy and Goliath"
but he thought the idea
of a talking dog
was blasphemous.
Hey, Mom, did you save
the love letters Dad sent you?
Of course I saved them.
Well, actually,
there's only one
and it's more
of a love postcard
from some brewery he visited.
HOMER: "Maybe it's
the beer talking, Marge,
"but you've got a butt
that won't quit.
They got these big,
chewy pretzels here..."
(slurring speech)
"...five dollars?!
Get outta here."
Wow, a side of Dad
I've never seen!
(sighs)
Penny for your thoughts,
Miss K.
I was just thinking...
You wouldn't
be interested.
Try me.
Sometimes it helps to talk.
(hawks and spits)
Well, I was just wishing
I could meet a man
who likes the way I look
first thing in the morning
-Laughs at my jokes...
-Uh-huh.
-Can fix my car.
-Oh, yeah.
BART: "Dear Edna, your photo
took my breath away.
WOODROW: "Truly, yours
is a butt that won't quit.
"Yesterday morning,
"I put your picture up
in my garage
to inspire me while I
gapped my spark plugs."
(moans and glugs)
At last,
we've built the mission.
Finally, the villagers
have a place to pray.
♪ Bringing in the sheaves ♪
♪ We shall come rejoicing... ♪
Well, he's not getting it
from his brother
that's for darn sure.
HOMER:
Damn crappy nails!
Super Glue, my butt!
(gasps)
D'oh! You bas--
Hit it! Shot! D'oh!
Homer?
What is it, Flanders?
I'm afraid I have a bone
to pick with you.
Look, if it's about your camcorder,
I lost it, okay?
No, I came to talk to you
about your potty mouth.
What the hell
are you talking about?
Look, Homer, all of us pull
a few boners now and then--
go off half-cocked,
make asses of ourselves.
So, I don't want
to be hard on you but
I just wish you wouldn't curse
in front of my boys.
Oh, come on now, Flanders.
I don't complain about your...
moustache.
What's wrong with my moustache?
Uh, it makes you look like
you got something to hide.
What?
People are talking.
Lots of people.
Okay, Mister, you've
got yourself a deal.
I'll shave off
the soup-strainer
if you give the sailor talk
the old heave-ho, okay?
Aye, aye... Admiral Butthead.
ANNOUNCER:
We now return to
"Two for Tunisia"
on Colorization Theater.
Ah, my love.
A million poets could try
for a million years
and still describe but
three-eighths of your beauty.
Whoa, slow down, Frenchy.
This stuff is gold.
Wow! "A million poets working
for a million years..."
You're so lucky.
When are you
going to meet him?
First, I ask him
to send a photo.
If he's got everything
where it should be
I'm reeling him in.
(laughing)
Strap on your skates, Gordie.
You're going in.
Hey, Marge, do you want
to hear something funny?
Flanders thinks
I swear too much.
(giggling)
Marge, you're not laughing.
Well, you know,
maybe he's right.
Well, what a surprise.
Marge sticks up
for Flanders.
Can we have
one conversation
where you don't bring up
your hero Ned Flanders?
Actually Homer,
you brought up Ned Flanders.
Look, we're past that.
Marge!
Maybe I do curse a little,
but that's the way God made me,
and I'm too old to stop now.
No, you're not.
When my father got
out of the Navy,
he used to curse
a blue streak.
It almost cost him his job
as a baby photographer.
So my Mom put a swear jar
in the kitchen.
Every time he said
a bad word,
he put in a quarter.
What do you think?
Well, Marge,
self-improvement has always
been a passion of mine.
Bring on the swear jar.
Do I have to pay
if I hit my hand with a hammer?
Yes, Homer.
-What if I catch on fire?
-No, Homer.
What if I see something
really weird in the sky?
Yes, Homer.
-What about when we snuggle?
-Hmm... that's okay.
MISS KRABAPPEL:
"Dear Woodrow, it's time for us to meet.
"Why don't we go out to dinner?
And afterward, we can go to
my apartment for some home cookin'."
Huh?
Ay, caramba!
"Hungrily yours, Edna."
Well, she's dangled
on the line long enough.
It's time to boat this bass.
"When I read your letters, I feel
as if you are right here watching me."
-Bart! Eyes down.
-Yes, Ma'am.
BART:
"Edna, every second until we meet
"stabs me like
a thousand needles.
WOODROW: "Join me at
the Gilded Truffle this Saturday at 8:00.
"Perhaps later
we will smooch up a storm.
Sexily yours, Woody."
(laughing)
(Bart sighing)
Huh?
(crying)
Oh, I can't help but feel
partly responsible.
-Homer, that was a 20.
-Da--
Oh, you son of a--
Homer, I owe you one, buddy.
No sooner had I shaved off
the old cookie duster
than a lady cast me
in a commercial.
I tell ya' the way these checks
keep coming in-- it's almost criminal.
You dirty bast--
What do you think,
Lisa?
How's the dog
supposed to get in?
Well, he just goes...
Ohh!
(snoring)
(screams)
(sighing)
Oh, Woodrow,
how could you stand me up?
Mrs. K., whoever this guy is,
you don't need him.
There are plenty
of good men around.
Name one.
What's wrong
with Principal Skinner?
Seymour? Hmph.
Let's just say his mommy
won't let him out to play.
What about Coach Fortner?
Glug, glug, glug, glug...
Wow.
What about Groundskeeper Willy?
Ugh! I'm not even gonna tell
you what that guy's into.
Bart, you are the closest
thing to a man in my life.
And that's so depressing,
I think I'm going to cry.
(sobbing)
(groaning)
Aah..!
Oh, fudge... that's broken.
Fiddle-dee-dee.
That will require
a tetanus shot.
I'm not going to swear
but I am going
to kick this doghouse down!
(ranting)
Dad, this is not
a commentary on your skills,
but we bought you
a new doghouse.
Where'd you get the money?
There was more than enough
in the swear jar,
and if you look inside the doghouse,
there's a little surprise.
Maggie.
Oh, cute.
No, behind her.
(gasps)
Beer!
How did you know?
Where's Maggie?
There's Maggie!
(makes raspberries
on her belly)
Mom, this is a little
ahead of schedule
but I need help
with my love life.
Oh, my special little guy
has a sweetheart.
(snickering)
I knew it!
Alright Bart,
who's your girlfriend?
Mrs. Krabappel.
-Hmm.
(whistles)
Bart, this is your teacher?
I should start going
to parent's night.
(growls)
Homer!
Bart, you did a
very cruel thing.
Boy, you've got to go
to your teacher
and tell her
the truth.
No, Homer. The truth
would humiliate her.
Oh Marge, I only said it because I thought
that's what you wanted to hear.
Maybe we should
write her another letter
One that says good-bye,
but let's her feel loved.
Step aside, everyone.
Sensitive love letters
are my specialty.
"Dear Baby,
Welcome to Dumpville.
Population: you."
We'll all help.
"Though I'll be inoculating
babies in Kampuchea,
my heart will
always be with you."
That sucks.
How about "crocodiles
bit off my face"?
That's disgusting,
and besides,
when a woman loves a man,
it doesn't matter that
a crocodile bit off his face.
I may hold you
to that, Marge.
Okay, okay. "I cannot see you
for the next five years,
for I will be farming
the ocean floor."
(buzzes)
"I must finish
this letter quickly,
for I have only
four minutes to live."
Three simple words:
"I am gay."
Homer, for the last time,
I am not putting that in.
"And anytime I hear
the wind blow,
it will whisper the name...
Edna."
Oh, that's very good, Lisa.
"P.S.: I am gay."
(both groaning)
How shall we end it?
How about, "With a love that
will echo through the ages."
-Aww.
-Ooh!
That's sweet.
Homer, you old
honey dripper.
Why, you little...
hee, hee.
Huh?
Wait!
WOODROW:
"Dearest Edna, I must leave you.
"Why? I cannot say.
"Where? You cannot know.
"How I will get there?
"I haven't decided yet.
"But one thing
I can tell you,
"any time I hear
the wind blow,
it will whisper
the name... Edna."
Ohh..!
(humming)
Bart, it's such
a nice day today,
let's have detention
outside.
It's a date.
(hockey arena organ playing)
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.