There's something very,
very weird about this place.
Even the seagulls
have a New England accent.
Why did we vacation here?
It was on a list
of top ten places to see
before you mysteriously
disappear.
Fool.
This whole contest was a ruse.
What the...?
You are here to be sacrificed
to an evil god
from the ocean depths.
- SpongeBob?
- No!
The eternal lord of horror,
Cthulhu.
What the...?!
Wait just a minute!
I was promised
an eating contest,
and by the ancient law
of the flyer,
you have to provide me with one.
Very well.
An eating contest
against the monstrous Cthulhu?
To him, the Great Barrier Reef
is just an average barrier reef.
Well, my dad
didn't eat breakfast.
How you doing, Cthu?
Shut up, okay?
Just shut up.
I need to take a walk,
that's all.
I'll be fine.
I win. And I get
to name the prize.
Fine.
I'll give you whatever you want.
Immortal life? Whale watching
where you actually see a whale?
I know exactly what I want.
Oh, man.
Ooh, ink sac.
Now for a word from our late,
beloved Mapple founder,
Steve Mobs.
Hello.
And stop.
Since my unfortunate passing,
if things have gone
as I've planned,
Mapple is now
a trillion-dollar company,
Roseanne has come and gone
like a summer storm
and a less exciting version
of me has taken my place.
I'm wearing your pants, Steve.
And now I'm here to introduce
the new Myphone Ultima,
which comes
in the colors black...
slate gray...
and that's it.
The time has come.
Commence operations.
Can't they see you?
They see nothing.
This is too easy.
For you. You just look
at the monitor.
Lenny? My phone says
that there's spores
from outer space
landing all around us.
Well, my phone says there are
divorced moms in my area
that want to meet me.
Oh, great, an homage
to Body Snatchers,
which in itself was a rip-off
of The Thing.
This will be the last word
I ever say, C minus!
I want to return
this comic book.
The dialogue sounded forced
when I read it aloud.
I will help you, but first,
you are in danger.
You can crash at my pod,
I mean pad.
No one says pad anymore.
Run!
Dad, I'm worried.
Everyone's turning
into a zombie.
Thank God you're okay.
Mom! Something's wrong.
There is no escape.
We are all-powerful.
Boy, Maggie, you're carrying
a lot of anger towards Mom.
Chief, Chief, space plants
are eating everyone.
You're telling me.
Don't feel bad.
He was a lousy chief.
You know, my feelings
haven't dissolved yet, Lou.
Now, kids,
that's just air escaping.
You cannot stop us.
It is really
just a matter of...
How comes aliens
never use contractions?
We think it is scary.
It is why we call Jerry's Deli
the Deli of Jerry.
Conifer down.
I'm not a plant!
Prove it. Name the roster
of the Glasgow soccer club.
I don't, I don't know.
Is there a Rooney?
There's always a Rooney.
Bart, dystopian movies have
taught me two things.
A, you can make a four-part
movie from a three-part book,
and B, there is no hope.
So I'm saying good-bye
to you now, Bart.
Good-bye, sister.
The last sound you hear
will be...
You don't win friends
with salad
with salad...
Congratulations,
fortunate Earth-being.
Welcome to your new paradise.
- Where are we?
- We're on a planet
in what you incorrectly call
the Crab Nebula.
You live
in the Crab Nebula. You.
Why would you kill me
and then bring me here?
We didn't kill you.
We have saved you.
When you were absorbed on Earth,
your consciousness
was transferred here
to this utopia.
Well, my daughter will be
very happy
living with you green beans.
She's a vegetarian.
Murderer.
Just kidding.
Have a piece of my ass.
So wait, wait, wait.
We're all pod people?
I'm afraid you were
already pod people.
What are you talking about?
iPod people, phone checkers,
tablet gazers.
Never lifting your petals
to see the sun.
Yes. Yes. This is perfect.
A sci-fi story
with a happy ending.
Now let us brag some more.
We are many,
but we move as one.
Finding out the best
of each other.
Giving the love
that lets us go on.
Where'd you get those?
We just found them
wrapped under that guy.
It's what I do, man.
How you doing?
Herb Tannenbaum.
- He's waking up.
- Yes.
Is there anything
punching can't do?
It can't set a clock.
What's going on?
Where are we?
Who did this to us?
The last thing I remember
is crashing a sleepover
at Milhouse's.
I got to work.
So spend the night here.
But I'm not invited.
You think I was invited
on the Toledo Mud Hens team bus?
When I was asked to leave, my
left boob suddenly popped out.
That was a game-changer.
Then somebody
mysteriously sent
a case of orange drink,
which we drank.
You guys passed out,
and my first thought
was call the police.
But even heroes fall.
Lisa?
I'm not Lisa.
I'm Penelope.
Whassup?
Seriously, I want to know.
I'm the one
who brought you here
after drugging
your SunnyD with Special K
as in ketamine.
You K'd our D? You're crazy.
Crazy, you say?
Crazy.
Crazy!
Who are you calling crazy?
I'm not that loud.
I'm gonna belt you.
With a brassy Broadway tune.
You'll be trapped
Trapped like rats
No one knows
where you're ats
You'll eat my shorts
then you'll have a cow
I'm gonna kick you now
Applaud or die.
- You die, boys.
- What? Why?
Not one of you said encore.
But I think encores are
a ridiculous tradition.
Just sing your songs and go.
More pancakes, Lisa?
Pancakes are meaningless.
Life is meaningless.
Marge, Lisa's being unusual.
And where's Bart?
Oh, yes, the Simpson boy.
He called. He's staying with
the Milhouse for an extra day.
And the great thing
about boys is
that nothing bad
can ever happen to them.
Come on, Milhouse,
put your brain into it.
The door isn't even scratched.
Oh, we were trying
to break the door?
Okay, I got a plan.
First, Milhouse,
gnaw through your ankle.
I will,
but I'm allergic to myself.
I swear, if you say
one more wimpy thing...
Not my Gloria Vanderbilt
glasses.
They were on the cover
of Women's Health.
Lisa's wearing a dress.
All right, ya little beasties.
Are ye ready for a trip
to the Scottish Die-lands?
Just let yourselves out,
but beware the Beast!
Ah, isn't that cute?
She learned an accent
from Groundskeeper Willie.
Not that cute.
Ay caramba!
Wish I could burn
the calories off that easily.
You've got body issues.
It's time to recycle,
you stupid boys.
Careful, Lisa.
If you keep yelling like that,
you'll get vocal polyps
like Adele.
Please wear one of my bones
around your neck...
You missed.
What happened to you?
You know what you did!
Well, well, Little Miss Perfect.
I'm sure somebody changed this,
but I don't care.
You know, I never feel more like
a trademark corporate spokesman
than when I wake up
in an empty bed.
You can never make me feel
as good as this.
Oh, no!
You ruined Lisa's life
and on that day,
the Beast was born!
One American creates
this much garbage in one day.
Oh, just kill me.
Don't teach me.
I'm your brother.
If you have a great speech
to save yourself,
now would be the time.
I'm rooting for ya.
Lis, please forgive me.
I'm your big brother.
I'll always be there for you.
When your boyfriend dumps you,
I'll take you drinking
and tell you what a jerk he was.
When he takes you back,
I'll tell you he's great
and go to games with him.
I'll humanize
your campaign biography.
Am I reaching you?
It worked.
I'm back.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Why'd you do it, sweetie?
Sometimes, Mom, a woman gets
pushed so far, she just snaps.
You know how that feels,
don't you? Don't you?
No, not at all.
Where's Dad?
Tied up in the trunk of the car.
How am I supposed to know
the day we got married
falls on our wedding
anniversary?
Always wanted to be a paper boy.
You know, you're cute this way.
Have a perfume sample.
So, Smithers, what do you think?
I'll rejuvenate the elderly
using untested dinosaur DNA.
It could make me a fortune or
fill the world with monsters.
It could make me a fortune.
Why do you need doors?
You could just
fly over the wall.
- Damn it.
- I hope Grandpa's happy
in this new retirement home.
I'm sure he's happier here
is what we'll always say
about old people
no matter where we put them.
There's something weird
about this place...
that doesn't show up
on any map.
Oh, Lisa, you're always
so suspicious.
Welcome to Geriatric Park
where our motto is,
no further questions.
Here at Geriatric Park,
we combine
speculative theories
with untested technologies
to give our seniors
a better life.
Possible side effects include
back spikes, protective plates,
giant claws, fear of asteroids,
being a precursor
to our modern birds,
a second tail brain, loss
of ears and increased libido.
If you are currently egg-laying
or expect to be egg-laying,
consult your paleontologist.
Now, meet your Jurassic
perked-up loved ones.
They were old
They were sad
And their joints all hurt
Now they're here
And they're glad
They've hit pay dirt
Geriatric Park
It's so, so safe
Nothing can go wrong
Can go wrong, can go wrong
Can go wrong...
Abe, I've never seen you
so vibrant and alive.
Well, I don't like to complain.
Wow, you have changed.
But they keep it
a little cold here.
Anything for you, Dad.
Don't want to read.
I'm on vacation.
What's happening?
Someone has raised
the temperature.
Let's take a look
at the microscopic level
with the peephole
and the twisty thing
and the little slide of glass.
You even taste disappointing.
Half of that taste is you.
Dang it.
You can't kill me.
I'm your creator,
for flaving out loud.
Credit hog.
You were listed
in the footnotes. Oy.
Oh, we're saved.
It's my mom.
In the best mood
we've ever seen her.
It's raining.
The old people will head
to the TV room
and watch
The Weather Channel.
That's not rain.
It's Grampa.
Lisa, no!
Sorry, I just believe in the
ultimate, basic goodness of people.
Grampa, I don't think
you want to hurt me.
You just want me
to see you as a person,
not some strange, scary monster
we call a senior citizen.
Grampa, I want
to hear your opinion
about everything.
She's making
the ultimate sacrifice.
Getting him started.
Grampa.
I still love you.
All they wanted
was to be cherished.
They've even learned how to get
respect from the orderlies.
I don't care
if you haven't finished.
I'm off the clock.
And once again, the true
monster, the soulless CEO,
escapes unscathed.
Oy. Too rich for my blood.
That was a lovely visit.
Although, I could've done
without some
of the decapitations.
Mom, where's the pilot?
Virgin Air I'm not.