[birds chirping]
Oh, man, these beauties
would diaper up real nice.
[Homer singsongy]
Dad!
We've got wonderful news.
It's a gift we've been hoping
to give you for years.
You're finally
off the wait list.
A better room opened up.
[gasps] Hot diggity!
Not diggity.
This room is tiny.
How's it better?
Better for us. It's cheaper.
Much cheaper.
Wouldn't you rather
we spend that money
on your grandkids' education?
No! They're dumb as dirt.
Look on the bright side.
You're right next
to the ice machine.
[ice dispensing loudly]
And the pill machine.
[pills dispensing loudly]
And how about
this beautiful view
they painted on
the cinder block wall?
It's too bright!
And what about all my stuff?
You'll just have to
get rid of some of it.
And once you're used to
this smaller space,
it'll ease your transition
to a cozy pine box.
Pine? You promised me
black walnut.
Oh, of course, of course.
Only the best for my dad.
What about this shoe tree?
Does it bring you joy?
It makes me furious!
I'm keeping it.
Whoa, Grampa, what's all this?
Eh, that's just
all my old war stuff.
Can I have it?
Oh, it warms my heart to
know my precious memories
are going to someone
who will cherish them.
So how much will you give me
for all this crap?
Well, most of these medals
are for cowardice.
Does this thing even work?
Mm, four, three, two...
Nothing.
I'll give you
a hundred dollars store credit.
A hundred dollars? Awesome!
No switchblades
or cyanide pills.
[sputters] Damn it.
Eh, nah.
Mm-mm. [scoffs]
Mm-mm. Nope.
[scoffs]
[groans, scoffs]
Ooh!
Army comic book about "VD"?
Why wouldn't I want
to catch Valentine's Day?
Oh, my God, are you there?
It's me, Margaret.
[angelic choir sings]
- Is that...
- You better believe it.
A human brain.
My life up to now
has been merely a prelude.
Today a prank king
becomes a prank god.
I want to buy your brain!
[heavy metal version of
"The Simpsons Theme" playing]
♪ ♪
[beeping]
[tires squealing]
[cat yowls]
[all exclaim, scream]
[laughing]
So you see, Comptroller Atkins,
we have put
your new funding to use.
We've redone the cafeteria floor
and the ceiling,
and we've added
exciting new menu options.
Indeed.
Today the children are enjoying
a panoply of nutrition.
Split pea soup, clam chowder,
both varietals.
Bart, are you really
gonna do it?
Guys, it's me, the Bartman.
[chuckles]
This is happening.
Venison chili, beef bourguignon,
a vibrant Indian curry...
And best of all,
brain under glass!
[students gasping, gagging]
[Skinner] Bart, you did
far more damage today
than just ruined
some administrators' suits.
We may be wearing clothes
from the lost and found,
but you are truly lost.
Today you traumatized
scores of students,
rendered the cafeteria
uninhabitable for weeks.
And worst of all, worst of all,
you-you broke Willie.
Chunks.
So many chunks.
What do you have to say
for yourself?
I regret nothing.
I'll gladly accept whatever book
you throw at me,
because there's no way
I could ever live with myself
if I hadn't done this today.
So give me all the F's,
send me to juvie
or even kill me,
because I'm already immortal.
And when I do die...
Oh, shut up.
Four weeks' detention
and you're not going
on the trip
to Colonial Shelbyville.
You will be confined
to the detention trailer
while other students
delight in learning
how bricks were once made.
Um, Principal Skinner, if I may.
I believe we can deal
with Bart's behavior
in a more constructive way.
Turn this into
a learning opportunity.
[Chalmers]
It's not a learning opportunity.
It's a punishing opportunity.
The boy should suffer.
He brought
a human brain to school.
Exactly. And I think he should
bring it to school every day.
Learn to take care of it,
journal his experience,
gain a sense of
[in slow motion]
responsibility.
No, no, please don't do this!
I'm begging you!
Pale skin, sweaty lip,
twitchy eye.
Now, that's suffering.
Ms. Peyton, make it so.
[Skinner and Chalmers laughing]
[groans]
Oh!
My greatest prank
has become homework.
For the next two weeks,
everyone is responsible
for the care and protection
of a fragile and helpless egg.
Or in Bart's case, a brain.
[students]
Ew!
[groans] I don't want to lug
this thing everywhere I go.
I had my fun for five minutes,
and now I want
to move on with my life.
And that's parenthood.
Aw, man, how do I even know
this thing's mine?
Um, I'm going out
for candy cigarettes.
Be right back, slugger.
Be sure to keep your
caregiver journal up to date,
because that's
what you'll be graded on.
[groans] Using a human brain
for homework?
That's the stupidest thing
I've ever heard.
[Bart's brain] You know,
Bart, I'm your brain, too,
and I can help you study
all your subjects.
Shut up, stupid, or I'll go back
to sniffing permanent markers!
[Bart's brain]
I'll be good.
♪ ♪
[over TV]
♪ The Itchy and Scratchy Show. ♪
Hey, Bart, do you really think
Itchy and Scratchy
is appropriate
for a developing mind?
It's not a baby.
It's a glop of gunk
in a jar of goo.
Your baby journal's
pretty empty.
Are you sure this isn't
your second fake kid?
[laughing]
Oh, this sucks.
I need some me time.
I'm going to Milhouse's
to watch reaction videos
to reaction videos.
Your teacher wouldn't like
you leaving your baby all alone.
Unless you get a sitter.
Last minute? I'll never find
someone on such short notice.
Unless...
Uh, Dad, would you watch
your grandson tonight?
[scoffs] No. I told you
to get rid of it, remember?
Oh, come on, please?
I need some me time.
Well, I guess I could give it
the same love
and attention I gave you
when you were a baby.
I'm sorry, Homer.
I'm not accepting organs
as payment.
Anymore.
Nah, it's just my kid's brain.
They grow up so fast.
Guys, I just found out I'm next
on the list for a new liver!
- [cheering] - Yay!
- All right!
Then let's give the old liver
one last night
he'll never forget.
Set 'em up, Moe.
[chanting]
One last night!
- One last night!
- [Barney exclaims]
[upbeat video game music
playing]
[video game announcer]
Atomic wedgie!
Oh, it feels so good
to get out of the house
and away from
that stupid needy brain.
Am I right?
I'm enjoying being a Dad.
I can fix the mistakes
my parents made with me.
[video game announcer]
Player two loses.
[frustrated shout]
I'm a failure because of you!
[video game announcer]
Bonus humiliation.
Defile him.
Aw, kind of reminds me
of my little guy.
Uh... [stammers]
not that I care or anything.
Boys, I made you
a healthy snack,
roasted cauliflower.
[Bart]
Aw, look at him there.
So cute on that plate.
Maybe I should get home.
Sweet.
More roastie-collies for me.
Oh, where is Dad with my brain?
They should be home by now.
[car door closes outside]
Ugh, finally.
It's about time,
you good-for-nothing!
Relax, Marge.
The baby's fine.
Oh, there you are.
Oh, my sweet little precious...
- [screams] Pickled eggs!
- [glass shatters]
Where's my brain?!
Oh, must've gotten mixed up.
Two jars.
[chuckles]
We were making 'em kiss.
He's too young for kissing.
I got to go find him.
What happened to that brain
my dad had?
Well, years of drinking,
not to mention
all that nuclear stuff,
and, uh, I don't think it was
all that great to begin with.
The one in the jar.
Oh, that. Oh. [chuckles]
I left that in the alley
for the raccoons.
They'll eat tonight. [chuckles]
- [gasps] No!
- [raccoons chittering]
[whimpers]
[sighs]
Huh?
Nicotine beef jerky?
I know who took you.
[chewing noisily]
I'm so jerked-up.
I feel like
I smoked a whole cow.
Let's mess up this brain.
[Bart]
Leave it alone!
That's my brain!
After we blow it up,
you can have the biggest chunk.
This isn't some frog
where you can put a firecracker
in its butt.
It's a living thing,
and it's my job
to take care of it
and teach it to do
cool stuff like, um,
paintball and-and
pooping in jack-o'-lanterns.
So hands off my brain!
Okay, okay.
You can have
your stupid head cheese.
Don't worry.
I'm taking you home.
I wonder if
anyone will ever love me
the way he loves that brain.
Look, man, I'm gonna
take better care of you.
You're the only brain I've got.
You need a name, bud.
Wait. Buddy.
Perfect! 'Cause you're my buddy.
Also I don't want to think
about this any harder.
[Bart]
Thursday, May 14th.
Buddy and I had
quite the adventure tonight.
I realized he's more than
just some dumb prank
or a homework assignment.
He's a badass like me.
- [fingers snap]
- Garçon!
Another high chair
for my associate here.
[groans]
You brought your jar friend.
Oh, I get it.
Buddy's a little different.
But he's my responsibility.
Plus he's pretty cool.
Well, uh, maybe he can be
under the table.
Whoa! Buddy's my plus-one.
Would you rather me
bring Milhouse?
No, no, no, no, no.
No one said Milhouse.
Simpsons, a-welcome.
Oh, my favorite a-family.
A-Homer, a-Marge, a-Lisa,
a-Maggie, a-Bart, a-brain.
A-brain?!
[praying in Latin]
It's okay, it's okay.
It's just a school project.
Good a-news.
A table, she just open up
in a-private dining room.
[winded]
You can... go into...
[panting]
My pasta's cold.
Everything's cold!
Ugh, this brain business
will not be good for Bart
if he keeps it up.
Oh, come on, think of all the
worse stuff he could be doing.
Or all the worse stuff
he's done.
He named it!
And I think he gave it
a bite of tiramisu.
[sighs]
This is different for Bart.
What if he becomes
the town weirdo?
Oh, weirdos aren't
what they used to be.
They start computer companies
or own the Las Vegas Raiders.
Or become serial killers.
But still, his odds are
at least two out of three.
Children label each other.
Bart's in danger of becoming
"The Brain Boy."
You worry too much.
Remember when you thought
Lisa was going to hell
because she was a vegetarian?
I still think that.
Excellent work
on your egg projects, class.
And your parenting journals
were really inspired.
An A-plus? I can't believe it.
I've never gotten one of those.
I thought those were just
for suck-wads like Martin.
Okay, everybody,
you did a great job,
so it's time
to turn in your eggs.
Whoa, hold on there.
I am not giving you Buddy.
Well, one of the hardest parts
of parenting
is watching your child move on.
To be Willy's breakfast.
[laughing]
Your brain can have a home
on a shelf
in the school science lab.
[grunts] Buddy hates science.
He's like me.
He's into MeatCanyon videos
and doing wrestling moves
on the dog
and pouring Red Bull
on pancakes!
Bart, it might be healthy
for you
to take a break from Buddy.
And it might be healthy for you
to have your own kid
and not live through us!
I never should've told you
that we were trying!
Don't you worry. It'll work out.
It's only been three months.
Give it time.
Ah, wifeless shopping,
where all the meat is nuggets
and the produce section
doesn't exist.
Ooh, the candy aisle.
Formerly known as cereal.
[humming happily]
I don't care if he is
Milhouse's best friend.
He's just weird.
And not the kind
with "a diagnosis"
that we have to like now.
My JJ says that he talks
to the brain
when no one's looking.
My little Seymour says the kids
all call him "Brain Boy"
behind his back.
Hmm. I wonder
who they're talking about.
Moleman?
Well, whatever
they're calling him,
I don't want Bart Simpson
around my son.
No surprise to me that Bart
Simpson has become a weirdo.
[whispering]
When I had him in second grade,
he ate a booger.
I hear Bart shares his bed
with that brain.
Puts a little sleep mask on it.
It's my fault, girls.
I should've noogied him more,
knuckled some sense into him.
He had potential, but I guess
he's just the town freak now.
[sadly]
Haw-haw.
[humming a tune]
[panting] Marge, you were right.
Everyone in the store
is calling Bart "Brain Boy."
It's already started
with the yentas.
It won't be long before
it spreads to the slaggards!
That's the whole rest
of the town!
Bart is lost.
He won't be known by his name
but by his thing.
Like Comic Book Guy
or Crazy Cat Lady
or Professor Pocket Pool.
Mmm. Mmm.
At least that professor
has lifetime tenure.
Bart's gonna be unemployable.
Mom, Dad, I think
I have a suggestion.
[screams]
Little Miss Know-It-All!
I watched
this nature documentary
that may apply to us.
When a chimp
starts acting strangely,
if it doesn't stop the behavior,
the tribe will
savagely attack it,
leaving it scarred
and isolated forever.
I knew it.
We need to protect
my special little chimp
from the cruel people
in this town who would shun him.
Yes, we must be the loving
parents who keep him locked up.
[Marge hushed]
Open the door quietly.
[whispering]
You know how squeaky it is.
I told you to oil it.
I'm not an architect.
Your stage whispers
are too loud.
Where are you guys going?
Bart! We, um...
We're going to church.
Why didn't you wake me up?
Uh, you hate church.
The itchy pants, the big book
of stuff that never happened.
We thought maybe you'd like
to skip it this week.
As a reward.
Uh, for being so normal.
[Homer chuckles nervously]
This is about Buddy, isn't it?
You're ashamed
to be seen with me.
- Of course not.
- No!
Why would we be ashamed
of our son and his BFF,
a jar of human remains?
Look, sweetie,
why don't you just
make yourself
some Red Bull pancakes,
put on cartoons,
and we'll be back
before you know it.
Go. Go, go, go, go.
[door closes]
"...two oxen, five he-goats,
"five lambs
of the first year, this..."
[quietly]
It's so boring.
But finally some peace
away from Brain Boy.
I hate to say this,
but you're right.
My jaw is unclenched
for the first time in weeks.
[sighing heavily]
[Bart]
Sorry I'm late, everyone!
- Good to see ya.
- [congregation gasps]
Don't mind us. Just gonna sit
with my loving family.
That's the Brain Boy.
It's so gross and wrinkled.
Don't look at him, JJ.
Bart is troubled. Mmm.
So, what episode of Jesus
are we on today?
Is he still talking about
not judging people?
You know, loving your brother?
- Or your son?
- [congregation groaning]
Ugh, Bart, stop it!
This is enough!
Yeah, this isn't just
some little quirk
like wearing a fedora
or being a Libertarian.
You got a disgusting brain
in a greasy jar.
[scoffs] My family.
You're the ones who always said
you'd love me no matter what.
Unconditionally!
This was
an unforeseen condition!
[gasps] Oh, wait.
I didn't mean that.
Too late, Mom.
Yes, I have a brain in a jar.
So what?
Sideshow Mel has
a human bone in his hair
and nobody talks about that.
For your information, weirdo,
this is the femur of a kangaroo!
It was given to me
by Yahoo Serious!
Go ahead, laugh and point at me.
Call me Brain Boy. I don't care.
I have a friend
who will never judge me,
who's always been there for me:
this brain!
He gets me,
'cause we're one in the same:
badasses who don't play
by society's rules.
We're the Bartmen.
Me and my best pal!
Corbin Everly?
Who's Corbin Everly?
Hold on.
He was a local tax accountant
who donated his body to science
hoping it could benefit
the world after his passing.
So Buddy's nothing like me?
He's not some rude, crude,
prankin' dude
with the freaky fresh 'tude?
He was just some guy
named Corbin?
Oh, maybe I shouldn't have been
sloshing him all over town.
Mm. I feel bad for Bart.
No boy wants his brain
to turn out to be a nerd.
Mom, I don't think I want to be
the Brain Boy anymore.
Oh, sweetie.
I'm sorry we weren't more
supportive during this phase.
You hear that?
It was just a phase!
♪ It's been a long day ♪
♪ Without you, my friend ♪
♪ And I'll tell you
all about it ♪
♪ When I see you again ♪
♪ We've come a long way ♪
♪ From where we began ♪
♪ Oh, I'll tell you
all about it ♪
♪ When I see you again ♪
♪ When I see you again... ♪
Oh, my goodness,
it's the brain of Corbin Everly!
Oh, where have you been,
old chum?
Oh, oh, let's never fight again.
[scoffs] What a weirdo.
♪ Oh, I'll tell you
all about it ♪
♪ When I see you again. ♪
♪ ♪
Captioning sponsored by
20th CENTURY FOX TELEVISION
and FOX BROADCASTING COMPANY
and TOYOTA.
Captioned by Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Mom, this is stupid.
I don't want to do this.
No, we're doing this
because I support you
unconditionally.
[snake hisses]
Maybe we should
just get ice cream.
Shh!