♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
Well, Edna, for a school
with no Asian kids,
I think we put on a pretty
darn good science fair.
Go-go ray?
Allow me to demonstrate.
Dah!
What the...
(laughing)
Ahh!
Can't... stop... doing...
The Monkey.
(go-go music playing)
(laughing)
I'm disrupting
the learning process,
and I love it!
(laughs)
First prize.
LISA: First prize.
Why are you saying that?
Just screwing
with your mind.
(chuckling)
Homer, I want you
to encourage Lisa
with her science fair project.
Yeah, syrup is better
than jelly.
I've grown
a futuristic tomato
by fertilizing it
with anabolic steroids.
The kind that help
our Olympic athletes
reach new peaks of excellence?
The very same.
I think this tomato
could wipe out world hunger.
More tomato?
CHILDREN:
Yes, please.
Where's your science
fair project, boy?
I thought I'd investigate
the effects
of cigarette smoking on dogs.
(coughing)
(barks weakly)
Bart, don't give
the dog cigarettes.
(yawns)
Well...
time to go to work.
Little do they know
I'm ducking out early
to take the Duff Brewery tour.
Roll in at 9:00,
punch out at 5:00.
That's the plan.
(chuckles)
They don't suspect a thing.
Well, off to the plant.
Then to the Duff Brewery.
Uh-oh.
Did I say that
or just think it?
I got to think of a lie fast.
Homer, are you going
to the Duff Brewery?
Aah!
"If the plant ye wish to flee,
go to sector 7-B."
(screams)
(hisses)
"To overcome
the spider's curse,
simply quote a bible verse."
Uh... thou shalt not...
Oh...
Hey, that looks
like Princess Di.
(hard thud)
Aw, wait, it's just
a pile of rags.
Oh, Bart, I forgot
my math book.
Would you hold
this for me, please?
(as Curly)
Soitenly.
Nyuck, nyuck, nyuck.
(humming)
Whoop. Shoe's untied.
Over, under,
in and out.
That's what shoe
tying's all about.
(humming)
Huh?
Noooo!
(laughter)
Bart!
(burping)
Welcome to the Duff brewery.
Now I'm sure all of you
have heard the rumors
that a batch of Duff
was contaminated
with strychnine.
GROUP:
Strychnine?
That's news to me.
Are you sure?
Well, everyone's
talking about it.
It was even on CNN
last night.
CNN?
Oh...
Well, it's not true.
Let's go!
Now here's one of our favorite
Duff Beer commercials
from the early 1950s.
Only Duff fills your Q-zone
with pure beer goodness.
So drink up...
and up...
and up.
Duff Beer,
Proud sponsors of
"Amos 'n' Andy."
We're proud of all
of our Duff commercials,
but here's a very special
one from 1960.
Well, I would suggest,
Mr. Vanocur,
that if you knew
the president,
that that was probably
just a facetious remark.
ANNOUNCER: And now
a word from our sponsor.
I would like to take
this opportunity
to express my fondness
for Duff Beer.
(crowd cheering)
I'd also like
to express my fondness
for that particular beer.
(crowd murmuring)
The man never drank
a Duff in his life.
And here we have Duff,
Duff Lite,
and our newest flavor,
Duff Dry.
What does the future
hold for Duff?
Let's just say we've got
a few ideas up our sleeve.
-Like what?
-Um...
I'd rather not
get into it right now.
-Why not?
-All right,
we don't have any ideas
for the future.
-We got nothing. Happy?
-No.
(sobbing)
Mom, Bart wrecked
my project
and the science fair's
in three days.
Hmm.
Well, I've got an idea.
Why don't you
run a hamster
through a maze?
Help me.
Help me!
(evil chuckle)
What's so funny?
Oh... uh...
I was just thinking
of a joke I saw on "Herman's Head".
(insincere chuckle)
Mmm.
Now this is the most
important man on the tour.
He's in charge
of quality control.
Fine. Fine. Mouse. Fine.
Mouse. Rat. Fine.
Syringe. Fine.
Nose. Fine.
Let me just say, you're doing
a great job, Phil.
Hey, thanks a lot.
That makes it all worthwhile.
HOMER: Mmm...
Gummi beer.
Hey, Barney, I think
you've had enough.
Are you crazy?
We still haven't tried
Raspberry Duff,
Lady Duff,
Tartar Control Duff...
(groans)
Barney, give me your keys.
You're too drunk
to drive.
I'm fine.
Okay. You leave me
no option.
Ow! What was that for?
I'm trying
to knock you out!
Ow!
Cut it out!
All right, here.
Take the keys.
Look alive, boys.
A couple of stewed prunes
heading your way.
(sirens wailing)
Gulp.
♪ ...w, x, y and z ♪
♪ Now I know my abc's ♪
♪ Won't you come
and play with me? ♪
Flawless.
We also would
have accepted
"Tell me what you
think of me."
Well, I guess
you're free to--
Give him the breathalyzer!
Huh?
(buzzes)
-You're under arrest.
-D'oh!
Think you can
get this car home?
Sure thing, giant beer.
Ooh! Ow!
Ow! Mother of mercy!
(laughing)
Hey, this is kind of fun.
Whee! (laughs)
Whee! Ow!
(phone ringing)
Hello?
Yeah, Mrs. Simpson
I have some bad news.
Your husband was found D.O.A.
Oh, my god!
He's dead?!
Oh, wait! I mean D.W.I.
(chuckles)
I always get
those two mixed up.
My name's Mrs. Phillips.
You said my husband
is D.W.I.?
Uh...
Why don't you talk
to that officer over there?
I'm going out to lunch.
Don't worry, Homer.
I have a foolproof strategy
to get you out of here.
Surprise witnesses--
Each more surprising
than the last.
I tell you, the judge
won't know what hit him.
-Ow!
-Pipe down in there, Hutz.
Your license
is hereby revoked,
and you are to attend
traffic school,
and two months
of alch-anon meetings.
Your honor,
I'd like that last remark
-stricken from the record.
-No.
It doesn't get
any better than this.
I want the most
intelligent hamster you've got.
Okay.
Uh...
This little guy
writes mysteries
under the name
of J.D. MacGregor.
How can a hamster
write mysteries?
Well, he gets the ending first
then he works backward.
Aw, come on.
Look, kid, just take him
before his mother eats him,
all right?
Have a good day
at work, honey.
Ha-ha!
Stupid bicycle.
Can't believe this.
No good, rotten...
(bell rings)
(chuckles)
I guess it's not all bad.
"I propose to determine
the answer to the question:
Is my brother dumber
than a hamster?"
Hey, Lis.
Look what I can do.
(muffled grunts)
Doggone it.
(gasps)
Remarkable!
Stupid books.
Hey, a cupcake.
(grunting)
Mm-hmm.
Dah!
Hamster: One...
Bart: Zero.
Experiment two.
The food is connected to a mild
electrical current.
The hamster has learned
a valuable lesson--
"Beware the hand of man."
(whistling)
Oh, a wise guy, eh?
(grunts like Curly)
Ow.
(snickers)
Hamster: Two, Bart: Zero.
Now, if any of you ever think
of drinking and driving again,
this film will scare
the pants off of you.
(screams)
Guys, guys,
this is the wrong movie.
Oh, wait a second.
I do something
really funny here.
(laughing)
(sighs)
What a terrible waste.
Hi. I'm actor Troy McClure.
You might remember me
from such driver's ed films as
"Alice's Adventures
Through the Windshield Glass
and "The Decapitation
of Larry Leadfoot."
For the next 60 minutes,
we'll be seeing actual film
of car crash victims.
(wacky comedy music playing)
(tires screeching)
(crashing)
TROY:
Here's an appealing fellow.
In fact, they're a-peeling
him off the sidewalk.
(laughing)
It's funny
'cause I don't know him.
I'm here for
the alch-anon meeting.
Mm-hmm. Third door
on your left.
Coping with senility?
No. I'm here
for microwave cookery.
No, wait.
Coping with senility.
My name is Ned.
-Hello, Ned.
It's been 4,000 days
since my last drink.
It was my first
and last blackberry schnapps.
Ned, did you clip
Ann Landers today?
Ann Landers
is a boring old biddy.
(gasps) Ned!
I was more animal than man.
My name is Otto.
I love to get blotto.
My name is Hans.
Drinking has ruined my life.
I'm 31 years old.
My name is Homer,
and I'm just here because
the court made me come.
Homer, with our help,
you'll never
touch a beer again.
(screaming)
So they say
I might have a problem.
(snorts)
Homie, do you ever
drink alone?
Does the Lord
count as a person?
No.
Then yes.
Do you need a beer
to fall asleep?
Thank you.
That would be nice.
Do you ever hide beer
around the house?
Do I ever.
Ah!
Do you ever drink
to escape from reality?
(humming "The Cancan")
Homie, I'd like you
to do something for me.
You name it.
I want you to give up
beer for a month.
You got it.
No deer for a month.
Did you say "beer"
or "deer"?
Deer.
Please, Homie.
I know you can do this.
All right.
Starting tomorrow,
no beer for a month.
(pop-top can opens)
MARGE:
What was that noise?
HOMER: I was saying,
"Psst, I love you."
Bart, could you go
get the cupcakes?
Cupcakes, cupcakes!
Yes, sweet cakes for all.
(shivering)
Well, beer,
we've had some great times.
♪ When I was seventeen ♪
♪ I drank some
very good beer ♪
♪ I drank some very good beer
I purchased with a fake I.D. ♪
♪ My name was Brian McGee ♪
♪ I stayed up
listening to Queen ♪
♪ When I was seventeen ♪
(sniffles)
Huh?
She'll pay for this.
I'm going to crush
her like this pellet.
Ow!
(gasps)
BART: Looking for something?
What have you done
with my report?
I've hidden it.
To find it, you'll need
to decipher a series of clues,
-each more fiendish than--
-Got it.
D'oh!
Behold gravity
in all its glory.
Pretty lame, Milhouse.
Can I touch it?
I've worked
too long and hard on this
for you to screw it up now.
But it's got
my name on it.
Just stand over there.
Over there!
Behold the flying machine
that will carry me,
Phileas Fogg,
around the world
in 80 days.
Dang! I was aiming
for his head.
Don't think about beer.
Mmm, alcohol-fueled car.
One for you.
One for me.
One for you. One for me.
(groans)
I don't know if I like you
experimenting on your brother.
Please, Mother,
it's purely in
the interest of science.
That'll learn him
to bust my tomater.
(crowd cheering)
(gasps)
BART: Step right up, folks.
We'll answer the question
that has been plaguing
scientists for ages--
Can hamsters fly planes?
(crowd murmuring)
MAN: Oh, look he's got
miniature goggles on.
Oh! And a little scarf.
-Isn't that adorable?
-Oh-ho!
But this project
has no scientific merit.
Take a hike, sister.
Oh, missy,
sour grapes.
Lisa, every good scientist
is half B.F. Skinner
and half P.T. Barnum.
I don't think I need to see
the other exhibits.
First prize.
(crowd applauds)
(sighs)
One down.
29 to go.
WOMEN:
Down with sexism!
Look at all
those feminists.
You thinking
what I'm thinking?
(rock music playing)
(women laughing)
-Yeah!
All right!
TV, have you
turned on me too?
(organ plays)
ANNOUNCER: The windup
and the two-two pitch...
Oh, no, sir!
Wait a minute.
The batter
is calling for time.
Looks like he's going
and getting himself a new bat.
And now there's a
beach ball on the field.
And the ball boys
are discussing
which one of them's
going to go get it.
I never realized
how boring this game is.
I think I've lost weight.
You've never
looked better.
Thank you all for coming.
We've got some very
interesting developments
in the field
of supperware.
Uh-huh.
This is the 128-ounce tub.
You can fit your whole
head in it.
Don't be scared, Jubjub.
It's mama.
I would kill everyone
in this room
for a drop of sweet beer.
So, Homer, please feel
free to tell us anything.
There's no judgment here.
The other day I was
so desperate for a beer
I snuck
into the football stadium
and ate the dirt
under the bleachers.
-(gasping)
-I cast thee out!
Don't think about beer.
Ah!
(train whistle blowing)
TRAIN: Chug-a-lug, chug-a-lug,
chug-a-lug, chug-a-lug,
chug-a-lug, chug-a-lug.
(screams)
No!
30 days.
I'm proud of you,
Homie.
Marge, I'm going to Moe's.
Send the kids to the neighbors
I'm coming back loaded.
Mmm... you don't have to
start drinking right away.
I was thinking we could
go for a bike ride.
But Marge, the barflies
are expecting me.
Moe and Barney and that guy
who calls me Bill.
But you look better.
You don't sweat
while you eat anymore,
and look, you've saved
more than $100.
I found it in your pants.
Yoink!
Mmm.
-(panting)
-Well, well,
look who it is?
Mr. I-don't-need-alcohol-
to-enjoy-life.
We hate him, right, fellas?
(muttering)
Moe, give me a beer.
Hey, everybody,
Homer's back!
(muttering)
(burps)
Come on, Homer,
do it for your old pal, Moesy.
But, Moe, yesterday you called
Homer a worthless sack of--
Pipe down,
Rub-a-dub!
Ow.
Put it in the fridge,
Moe.
I've got a date
with my wife.
You'll be back!
And so will you,
and you,
and you.
Of course, I'll be back.
If you didn't close,
I'd never leave.
HOMER:
♪ Raindrops keep falling on my head ♪
♪ But that doesn't mean my eyes
will soon be turning red ♪
BOTH:
♪ La-la la-la-la, la ♪
♪ La-la la-la-la-la-la
la-la la-la-la... ♪
♪ Because I'm free ♪
♪ Nothing's worrying me ♪
♪♪
♪ It won't be long till
happiness steps up to greet me♪
♪ Raindrops keep falling
on my head ♪
♪ But that doesn't mean my eyes
will soon be turning red ♪
♪ Crying's not for me ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm never gonna
stop the rain by complaining ♪
♪ Because I'm free ♪
♪ Nothing's worrying me ♪
(bell rings, Homer laughs)
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.