(exclaiming)
(school bell ringing)
(Barney belches)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
(tires screeching)
(grunts)
(gentle orchestral
music playing)
♪ The Simpsons 25x03 ♪
Four Regrettings and a Funeral
Original Air Date on October 6, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
(wind whistling)
S-So lonely.
(raspy): No sex
without a ring.
Damn it!
(gentle orchestral music
continues, giants laughing)
(belches)
(creaking)
♪
Mm.
What the...?! Hey, whoa!
(ghostly moaning)
(crackling)
- What about us, man?
- Get your own couch.
♪
(soft organ music playing)
(organ music continues)
Poor Chip. Such a big part
of everyone's life.
People called him the
"sixth Simpson."
I'm not sure why.
Chip did such a wonderful
job with my biography.
(people murmuring)
Chip was the life of Sector
6-F at the nuclear plant,
but Chip once confessed to me
he did have a few regrets.
(all gasp)
Chip regretted never ascending Mount
Springfield from the south face.
He regretted that the high school long
jump record he set was wind-aided.
He often spoke of that asterisk.
He never broke par on hole
17 at Springfield Mini Golf.
(organ music resumes)
Let us pray.
Eh, everyone has regrets.
Not me.
You? Your marriage is a dead fish
floating in a tank of stale beer.
Your baby's addicted
to pacifiers.
And your son is out of control.
Let us kneel.
(pained groans)
Ow! My knees!
40 years of healing, gone!
(cackling)
He's such a little dickens.
Although Dickens was
pretty well behaved.
He's been screwed up since the moment
Homer's DNA staggered into your womb.
I have no regrets about that.
It was a perfect pregnancy.
Didn't smoke, didn't
drink, lost three pounds.
And every night before bed, Homer
would give me a little kiss...
music! (gasps)
Could Bart have been prenatally
screwed up by the KISS music?
♪ Get up! Everybody's
gonna move their feet ♪
♪ Get down! Everybody's
gonna leave their seats ♪
♪ You got to lose your mind
in Detroit Rock City. ♪
Huh?
Man, this is the weirdest
pregnancy craving ever.
Well, for some reason
it relaxes me.
Now, do that thing
Gene Simmons does.
Overstay my welcome
for 40 years?
(whistling a tune)
KENT BROCKMAN: Regrets, eh?
This local newsman's had a few.
Covering a town of backwater rubes
who, for some reason, hate my guts.
This is Kent Brockman...
(sighs)
live at the Springfield
Peach Parade.
Sir, could you give us eight
seconds of your homespun wisdom?
It's a little-known fact that you
can get head lice from peaches.
Uh, this is my
daughter Peaches.
(sighs)
We'll have more regrets at 11:00 tonight
following an all-new bottle of scotch.
HOMER (scoffs): You have regrets, Mr.
"I Get to See the Weathergirl From the Side"!
I made the worst financial
decision of all time.
Oh, I can't think about it.
I won't think about it. I
don't want to think about it!
Oh, I'm thinking about it!
Mm...
Hmm.
Huh?
(shudders): Oh... that's the coolest
bowling ball I've ever seen.
Hello, Bear Stearns?
I'd like to sell all my Apple stock
so I can buy a fancy bowling ball.
You heard me.
Technology is a fad.
Heavy, blue balls
are the future.
Now let us text on our ubiquitous
Apple tablets and phones.
(keys clicking)
Oh, you cost me a
piece of all that!
Oh, don't cry.
If it makes you feel worse, I'm the
man who bought the stock you sold.
I'll bet a rich man like you
has no regrets at all.
Just one.
The girl that got away.
She broke my first heart.
So, is there truly anyone
among us without regrets?
I have no regrets.
Really, Mother?
Oh, I didn't see you there.
(Irish accent): I'm Father O'Greedy.
Dimes for the needy.
(Milhouse chuckles)
Milhouse, are you the bottom
half of that mischief?
MILHOUSE:
Uh... uh... uh...
Oh, my.
My pants, like the Lord,
work in mysterious ways.
Return those vestments.
Speaking of return on investments,
my Apple stock is up 3,500%.
Aw, you misheard
that on purpose!
(grunting)
Tithe denied!
Mm. Must find way...
to blame myself.
Um, it says I should
give you lumbar support.
- Better go to the lumber yard.
- "Lum-bar." It means "lower back."
How many times will you
make that mistake?
(groans) Just put on
the KISS record.
- Which one?
- Anything from Love Gun.
♪
Hey, book, are you
expecting this?
And while I'm at it...
Burn, dumb, helpful books.
That is a good fire.
(grunting)
(pants)
You're going down, Bart!
(grunts, groans)Why?
- Ah, reckless youth.
- He'll be okay.
I was referring to him.
I had a spring in my
step like that once.
Back when I met Lilah.
Lilah ran a little crepe stand
in the seventh arrondissement.
Oh, Monty,
looking at you, I could lie in
this unheated garret forever.
There's heat. I just
don't turn it on.
Seeing you there, in the sweet
light of Paris between the wars,
there's a question I must pose.
I have something for you.
Oh! Not that.
(chuckles)
(grunts)
(bubbling)
(chuckles)
Wrong box. Lilah, will you take
that big step from cousin to wife?
(gasps) Oh, Monty, you
must promise me one thing.
Anything she wanted
I was willing to do.
Anything, except...
All I ask is that you set aside five
minutes a day to think of others.
When you say "others,"
could they be bars of gold?
(crying): I shall find another
husband as good as you are evil.
No one's that good.
(sobbing)
All I have left is my drawing.
Hm. It looked a lot better
in my memory.
Uh, but you know what, Smithers?
I will find Lilah
and win her back.
I'll just check
with the old gang.
Hemingway!
Picasso.
Matador Juan Belmonte.
And Stalin.
That man could really
put pressure on you.
Hello, Kent.
Well, well, well.
Rachel Maddow.
Everyone came back
for Chip's funeral.
I was flying from DC to New York and, of
course, I had the layover in Springfield.
How's the gang at Channel 6?
Look, let's get this out of the
way... just because we both
worked at Channel 6 and you made it big
and I didn't doesn't mean I'm bitter.
Um, Is that your car?
Maybe.
Kent, I'm gonna tell you the most
important mistake you ever made...
after this break.
So, Kent, that
mistake you made,
that fundamental, life-changing
error, that cosmic fail, that...
- Just tell me already!
- After this break.
You could have come with me,
but you were suckling the dual teats
of infotainment and celebrifawning.
(upbeat theme plays)
So, tell us about
your new movie.
It's fantastic.
The studio let us play
in their sandbox.
- Great. We have a clip.
- No! No, don't show it.
There aren't five good
seconds in the whole film.
(car door closes,
tires screeching)
I'm not a newsman anymore,
I'm a geologist.
I keep discovering
a new rock bottom.
Kent, I think I found my
ticket out of this town.
Or at least to a
better Springfield.
You two newshounds
working on a story?
How about this?
Mario's down the street
found a rat in their pasta.
- When did that happen?
- Whenever you want. Eh?
Rachel, can I come?
We can share blazers.
Just follow me.
At Mario's, the picture of Sinatra on
the wall is signed by Frank Junior.
The frame hides the "Junior"!
Someone's been dumping
tires in the forest.
Willikers! In my three years of soft news,
I've never seen anything like this.
Those are tires from my
ill-fated Krusty Town Car.
It would explode if people
gripped the wheel too tightly.
(laughs):
What a scoop!
You're not telling no one.
As the 4:00 p.m. clown, I have complete
control of the Channel 6 news division.
Local news is a joke.
I'm going to cable.
Cable news!
Bah! People only want news
at 6:00 p.m.
from white guys on weekdays
and black guys on weekends.
We'll see about that.
Yes, we shall see.
About that, things will be seen.
By us.
Kent, you coming?
He ain't comin'.
This little piggy's afraid to leave
his cushy anchorman slop trough.
Could you, uh, phrase that
a little more nicely?
Sorry. He "isn't" coming.
You'll regret this, Kent.
When I have my own show
and you're stuck here
tracking Santa's flight
from the North Pole.
"Oh, look, he's over Greenland!"
Don't worry, piggy, you
made the right choice.
Eh, it'll burn out
in an hour or so.
Look, Burns, I've got the dope
on your sweetie.
She's still alive, and she just got
over being mad at you last week.
Lilah's alive?
Yeah, well, uh, she's
alive, but she's a nun.
Married to Jesus, eh?
Does he beat her?
Jesus? No, he's a real
Eagle Scout, that one.
But your penguin's not a Catholic,
she's a Buddhist nun...
spent her life expressing her
sexuality with a Zen garden.
Those raked rocks
could have been me.
Now, since you're so good at
finding things, find the exit.
There is the little
matter of my fee.
You're becoming very tiresome.
Who moved my desk?!
♪
Well, here I am.
Cable news alley.
(dog howls)
Fox News. Is this really how I want
to get back in the big leagues?
Let's see how print
journalism is doing.
Sir, do you sell The
New York Times?
Sir, we are The New York Times.
And in I go.
Why are you doing this, Bart?
50% attention-seeking, 50%
to drop things on people.
He's gonna visit my sky granny.
To work at Fox News, all you have to
be able to do is operate this device.
Now, when a Republican
is in trouble...
At the time, I didn't know it was illegal
to sex up a cow on the Capitol steps.
...we simply do this.
Now you try.
Sorry, but I just discovered
I have some scruples.
I'm going back to my sweet little
town where I can decide what news is.
Like a god.
We've had some good times.
♪ Memories
♪ Rest between the
pages of my mind ♪
♪ Memories
♪ See me through the
ages just like wine... ♪
And you sat on the gas pedal
when my foot fell asleep,
so I'm getting you
shined up nice.
What the...?
Oh!
That's a ball-proof window, sir.
Would you like me to ask Siri
for a nearby hospital?
SIRI: I'm sorry, I don't see
any "hops petals" near you.
Deleting all contact
information.
No, no, I didn't ask you
to do that, Siri. I...
SIRI: Delete confirmed.
BART (groans):
Oh. Okay, Bart, be cool.
Calm down, you're not
gonna die up here.
(indistinct chatter)
(whooping, gunfire)
(yells, whimpers)
Aw...
D'oh!
Oh, Monty, I can't believe you
found me after all these years.
I've saved myself for you.
Well, then, uh...
(nervous chuckle)
I should disrobe at once.
Housekeeping? Send up a
Chinese dressing screen
and one of Firestone's finest
vulcanized prophylactics.
Be right back.
(laughs softly)
Smithers? Which do I take first, the
rhino horn or the tiger tongue?
I have my doubts
about both, sir.
Bah! I'll just do it
the old-fashioned way.
With my pump.
(engine sputtering)
(sputtering continues)
(chuckles): Just powdering
my nose, darling.
(engine continues sputtering)
Smithers, run down
to Sears, Roebuck
and get a five-eighths-inch
Phillips head bolt.
(tires screech)
(sighs)
Here I am, slowly dying every
day at 5:00, 6:00 and 11:00.
BART:
Help! Help!
Child in danger with
exciting visuals!
This kid's corpse could be my magic
carpet. Get me a cameraman!
The movie Up has come horribly
to life over Springfield.
A local boy clings to life in a story
that proves this reporter's relevance.
BART:
Ay, caramba!
(gasps)
It's Bart!
Pray for a miracle, boy.
God can hear you
better from up there.
Dear Lord, please
help me land safely.
Or transform this basket
into a flying killer robot
that I control with my mind.
Amen.
That's not a prayer.
My God says it is.
Oh, I see you're ice-cold
with anticipation.
Dead? Oh, Lilah.
Even at the end,
I waited too long.
What if I give her
the breath of life?
(soft exhale)
Oh, boy.
I guess one regret
just leads to another.
You know, sir, maybe it
would bring you peace
to honor the one thing
Lilah ever asked of you.
Here you are, my good man.
A little broth will cure your
mental illness. (chuckles)
Sir, that's five minutes. You can
stop thinking of other people now.
You know what, I think
I'll give it another five.
I'm proud of you, Monty.
(kissing)
I ain't eatin' that.
Chief, what are you
doing to save our son?
Well, I've placed marksmen on the roof
to shoot the balloons one by one,
but frankly they're
not very good.
(gunshot)
(grunts)
(whining): Chief,
it happened again.
Aw, come on, guys,
spread out. Arm's length.
It's all my fault.
I should never have listened to those
KISS albums when I was pregnant.
Marge, with all due
respect, that's ridiculous.
My Sarah listened to Mozart
and Churchill speeches
when she was pregnant with Ralphie, and
he can't even open a refrigerator.
Pushing, always...
always pushing.
- Really?
- Oh, yeah. That kid's a mess.
Hey! Only I get to
criticize him, Lou.
Kid's scared to flush.
Think's it's his brother.
Can we focus on my
son up in the sky?
Oh, I've got a long-shot idea.
By which I mean firing a
shot over a long distance.
(chuckling)
Yeah, you see, if we could fire an exactly
12-and-a-half-pound weight into the basket,
it would lower the boy
very gently to the ground.
Unfortunately, all our
cannonballs were melted down
to make a statue of Joe Paterno,
which we changed to
look like Eugene Levy.
I think I just might have
what you're looking for.
♪
Today I'm glad that
I sold that stock.
Uh, Apple closed up
another 20 points today.
(whining):
Why does everyone know?
Because their terrific products
keep track of it for you.
And anything else you
could ever think of.
That kid's not
dying on my watch.
Which ends... right
now, fortunately.
(hums a tune)
(whimpers)
CROWD (chanting): Bart! Bart!
Bart! Bart! Bart! Bart!
(laughing):
Hey.
- Hmm. (yells)
- CROWD: Bart! Bart!
Homer's rising faster
than Apple stock.
(laughter)
(Homer yells, grunts)
My boy's okay!
CROWD (chanting):
Bart! Bart! Bart!
I won the science fair!
I get to go to Chicago!
CROWD:
Bart! Bart! Bart!
Ugh. Bart, Bart, Bart.
You know what I think
about regrets?
As long as your family
is together,
every choice you've ever
made is the right one.
And together we are.
(gunshot)
Would you guys knock it off?
He's down safe already.
(gunshot)
MAN: Sorry, Chief, that
was me putting it down.
And there you have it...
a family reunited.
And a grateful nation gives
thanks for some solid reporting.
Back to you, Rachel Maddow.
Great job, Kent.
I think we might have an
opening for you at MSNBC
between our weekend prison documentary
block and the two hours it takes
to make up Joe Scarborough
on Monday morning.
(chuckles): No, thanks, Rachel Maddow.
I'm happy right here.
No regrets.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
Hah!
Shh!