♪ The Simpsons ♪
(chalk screeches)
(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(tires screeching)
(horn honks)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
Well, children,
it's the last day of school.
ALL:
Yay!
Here are your grades.
Oh, no, Mrs. Krabappel,
if I don't get
a "C" average,
my dad won't let me go
to Kamp Krusty.
Well, it isn't fair
to the other children,
but all right.
Much obliged, doll.
Oh, Bart Simpson,
I'm gonna miss you.
SKINNER:
Attention, everyone.
This is Principal Skinner.
I trust you all
remembered to bring in
your implements
of destruction?
Now let's trash this dump.
♪ School's out for summer ♪
♪ School's out forever ♪
Somebody put a torch
to these permanent records.
Quickly now.
♪ Fa-la-la-la-la ♪
♪ La-la-la-la-la-la-la-la ♪
♪ La-la-la-la-la... ♪
Wake up, boy.
(groaning)
Oh... I dreamt it was
the last day of school.
Well, it is.
BART:
Oh, how do I know
this isn't some
beautiful dream, too?
Ow!
You know, a pinch
is more traditional.
(grunting, slurping,
and belching)
MARGE: Homer, you do
remember your promise to the children.
Sure do.
When you're 18,
you're out the door.
No, Dad, you promised
if Bart and I
got "C" averages,
we could go
to Kamp Krusty.
And with no false modesty,
you're looking
at one happy camper.
Heh, yeah, well...
just remember,
when you see my report card
they got this whole new
grading system this year.
It now goes,
"D," "B," "A," "C."
Now, listen, boy,
we have an understanding
and you better keep
your end of it.
I don't think I'd be
any kind of a father
if you got "D's," and
I let you go to Kamp Krusty.
-But, Dad--
-Son,
if you really
want something in this life,
you have to work for it.
Now quiet--
They're about to announce
the lottery numbers.
ANNOUNCER:
17...
D'oh!
-32...
-D'oh!
-Five...
-Eight...
-Woo-hoo!
-47...
-D'oh!
SKINNER:
Attention, students,
Please clear out
your lockers
into the
wastebaskets provided.
36-24-36.
(chuckling)
(birds screeching
and drums beating)
Now, let's see
what we got here.
Ah, my gym shorts.
(banging)
Here are your final
report cards.
I have nothing left
to say to any of you.
So if nobody minds,
let's just quietly
run out the clock.
(gasps)
I've never gotten
a "B" before.
How could this
have happened?
I feel so dirty.
The dirt's not coming off.
Okay, calm down.
This must just be
a little typo.
(nervous giggle)
Oh, Miss Hoover.
There appears to be
a mistake on my report card.
You gave me a B+
in conduct?
Now Lisa, everyone
needs a blotch
on their
permanent record.
Perhaps I'm not
making myself clear.
I think you should reconsider.
Lisa... you're hurting me.
Mrs. Krabappel,
in figuring out my final grades
I hope you'll note
that all of my textbooks
are being returned
in excellent condition--
In some cases, still
in their original wrappings.
Duly noted.
I'd also like to add,
as I gaze upon your beauty,
I've never seen
an angel fly so low.
Forget it, short pants.
Mrs. Krabappel, If I don't get
at least a "C" average
I can't go to Kamp Krusty.
Have a "D"-lightful summer.
(laughing)
ALL:
Five...
Four...
Three...
-Two...
-Don't open your mouth.
One.
(bell ringing)
(cheering)
Wait a minute.
You didn't learn how
World War II ended.
-We won!
-(cheering)
(chanting:)
U.S.A.! U.S.A.!
I haven't seen such
unfettered hurly-burlies
since the fall of Saigon.
Well, William,
another school year gone by.
And may I say,
a job well done, sir.
Well, back to work then.
Make sure to give those
toilets a good scrubbing.
We want the old girls
sparkling when I get back.
Aye, sir.
Eh, you silk-wearing
buttercup.
All right, three whole months
of Spaghetti-O's
and daytime TV.
So, Bart, will you
be joining me
in the bucolic splendor
of Kamp Krusty?
You bet.
Check out this hand:
All aces.
(laughing)
"A+"?
Oh, Bart, why didn't you
at least forge plausible grades?
(groaning)
Hi, kids!
Only one week left to sign up
for the bestest summer ever
at Kamp Krusty.
(laughing)
Whup!
Hey! Hah!
Ho! Ho!
Hey! Ho! Ugh!
Hey!
Kamp Krusty is built on an
actual Indian burial ground.
We've got archery,
wallet-making,
the whole megillah.
(goofy laughter)
And for you fat kids,
my exclusive program
of diet and ridicule
will really get results.
And the best part is, when
you come to Kamp Krusty,
you'll spend the summer
with me!
Honest injun.
(goofy laughter)
Well... here goes nothing.
-(clanking)
-D'oh!
Stupid roller skate.
Well, Dad,
here's my report card.
I think you'll be
pleasantly surprised.
"A+"? You don't think
much of me, do you, boy?
-No, sir.
-You know,
a "D" turns into
a "B" so easily.
You just got greedy.
So I won't get to go to camp?
Now, Bart, we made this deal
because I thought it would
help you get good grades,
and you didn't.
But why should you pay
for my mistake?
You mean I can go?
Yeah, I didn't want you
hanging around
all summer anyway.
Oh, Dad, you're the best father
a boy could ever have.
Thanks, son.
Now you got little hands.
Can you reach under that mower
and pull out that skate?
(engine whirring)
Pff. Never mind.
(Marge humming)
Bart, where's your
bathing suit?
-I'm gonna swim naked.
-You're what?
Ah, sure, there'll be
a couple of uptight counselors
who won't dig
the Bart philosophy,
but I feel the human body
is a thing of beauty.
Marge, am I crazy
or is my back getting hairier?
Before I go to camp,
I'll need boosters
for malaria,
German measles
encephalitis,
Hansen's disease.
Oh, now, I'm afraid
what we have here
is an advanced case
of hypochondria.
There's only one
known cure:
A wowipop.
(laughs)
Don't patronize me, doctor.
It's our last family
dinner for six weeks,
but I promised myself
I wouldn't cry.
(grunting and slurping)
(sobbing)
Oh, I'm going to miss this.
Hey, hands off my pickle.
I don't see your name
on it, boy.
No, but...
Oh, yeah?
Checkmate.
Always thinking
two moves ahead.
We'll see you
when you get back
from image
enhancement camp.
Spare me your euphemisms.
It's fat camp for Daddy's
chubby little secret.
You promised you wouldn't
make a scene.
(kissing loudly)
Good-bye,
my special little guy.
Lisa, watch out
for poison ivy.
Remember, leaves of three,
let it be.
Leaves of four, eat some more.
-Good-bye.
-Good-bye, Mom!
-Good-bye!
-Good-bye, Dad!
I'll write you every day.
Don't look in my closet.
In fact, stay out of
my room altogether.
If the pets die don't
replace them. I'll know!
(cheering)
WOMAN: So long!
Don't come back.
Hi, kids.
Welcome to Kamp Krusty.
(goofy laughter)
I'll see you in a few weeks.
Until then,
I've turned things over to my bestest
buddy in the whole wide world--
(a different voice:)
Mr. Black.
-I want you to treat...
-Mr. Black
...with the same respect
you would give me.
-Now, here's...
-Mr. Black.
Thank you, Krusty,
and welcome, children.
I am Mr. Black,
your head counselor.
For the past 15 years,
I was president
of Euro-Krusty land
until it blew up.
I'll take any questions
you might have.
You and then, uh...
one more.
Can we call you
Uncle Blackie?
No. Last question.
When do we get
to see Krusty?
Uh, he will be
along eventually.
In the meantime
our counselors,
Dolph, Jimbo, and Kearney
will be happy to handle
any problems you may have.
(coughs)
Looks like we got ourselves
a troublemaker.
Hee hee hee.
You can have the shower
to yourself, Homie.
-I'm finished.
-Oh, no, you're not.
Ooh.
KEARNY:
Here's your cabin.
If you don't like it, T.S.
(chicken clucking)
This is a little more rustic
than I expected.
I'm not worried, Lis.
You know why?
Because of this--
The Krusty brand
seal of approval.
You can only
find it on products
which meet the high
personal standards
of Krusty the Klown.
Ow!
Oops, I should have
warned you.
That clock gets incredibly hot
if you leave it plugged in.
That's okay.
Uh... all this stuff is fine.
(warbling laughter)
Now, I am off to Wimbledon.
Don't we get
to roast marshmallows?
Shut up and eat
your pine cone.
Uh... are you sure that's safe?
Well, it ain't
getting any safer.
(gasping)
All right, you balls
of pan drippings,
I want to see Crisco
coming out of those pores.
We're not leaving
until this Christmas ham
gives me a pull-up.
(acoustic guitar plays)
♪ Hail to thee, Kamp Krusty ♪
♪ By the shores
of Big Snake lake ♪
♪ Though your swings
are rusty ♪
♪ We know
they'll never break ♪
Louder! Faster!
♪ From your
gleaming mess hall♪
♪ To your hallowed
baseball field ♪
♪ To your spic-and-span
infirmary ♪
♪ Where all our wounds
are healed ♪
♪ Hail to thee, Kamp Krusty ♪
♪ Below Mount Avalanche ♪
♪ We will always
love Kamp Krusty... ♪
♪ A registered trademark
of the Krusty corporation ♪
♪ All rights reserved ♪
(wood creaking)
You're serving us gruel?
Not quite.
This is Krusty brand
imitation gruel.
Nine out of ten orphans
can't tell the difference.
Yo, Mr. Black--
Another brandy.
Gentlemen, to evil.
Marge,
since the kids left,
I've lost five pounds.
Oh, that's wonderful.
And look, new hair.
I'm this close
to having a comb-over.
(growls)
(giggles)
(chuckling)
Lights out, losers.
Yeah. We're meeting
some tail
on the other side
of the lake.
(laughing)
(door being locked)
I feel like
I'm going to die, Bart.
We're all going
to die, Lis.
I meant soon.
So did I.
(band playing
"Rule, Britannia")
Mmm... strawberries. Mmm.
(slurping)
Oh, that's good.
Hey, Lendl!
Choke! Choke!
Yeah!
Point and game, Becker.
And will the harlequin
in the third row
please keep his voice down.
(chuckling)
Sorry, folks.
Sorry, your majesty.
Hmph.
"Dear kids:
"I hope this letter
finds you well.
"We are doing great.
"Your father
is in the best shape
he's been since...
well, ever."
Size!
Strength! Agility!
"We miss you terribly.
"I hope these jellybean cookies
will tide you over
until you get home."
Hey, Simpson.
Tell your mom
her cookies sucked.
"Dear Mom and Dad:
"I no longer fear hell
"because I've been
to Kamp Krusty.
Our nature hikes have become
grim death marches."
(groaning)
A snake bit me.
Back in line, maggot.
"Our arts and crafts center
is, in actuality,
a Dickensian workhouse."
Come on, wimps.
These Gucci wallets
have to be on the streets
of Hong Kong by Friday.
(tempo speeds up)
"Bart makes it
through the days
relying on his
unwavering belief
that Krusty the Klown
will come through..."
Krusty is coming. Krusty is coming.
Krusty is coming.
"But I am far more
pessimistic.
"I am not sure if this
letter will reach you
as our lines of
communication have been cut."
Giddyap.
"Now the effort of writing
"has made me lightheaded
"so I close by saying,
'Save us! Save us now!'
Bart and Lisa."
(chuckling)
Ah, kids' letters
from camp.
Oh, she complains now
but when we go
to pick her up,
she won't want to leave.
(wind howling)
(thunder crashing)
Lisa, I've been
thinking it over.
Next summer
I'm getting a job.
(moaning)
Oh, Homer,
it's getting late.
We'll miss
the fireworks.
Marge, we've got all
the fireworks we need
right here.
Well, kids, I promised you
a little treat
in lieu of dinner,
and here it is:
The man who took
an abandoned mule tannery
and turned it
into a summer wonderland:
Mr. Krusty the Klown.
See, I told you
Krusty would come.
Just like I said.
He's gonna bring us
food and water
and smite our enemies.
Now I must tell you kids,
Krusty has laryngitis
and a bad back,
so he won't be saying
anything or doing anything.
Krusty looks fat.
He's really having trouble
keeping his balance.
He's still funny,
but not ha-ha funny.
-That's not Krusty the Klown!
-(kids gasping)
What, do you think I slapped
a clown suit on some wino?
(nervous laughter)
Yeah, Bart, I am so
Krunchy the Klown.
(belching)
All right, that's it.
I've been scorched
by Krusty before.
I got a rapid heartbeat from
his Krusty brand vitamins.
My Krusty calculator didn't
have a seven or an eight.
And Krusty's autobiography
was self-serving
with many glaring omissions.
But this time,
he's gone too far.
We want Krusty!
(all chanting) We want Krusty!
Yeah, we want Krunchy!
We want Krunchy!
I thought you said
you broke their spirits.
We did.
You broke nothing.
BART:
Let's get 'em!
To the hydrofoil.
(angry shouting)
My chunky brothers,
gorge yourselves
at the trough of freedom.
Oh, sweet, nourishing gruel!
Kowalski!
My brownies!
Wiggum.
A change of underwear.
Crandall.
My insulin!
Bart, you said you're gonna
name it Camp Freedom.
Eh, this has more zing.
I dub thee sir...
Urgent call
for Mr. Klown.
This better be important.
Oy gevalt!
Just let your head flop
back and forth.
Your neck is a well-cooked
piece of asparagus.
We interrupt "Surdrudinma
Baradad's Yoga Party"
for this special bulletin.
-(gasps)
-Ladies and gentlemen
I've been to Vietnam,
Afghanistan and Iraq,
and I can say without
hyperbole that
this is a million times worse
than all of them put together.
Burn, Krusty, burn!
A group
of school-age Spartacuses
has taken this camp by force.
Three counselors are missing
and presumed scared.
What's that?
I'm being told I can have
an exclusive interview
with the ringleader.
Don't be the boy.
D'oh!
I just want
the whole world to know
that this was
a really crappy camp.
Can I say "crappy" on TV?
Yes, on this
network you can.
Is it true you attempted suicide
when you heard the news?
Are you and Princess Di
just friends?
You people make me sick!
You're vultures!
Where were you when
I sang at Farm Aid?
Out of my way, you parasites.
I said out of my way!
I'm no fake.
I'm the real Krusty.
Oh, yeah?
Who played your daughter
on the short-lived sitcom
President Clown?
I don't know her name.
But she held up a
liquor store last year.
I smell bacon.
Let's see if he's
wearing a wire.
Hey, whoa!
-Not the face.
-(gasping)
LISA:
It is the real Krusty.
Look at that pacemaker scar.
The cattle skull birthmark,
and his famous
superfluous nipple.
Well, at least
you're not as bad as customs.
How could you, Krusty?
I'd never lend my name
to an inferior product.
(hysterical sobbing)
They drove a dump truck
full of money to my house.
I'm not made of stone.
Krusty, this camp
was a nightmare.
They fed us gruel.
They forced us to make
wallets for export,
and one of the campers
was eaten by a bear.
Oh, my God!
Well, actually, the bear
just ate his hat.
-Was it a nice hat?
-Oh, yeah.
Oh, my God!
Well, I'm gonna make it
all up to you.
I'm gonna show you kids
the time of your life.
Get ready for two weeks at
the happiest place on earth.
Tijuana!
(cheering)
♪ South of the border ♪
♪ Down Mexico way ♪
♪ That's where
I fell in love ♪
♪ When stars above
came out to play ♪
♪ And now, as I wander ♪
♪ My thoughts ever stray ♪
♪ South of the border ♪
♪ Down Mexico way ♪
♪ Yes, she was a picture ♪
♪ In old Spanish lace ♪
♪ And just for
a tender while ♪
♪ I kissed the smile
upon her face ♪
♪ For it was fiesta ♪
♪ And we were so gay ♪
♪ South of the border ♪
♪ Down Mexico way ♪
♪ Those mission bells
told me ♪
♪ That I must not stray ♪
♪ South of the border ♪
♪ Down Mexico way ♪
Olé!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.