(SINGING) The Simpsons
(TIRES SCREECHING)
D'oh!
(SCREAMS)
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
ALL: Huh?
D'oh!
(GRUNTING)
Check it out, girls.
Sixty-eight squares
of ankle-busting fury.
That's right.
A double dog-leg,
hamstring-knotting,
hop-way to hell.
LISA: What insane kangaroo
dreamed this
fevered nightmare?
Behold!
Ladies, grab your pebbles.
GIRLS: Mmm.
(GIGGLING)
What?
Nothing.
(SHERRI GIGGLES)
Lisa has a big butt.
(CHANTING)
Shut up! I do not!
Oh, no. Don't make Lisa mad!
She might crush us
all with her giant butt!
Shut up, you! Stop teasing
the big-bottomed lass.
She's just as God made her,
plump as a Christmas goose.
Dad, the kids at
school said my butt's big.
That's ridiculous, honey.
You're the cutest
little girl I know.
You just have
what is known
as the Simpson butt.
Permit me to elaborate.
Every Simpson
starts with a circle.
Daddy has one big circle here.
Then a smaller one up here.
Two big sexy
circles for eyes.
One macho muzzle.
And a snappy new outfit.
Ooh. I'm looking good.
Ooh. Cuffs, yeah.
And for some reason,
my hair and ear
form an "M" and a "G."
Party, party, party, party!
Hmm? You want to know
a little trick?
To downsize my derriere,
I just tie a sweater
around it.
See?
(GASPS)
(IN FEMALE VOICE)
"Oh, Homer. You're wasting
away to nothing.
"You simply must
eat something."
(IN NORMAL VOICE)
Well, you're the boss!
(IN FEMALE VOICE)
"Oh! I love to see
my man eat!"
Check it out, Homes.
You said if I ever
got 100 on a test,
you'd throw me a party.
There's my 100.
Where's my party?
(SCOFFS) Nice try, loser!
I bet you made up a fake test.
Nope. It's real.
Check out the watermark.
All right.
HOMER: D'oh!
A-ha!
Here's a mistake.
It says the capital of
Kentucky is Frankfort.
(LAUGHS DERISIVELY)
Dream on, pal.
Homer, the capital of Kentucky
is Frankfort.
Really? Frankfort-er.
Is that anything?
Uh, yes, it's something, dear.
See, it's all legit.
Now make with the party.
All right, boy!
Which con did you work here?
Copy off another kid?
Pay attention and take notes?
Well, take note of this.
(CHOKING)
(CHUCKLES)
(SIGHS)
Bart really did get 100.
I gave a test
on state capitals
but I forgot to
roll up the map.
Everyone got 100.
I win! P-A-R-T! Par-t!
(BLOWING)
People, please.
It's a school night.
I thought you two broke up.
(SCOFFS)
This means nothing.
Yes, yes.
You've made that quite clear.
Maybe a different outfit
would make me look thinner.
Hmm.
(MOANS)
This store makes me feel
even worse about myself.
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
Oh!
I heard she's back
to her birth weight.
Must be nice.
Ew.
No, no.
The body on this
mannequin is all wrong.
I know.
It's such an unrealistic
standard for young...
Huh?
(SINGING)
Planing down the thighs
I make four bucks an hour
planing down the thighs
Hey, I don't look so bad.
Don't worry, Lisa.
You can still find
someone to love you.
Now you've got no choice.
(CHUCKLES)
No!
Oh, boy! Barty's gonna party!
He sure is if he can keep up
with these party animals.
Aunt Patty, Aunt Selma,
Grandma Bouvier and...
(SCATTING)
Grampa!
(SNORING)
Plus your schoolyard chums,
Martin and Ralph.
Bart's my bestest boy friend.
Oh, Mom.
This guest list sucks.
Well,
it was the best I could do
on such short notice.
(GROANS) Where's Milhouse?
He's got the measles.
But we've got him
on speaker phone.
MILHOUSE: (DISTORTED) Rock on!
You know, the first time
I met Bart was at
recess in first grade.
Oh, I told him
to use a land line.
Okay, gang.
Let's get this
party started.
Or should I say "Barted."
Eh? Mmm.
For our first game,
I need everyone
to draw a picture
of President Eisenhower.
(RALPH HUMS)
I drew him with
Canadian Prime Minster
Louis St. Laurent.
Their relationship
was frosty at best.
(GROANS)
Duck, duck, duck, duck.
Say "goose," you stupid freak!
(CRYING)
(GROANS)
Oh, Mom. This was
the worst party ever.
(MOANS)
Gee, I did
the best I could.
Ah! Here's Lisa!
She'll save the party!
Honey, sit down.
Have a big slice of cake!
What?
I'm not fat enough already?
How could you say that to me?
(CRYING)
Lisa, wait!
(GRUNTING)
MILHOUSE: Hello? Hello?
I had to leave because
my French bread pizza dinged.
Hello?
Duck, duck, duck, duck.
Oh, what's the big deal?
Bart didn't like his presents.
So what?
It's not like he
gives us such great gifts.
Remember that
maple leaf ironed
between the sheets
of wax paper?
What was that?
That was crap.
Aw, It's not just the
presents. The kids don't
appreciate me anymore.
They'd rather hang
out with their friends
than with their mom.
So they're growing up.
Soon they'll be
leaving the nest
and you'll have
time for yourself.
Hundreds of
thousands of hours.
And then
the peace of the grave.
No! No, I've got a lot more
mothering left in me!
I'll be right here at
3:00 to pick you up.
Then I'll take you to the zoo.
We can eat fries
out of a safari hat!
No, thanks.
I'm gonna stay in the library
and do a little reading.
MARGE: Hmm.
Well, I guess it's
just you and me, Bart.
Mom, after that
lame party you threw,
I'd rather hang out
with thunder thighs here.
(GRUNTS)
Mmm, they grow up so fast.
They're just
asserting their independence.
If a child doesn't do it now,
it may never happen.
Seymour!
Do you want your
vitamin in applesauce
or are you gonna
take it like a big boy?
Applesauce.
(MAGGIE SQUEALS)
Oh, sure. You love me
now but you'll turn.
(GRUNTING)
Stop struggling
and get in my mouth, jerks!
Aren't you the boy
who beats up my son?
Probably. What's your name?
Simpson.
Oh, yeah.
Bart Simpson.
Spiky hair, soft kidneys,
always hitting himself.
(SIGHS)
Those tadpoles are your lunch?
Technically brunch.
Well, here. Take this.
My daughter didn't
want the lunch I made.
(SNIFFING)
Oh, this sandwich rocks.
My tadpoles seem
crude by comparison.
Ha-ha! You're nocturnal.
You don't have to impress me
by making fun of others.
I already like you.
Ha-ha!
I'm starting to let
down my guard. Ha-ha!
Thanks, Mrs. S.
Today didn't
totally suck nard.
It's nice to be appreciated.
Uh, whatever.
Take it sleazy.
Mom?
Nelson?
I thought you were sleeping
in the park tonight.
Oh, that's okay.
The kid don't
bother me none.
Hey, Nelson.
Say hello to Moe.
He said he'd take
you camping sometime.
(CHUCKLES)
I said I might.
Hey, kids. I just heard
they canceled league night
down at the bowling alley.
You know what that means?
Open lanes!
(GRUNTING)
What do you say?
It'll be BLAM!
Bart-Lisa-and-Mom! Huh?
Mom, when I want
lame and needy,
I'll call Milhouse.
No offense.
Fine.
I'll take my
mothering elsewhere.
Yeah!
Ooh, great roll, Nelson.
Here, I cut up
your hotdog for you.
Wow! Hotdogs are awesome!
You've never had one before?
No. But I saw some
in a catalog once.
People in sweaters
were eating them at a picnic.
(SLURPS)
So my mom works at Hooters.
But her dream
is to go to Vegas
and work in a real strip club.
(GROANS)
And where's your
dad in all this?
He went out for
a pack of cigarettes
and never came back.
He said, "Smell you later."
But he never smelled me again!
(SOBS)
Nelson, how would
you like to earn
some extra money
around our house?
I have some odd
jobs my kids won't do.
Yeah.
I get the feeling
Bart isn't everything
he could be in
the son department.
Uh, sometimes I think
he's more interested
in his Itchy and Mitchy
cartoons than me.
Hey, I'm sure
it's just a phase.
Like when I used to
stand on the overpass
and drop computers
on the freeway.
Uh-huh. That's how
we got our Kaypro!
LISA: 64, 65, 66.
Hey, Lisa.
Are you counting
how many days it takes
to wash your big butt?
(BOTH GIGGLING)
I can't hear you.
That's because your
butt blocks your ears.
That doesn't make any sense.
Neither does your butt!
(GIGGLING)
(GRUNTS)
I know this
obsession with thinness
is unhealthy
and anti-feminist.
But that's what
a fat girl would say.
Lise, look!
(GASPS)
Now I know there's
a handsome young man behind
all that hair and dirt.
Hmm. Maybe not.
But you did a great job
on the lawn!
Thanks, dingus.
I mean, ma'am.
My mother. My bully. My God!
Lisa, just take a bite.
One bite,
that's all I ask.
(GROANS)
Now I can't have
toothpaste tonight.
Oh!
(DOORBELL RINGS)
Here's the money
you gave my son.
We don't want your charity.
I didn't give
your son charity.
I gave him self-respect.
(SCOFFS)
Self-respect, huh?
No wonder he came
home with his vest
all buttoned like
he was somebody.
Go home to your son,
Mrs. Muntz.
And try not to
have intercourse
on the way!
(MEOWS)
Nelson, what are you
doing out this late?
My mom ditched me.
She went to Hollywood
to be an actress.
But her range is limited.
(SOBS)
Oh!
She's still your mother.
Come inside.
Hmm?
Can I get you
a glass of milk?
Cow milk?
Uh-huh.
(YAWNS)
(BART GASPS)
What are you
doing in myjammies?
I'm your new roommate.
I call top bunk.
But it's a single bed.
I said top bunk!
(HUMMING)
Mom, the reason God
invented deadbolts
is to keep
people like Nelson
out of your house.
Bart, have you ever
eaten a Tootsie Pop?
You know there's
a tough crunchy shell.
But if you lick it,
there's a delicious
sweetness inside.
Be nice to Nelson
and I'll give
you a Tootsie Pop.
Morning, losers.
Mrs. Simpson.
Pancakes! My favorite!
(MUNCHING)
Bart, eat up or
you'll be late for school.
I'm not hungry.
(GRUNTS)
You heard the lady!
Clean your plate!
Savor it.
Let the flavors
dance on your palate.
Mmm, mmm.
ANNOUNCER: Next on ABC.
Who's Dropping by
to See George Lopez?
We Pray it's you!
Open.
Nelson, doesn't that
hurt your teeth?
(SHRUGS) My teeth hurt
all the time. I just try
to think about motorcycles.
I don't like
the sound of that.
Tomorrow I'm taking you
to Dr. Shapiro.
A doctor? For your teeth?
What's next?
A lawyer for your hair?
(SNIGGERING)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
NELSON: (SINGING)
Papa, can you hear me?
Papa, can you see me?
Papa, can you
find me in the night?
Papa, are you near me?
Papa, can you hear me?
Papa, can you help me
not be frightened?
Looking at the skies
I seem to see a million eyes
Which ones are yours?
(SOBBING)
I gotta do
something about him.
(DOOR OPENS)
Huh?
(CLATTERING)
This is the perfect test.
If I can have
one dab of frosting
and then stop,
I'll know I've
conquered food at last.
That was too easy.
(CHUCKLES)
Okay. If I stop here,
I still have some dignity.
(LAUGHING)
Well, at least she's
not singing Streisand.
(LAUGHING)
Hey, Lise, still
insecure about your body?
(CLEARS THROAT)
Yeah, a little.
Those mean girls
just get to me.
I understand.
I have a sister,
I think she's dead now,
who had the same problem.
And I know just the solution.
Sherri, Terri.
The only thing
sweeter than you two,
are these stolen cookies.
Enjoy-
(BOTH GIGGLING)
Thank you, Nelson.
(SCREAMING)
(CHUCKUNG)
(ALL SINGING)
Sherri smells, Terri smells
Stinky all the way
Stink, stink, stink.
Stink, stink, stink
One horse open sleigh
(BOTH SCREAMING)
Thank you, Nelson.
He who ha-ha's last,
ha-ha's best.
I really appreciate
you teaching those
mean girls a lesson.
Tomorrow I can
bleach a swear word
into their hair.
I'd like that.
Nelson?
Papa!
You came back!
(SOBBING)
I never meant to
leave you, Nelson.
But something awful happened
when I went to the store.
Well, that explains a lot.
Who's hungry?
No. I want to hear
what happened at the store.
Well, I went in
to buy cigarettes.
Can you gift
wrap them, please?
They're for my son.
I also bought
myself a candy bar.
Which unfortunately
was filled with peanuts,
to which I am allergic.
(INCOHERENT BABBLING)
I ran outside just as a circus
was rolling into town.
(CYMBALS PLPOHNG)
(INCOHERENT BABBLING)
(LAUGHING)
BART:
And that's where I found him.
I brought him back here
so he could take Nelson away
and my bruises would heal.
I want to give you
a home again, son.
MRS. MUNTZ:
And so do I.
Mom!
I got an acting job
from the third
director I slept with.
I play Lady Macbeth.
I don't have to
take my top off,
but I do anyway.
Well, I'm glad everything
worked out so well.
Yep. The Muntzes
are back in business.
Yep, the four Muntzes!
(GROANS)
Thanks for
finding my dad, Bart.
And thanks, lady,
for making me feel
good about myself.
So now that
you're happy again,
I guess you won't beat me up
at school anymore.
I wish it were
that simple.
I really do.
They're a family again,
and so are we.
What happened?
Hmm. Sometimes you have
to adopt your son's bully
in order to bring your
own family temporarily closer.
And Lisa,
what have you learned?
Nothing.
Like many women,
I still have an
unhealthy obsession
with my weight.
But talking about
the problem is the
first step towards
a solution, right?
I guess. But there's
a long way to go.
(GRUNTS IMPATIENTLY)
Come on,
say something conclusive.
I'm afraid this is
a very open-ended problem.
HOMER: Oh, open-ended?
Come on, Lisa.
Say everything's fine.
(IN FEMALE VOICE)
"Everything's fine."
LISA: That was you.
HOMER: Prove it.
(HOMER CHUCKLES)