CHORUS: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(theme music playing)
(bell ringing)
(whistle blows)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
(tires sreeching)
(honking horn)
D'oh! (screams)
(tires screeching)
Whoo-hoo!
♪ You put the beer in the
coconut and drink it all up ♪
♪ You put the beer
in the coconut ♪
♪ And throw the can away... ♪
Homer!
♪ You throw the can away... ♪
I said, "Homer!"
♪ You throw the can away ♪
Marge, I'm out of beer.
You know, Homie, a lot of men
use their Saturdays
to do things around the house.
Hint, hint.
But, Marge,
I'm not like other men.
That's why you buy my pants
at that special store.
I'm serious. You never finished
painting the garage...
And you could at least
get that snake out of the piano.
-(playing dance hall tune)
-(snake hissing)
Fine. I'll drop everything
I'm doing just for you.
But you'll have to live with the
guilt of ruining my Saturday.
Can you live with that, Marge?
Huh? Can you?
-Yup!
-Can you?
Oh...
FLANDERS: God... bless him!
Excuse me, I have
a few questions for Pop.
That's me.
You're Pop?
No offense, but even
I could kick your ass.
Hey, get off my case.
The only reason
I'm working here is
'cause I'm trying to get
a date with Mom.
Look, Pop, I'm planning
some expert home repairs
and I need a pair of
bolt cutters or wire cutters,
or something to get
the lock off my toolbox.
Aisle one,
next to the cat poison.
Edna, look. A dimmer switch
could ratchet up the romance
in our love nest.
You mean
the janitor's closet? Ha!
(sighs) What's the matter, Edna?
Lately you just say "ha"
to everything.
I want a baby... now.
Why don't we continue this
in Pool Supplies?
Hi, I'm Doug Vaccaro.
You know me as Chip,
the wisecracking assistant
on the hit sitcom
Toolin' Around.
(snickering) A man in an apron.
(guffawing)
But today, I'm here as a "tool"
of Global Dynamics Corp.
You know, installing your own
barbecue pit is no harder
than adding an aviary
or Olympic-sized swimming pool.
In fact, it's a snap.
Or if you're not into chicken...
No, no! I'm into chicken!
How about wild boar,
or swordfish,
or hippo?
Mmm... Hippo.
(gurgling)
ANNOUNCER: Light-hearted apron
not included.
Snapping fingers
may not make food appear.
How about it, Bart?
Would you like
a new backyard barbecue pit?
Can I burn evidence in it?
We can all burn evidence in it.
There. That wasn't so hard,
was it, honey?
Dad, I really need
to rest my back.
OK, sweetie. Daddy'll take over.
Oh, yeah.
That's a fine-looking...
-(contents breaking)
-D'oh!
OK, no big deal.
(straining)
(shrieks) Stupid Lisa!
(whimpering) I got
to build fast. Cement drying!
All right, let's see.
Oh... English side ruined.
Must use French instructions.
"Le grille"?
What the hell is that?
Aw, come here... Get... (grunts)
Come on, fit. You...
(mumbling)
Huh? (grunting)
(sighs)
Yeah, that's one
fine-looking barbecue pit.
Why doesn't mine look like that?
(screaming)
Why? (grunts) Why?
Why must life be so hard?
Why must I fail
in every attempt at masonry?
(screaming and sobbing)
How's your father's project
coming along?
I think he's almost done.
(screaming)
Yeah, he's done.
(clears throat) I'd like
to return this barbecue kit.
All returned items
must be in a box
and accompanied by a receipt.
Well, if you'll follow
the flashlight,
you'll see the receipt
embedded here, and here,
and elements of the box here,
here, and possibly here.
Sorry, I didn't get
this hammer hat
by handing out refunds.
Oh!
(grunting) Come on.
Hold on, there, Santa Claus.
That box is for toys only.
Well, of course.
Any kid would love to have this,
uh, activity center.
It teaches them
while they learn.
Yeah, nice try, Saint Nick.
Now, hit the road, Kris Kringle.
-But... but...
-You heard me, "Pear" Noel.
(groans)
-What you got there?
-Beanie Baby.
(wheels rattling)
I'll never get rid of it.
It'll follow me
to the ends of the Earth.
(clanking and scraping)
All right! My bumper fell off!
-(scraping)
-(honking and tires screeching)
Not my fault. Act of God.
Act of God. (laughing)
Uh-oh.
Ah...
(tires screeching)
♪ Shaving my shoulders ♪
♪ I'm getting it
all shaved off ♪
Homie, someone's at the door.
They want to talk to you
about some sort of car accident.
Take the kids out back.
I'll handle this.
Mr. Simpson?
I believe something of yours
struck my car yesterday.
Oh, yeah. Prove it.
That's your license plate,
isn't it?
Uh...
(sobbing)
All right, just go ahead
and sue me!
Everybody else does.
The average settlement
is $68,000.
(chuckling)
I'm not here to sue you.
My name is Astrid Weller.
I own an art gallery
and I'd love to display
your piece.
You mean this hunk of junk?
This isn't art.
It's just the barbecue
that pushed me over the edge.
Didn't you? Didn't you?
You stupid... (screams)
Art isn't just pretty pictures.
It's an expression
of raw human emotion.
In your case, rage.
Oh, I got that, lady.
Is everything OK?
I got worried when
I didn't hear any shots.
This lady says I'm an artist.
You? An artist?
Your husband's work
is what we call "outsider art."
It could be by a mental patient,
or a hillbilly, or a chimpanzee.
(gasps) In high school,
I was voted
"Most likely to be
a mental patient,
hillbilly, or chimpanzee."
Well, you should be
very excited,
because outsider art
couldn't be hotter.
So you'd better catch the fever.
Catch it.
(munching)
Dad, chew with
your mouth closed.
You're losing your mystique.
Lisa, all great artists
love free food.
Check out Jasper Johns.
You squeal on me, I'll kill you.
Mmm. I don't know.
I studied art for years,
but I just don't get this.
Sounds like somebody's jealous.
No, I'm not.
I just can't believe some people
are paying hundreds of dollars
for something a hillbilly
pulled out of the trash.
Hey, I done studied for years
on how to get over
that junkyard fence.
Then I learnt the gate was open.
Smithers, I think I'm in love...
-(gasps)
-...with this sculpture.
Sir, that's by Homer Simpson.
I don't think
you want to buy it.
Smithers, years ago,
I blew the chance
to buy Picasso's
Guernica for a song.
Luckily, that song
was "White Christmas."
And by hanging on to it,
I made billions.
Anyway, I love
this hideous thing.
Young lady, I'll take it.
Congratulations, Homer.
You're now
a professional artist.
Whoo-hoo!
Look, Marge, my first sale!
In your face Jasper Johns!
Huh?
(grunting)
Where are you going
with that junk, Dad?
I'm going to be
an outsider artist.
That way, I can turn
all these old baseball cards,
Disney memorabilia and antiques
into something valuable.
Homie, I'm really happy
you sold your sculpture,
but don't you think
it may have been a fluke?
Hey, I've always had
an interest in art
dating back
to my schoolgirl days,
when I painted portrait
after portrait of Ringo Starr.
That's my life
you're describing.
I think I remember
my own life, Marge.
Astrid said the key to my art
is anger, but you know me.
-I'm Mr. Mellow.
-BOTH: Hmm?
So, I'm giving you kids
permission to get me mad.
Come on. Gimme what you got.
Well, if it'll help, um...
Mom found out her engagement
ring is made of rock candy.
(grunting) Good work, honey.
Keep it coming.
Well, I'm flunking math,
and the other day
I was a little attracted
to Milhouse.
(yelling)
(screaming)
Moe, this is Astrid, my dealer.
And these are my fans,
Gunter, Kyoto
and Cecil
Hampstead-on-Cecil-Cecil.
So, uh, you guys
are Eurotrash, huh?
How's that, uh,
working out for you?
Eh, to be honest, we are adrift
in a sea of decadent luxury
and meaningless sex.
Uh-huh. So, where might
this sea be located? Hmm?
I must get back to my hotel
and practice
my affectations for tomorrow.
[in French] Bon soir.
[in English] What do we
owe you, Moe?
Nothing, nothing.
Just give me a priceless sketch
with a certificate
of authenticity.
All right. (mumbling)
Hey, Moe, could I pay
with a drawing?
Yeah, nice try, there, 12-step.
Aw!
Uh, Homer, you're making us
a little bit uncomfortable.
Relax, big guy. He's just doing
this for his art. Right, Homer?
Oh, yeah... art.
Why won't you be art? (grunts)
Here he is.
This is where the magic happens.
Wonderful news, Homer.
Is it about pies?
Uh, um, no.
We're going to hold a show
devoted entirely to you.
Wow. It's like Marge's dream
come true for me.
Isn't that great, Marge? For me.
(Marge groaning)
Look, Marge. They're advertising
my show in Art in America.
It's the first time I've been
mentioned there that I know of.
I'm happy for you.
Now, good night.
Good night.
You're upset about something.
Is this about that trip
Barney and I took
to Machu Picchu?
Now, Homer,
being an artist was my dream.
But now, without even trying,
you've accomplished
more in a week
than I have in my whole life.
Aw, honey,
I've always liked your art.
Your paintings look like
the things they look like.
That's sweet, but...
How would you like it if I,
I don't know,
entered a belching contest?
Frankly, I'd be
a little turned on.
(sighs) You don't understand.
Marge, I've screwed up
everything I've ever done.
I mean, look at Bart.
But I finally found something
where people worship me
for screwing up,
and that feels pretty good.
I guess nothing else matters
as long as you're happy.
Now you're making sense.
Good night.
(Homer snoring)
(indistinct chattering)
-Then I bought a Rembrandt.
-(burps)
Homer is the most dangerous
artist on the Springfield scene.
Now, let's see what surprises
he has for us tonight.
(applause)
I give you "botched hibachi."
The tricycle's on loan from
the Maggie Simpson collection.
This piece I call
"failed shelving unit
with stupid, stuck chainsaw
and applesauce."
And finally,
my thing de resistance,
"attempted birdhouse one."
(cawing)
(appalled murmuring)
Shall we start the bidding at,
say, $10,000?
(indistinct throat-clearing)
All right, how about a million?
I'll give you two bucks for
the bird if it's still alive.
What's going on here?
You weirdos love this stuff.
Homer, I'm afraid they only
love what's new and shocking.
These pieces are just like
your earlier work.
You've gone from hip to boring.
Why don't you call us
when you get to kitsch?
(strained laugh)
Come on, Gunter, Kyoto.
If we hurry, we can still catch
the heroin craze. Mm.
Wait! Come back!
I'm a God to you!
Worship me
or fear my wrath!
Oh, please, fear my wrath!
Please!
Call me.
I don't get it.
Why don't people
like my art anymore?
Homer, I know you worked hard,
but all of your things
were kind of the same.
Hey, Ray Jay Johnson
never changed his act.
And he's more popular now
than he's ever been.
Who?
♪ You can call him Ray ♪
♪ Or you can call him Jay ♪
♪ Or you can call him Ray-Jay ♪
♪ But you doesn't have to... ♪
I'm sick of him already.
The point is, great artists
are always trying new things.
Like Michelangelo,
or Shaquille O'Neal.
You just need some inspiration.
It's so exciting to do
something cultural together.
Matt Groening?
What's he doing in a museum?
He can barely draw.
Ow! Oh, no! I'm being erased!
Move it, bub. We got
an installation to installate.
Mm, a Claes Oldenburg.
He's a European
who defied convention
and embraced
American popular culture.
(whistles)
He must be 100 feet tall.
Now this is a Joseph Turner.
In an era when everyone else
painted portraits,
he broke away by painting
the Venetian canals.
It's glorious. The streets are
paved with water.
You could ride a walrus to work.
And Picasso started out
painting realistically,
then moved on to cubism.
By the end of his life,
he was just painting
crank letters to the editor.
they call it his
"angry jerk" period.
(gurgling)
Mm... Split-pea.
(gasping) With ham!
Any ideas yet?
No. These guys are geniuses.
I could never think of something
like soup or a pencil.
Oh!
I'm just going to rest
for a minute.
(snoring)
(growling)
(sniffing)
What the... Who the... Hey!
(karate yell)
(yelping) You're mean.
(playing happy Spanish music)
-(guns cocking)
-Hasta la vista, baby!
(machine gun firing)
(moaning)
Hmm? (groans) What the...
Ew!
(gasps) D'oh!
(grunts) Soup's on, fat boy.
Ow! (screams) No!
Ow! No! Ow! No. No.
-Andy, no!
-Homer. Homer!
Marge! Oh, why does art hate me?
I never did anything to art.
Oh. Let's get out of here.
Well, Dad, if the museum
didn't inspire you,
maybe you should do something
really radical, like Christo.
Is he that jerk that revealed
the magician's secrets?
No. Christo is
a conceptual artist
who does huge outdoor projects.
He once wrapped
the Reichstag in plastic.
Not the Reichstag!
Oh, yes, and he also set up
hundreds of yellow umbrellas
-along the California highway.
-Why did he do that?
To make the world a more
magical place, I guess,
Although they did blow over
and kill some people.
Killer umbrellas?
Of course.
Exquisite.
No, Dad. No. My point is,
you have to do
something big and daring.
Big? Daring? Lisa, that's it!
I've got an idea
for a wonderful art project
that'll make everyone
love me again.
Step one, steal all
the doormats in town.
Hit the road, "Welcome home."
Adios , "Casa de Flanders."
See ya in hell,
"God bless this house."
So long, "The Simpsons."
D'oh!
HOMER: Step two,
snorkel the animals.
(panting) It wasn't easy
But I got all the grizzlies.
Great. I'll do the pony
while you do the lions.
Make sure you
strap 'em on real tight.
Now, step three.
Are you sure this is art
and not vandalism?
That's for the courts
to decide, son.
-(water gurgling)
-(birds chirping)
(creaking)
HOMER: Wake up!
Wake up, Springfield!
I've got a surprise for you.
Oh, Lord, what now?
(dolphin clicking)
Oh, that can't be good.
People of Springfield,
behold, my latest work!
Homer, what have you done?
It's conceptual art.
The grand canals of Springfield.
Just like Venice, without the
black plague. What do you think?
I think some people
are going to be upset.
I love it, Homer.
You've turned this town
into a work of art.
I just wish Jasper Johns
hadn't stolen my boat.
-(screams)
-So long, suckers!
Well, they're in the business.
Real people might not be
so understanding.
FLANDERS: What the flood?
Maude, it's a miracle!
The Lord has drowned the wicked
and spared the righteous.
(gasps) Isn't that
Homer Simpson?
Ugh. Looks like heaven's easier
to get into than Arizona State.
Oh! I hate these flood pants.
Hey! They're working!
My feet are soaked,
but my cuffs are bone-dry.
Everything's comin' up,
Milhouse.
BURN VICTIMS: Ah...
[singing in Italian]
♪ Arrivederci ♪
♪ Roma ♪
Edna, I'm going to
pop you a question.
I hope the answer is yes.
Do you think mother would like
this hat pin?
Oh... yes.
Oh, you've made me
the happiest man on Earth.
Well, Homer, I have to admit,
you created something
people really love.
You truly are an artist.
No, I'm just a nut
who couldn't build a barbecue.
You'll always be
the artist in the family.
Aw.
-Is that our house?
-Yep.
-And is that us on the roof?
-That's us.
Are we kissing?
Ooh, I don't know. Could be.
I need some inspiration.
[singing in Italian]
♪ Arrivederci ♪
♪ Roma ♪
JASPER JOHNS: Yoink.
♪ It's time for us to part ♪
♪ Save the wedding bells
for my returning ♪
♪ Keep my lover's arms
outstretched and yearning ♪
♪ Please be sure the flame
of love keeps burning ♪
♪ In her heart ♪
(audience murmuring)
Shh!
Captioned by
Visual Data Media Services