(SINGING) The Simpsons
(TIRES SCREECHING)
D'oh!
(EXCLAIMING)
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
(YOWLING)
EDNA:
Good news, children.
This Friday, we'll be holding
a school-wide
medieval festival.
Medieval?
Like Lord of the Rings?
No. Not at all.
(ALL GROAN)
Can't we just
keep going forward
in our textbooks?
No! Now I've already
assigned each of you
a role in the medieval court.
Martin, you shall
be our king.
I shall pattern my reign
on Enguerrand the Seventh,
Sire de Coucy!
Tralloo trallay!
EDNA: Not so fast, Nelson.
You're one of
King Martin's guards.
Ha ha!
You'll pay for this!
My Liege.
What am I gonna be?
Black Knight? Court Ninja?
Bart the Impaler!
Bart, you'll be
playing the village cooper.
What kind
of a knight
is that?
The kind of knight
that makes barrels
and isn't a knight. Ha!
Ay, caramba!
Well, this stinks.
But I bet Lisa got
something even stupider.
(FANFARE PLAYS)
Hmm?
All hail the Queen!
Now, as queen,
you shall be entitled
to eat the same French fries
the teachers do.
The ones made from potatoes?
The very same.
(INDISTINCT TALKING)
My coat of arms
is a Spiderman
couchant on a field vert.
What's "couchant" mean?
Lying down.
(GROANS)
You mean like you?
Now what does
"vert" mean?
Say it means punching.
Oh, Willie,
during the festival,
you'll be wearing these
urine-soaked rags.
You're the village idiot.
Now, allow me to apply this
rubber cement to your face
to represent
the ravages of plague.
Ach! My face!
What drunken call girl
will have me now? Oh!
(RENAISSANCE MUSIC PLAYING)
Now, peasants,
since the Middle Ages
had no compact disks
or Super Mario men,
people found entertainment
in abusing the village idiot.
So let history
come alive.
ALL: Yeah!
Wait! Let me take out
my contact lenses!
(GROANS)
Pelt all you want.
But revenge will be Willie's!
(SCREAMS) That was a stapler!
(SINGING)
Dragon in the dungeon
Maiden in my lair
There's potions
in my Wizard's pot
Now drink it if you dare
Lute solo!
Yeah! (GRUNTS)
(ALL GASPING)
(LAUGHS)
Cooper! More pink lemon-ale!
(ALE SLOSHING)
(GRUNTING)
Cooper, thy staves
are not flush.
Whoa!
(ALL LAUGHING)
You'll pay for this,
my queen.
Guards, take him
to the tower!
(SHUDDERS)
(GRUNTS)
Where is
the tower?
It's the backseat
of my Merkur.
There's 37 cents
in the coin caddy
and stay out of my diary!
(RATS SQUEAKING)
Quiet, my pretties.
Soon, we'll have revenge
on those who mocked me!
Also on those who
were kind to me.
And on the parents
who took time
from their busy schedules
to make today
such a success.
Oh, I hate them all!
Noble idiot,
bring in the pie!
(TRUMPETS PLAYING)
I dedicate this pie
to the backbone
of the feudal system.
The serfs!
(ALL SCREAMING)
(CACKLING)
Scary McBeasties,
nibble and gnaw
at their overstuffed buttocks!
Milhouse,
don't open your mouth!
Whoa! (GAGGING)
(ALL SCREAMING)
(CLATTERING)
This is no accident.
(LAUGHING)
Nice party, dink.
You're responsible
for this, Simpson.
No way!
I didn't do it!
Unlike all the other stuff
I told you I didn't do
which I did.
Bart, I'm sick
of playing
the tomfool!
You are hereby
expelled from
Springfield Elementary!
Boy, I can't believe
you got expelled!
Well, don't expect
to spend all week
lying around
on the couch
like a bum!
'Cause that's my thing!
Bart, a school-sponsored
medieval festival
is supposed to be
the best day of
a young girl's life.
And you ruined it!
You deserved
to be expelled!
I didn't do it!
Mom, you believe me,
don't you?
Bart, I love you.
But sometimes
ldon%love
your choices.
(SIGHS)
Now we have to find
another school for you.
And if you get
kicked out of
that one,
you're going
straight in the army
where you'll be sent
straight to America's
latest military quagmire.
Where will it be?
North Korea, Iran?
Anything's possible with
Commander Cuckoo Bananas
in charge!
Bart, this could be
a good new school.
Oakwood Academy! Huh?
Mom, that's a school
for the blind.
Think of the leg up
you'd have.
How can we afford
any of these
private schools?
They're all
so expensive.
If we want to throw
good money after bad,
why don't we just
get Grampa
that new pacemaker?
I need two
double-A batteries, now!
Get 'em from
the smoke detector.
What if
there's a fire?
The smoke
will wake us up.
How about this one?
St. Jerome's Catholic School.
Catholic schools are usually
the most affordable
private schools.
Catholic school, eh?
That'll straighten
you out, boy.
There you don't just
get bad grades,
you go to hell!
Oh! Oh, no!
(SCREAMING)
My pacemaker!
(BEEPING)
Classic Grampa!
Class, we have
a new student.
Bart, would you like
to introduce yourself?
Hi, I'm Bart Simpson.
Ay, caramba. Do the Bartman,
et cetera, et cetera.
(VIDEOGAME BEEPING)
(GRUNTS)
In the old days,
we'd use a ruler
to deal with
incorrigibles like you.
Thanks for
the history lesson, Sis.
These days,
we use a yardstick!
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMS)
I'll show you.
I'll move 33 inches away.
A yard's 36!
(SCREAMS)
(GROANING)
Now you tell me.
I don't know
what they taught you
in public school.
But at St. Jerome's,
we don't tolerate
back sass.
Stretch out your arms
like our Lord on the cross.
Now hold these dictionaries.
Now think what
it would be like
if you had nails
in your hands.
Well, I guess they'd help me
hold the dictionaries up.
Wrong answer!
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMS)
Stupid Catholic school.
Suffering from
my hip attitude.
I'm the real Jesus here.
(MAN LAUGHING)
So, it's sacrilege
you're spoutin' now.
What's it to you, Irish?
My name's Father Sean.
And I used to be
an ornery wee cuss myself.
Until one day
after a drunken brawl
with me dad...
(BOTH GRUNTING)
You're just like
your mother!
Can't take a punch!
(GROANING)
FATHER SEAN:
I was laying in the gutter
picking up my teeth
when Saint Peter himself
appears before me.
Sean, you wanker...
He says.
Repent of
your wicked ways
or sod off.
Then he gobbed in my face
and turned back
into a streetlight.
And that's how
I came to the Church.
Well, I'm only here
because I got blamed
for a prank I didn't do!
Mmm-hmm.
Call me crazy,
but I believe you.
You do?
Of course I do.
You know, lots of
church types started off
as rotten wee buggers.
St. Augustine himself
got his start stealing pears.
Stealing pairs of what?
Hubcaps, Reeboks,
human eyes?
It's all in here.
See for yourself.
Cool!
Sister Thomasina,
I've taken the liberty
of knocking the vinegar
out of him.
He's all yours.
Yeah, whatever.
Now, class,
open your math books
to the word problems
of our Lord.
"Billy and Joseph
start their penance
at the same time.
"If each swear word
brings 1,000 years in hell..."
BART: "Saint Sebastian was
a pious Roman soldier.
"For preaching Christianity
to the Romans,
"the Emperor Diocletian
sentenced him to death
by hail of arrows."
(GROANS)
Now it's payback time!
(GRUNTING)
I wish I'd gone
to more orgies.
(GROANS)
Wow! This stuff is great!
It's way better
than the comics
I get at the dentist!
Then Father Sean
quoted Eminem
in his sermon.
And in art class,
we painted Saint Joan
burning at the stake.
And mine
was the grossest.
(CACKLING) Catholics rock!
(MUTTERS)
Bart, I'm glad
you had fun.
But I wouldn't get
too into that
Catholic church
with all the sitting
and standing and kneeling.
It's like Simon Says
without a winner.
Mom, that's blasphemy.
I'll say
a rosary for you.
Don't you touch
bead one! (GRUNTS)
Homer, maybe
we should be concerned.
Catholics can be
a peculiar bunch.
No birth control,
no meat on Friday.
No meat?
What do they eat?
Light bulbs?
Let's just change
the subject.
Bart, would you
like to say grace?
Yes'm.
In nomine Patris
et fillii et Spiritus Sancti.
Bart, what the hell
are you saying?
That's Latin, Dad.
The language of Plutarch.
Mickey Mouse's dog?
No. Plutarch!
He chronicled the lives
of the Roman emperors.
Oh! I didn't need
that new fact!
Now I forgot
who won Bud Bowl VIII.
Boy, I'm pulling you
out of that crazy school!
(GRUNTING)
Hey!
I'm Bart Simpson's father.
And I'm sick of you
teaching my son
your time-tested values.
(SNIFFS)
Hey, what's that smell?
We're having our monthly
pancake dinner.
Care to join us?
You've transformed
breakfast into dinner.
It's a miracle!
Log Cabin, full of taste,
my stomach is with thee.
Blessed art thou
among syrups.
And bless...
No praying
to the condiments!
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
Que buenos
cake-os de pan-o!
Oh, boy!
Oh. yeah! Good!
Um...
All pancakes aside,
I really came here
to talk about my son.
I understand.
But can it wait
until after Bingo?
Bingo?
That's my favorite game.
I just can't remember
what to yell out
when you win.
"Bingo."
That's my favorite game.
I just can't remember
what to yell out
when you win.
Oh! How about
you just say,
"Yay, l won!"
Bingo!
I've never seen
such masterful
Bingo playing.
What's your secret, Homer?
(WHISPERS)
You have to cheat!
Uh, listen.
Is it true
you priest guys
can't ever...
(MUTTERS) You know...
I'll admit,
the vow of celibacy
is one of
our sterner challenges.
Celibacy?
I was talking about the meat
on Friday thing!
Man, you guys
got more crazy rules
than Blockbuster Video!
Well, that's true.
But if you do break a rule,
you can always find absolution
in the sacrament
of confession.
Wait, wait, wait.
No matter what I did,
no matter how many people
lost their pensions,
it's forgiven like that?
If you truly repent,
then yes.
Okay! Let's make
some magic here.
I wiped a booger
on your shirt.
I made a dog and a cat kiss.
I swiped a bolted down TV
from a Holiday Inn,
I coveted the wife
in Jaws 2,
I lied to a waiter,
I masturbated
eight billion times,
and I have no plans
to stop masturbating
in the future.
Whoo-hoo! I'm clean!
In your face, Lord!
Um, not quite,
Mr. Simpson.
I can only absolve you
if you're a Catholic.
Right.
And how do I join?
Do I whale on
some Unitarians?
Well, it's a little harder
than that.
It begins by
looking inside yourself.
(MOANS)
But it ends with
bread and wine.
Whoo-hoo!
Homer, you've been
out all night.
And you look like
you've accepted someone
as your personal
something.
Were you at that
Catholic church?
Look, Marge.
I know I was supposed
to yell at that priest.
But he's so cool!
He plays drums in a band
with a bunch of other priests!
I knew they'd try
to convert you!
That's what they do!
Well, I'm not having
another 12 kids!
Marge, no one is saying 12.
Nine, 10, tops. See?
Forget it!
And you know, I went to
a Catholic wedding once.
The incense
ruined my pantsuit!
Marge, relax.
I never heard of anyone
getting so upset
about religion.
(INAUDIBLE)
(ORGAN PLAYING)
Marge is here
all alone.
I heard her son
is Catholic now.
Her husband, too.
(GROANS)
Marge, all by yourself today?
Well, Homer
and Bart are...
Well, they're under
the weather.
Mmm-hmm.
Under the weather?
Or under the spell of a man
in a pointy white hat?
All right. I admit it!
They're both at
the Catholic church!
Reverend,
what should I do?
Marge, this calls for
an emergency meeting
of the church's
spiritual council.
To Stuckey's!
Bart and Homer
can't go Catholic.
Romans have been
separate from us
since the Schism of Lourdes
in 1573.
And that was about
our holy right
to come to church
with wet hair!
Which we've
since abolished.
I guess it's good that
they're taking an interest
in spirituality.
Oh, spirituality's
great, Marge.
Hey, I'm Mr. Spiritual.
But remember,
a different faith
means a different afterlife.
Hmm...
Marge Simpson,
welcome to Protestant Heaven.
Through in one?
Hurrah.
Poppy, have you
seen Dash?
Where's Homer and Bart?
(GASPS)
(MARIACHI MUSIC PLAYING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GROANS) Wow! Up here,
that feels good!
Now dance,
you heavenly gobs!
(IRISH MUSIC PLAYING)
Oh, I wish my family
was with me.
Sorry, Marge.
They're just
not our sort.
Well, then I'd like to
speak with Jesus.
I'm afraid
he's gone native.
(LAUGHING)
Whoa! Stop it!
Guys, I'm serious!
No!
Don't worry, Marge.
We'll get your boy back.
Excuse me.
That better be decaf.
The rim is orange,
ain't it?
Or does under-tipping
make you color blind?
Her husband's
sleeping with her sister.
Who said that?
So now what do we call it
when the communion wafer
becomes the body of Christ?
(GRUNTING)
KEVIN: Hey!
Yes, Homer?
Transubstantiation.
Very good.
He cheated.
He's got it written
on his arm.
(HOMER LAUGHING)
Welcome to
the jungle, Kevin!
(GASPS)
First communion?
Oh, we've gotta
stop 'em now!
Once they seal the deal,
there's no turning back!
Just like the Jews
with their snippety-snip.
Bart, get your things!
You're leaving with me!
Sorry, Mom. But this
is a Catholic church.
Chicks don't have
any authority here.
Mrs. Simpson, please.
If there's a problem,
I'm sure we can talk it over.
Back off,
Pope-y LaPew!
Marge, what are you
doing here?
Homer,
you're physically an adult.
And what you do
in the privacy
of your own soul
is your business.
But I didn't change
Bart's diapers
for five years
to see him
become a Catholic!
I thought
there was a monster
in the potty.
Let's go! (GRUNTS)
I think
we've lost them.
They weren't
following us.
Then why
did I drive through
that barn?
Oh! Why did you guys
have to take me away?
You're always nagging me
to go to church.
And now that I am,
it's the wrong one.
I just don't think
your father's
the right person
to pick out
a religion for you.
Okay. I'll pick
a religion for me.
Judaism.
(SINGING)
Don't have a cow, man
Have a piece of fish
Oy!
Bart, we're here
to bring you back
to the one true faith,
the Western Branch
of American Reform
Presbylutheranism.
(HAWAII FIVE-O RINGTONE)
Hello, Homer.
Marge, you bring
Bart home now!
Once you go Vatican,
you can't go back again!
It wasn't
a fair fight!
Your church
suckered him in
with gory stories!
Just like we were
suckered into
getting Cinemax!
Face it, Marge.
Catholics rule.
We got Boston, South America,
the good part of Ireland,
and we're making
serious inroads
in Mozambique, baby!
Well, I'm gonna show Bart
that Protestants
can be hip, too.
How do you like
those croutons?
Oh! Why does that woman
thwart my sporadic interest
in my children?
Shouldn't Bart and I be able
to choose our own religion
if we want to?
Strange as it sounds, Dad,
I agree with you.
Huh?
Everyone should be able
to choose their faith.
Just like I chose Buddhism.
Buddhism?
VVell, l guess
lots of kids have
imaginary friends.
I'll ignore that.
In fact,
I'm gonna help you.
I have a pretty good idea
where they are.
We can't lose Bart
now that we're so close.
If I do, I'll be
the worst priest ever.
Well, except for, you know...
Ahem!
Now, Bart, isn't this
the kind of religion
you'd like
to be a part of
for all eternity?
Ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome,
hot off their conversion
to Christianity,
the band once known
as Quiet Riot, Pious Riot!
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
(SINGING)
Come on, feel the Lord
Heaven's your reward
We'll get saved,
saved,saved
What's wrong, Bart?
You love youth culture.
Mom, a religion isn't cool
just because they've
glommed onto some crappy
rock band from the 1940s.
Hey, we've played
more state fairs
than The Beatles!
Yeah, that's right.
That's right.
You just don't get it.
I've made a sacred commitment
to the Catholic Church
and... (GASPS)
Paintball! Awesome!
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMS)
Die! Die! Die!
Oh, Bart, I knew
one of these dumb things
would work.
Mmm.
(GASPS) My hive!
My trademark hive!
Hop in, boy.
We'll show your mother
our God
kicks her God's butt.
Back off,
you servants
of the Holy See!
(GUNS COCKING)
Easy on the zeal, church-os.
I've got something to say.
Don't you get it?
It's all Christianity, people.
The little stupid
differences are nothing
next to the big
stupid similarities!
He's right!
Can't we all
get together
and concentrate
on our real enemies?
Monogamous gays
and stem cells?
Well said, mate.
Put 'er there.
(CHUCKLES)
My pleasure.
Note to self,
have hand re-blessed.
Bart, you've taught us all
an important lesson.
We Christians have been
niggling over details
for far too long.
Amen. And I hope that
from this day forward,
we all learn to take
Bart's message of tolerance
and understanding to heart.
We believe that
God's last prophet,
Bart Simpson,
preached a message
of tolerance and love.
We believe the holy Bartman
preached a message of
understanding and peace
before he was betrayed
by his follower, Milhouse,
and pulled apart
by snowmobiles
until he died.
ALL: Eat my shorts!
ALL: Cowabunga!
(ALL SHOUTING)
(EXPLOSION)
(IRISH MUSIC PLAYING)
(SHUSHING)