The Simpsons
D'oh!
What the...
Honey, I've got some
bad news for you.
Not now, Marge. I'm waiting
for the new XFL season!
Who will win this year's
million-dollar game?
Who? Who?
Honey.
The "X" is for "Extreme. "
There is no XFL
this year.
The league folded.
Who told you?
Last year's MVP.
He sweeps up toenails
at the beauty parlor.
Hello?
Hello.
This is the Springfield
Retirement Castle.
Your parent...
Abraham Simpson.
...is dead.
Oh, my God!
He died from...
Complications of
a medical nature.
The nursing home
was not responsible.
Homer, your father's dead.
And he never even
lived to be a vegetable.
I'm really gonna miss him.
It's Grampa's smell.
Oh, my dad never even
knew how I felt about him.
But you were very
open with your feelings.
Sure, I said I loved him,
but never that I was
in love with him.
What are you
crying about?
You don't have to live here.
Dad!
Grampa!
Stop it! You're
stretching out my skin.
What's got into you punks?
The home told
us you were dead.
Me? I ain't dead.
It was Stamson
down the hall.
So much for Mr. I Can
Button My Own Shirt.
Oh, Dad.
We've got what
people never get.
A second chance.
Yeah, there's so
many things we can...
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
We'll call you
or send you some fruit.
Look, Grampa.
You're already
getting a new neighbor.
Hi. I'm Zelda.
I put the "ass"
in assisted living.
Holy mac...
Abe Simpson's the name,
and now that you're here,
I'm changing
my instructions
to "do resuscitate. "
Now, let me show you around.
Over there are the preppies...
And over there's the comatose,
and the cool comatose.
Hey, who's the tall
drink of Maalox?
Are you young ladies
here to visit your mothers?
Eh, that's Zack.
He's as smooth as
a 50-year-old behind.
Who wants to go
get some sweet corn
in my minivan?
It's got a wheelchair lift.
If you can drive,
they're all over you.
I used to drive,
but they pulled my license.
Is this the Dairy Queen?
But Zelda, if you're
looking for something
with a big backseat
and a lot of gas,
I'm your man.
Oh!
You've never heard
Garrison Keillor
till you've heard him
through five speakers.
Tramp.
B-6.
You sunk my Scrabbleship.
This game makes no sense.
Tell that to the good men
who just lost their lives.
Semper Fi.
I want to drive again!
You? No way!
It's too dangerous.
Well, you're no
angel behind the wheel.
What about your DUl?
That was a DWI!
Give Grampa a chance.
Statistics show that
old people drive
at least as well
as sleep-deprived apes.
Please, Son.
Driving is my last
chance to feel alive.
Well, you brought me
into this world, so no!
Fine. I'm dead.
Dad, get up.
No, I'm dead.
Grampa, come on.
Dead!
Dead, dead, dead, dead, dead!
All right, Grampa.
I'll help you get
your license back.
Woo-hoo! And I want
driving gloves.
No way!
Dead, dead, dead, dead!
First of all, I'd like to ask
if anyone has any questions.
Yeah. Where's the men's room?
It's down the hall.
Okay. Now, let's pretend
that we're going for a drive.
Leo, slow down.
That looks like
a nice place to eat.
Carla's daughter works
in that building.
You know,
it's kind of ironic.
These old people
are being kept alive
by the organs
of the young people
they ran over.
Makes you think,
huh, Chief?
Not really.
Next!
Grampa's here to get
his driver's license.
Okay. Look at the eye chart
and cover your left eye.
That's my seeing eye.
The right one's
my winking eye.
I'll give you your license
if you never do that again.
Oh, everything's
the last time
I do everything.
Can't you just use
this recent photo?
Mmm. All right.
Here you go.
Woo-hoo!
Who's laughing now?
Shut up!
What's the scoop,
milkshakes?
I got me a date with Zelda,
so I need the car.
Oh, no.
I'm not giving you my car.
You'd probably drive it.
You don't trust your old man?
You ungrateful milkshake.
Why don't we double-date?
Then the restaurant
will have to
give us that booth.
Wow, a booth.
If I'm tired,
I can just lie down.
Cut it out! I can
work the brake myself.
No, you can't.
You're slow to react, Dad.
Baloney!
This is the best
party of my life.
Bro, you tapped
the septic tank.
Dude sure got
his comeuppance.
In real life,
he would die.
Oh, Abe.
Oh, Zelda.
Hey, watch the movie.
Movies were better
in our day.
For a nickel you got
two movies, a cartoon,
a bag of popcorn
and a whipping.
Kept your mind
on your business.
Hop in, beautiful.
'Cause every girl's crazy
'bout a sharp dressed man
Now, there's a few things
I want to say to you, Zelda.
Save your breath.
Seriously.
Well, I gotta do something
before the Viagra kicks in.
I know.
I'll suck my teeth.
Whoa! Here we go.
Give me those keys!
Do you have any idea
what you put us through?
I called the police,
the hospital,
my bookie, the kennel...
Okay, this isn't
about who I called.
See you later.
I'm going to the library.
Lisa gets to do
what she wants
and you don't yell at her.
Hey, I've earned their trust.
Oh! Everybody trusts Lisa.
Precious little Lisa.
Apple of her daddy's eye.
Lisa doesn't borrow my car
and stay out all night
with some hoochie.
She's no hoochie.
Her name is Zelda
and she understands me.
Grampa, I gotta tell you,
she's a stone-cold hoochie.
Straight up, Marge.
That hoochie only likes
you because you can drive.
Shut up!
You don't know her!
Zelda loves me!
I hate this house!
Turn that down!
You call that music?
I just don't know
what to do.
He used to be
such an angel.
Maybe you should give
him another chance.
No. He's gotta learn, Marge.
The way my dad made me learn.
He is your dad.
Cosmic.
Hey, Abe, what are
you doing here?
We heard you lost
your driving privileges.
Well, for your information,
I can still
drive to the store,
but I have to be back
in five minutes with
these things for the baby.
Oh, Gentlemen,
the new scratch-and-win
tickets are out today.
I'll take one, Achu.
No, not "chu," "pu. "
I got troubles with both.
Finally the shakes
are working for me.
Pardon me, sir.
Your scrapings have landed
on my jacket from
Planet Hollywood, Orlando.
So, what if it did?
So, it is very thoughtless.
I should cut you
like I cut sodium
out of my diet.
You don't scare me
with your dignity
and your subtle cologne.
Then perhaps you should
be taught a lesson by us,
Los Souvenir Jacquitos!
Bring it on.
Please, gentlemen.
Violence is not the answer.
Then what is?
Some sort of death race?
That's what I would do.
Very well, Viejo.
You shall have
your death race.
Death race?
And another thing.
No death races.
Oh, I better not.
Fine! I'll meet you
at the abandoned aqueduct.
For the death race?
Yes, the death race.
All right,
seniors and señores,
whichever car makes it
through that tunnel
first is the winner.
But it's only big
enough for one car.
What are you
scared of, old man?
Everything. Dogs, Dutchmen,
the gathering darkness.
All right. When I yank down
my girlfriend's tube top,
the race will begin.
What? I'm just trying
to bring you into my world.
Just go.
Old friend,
your jacket,
she burns.
Then I burn with her,
for I would rather die
than have people not know
what stores I have been to.
Whoo-hoo!
We're the baddest punks
in our age bracket!
My beard.
I broke my beard.
Oh, my God!
We can't let Homer know.
Oh! That is it!
Abraham J. Simpson,
you are never
driving again! Ever!
I can't believe I cracked
up my only set of wheels.
Go home!
Put on a smile, high-pants.
I've got a surprise for you.
I've booked us
a room for the weekend
in Branson, Missouri.
The Gritz Carlton Hotel.
Oh! That's great,
but there's a slight hitch.
You see,
I'm temporarily
between cars.
But we don't need
anything to have fun
but ourselves.
Give me that old time fun
The kind where we stay home
Zelda, may I
offer you a lift?
No!
Don't feel bad, Abe.
I'll always think of you
as my friend without a car.
Don't go, Zelda! I love you!
Zelda, I'm gonna make
you forget about
your grandchildren.
Oh, what'll I do?
Hey, Grampa.
Stealing Mom's car?
Yeah, it's the only
way to win back Zelda.
And if I go to prison,
I'll get better food
and more hugs.
Uh, it's actually blue
wire to yellow wire.
It is?
Hot diggety Dodge!
Next stop, Branson, Missouri!
Can I tag along?
Sure, why not?
School ain't helping you.
Born to be wild
Oh, I hate this hippie crap.
And now,
WOMB, warm and safe radio,
takes you back
to the golden age
of radio theater.
It's The Itchy
and Scratchy Hour,
presented by
Hansen's Moustache Wax,
the moustache wax
Hitler doesn't use.
They Fight, and Bite
They Fight and Fight and Bite
Fight, fight, fight,
bite, bite, bite
The Itchy and Scratchy Show
As we join
tonight's adventure,
we find Itchy at the counter
of his butcher shop.
Hiya, Scratchy.
You're
crushing my head!
During the war,
Eleanor Roosevelt
was the voice of Scratchy.
The lady knows funny.
First he wrecks your car,
then he steals mine.
Your father's
out of control.
Oh, sure, when he does
something bad,
he's my father.
He must've dropped this.
We've gotta
go after them!
But how?
Branson is
a thousand miles away,
and we've got no car.
Oh! That was lucky.
Come on, boys.
Uh, we'll wait
for the next one.
What are those, Grampa?
These are hobo signs.
They're to tell
other hobos if a place
is friendly or not.
That one means good vittles.
Sexy daughter.
Mass hobo grave in cellar.
Here we are.
Branson, Missouri.
No, pally.
This is Bronson, Missouri.
Mmm. Hey.
Well, how do we
get to Branson?
Number 10 bus.
Hey, Ma, how about
some cookies?
No dice.
This ain't over.
There it is!
That's the glitziest
"Welcome To" sign ever!
Whoa!
Okay, keep an eye
peeled for Zelda.
Is that her?
No.
No!
Wait. It was
the second one.
Zelda, baby, it's me!
Two seniors, please.
Oh, no! He's taking
her to the hottest
matinee in town.
Come on, boy. After them!
Remember the stars
you loved yesterday
Where did they go?
Did they all pass away?
Was it drugs or a car crash
Or facelift gone wrong?
No, they're right here
in Branson
And singing this song
My name is Charo
I shake my maracas
Remember me, fool?
I was B. A. Baracus
We're the performers
You thought were dead
Like Bonnie Franklin
and Adrian Zmed
Branson's the place
We can always be found
They took Nick at Nite
And made it a town
You can call me Ray
Or you can call me Jay
Just don't call me washed up
I do three shows a day
Charlie Callas doesn't
sleep in the ground
Yes, I'm still alive
And I'm making my sounds
So sit back, relax
And watch our revue
In Soviet Union
Revue watches you
Tennessee Ernie Ford?
Now, I know you're dead.
No. You just think I'm dead.
No, you're dead.
I was your biggest fan.
Look, I clipped
your obituary.
Let's take a quick
gambling break.
A little action
will really
sharpen our senses.
Mom, there's no
gambling in Branson.
It was designed as
a family destination.
Oh, no, there's gambling.
We just have to find it!
Look, Mom, it's your car.
Grampa and Bart must
be in that theater.
Bet you they're not.
Three to one.
How much you got?
Mom, you're hurting me.
Grampa, look over there.
It's Captain Bringdown
and The Buzzkillers.
If you're gonna
make your move,
you better do it quick.
Mmm...
Wait! Stop the music!
A- ha! Oh!
It's Grampa!
Munster?
No, Simpson.
Oh, darn, darn, darn!
I've driven hundreds of miles
to say something very special
to someone in
this audience tonight.
Aw!
Huh?
Zelda, will you
come up here?
Drive me, Abe.
Drive me.
I just want to
say we're through!
Nobody dumps Abe Simpson.
You're nothing but a hoochie.
Hoochie, hoochie, hoochie!
Now I'd like my son
to come up here.
Son, can you
forgive an old fool?
Only in public.
Oh!
Aw!
Now, let's go home.
In Russia, stage is
for performers only.
Hey!
This has been
a Gracie Films presentation!
English - US - PSDH