(theme music playing)
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
(whistle blowing)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screeching)
(chimes)
(honking horn)
D'oh!
(screams)
(all yelling)
(loud chattering)
Hey, hey. Settle down, children.
Now, who's ever wondered
how the post office works?
No one?
I did until we came here last year.
Ah, yes. Last year.
Anyway, look.
Here comes our guide
for the day, Postmaster Bill.
(chuckling) Howdy, partners.
Welcome to your post office.
Wow! It's ours? (grunts)
SKINNER: Bart!
Be with you in a minute.
This is the lobby where customers come
for all their postalistic needs.
Legends Of Comedy, my tuches.
What has fatty Arbuckle done
that I haven't done?
This machine reads zip codes.
These five digits tell us
where to direct your mail.
But it's nine digits now.
What's the point
of these other four numbers?
Those are citizen relocation codes.
With any luck, we'll never need 'em.
She's on to us.
Should I flood the chamber?
Not yet. Let's get some lunch.
Well, children, any questions
for Postmaster Bill?
You ever gone on a killing spree?
(chuckling) No, no.
The day of the gun-toting,
disgruntled postman
shooting up the place
went out with the Macarena.
Well, I'm just glad
I work at an elementary school.
And this is where
our employees gather to unwind
after a hard day of serving the public.
-Bingo! Birthday card!
-Graduation!
Ding, ding, ding! Wedding.
(cheering)
(chuckling, groans)
I'm sure you all heard
of the dead letter office.
Well, as a souvenir of your visit
you can each help yourself
to one piece of undeliverable mail.
(cheering)
RALPH: I'll take you.
(children shouting)
(barking)
I got some dog food.
I got my letter to Santa.
A coupon book?
What am I gonna do
with this piece of junk?
Happy birthday, Dad.
Wow!
A Val-U-Qual coupon book.
Let's see.
Ten percent off carpet cleaning.
Ten! (gasps)
Two pizzas for the price of one
at Doughy's!
Doughy's has terrible pizza.
Yeah, but there's two!
Ooh, free foot pain analysis.
Oh, Marge, that's just a trick
to get you in there,
so they can cure your foot pain.
I guess. (moans softly)
See you, kids. Me and my Val-U-Qual book
are gonna paint the town red with savings.
I'll start with a couple of pizzas,
then a complimentary tango lesson,
and I'll cap it off
with a smooth, refreshing colonic.
Um, Dad...
♪ Do you like pina colonic ♪
♪ And getting caught In the rain? ♪
♪ Passing out in the ocean... ♪
Now this wheel balancing is free, right?
Oh, you betcha. Absolutely.
Eh... uh-oh. Wait a minute.
These tires won't take a balance.
They won't?
Nah, nah, no. You hear that clunk?
No.
Well, that tells me
you need four new tires.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Legally, I can't even let you
drive out of here on these.
Oh, please, can't you let me
slide this time?
Gee, I'd really like to,
but if my boss found out...
Hey, what's going on over here?
Were you gonna let this man
drive out of here on unsafe tires?
No, boss. I swear.
Uh, that's it. You're fired!
No. Wait. This is all my fault.
Oh, if I could only turn back the clock
and buy four new tires.
(muzak playing)
Oh.
Ooh, I know that look. (giggles)
You came in for the free wheel balance
and now it's costing you 500 simoleans.
Six with the tip.
Hey, you got off easy.
I just came in to use the phone
and they got me for the whole
road king package...
alignment, shocks, armor all, stem lube.
(chuckling) Stem lube.
Even I didn't fall for that
although winter is coming.
Man, we are a couple of
grade A suckers. (chuckles)
Wally Kogen.
Hey, I know you.
We were in the same pyramid scheme.
Oh, don't remind me.
Friends helping friends, my ass.
Say, you want to grab a beer
while we're waiting?
Yeah.
I'm getting tired of them
pointing and laughing at us.
(all laughing)
COMMENTATOR: The road to the Super Bowl
is long and pointless.
I mean, when you think about it...
(chuckles)
Football's so great.
COMMENTATOR: But now,
the two conference champs
must survive a harrowing bye week
that no one enjoys.
Bye weeks. Bronko Nagurski
didn't get no bye weeks,
and now he's dead.
Well, maybe they're a good thing.
Yeah, how about that Super Bowl?
You going this year?
Me? Nah.
(gasps) Unless there's a coupon
for it! Nah.
Well, I run the Springfield Travel Agency.
We've got a charter bus
going down to the game.
You help us fill it,
you can ride for free.
Homer Simpson at the Super Bowl?
(crowd cheering)
Dang.
That was my last quarterback.
Now what am I gonna do?
You.
-Me?
-Yeah, you.
Get your hand off my wife's leg.
Sorry.
It's a deal.
Hey, Moe, you wanna come with me and Wally
to the Super Bowl?
Oh, absolutely. My favorite team's in it!
The Atlanta Falcons.
Yeah, every since I was a boy,
I've always loved
the Atlanta Falcons.
Yeah, they're good
but I wouldn't count out the...
Denver Broncos.
Yeah, I hear that President... Clinton
is gonna be watching
with his wife... Hillary.
Come on, Lenny,
I need four more guys
to fill my Super Bowl bus.
What do you say?
-LENNY (whining): Nah.
-Come on...
-Come on!
-LENNY (whining): Nah.
-Oh, come on.
-LENNY: Ah...
-Yes!
Now that Lenny's in
Carl will fall like a domino.
I'm so happy you're going to the big game.
My dream has always been
to see the Bolshoi Ballet.
Yeah, yeah. Do we have
any pencils that work?
Wow, you've signed up
quite a few people, Dad...
the Sea Captain, Bumblebee man,
comic-book guy, the squeaky-voiced teen...
Yeah, it's a good group.
I gotta hand it to you, Homer.
It's really a good group.
Yeah. Not a dame in sight.
Oh, thank God.
Now we can stop holding it in.
(all sighing)
All aboard for Miami.
(all groaning)
I don't know if I can last that long.
Super Bowl, please, and step on it!
(all cheering)
Hey, wait up.
Ah, crap. It's that pip-squeak Rudy.
(panting)
What is it, Rudy?
Can I come, too?
Forget it, kid.
You're too small to go to the Super Bowl.
But what I lack in size,
I make up for in...
obnoxiousness. (grunts)
(all cheering)
("Wild Weekend" by NRBQ playing)
♪ Hey, boys it's a wild weekend ♪
-(raucous laughter)
-Whoo!
♪ We did it then and we'll do it again ♪
Well, sports fans, I see
you've located the beer supply,
so let's all enjoy it in moderation.
MAN: Boo!
Hey, don't make me come back there.
Seriously, now, if you have any questions,
just ask our team leader, Homer Simpson.
(singing drunkenly)
Or me. Be-- Better ask me.
(sighs)
It's so nice to have
a peaceful weekend together.
Yeah, I'm bored, too.
Mm-hmm.
Hey, why don't we do
one of those craft kits
Aunt Patty always gives us?
Hmm... ooh, how about Paint-By-Numbers?
It's so rigid and uncreative.
OK.
Oh, Leather Craft.
Oh! Those poor, helpless cows.
Mm-hmm. What about Clay?
You got any problem with Clay?
Hey, what's this? (blows)
"Vincent Price's Egg Magic."
Well, what are we waiting for?
Keep-away Lovejoy's collar.
(all laughing)
Now look what you've done.
All right, all right,
you guys have had way too much booze.
Last call.
(clamoring)
Come on, come on, give me an excuse.
Pro player stadium, Super Bowl.
(all cheering)
(bleating)
(chuckles) I'm sorry.
The guys made kind of a mess
in your bathroom.
What bathroom?
Uh, OK, fellas, enjoy the pre-game fun.
I don't wanna be a panicky Pete,
but it's Sunday and I haven't
been to church yet.
No problem. The NFL's got you covered.
...and that the wandering Oakland Raiders
may someday find a home.
Lord, hear our prayer.
Can I get an amen to that?
ALL: Amen.
Cool! The NFL's oldest surviving player.
I'm 53 years young.
Ugh.
MAN: Whoo!
Hey, Troy Aikman.
So, Ned, you like dune buggies?
Well... (giggles) not my cup of...
Sure, you do.
Everyone likes dune buggies.
(grunts)
Great spiral, Daniel.
Man, that hurts.
Excuse me. Coming through.
Friends of Dan Marino.
OK, Dan, fire away.
(scoffs) I'm Dan's manager. This is Dan.
Go long, son.
Yes, sir.
(whimpering)
I'm catching a pass from Dan Marino.
This is the greatest moment of my--
Whoo-hoo! Homer Simpson with a pick!
Hey, Bubba, Hacksaw, get that moron.
(growling)
Uh-oh. Lateral to Bart!
(screams)
-(cracking)
-HOMER: My spine.
Oh, honey, that is egg-ceptional.
(giggling)
OK, now we just have to stick
the feet on.
Right. Now... hmm.
Lisa, I don't want to alarm you
but I'm not finding any.
But it clearly says feet included.
They have to be here.
No, nothing.
I can't believe Vincent Price
would lend his name
to such a shoddy product.
Now what do we do?
Let's call the company.
Mom, this was made in 1967.
They're probably out of business.
Well, we'll just see.
Murray Hill, 5-9-2-3-2.
(telephone ringing)
VINCENT (over telephone):
Hello. This is Vincent Price.
(gasps) It's Vincent Price.
I thought he was dead.
VINCENT: You should know
the grave could never tame me.
(ghoulish laugh)
Oh, Mr. Price, I loved you
in the Abominable Doct--
VINCENT: If you are calling
about the missing feet,
leave your address
and the replacement feet
will be rushed to you by my grandson Jody.
And now, I must return
to the sweet embrace of the crypt,
but I'll be back.
(ghoulish laugh)
So, is he alive or not?
-(beep)
-742 Evergreen Terrace, Springfield.
Oh, hiya, Maude.
Come on in.
Who needs tickets? Tickets right here.
How about you, slick?
Scalping tickets to the Super Bowl.
Have you no shame, sir?
I should give you a royal caning.
(cheering in agreement)
Hey, hey, I'm just trying to make
an honest buck.
Ah, get lost, you bloodsucking parasite.
Wally and I have all the tickets we need.
Uh, sorry, fellas,
but these tickets are counterfeit.
-What?
-Counterfeit?
Yeah, see, the hologram's missing,
and there's no such team as The Spungos,
and finally, these seem to be
printed on some sort of cracker.
Stop eating our tickets!
Oh, how could I fall for fake tickets?
Gee, the fellas are gonna be crestfallen.
Yes, if by "crestfallen,"
you mean "kill us."
Listen, let me talk to them.
Maybe I can smooth this over.
(sweetly) My friends...
They don't have the tickets!
-Kill 'em!
-(all shouting)
Please, my friends... Ow!
All right! I'll get you into the game!
Excuse me, uh... Mr. Scalper, sir.
Have I told you that I love you?
Forget it.
You'll just hurt me like all the others.
OK, Moe, I believe
you had me by the throat.
Reverend Lovejoy was working the body.
Wait. Dad, look.
Hello.
Gentlemen, I have an idea.
(grunts) Run!
(cheering and hooting)
-OFFICER: Get back here!
-(whistling)
We can still make the kickoff!
Here comes the kick!
(yell crescendos)
Ow!
Yay!
As a doctor, I'd say he's had enough...
but as a football fan...
-(yell crescendos)
-Aaah!
(wind whistling)
(honks)
(ZZ Top's "Legs" playing)
MAN: The church...
we've made a few changes.
These Super Bowl commercials are weird.
MAN: Just about ready
for the second quarter here in Miami.
I tell you, Pat,
that wild first quarter
blew out my telestrator,
and now the fans are screaming for more.
(screaming)
Let us out of here!
Relax, Simpson, relax.
A little-known fact about jail cells
is they always have one phony bar
for, like, emergencies.
Real, real, real, real, real.
So, by the process of elimination,
this one is the fake.
(yells) Ah, that's painful.
(crowd cheering on TV)
Ah, nuts. That sounds like a touchdown.
(all groaning)
No, no, no. I know my roars,
and that was most definitely a safety.
(groaning)
Man.
Gosh, fellas, to see you all stuck in here
when even guys in China
can watch all the action
from their town squares or what have you,
well, I just feel pretty doggone bad.
If they were electing
a president of Dumbville,
I'd have to nominate me.
You got my vote.
Oh, we're never going to get out of...
Psst! Cleaning lady!
Would you let us out of here?
Me? I'm Dolly Parton.
I didn't ask for your life story,
just the key.
Young man, where I come from,
the South, folks say "please,"
and besides, I got to go sing a medley
with Rob Lowe and Stomp.
Dolly, wait!
Wally?
You know Dolly Parton?
Yeah. I book a lot of package tours
to Dollywood
and Euro-Dollywood.
That's in Alabama.
Wally Kogen,
what are you doing in Super Bowl jail?
Ask her if she'll go out with me.
We had a little ticket snafu.
Do you think you can bust
old Wally and his pals
out of the pokey?
Well, I do have
some of my extra-strength makeup remover.
Uh, shield your eyes.
(sizzling)
(all cheering)
Oh, thanks, Miss Parton.
Oh, way to go, Dolly.
-Thanks, babe.
-Will you go out with me?
Ooh, look at the time.
I better scoot to that halftime show.
See y'all.
Oh, man, that's gonna be some show.
Who's ready for some football?
Football!
(cheering)
("Song 2" by Blur playing)
Hey, Homer, we've been running around
cheering for an hour.
Where the hell's the game?
-Yeah, where's the game?
-BART: Yeah, where's the game?
You guys are following me?
I was following Flanders.
Hey, look what I found.
Whoo-hoo!
(crowd cheering)
Hey.
-Hey, somebody just scored.
-HOMER: In a minute.
(all chattering)
(helicopter whirring)
HOMER: Hey, it's the beer copter!
What the bloody hell?
Hit the road, gramps.
This is a private sky box.
I'm Rupert Murdoch,
the billionaire tyrant,
and this is my sky box.
If you're Rupert Murdoch, prove it.
(whispering)
(20th Century Fox Fanfare)
CROWD: Hi, Rupert!
ALL: Uh-oh.
Well, I'm convinced.
Tell you what, Mr. Murdoch,
let's just split the difference.
The boys and I will just
crouch here quietly
and take it easy on the snacks...
Silence!
Seize them!
(terrified yelling)
Oi! Oi! Oi! Oi! Oi! Oi!
(crowd cheering)
The game! We're so close.
Follow me, boys!
We're finally going to the Super... Ow!
We did it! We're number one!
We're rich!
How does it feel?
Did you ever stop believing?
Does this suit make me look fat?
Players and VIPs only.
(reporters groaning)
(cheering)
I can't believe it!
We're actually in the winning locker room.
Whoo! I'm going to Disneyland.
Really? Cause I'm a travel agent
and I've heard nothing but bad things.
(grunting)
(phone ringing)
Y'ello.
Uh, hello, this is President Clinton.
Hey, how you doing?
You know, your determination and grit
under extreme pressure are an inspiration.
The whole country is proud of you.
Well, it's about time.
And on behalf of America, I'd like to--
Ow!
(laughing) Oh! All right, Lovejoy.
You're gonna get it.
Hello? Hello?
I command you to answer me!
Hello?
Al, do you have to do that right now?
What are you gonna do
with your Super Bowl ring, Carl?
I'll probably give it to my wife.
It's our anniversary today.
ALL: Ah!
Dad, that doesn't belong to you.
But this might be my last chance
to win one.
Well, we sure put together
a heck of a trip, Homer.
Ever thought about being a travel agent?
Wally, I'd be lying if I said I hadn't.
Cause you can really "go places"
in the travel business.
(laughs)
Feel free to use that one.
What one?
Well, John, what did you think
of tonight's episode?
I loved it.
The last-minute addition
of Wally Kogen to the lineup
was a bit of a gamble,
but it really paid off.
Marge and Lisa painting eggs?
Did that work for you?
Oh, big time.
They came off the bench with a huge effort
that allowed Homer and Bart
to make some significant gains.
Did it strike you as odd
that in a Super Bowl show
with Dolly Parton,
we didn't see any football or singing?
I hadn't thought about it, Pat,
but in retrospect,
it was kind of a rip-off.
What a way to treat the loyal fans
who put up with so much nonsense
from this franchise.
Any final thoughts?
Nah, I'm too mad.
Let's get the heck out of here.
All aboard, boys.
I've been waiting for you.
Now, I'll tell you.
That doesn't make a lick of sense.
I know. Just get on the bus.
(gears grinding)
VINCENT: Where's that infernal clutch?
Wait, wait. I'll get it.
JODY: Give it some gas, Grandpa.
VINCENT: Oh, quiet, Jody.
You're not helping.
(gears grinding)
(rock music)
(theme music playing)
RUPERT MURDOCH: Silence!
Captioned by
Visual Data Media Services