♪ The Simpsons ♪
(chalk screeches)
(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(tires screeching)
(horn honks)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
(dance music playing)
Oh, ain't that cute?
Hey! Where in God's name
did you learn that kind of...
dancing?
Whoa.
Ooh.
Oh, yeah.
Dad, can I have
some money
to buy Bart
a birthday present?
Money.
Dad, this is $110.
-Oh, sorry.
-MAN: That's very righteous.
Funky See, Funky Do
will be back to lip sync
another one of their
hits right after this.
ANNOUNCER:
Hey, kids, why sit in front of the TV
when you can be
on the radio?
♪ We're gonna roll
this truckin' convoy ♪
♪ Across the U.S.A. ♪
♪ Convoy ♪
That could be Bart.
Throw away
your bulky transmitters
and broadcasting towers.
The Superstar
Celebrity Microphone
lets you hear your voice
through any A.M. radio.
Hey, good-looking,
we'll be back
to pick you up later.
Whew!
He's in for some loving.
It's the perfect gift
for birthdays, graduations,
-board meetings.
-You're fired.
Hmm. Bart's birthday's
coming up.
But order now,
supply is limited.
-(gasps) Limited?
-(dialing)
Do you have any of
those microphones left?
Yeah, a couple.
You know, Marge,
Bart's really going to like
my birthday present this year.
It won't be like
those shoe trees
I got him last year
or the shelf paper
I bought him for Christmas.
-I'll buy his love yet.
-Mmm, yeah.
(whistling "Happy Birthday")
Okay, Sideshow Mel,
bring out the birthday cake.
(children laughing)
(cheering)
Hey, kids,
while Sideshow Mel mops up,
Let's see the names of our
Krusty birthday pals for today.
All right,
here comes my name.
Wow. Best eight bucks
I ever spent.
Bart,
your Grampa's on the phone.
He wants to wish you
a happy birthday.
Isn't that nice?
Take a message.
Right now, I'm off
to hit 46 local merchants
for free birthday
goods and services.
I'm here for my free
birthday sundae.
Eat it and get out.
Digital audio tape,
my butt.
When I was a kid,
we had compact discs,
and I don't recall
no one complaining.
Damn right.
♪♪ (tango music playing)
-(watch alarm beeping)
-Sorry, Rosarita.
I got to get
to my birthday party.
Farewell, Señor Bart.
Hey, good to see you.
Glad you could make it.
Toby, have you lost weight?
Uh-oh, here comes trouble.
(chuckles)
It's Wall E.!
(kids cheering)
Hey, Wall E.,
do something funny.
WALL E.:
Hey, later, okay?
Hey, why don't you
go bug your parents?
Cool, Larry the Looter.
(chuckles) All right,
stick it to the man.
(groans)
Hey, there.
I hear it's your birthday.
-How old are you?
-Well, I'm...
That's great. Would you like us
to sing you a special song?
-Hell no.
-You got it.
Ready, Señor Beaveratti?
I'm a-ready.
And a-one,
and a-two...
(singing off-key)
♪ You're the birthday ♪
♪ You're the birthday boy
or girl... ♪
What the...
-It's a label maker.
-Mm-hmm.
We have one at home.
Before we got it,
I was always finding
Patty's stubble
in my leg razor.
(groans)
Bart, I'll bet you think
nothing's going
to top that cactus.
Well,
check out my present.
-Next.
-Bart, be polite.
-Next, please.
-Bart, I've noticed
your birthday presents
are a poor crop at best.
I hope this turns the tide.
Ooh, just gorgeous.
Now we can be twins.
(quizzical growl)
Aw, there's only one can of
beer left, and it's Bart's.
Hey, boy,
how's the microphone working?
Fine.
Bart! I would love
to get a present like that.
Here you go.
Enjoy.
D'oh!
Listen boy, this is
a great invention. Watch.
(off-key)
♪ We got a great big convoy ♪
♪ Rocking through
the night ♪
♪ We got a great big convoy,
ain't she a beautiful sight? ♪
-♪ Convoy ♪
-(dog howling)
Quit it, Dad!
Hey, good-looking,
we'll be back
for some dinner later.
What did you say?
I can't understand you
with all that distortion.
(groans)
What a crappy birthday.
You know Bart, I don't think
this is such a bad present.
Maybe you just shouldn't
talk into it as loud as your father does.
Testing.
Testing one-two-three.
Oh, my.
Do I sound like that?
Hey, it does work.
I bet you could
have a lot of fun with this.
Why don't you
go show your father?
Hmm.
Mmm, chocolate.
D'oh!
Marge, we need some more
vanilla, chocolate,
and strawberry ice cream.
MARGE: I'll get some
at the store tomorrow, Homer.
Mmm, chocolate.
BART: People of earth,
this is Bartron--
commander of the Martian
invasion force.
Your planet is in our hands.
Resistance is useless.
(screams)
We have captured
your president.
He was delicious.
-Why, you little...
-(gagging)
Wait a minute.
Does this mean
you like my present?
Uh-huh.
Oh... Just promise me
you won't play
any more practical jokes.
I promise.
(Bart chuckling)
Mama. Mama.
(gasps)
Maggie, you talked!
Can you say
"mama" again?
Sorry, lady.
Show's over.
Oh, Bart.
(laughing)
I dreamed
I was married to Corey,
and we lived
on a pony farm,
and Corey was always
walking around
with his shirt off.
(both laughing)
Oh, brother.
(fart noise)
(laughing)
Mrs. Krabapple,
that was uncalled for.
(grumbling)
Bravo!
Well done, old man.
Hmm.
Rod, Todd, this is God.
How did you get
on the radio?
What do you mean,
"how did I get on the radio"?
I created the universe,
stupid kids.
Forgive my brother.
We believe you.
Talk is cheap.
Perhaps a test
of thy faith.
Walk through the wall.
I will remove it for you...
...later.
(laughing)
What do you want from us?
I got a job for thee.
Bring forth all the
cookies from your kitchen
and leave them
on the Simpsons' porch.
But those cookies belong
to our parents.
(frustrated sigh)
Look, do you want a happy God
-or a vengeful God?
-Happy God.
Then quit flapping your lip,
and make with the cookies!
-Yes, sir.
(whistling)
Whoops.
(humming)
BART:
Help! Help!
Sounds like trouble a-brewing
at the old well!
Help me, please.
I fell down the well!
I'll get help,
laddie.
A little nip of courage.
Out of my way!
Look out, you horse's arse!
(laughing)
Sucker.
Huh?
Hey, what's up?
Some poor kid
fell down a well.
Yes!
(high-pitched voice)
My name is Timmy O'Toole.
I just turned ten years old.
Timmy, where are
your parents?
Uh... I have no family.
I tried to enroll in school,
but your Principal Skinner
turned me away
-because of my shabby clothes.
-(crowd gasps)
He's a liar.
(crowd booing)
The circumference
of the well is 34 inches.
So, unfortunately,
not one member of our
city's police force
is slender enough
to rescue the boy.
By God, men,
you're a bunch of marshmallows.
Why don't
you go, Chief?
Well, I'm too f...
-...important.
-(scoffs)
Although the well
is too dark to see the boy,
Timmy has told us his foot
is trapped under a rock.
Thus any attempt
to pull him up
would snap him like a twig.
In desperation,
the city is considering
more unorthodox solutions.
Grasping the child
firmly in his talons,
Socrates here will
fly him to safety.
Just watch.
(screeches)
I don't think
he's coming back.
With this hook
and this hunk of chocolate,
I'll land your boy,
and I'll clean him for free.
Although we can't reach
the boy,
we can freeze him
with liquid nitrogen
so that future generations
can rescue him.
Dear Lord, before we peel
the foil back from your bounty,
we ask you to watch over
little Timmy O'Toole
trapped in that well.
(Bart laughing loudly)
Bart, what's wrong with you?
Yeah, that Timmy
is a real hero.
How do you mean, Dad?
Well, he fell down a well
and can't get out.
How does that
make him a hero?
Well, it's more
than you did.
And finally, Channel 6's own
Krusty the Clown
has gathered members of
the entertainment community,
who normally steer clear
of fashionable causes,
for a video called
"We're Sending Our Love
Down the Well."
I wanted to do something
to help that boy.
so I called my
good friend Sting.
He said "Krusty,
when do you need me?"
I said, "Thursday."
He said,
"I'm busy Thursday."
I said,
"What about Friday?"
He said, "Friday's worse
than Thursday."
Then he said,
"How about Saturday?"
I said "Fine."
True story.
Yeah. I used to open
for Krusty in '69.
In fact, he fired me
as I recall.
(chuckles)
Oh, Sting.
But this isn't
about show business.
This is about some kid
down a hole or something.
and we've all got to do
what we can.
♪♪ (piano)
♪ There's a hole in my heart
as deep as a well ♪
♪ For that poor little boy
who's stuck halfway to hell ♪
♪ Though we can't get him out,
we'll do the next best thing ♪
♪ And go on TV
and sing, sing, sing ♪
♪ And we're sending our love
down the well ♪
♪ All the way down ♪
♪ We're sending our love
down the well ♪
♪ Down that well ♪
Krusty, what are your plans
for the royalties?
Well, we got to pay
for promotion, shipping,
distribution.
You know, those limos out back,
they aren't free.
Whatever's left,
we throw down the well.
(carnival music,
children laughing)
Authentic Timmy O'Toole
baby teeth.
$6.00 a bag.
Step to the rear.
Plenty of room
in the back.
(crowd laughing and talking)
♪ The Itchy & Scratchy Show ♪
Hmm?
(yells)
(screaming)
(chomping)
♪♪
Hmm?
(screaming)
(laughing)
-Aw.
-(dog barking)
Drop that
microphone.
Drop it, boy!
This is a special report
from Channel 6 News.
Disturbing news
from the Old Town well
where young Timmy O'Toole
has apparently taken
a turn for the worse.
(growling)
It's very simple, Kent.
The child is reverting
to a feral
or wolf-like state.
Here's an artist's conception.
-(growling)
-Bart.
(snarling)
Ahem. I was trying
to gnaw my foot off, but...
I couldn't get through my sock.
Good night, everybody.
(snoring)
Bart Simpson!
The thought of a boy
trapped in a well
brought out the kindness
and love of the entire community.
When they find out
you've been fooling them,
they're gonna want to cut
you up with rusty razors.
Oh, yeah? And how are they
gonna find out?
The police will catch you,
sooner or later.
The police. (scoffs)
They couldn't catch a cold.
Maybe not, but I bet
you're stupid enough
to have left a "Property of Bart Simpson"
label on that radio.
D'oh!
"And Cinderella had
"the most beautiful gown
at the ball
"with eight
satin petticoats
each more delicate
than the last."
I think he's asleep.
Want to get
a cup of coffee?
Okay.
Brave little guy.
(grunts)
(grunting)
(yells)
Hey. Almost tripped
over this thing.
(screaming)
Ugh!
(groaning)
What did I do to deserve this?
Help! Help!
I fell down the well.
Tell us something
we don't know.
(policemen laughing)
No, my name is Bart Simpson.
What are you doing
down there?
Look, I'll level with you.
There is no Timmy O'Toole.
It was just a prank
I was playing on everybody.
Well, you sure
fooled us, kid.
Hey, I got an idea
for a prank.
Let's go home
and go to sleep.
(laughing)
Good one, Eddie.
Ha, ha. Great joke, guys.
(fake laughing)
-Guys?
-(wolf howls in distance)
So I'm afraid your son
is trapped down the well.
You must think we're the worst
parents in the world.
Yes, that's pretty much
the feeling down at the station.
Don't worry, son.
Just 'cause you're trapped in a hole
doesn't mean you can't live
a rich and full life.
I brought you your Krusty doll.
Ow!
Knock it off, you bald boob!
Hey! Don't make me
come down there!
Like to see you fit.
Why you little--
-Put a man on him.
-(grunting)
I like the other boy.
So polite.
What are you doing
to save my baby boy?
Well, ma'am, we've located
a piece of machinery
in Shreveport,
Louisiana
that could pop him out
lickety-split.
Well, why don't you get it?
Well, I'm afraid we've
got a budget problem, Mrs. Simpson.
Your boy picked a bad time
to fall down a well.
Had he done it at the start of
the fiscal year, no problemo.
You're telling me
that the city won't pay
to get a boy
out of a well?
Well they would have for Timmy.
People love that little guy.
But your son, well, he kinda
played us all for a bunch of saps.
Mmm...
So it seems we've all been
the victims of a cruel hoax
perpetrated by
a ten-year-old hooligan.
The time has come
for finger pointing,
and most of them
are squarely aimed
at the boy's parents.
It's not our fault.
We didn't want the boy.
He was an accident.
Homer!
Could you edit
that last part out?
Mr. Simpson, we're live,
coast to coast.
D'oh!
♪ One plus one
plus three is five ♪
♪ Little Bart Simpson's
buried alive ♪
♪ He's so neat,
he's so sweet ♪
♪  Now the rats
have Bart to eat... ♪
Hey, stop that!
Oh. Sorry, Lisa.
♪ How many days
until Bart croaks? ♪
♪ One, two, three, four... ♪
And our new number one hit,
"I Do Believe We're Naked"
by Funky See, Funky Do
replaces "We're Sending
Our Love Down the Well,"
which plunges
all the way down to number 97.
Ever since I called
for the rescue
of that Simpson lad,
I have taken a lot of heat,
so I am flip-flopping.
I say let him stay down there.
(cheering)
(ringing)
Yeah, Shutton here.
Now that's a story.
Bart, honey, I made you
an extra warm sweater
you can wear while
you're down in the well.
Mom, it's too big.
Don't worry,
you'll grow into it.
Homer!
You know, I've done
a lot of bad stuff
through the years.
I guess now
I'm paying the price,
but there's so many things
I'll never get a chance to do.
Smoke a cigarette,
Use a fake I.D.,
Shave a swear word
in my hair...
(sniffling)
That's all I can stands.
I can't stands no more.
I'm going to get you
out of there myself.
(Homer grunting)
Now why didn't I think of that?
Agnes, we've got work to do.
(grunting)
This is Kent Brockman
with a special bulletin.
The Lincoln squirrel
has been assassinated.
We'll stay with the story
all night, if we have to.
What's going on?
It's an old-fashioned
hole digging.
By gar, it's been a while.
(grunting)
(gasping)
The canary.
Gas!
Out of the hole!
(screaming)
Gentlemen, this canary
died of natural causes.
Back in the hole!
(screaming)
(panting)
Sting, you look tired.
Maybe you should
take a rest.
Not while one
of my fans needs me.
Actually, I don't know if I've ever heard
Bart play one of your albums.
Shh! Marge,
he's a good digger.
(panting)
Uhh!
Sting!
Mom! Dad!
Oh, Bart,
I've missed you so much.
Man, I was
so scared.
Don't worry, son.
They're going to make sure
no one ever falls down
this well again.
(grunting)
That should do it.
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.