CHORUS SINGS:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
Nighttime.
(school bell ringing)
Hello!
(whistle blows)
(yells)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
Hmm.
Ooh.
(gunfire)
(tires screeching)
(horn honking, Grampa shouts)
D'oh!
(tires screeching)
(grunts)
Hmm?
Man. (grunts)
HOMER/MARGE: Hmm.
Hmm?
Hey!
(all gasp)
(speaking gibberish)
OMINOUS ANNOUNCER: In a
conflict as old as pencil and
paper...
two mighty armies square off
in a battle
between cross and circle...
(rapid laser fire)
Remember my son,
the one who controls the center
controls the board.
I don't understand,
Master.
I begin to fear
you are too stupid.
I love you, Romeo!
I love you, Julie-x!
Tic-tac-noooo!
ANNOUNCER:
On July 4...
From the producers of
Duck, Duck Goose,"
Got Your Nose and One Day
in the Life of Ivan Denisovich.
-What's going on?
-(groans)
Look at this
electric bill!
I'm not made of money!
I'm made of man-meat
and a skeleton!
It's time to unplug these
vampire appliances
that plunge their prongs
into our creamy white outlets
to quench their unholy
thirst for electrons.
Lamp, computer,
Jacob's Ladder...
What the...?
How long has this been running?
(mumbling): I don't know.
Dad, while I agree
reducing consumption is great,
it's hard to make permanent
changes in your lifestyle.
Are you calling me fat?
No.
I am suggesting
you consider cheaper,
alternate sources of energy.
Hmm, Alternative
Energy Expo.
Where there's expos,
there's free Frisbees!
Let's roll.
But we'd better make sure
robbers don't know we're out.
(electricity buzzing)
MARGE: Come on, let's go.
Who you waiting for?
Come on.
Do they think I'm like an idiot?
I'm going to enjoy pooping
on their carpet.
(moans)
(grunting)
-(spits)
-Why, you...
(both grunting)
-You son of a...
-(grunting)
(belching)
(giggling)
Now, on to the next funny booth.
Solar power is
a bright idea!
Yeah, so is getting a real job.
-Hey-- oh.
-Dad!
I found what
you're looking for!
A churro you can eat
in the shower?
Goddag, friendlys.
Behold to you-- wind!
The energy that
powers Denmark.
Well, I'm not usually one
to take the word of a Dane.
Plus, how can I afford it?
Well, there are tax credits,
government rebates.
It will pay for itself
in 12 to 18...
-Months?
-Lifetimes.
Hmm, tie it to my car,
and you got a deal.
Lars, get the twine!
You will not
regret this.
I'm starting to regret it
already.
Too late.
Lars got the twine.
(groans)
Dad, you are leading the way
in clean energy.
Yup, I Al-Gored it pretty good.
Where's my Grammy for
audio book narration?
It's making our meter run
backwards!
Oh, my goodness!
It means we're traveling
back in time!
I can warn President Lincoln
to dump his wife before
she goes crazy!
Dad, all it means is,
we're providing power
to the electric company.
Oh, that's just great.
I discover electricity, and
they want to take it from me!
(dialing)
Hello, local utility?
You greedy bastards have gouged
Homer Simpson for the last time.
We will cancel your account,
sir.
The Simpsons are
off the grid.
And so far it's
going great.
(all cheering)
Gentlemen, tonight's game
is brought to us
by something special.
The kite's best friend, the
flag's partner in patriotism,
you've seen cherubs blow it
from map corners--
the wind!
-LENNY: All right!
-CARL:
Yeah, blow me some sports!
♪ Perilous fight ♪
♪ O'er the ramparts, we... ♪
"O'er the ramparts we" what?!
Don't worry,
I'll go see what's wrong.
What the...?
Who turned off the wind?
Dad, if we're really
off the grid,
then we won't get power
when the air is still.
Oh.
Well, I'm not crawling back
to big electricity!
From now on,
the Simpsons are living...
intermittently.
-(kids laughing)
-♪ Danger, danger ♪
-(kids gasping)
-♪ High voltage ♪
♪ When we touch ♪
-(nervous laughter)
-♪ And when we kiss ♪
♪ Danger, danger ♪
♪ High voltage ♪
♪ When we touch, when we kiss ♪
♪ When we touch,
when we kiss... ♪
(groans)
Hmm?
(yawns)
(blender goes on and off)
Oh, my smoothie is all lumpy!
The wind may have stopped
working, but my brain nev...
...er does.
Check it out, gang.
But, Dad, it defeats the purpose
if you're powering our windmill
with the electricity
from Flanders.
Homer, this meeting of your
fan club is adjourned!
But we haven't read the minutes
of last week's meeting!
(grunts)
You used to be nicer!
(Bart grunting)
(grunts)
(groans)
When is my turn over?
Ugh, Bart, please!
I'm trying to hear Dr. House's
third incorrect diagnosis
before his final
correct diagnosis!
(sighs)
Dear Lord, you've got
the wind I need,
I've got the prayers you crave.
Let's make a deal.
(wind howling)
Whoa!
Kent's Weather Worriers are
reporting gusts up to 75...
(electrical shorting noise,
Homer chuckles)
Now we're cookin' with wind!
Homie, maybe this is
too much electricity.
(sighs) Nothing is ever
right for you.
Oh, why can't our house
ever be that bright?
Nothing is ever right
for you.
(wind rushing)
Finally.
(startled gasp)
Well, the lesson here is...
(humming)
We're gonna go check out
the wind damage.
Be careful!
If you see
a downed power line,
do whatever it is
people are supposed to do
in that situation.
(wind chimes tinkling)
Make it stop! Make it stop!
Look at the cool stuff
that washed up!
(gasps) Scuba goggles!
Oh, medical waste!
-(sad moans)
-BOTH: Hmm?
(gasps)
Whoa!
LISA: Oh, my God!
A beached whale!
(whale moaning sadly)
Bart, can you believe
that something so mighty has
been rendered so powerless?
I'm gonna have my next birthday
party on this thing.
(humming)
Whoa!
BART:
Ay, caramba!
Whoa!
(whale moaning sadly)
She's such a beautiful shade
of blue.
I'm going to call you
Bluella the whale.
Hmm?
Check it out!
World's biggest armpit fart.
(loud fart noise)
You just made
a powerful enemy!
Come on, everybody!
A whale needs help!
Why should we?
Yeah, where was that whale
when my mom moved out?
Whales are mammals like us.
They're sensitive
and deeply intelligent.
(laughs)
Nerd!
(boys laugh)
I'm going to get real help.
Just try to keep her wet.
(moaning)
Hey, Milhouse!
Want to learn more
about whaling?
Sure!
-(grunting)
-(groaning)
Hey, Milhouse!
Want me
to "knock
it off?"
I'm afraid to answer that.
Never tell a bully
you're afraid.
-(grunting)
-(groaning)
(Marge sighs)
Our wedding
china's ruined.
Oh, we'll have to eat
Thanksgiving dinner
off regular plates like animals.
Hey, Mom, Dad,
there's a whale
on the beach.
You got to help me
get her back in the ocean.
(sighs)
All right. Let me
get my tool belt.
(grunting)
Man, who are these belts
made for, French super models?
(grunting)
(sighs)
Hurry, Dad, hurry!
(grunting)
Homie, can I talk
to you for a second?
Sure. Lisa,
bring the car around.
But I don't know how to drive.
Haven't you
learned anything
from watching
Bart drive?
A little.
Homie, I happened to
read about beached whales
in Springfield
Geographic.
It usually does
not end well.
-We can't let Lisa
get her hopes up.
-(car horn toots twice)
Marge, how hard
can it be?
We're just rolling it
into the ocean from the beach.
It's not like it's stuck
in the bottom of a well
or in a Mexican prison.
(gasps)
But that would make
a great movie.
(laughs)
Lisa is very sensitive.
If something she loves
dies in front of her...
That whale's not gonna die.
We're busting him
out of prison,
no matter what you say,
Escobar!
God, this thing
writes itself.
(car horn toots twice)
Coming!
(tool belt squeaking)
Okay, we'll need
the town's strongest men
to roll the whale back
in the water.
(all grunting)
(groaning)
Hmm. We need
a better idea.
We'll have to find
our ten smartest men.
(straining mightily)
It's hard to believe
anyone in that contest
can be considered smart.
(moaning)
One... two...
three... tug!
(engines revving)
Aah.
(whistling)
Lisa, sweetheart,
it's almost dinner time.
Why don't you come home?
I'll catch up with you guys
in a little bit.
You know, when I'm sad,
I read something beautiful
and true-- poetry.
(sad moans)
No, no, you're gonna like it.
It's about the ocean.
"The world below the brine.
Forests at the bottom
of the sea.
The branches and leaves..."
(yawns)
"Sea-lettuce, vast lichens..."
BART:
Wake up, Lis!
They're doing it!
(gasps)
Dorsal straps secured!
Tail clamps
in position!
Congratulatory
T-shirts
silk-screened
and distributed!
Oh!
Operation Desert Ocean is a go!
Let's get this lady fish
into the blue zone!
It was my idea to
put the whale in the water.
Girl, you're
going home!
You're
Good-bye, Bluella!
Send me a post card
from Tierra Del Fuego.
Good-bye! Good-bye!
(ecstatic whale sounds)
Huh?
(groans, then gasps)
Bluella?
(gasps)
Oh, no. (gasps)
(sobbing quietly)
Don't worry, honey.
Right now she's lying
on God's beach.
She doesn't like lying
on the beach.
She likes being in the ocean.
Oh, Lisa, I'm sorry.
I tried my best.
I know it's really hard
when you discover
your dad isn't perfect.
Not perfect?
You can say
that again.
I'm trying
to be a sensitive father,
you unwanted moron!
Lisa, where were we?
Maybe I should just
be alone a little bit.
Of course.
Oh, it kills me
to see her like that.
And if there's one thing
I can't stand,
it's being killed.
(yawns)
Milhouse, this'll be
the biggest dead animal
we ever poked with a stick.
If that flattened squirrel
we poked last week
could only see us now.
(crowd murmuring)
All right, back
up, everybody.
Oh, but not too much.
You are definitely
gonna want to see this.
(explosion)
So clean, how part of it
just disappears like that.
Ah! Yuck!
(explosion)
(screaming and shouting)
(groaning and grunting)
Citizens, today
we honor Bluella the whale,
along with the victims
of the Great Whale Explosion.
(explosion)
Could you please
stop dynamiting?!
CHIEF WIGGUM:
Sorry. I sat on the plunger.
But Bluella will live on
among us
as we make use
of every part of her body,
from blowhole to fluke.
♪ And we did not
catch the whale,
brave boys... ♪
♪ And we did not
touch the whale... ♪
Behold, I am Captain Kirk
from Star Trek One.
Two.
Five. Generations.
Boston Legal.
Now, Lisa,
I know you miss
your whale.
so I got you a pet
that will never die.
An invisible dog.
Aw, look.
He's doing his business.
Hey! Not on the rug!
You bad dog!
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ooh! Ooh!
Stop biting my leg!
Ow! All right, that's it.
You're going outside.
(sighs)
HOMER:
Bad dog, stop!
(loud creaking)
Bluella?
Oh, hey, there, Lisa.
Just oiling the
old door here.
Finally silenced
that mournful wail.
(sad moaning)
-(gasps)
-(moaning)
Oh.
(squeaking)
Huh?
(loud pop)
(sighs)
(squeaking)
(whale song)
No. I'm not gonna be
disappointed again.
-(squeaking)
-Ew! Ew! Ew! Ew! Ew!
(amazed gasp)
(panting)
(gasps)
They must be Bluella's children!
Hello, whale calves!
Your mother lives on
through you! Huh?
Run! I mean, swim!
I mean...
(makes urgent
whale moaning sounds)
Those baby whales are doomed,
just like their mom.
Oh!
I guess it's just nature's way.
(boat approaching)
Nature is a toothless,
dying hag.
We are gonna save
those whale babies!
Dad? Where did you get
that boat?
I'm taking it on a test drive
from the boat store. Get in.
Shark Week
just got canceled.
Drop the 'poon!
Oh, come on! Leave me alone!
I'm trying
to save your precious whales!
We're not here
to protect the whales.
We're here
to protect the sharks.
Did you know that
over 40 million sharks
are slaughtered every year
to make shark-fin soup?
(mutters)
You like sharks?
Being a true eco-activist
means supporting
every animal's
struggle for life.
Except for
cockroaches. Yuck!
Linda, please.
Puh! Typical eco-jerks--
using words to talk.
Dad, no!
They're right.
If the only way
to save the whales
is to kill
another innocent creature,
I can't let you do it.
Sharks, innocent? Please.
Every year, they kill
a couple of people
who do a series
of stupid things.
A shark's reptilian brain
understands only one thing--
the crime of murder.
(yells, shouting)
(gasping)
Dad! The sharks must
think you're a baby whale.
HOMER:
Ooh, a baby whale.
My diet is working.
Why couldn't I be eaten
by a giraffe?
That would be fun.
Gently bonk the shark
on the nose with this.
It'll either make him go away
or eat you quicker.
D'oh! Huh?
Ooh, maybe the blood
will scare the sharks off.
(screaming)
(Homer gasps, whales bellowing)
LISA:
It's the baby
whales' dad!
Thanks, buddy!
(bellowing)
Thanks for not letting
me give up, Dad.
Hey, I'd do anything
for a sweet, intelligent mammal,
by which I mean you.
Oh.
Do you think
they'll be okay?
Absolutely.
He's young, he's got
two cute kids.
He'll be moving in with
a sexy lady octopus in no time.
They'll have to sell
their old place.
Too many memories.
But if I'm not mistaken,
there's a little
whale-a-puss on the way.
(chuckling)
Tonight let's all
draw pictures
of what your
father just said.
♪ La mer ♪
♪ Qu'on voit danser ♪
♪ Le long des golfes clairs ♪
♪ A des reflets d'argent ♪
♪ La mer ♪
♪ Des reflets changeants ♪
♪ Sous la pluie ♪
♪ La mer ♪
♪ Au ciel d'été confond ♪
♪ Ses blancs moutons ♪
♪ Avec les anges si purs ♪
♪ La mer bergère d'azur ♪
♪ Infinie ♪
♪ Voyez ♪
♪ Près des étangs ♪
♪ Ces grands roseaux
mouillés... ♪
(whale song)
Shh!
Enhanced by Fotokem