D'oh!
- Here's your raise.
- D'oh!
Light! Light! Light...!
Light!
- It's your turn to get up.
- Light.
I'll never understand
how something
that came from inside of you
became my responsibility.
Out!
Light!
Daddy. Breakfast.
Geez, this kid's kind of smart.
Tuesday.
Autumn.
- She's a genius.
- Foliage.
Like the guy who invented
shoes with lights in them.
Cornucopia?
Sweetie, it's no surprise
you're awesome.
We didn't have to pull you out
by the elbow, like the boy.
D'oh!
Harvard College,
admissions essay.
Lisa M. Simpson.
I was born with one
great advantage in life...
A voice that would make a rhino
stick its horn up its butt?
Rhinos are extinct, nimrod.
Not hippos. I just saw one
in smelly, blue pants.
Why you little...
I'm not little.
I'm 20, and I live at home.
- Why you disappointing...
- Oh, man.
You know you're choking
someone who can vote.
- But did you vote?
- No.
- Why you little...
- Oh, come on, man.
Not voting
fascist-enabling...
Must stop
President Kid Rock.
I was born with
one great advantage,
a family that never made
anything easy.
Never more than
on my seventh birthday.
It's my birthday!
Seven years old!
I'll wear
my favorite blue dress.
I'll wear red, just for today.
It's my birthday.
I want bacon!
I can't get Maggie to sleep.
I guess I'll just have
to start using these.
Whoa, okay, okay.
That's enough for now.
Geez, come on.
Don't make me put you
under warm water.
I give up.
Anyone have anything
to say to me?
Well, of course, honey.
Get ready for school
or you'll be late.
Oy, this baby.
Lisa, sweetie, I know
why you're excited.
This is a very big day.
Happy...
hour at Moe's
was extended by an hour.
What?
Happy hour at Moe's
Now he'll never close
Class, today is
a very special day.
It's someone's birthday.
Someone whose parents
pretended to forget.
Yes.
And that someone is
Hubert Wong.
Happy birthday, superstar.
Lisa, please don't ruin
Hubert's birthday.
You wouldn't like it
if someone ruined yours.
I am sorry, but if you
can't control yourself,
I'll have to send you
to the office.
But you saying that makes me
wants to cry more.
No, Hubert.
No cupcake for her.
Lisa, school is a place
for sitting quietly.
What about learning?
No longer part of our mandate.
Did your mom ever
disappoint you?
This isn't about mother,
so don't say
a mother word about her.
Don't you dare, Mother,
don't you dare.
It's just me, a student.
I can't hear you, Mother.
She's everywhere and everyone.
I'm everywhere
because you're nothing.
Thanks for getting me
out of work, sweetie.
- Want the rest of my donut?
- No, sir.
What?
Please tell me what's wrong.
I can't tell you.
You just have to know.
- Would tickling help matters?
- No.
Well, that's really
all I have in my toolbox.
Okay, let me think.
What's today? Tuesday?
Yes.
That would make you six years
and 365 days old.
Yes.
It's your birthday!
And you forgot it, Lisa.
But because it's your birthday,
I forgive you.
And you're gonna have
the best day ever.
Optimism, you're back.
Attention, world.
It's little Lisa's birthday,
and you all forgot.
Not me.
Now I suppose I got to get
your kid something.
Just remember them
in your prayers.
Both of them? Fine.
Happy birthday, dear Lisa
Happy birthday to you
We all forgot
And all was well,
until the next year,
when they forgot again.
I mean, really, two in a row?
Even Luigi remembers it.
Well, we have-a
the same-a birthday.
Makes it easy.
You, me, and Hubert Wong.
That's a-right, Hubert.
Cupcake for her.
As I got older,
I realized, as all must,
that my parents
were not demigods.
You are going to die soon.
Shut up.
Blood pressure spiking.
Shut up!
Calling your doctor.
Hello?
Shut up!
No, they are a man and a woman
trapped in a fragile marriage
that nearly fell apart
when I turned 14.
Happy birthday! Happy birthday!
I remembered!
Don't tell your therapist.
Lisa, it's your birthday
Here's five brand-new verses
Soon you'll be a woman
Soon you'll be in love
Who'd be better
to take advice from
Than a man who wears
one glove?
Lisa, it's your birthday
Happy birthday, Lisa
Yeah.
Thank you.
It's a wonderful cake, Dad,
but I'm 14.
D'oh!
Happy birthday, Lisa.
We miss you in second grade.
Oh, someday you'll
get out of there, Ralph.
I don't want to.
I'm bigger than teacher.
I broke my desk.
Teacher cry.
I'm growing a mustache
under my long nose.
Better use Mom's closet.
It's full?
Read me. Read me.
Come on, help a letter out.
Dear Homer,
by the time you read this...
I will be gone.
Since we married,
you've changed.
Not once for the better.
What's it say? I can't read.
So I'm taking
the kids and opening
a bed-and-breakfast.
Bitterly, Marge.
Is Mom really leaving Dad?
So, you finally left him.
Well, good for me
and good for you.
I finally learned how
to unhook a bra with one hand.
Lisa, I know what you're doing.
You're hiding when you're
supposed to help me
give the dog a bath.
Mom, Mom!
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
I'm not going anywhere.
Oh, God bless you, inertia.
Not until I wash this dog.
Bart, Mom's leaving Dad.
Oh, the poor guy.
Please let me tell him, please.
Pass the gravy.
We used to call it grave,
but that was too scary.
So we modified it to gravy,
unless it had meat chunks.
In which case, it was gravier,
but the war changed everything.
I wish you wouldn't drink
so much in front of the kids.
Marge, I tried to drink
in the pantry,
but you claim
that's antisocial.
Why don't you
just go to Moe's?
You want me to go to a bar
on my daughter's birthday?
That is so messed up.
I'm going, of course,
but it is so messed up.
Happy birthday.
Harvard will save me.
Kiss me, Lisa, in front of
the hall my grandfather endowed.
He made his money in opium,
but we said it was molasses.
First, I have to save
my parents' marriage.
Wait here in this fantasy?
Yeah, can we, you know,
see other people?
Sure.
Man, Moe, you sure are spry.
The job keeps me young, eh.
Dad! Mom is gonna leave you.
Sweetie, marriages
are like water heaters.
They sit peacefully for years
until they explode in a fireball
ruining everything you own.
Mom packed her bags.
Which suitcase?
The one with the broken wheel?
Because she won't get more than
a block away with that.
She fixed the wheel.
Oh, God!
Dad, you've got to shape up.
I'm 14-years-old.
These next four years
are the last memories I'll have
of all of us together.
I'll do anything
you say, sweetie.
I want you to stop drinking.
Stop drinking?
But that's like asking a golfer
to stop drinking.
I never thought I'd say this,
but I'd better text my sponsor.
Homer's got a sponsor?
What idiot would lean
into that buzz saw?
Hey, hey!
I'm the man from A-diddly-A!
Ned, I have
to quit drinking. Now!
All right, soberino,
it's just 12 simple steps.
Oh, 12?
Fine. Nine.
Okay, step one,
admit you're powerless.
I'm powerless.
Boom! Done.
Step two, admit there is a power
greater than yourself.
If I'm powerless, isn't every
power greater than myself?
This is the 12 steps,
not 20 questions.
Now, make a decision
to turn your life to God.
God. He's in every deal,
like undercoating. Fine.
Make a searching
moral inventory of yourself.
If I have one tiny flaw, it's
that I have many enormous flaws.
Admit the nature of your wrongs.
Well, I'm not
the best parallel parker.
Are you ready for God
to remove these defects?
Dear Lord, the Satan of Heaven,
I order you to fix me.
Okay, I'm just gonna
fast-forward through this.
- Make amends.
- Here's your wallet.
- Engage in prayer.
- I pray you're not mad.
And have a spiritual awakening.
Things that cost $9.99
are really ten dollars!
The Lord has spoken,
and it is good!
That's it.
No more drinking.
Look at those, guys.
I used to be like them.
Oh, I'm overjoyed for thee.
Call me anytime you hear
the devil's seductive voice.
Homer?
Homer...
How's about a Flaming Moe?
Drink me!
I'm the most overpriced thing
at Universal Studios!
No! I won't do it!
Lisa, sweetie,
let's celebrate your birthday!
Yes!
Ah, honey.
I'm so sorry.
I miss you so much.
He did quit, for good,
and it was the best
birthday present I ever got.
Well, the essay is pretty trite.
But her grades are perfect,
her extracurricular's stellar,
and she'll be the first
from her state, ever.
Admit! And now for our instantaneous
letter of acceptance.
I'm in! And I accept!
I'm here! And it's Ivy-er
than my Ivy-est dreams.
- Lisa Simpson.
- Lisa Simpson?
I'm sorry, but there must
be some mistake.
- Oh, no!
- Gotcha!
My one moment of superiority
before a lifetime
of begging you for money.
Come on, sweetie, let me
carry you over the threshold.
Dad! That's for weddings.
I think Dad's
turning into Grampa.
Hey, I don't need
to listen to that hooey!
Because I make tie clips
out of maple syrup,
but only for Flag Day!
By the sea, by the sea
By the beautiful sea...
This is great. We don't have
to visit Grampa anymore.
Chug, chug, chug.
Really, man, I've had enough.
The hazing ends
when we say it ends.
Do you need any help unpacking?
Mom, I need to learn
to do these things for myself.
Sorry, friend,
you can't pahk your cah
in Hahvahd Yahd.
I can't what my what
in what what what?
You can't pahk...
- Yes...?
- In Hahvahd Yahd.
- Are you on Novocain?
- Yes, but recreationally.
Now, move your craptastic cah.
Hi. I'm Caitlyn.
My roommate.
So, you play an instrument?
Bari sax.
- Are you good?
- I played at Kenny G's funeral.
Ooh, she's pretty impressive.
Any childhood heartbreak?
My parents forgot my birthday
three times.
She beats me at everything!
I don't belong here.
While you were feeling inferior,
I took the top bunk.
Stroke, stroke, stroke...
I'm not even gonna make it
through freshman week.
- Hey, little sister.
- Well!
At least you're having
a good time.
Yeah, these girls want me
to piss off their parents
before they head home.
Get away from him, Mandy!
I'll pay! I'll pay!
Tell him I have two kids.
The beauty part is,
it's not a lie.
You always know
what to say, Bart.
Well, try this.
I've known you all your life,
and if there's one thing I know,
it's that you belong here.
You're gonna study harder,
you're gonna ask
better questions,
you're gonna get into
their brains like an earworm
and chew, chew, chew!
Now, make Mom and Dad proud.
And then I'll make 'em proud.
- But you first.
- Thank you.
This is it.
I'm on my own
for the rest of my life.
Are you my roommate too?
For now.
Till they kick me out.
Everyone thinks
they're not gonna make it.
I already got kicked out
of a psycho single
'cause my roommate
didn't like me.
She used all the shampoo!
I just think you're funny.
So I suppose
you want to tell me your SATs.
Very much. But I won't.
Tell me about you.
I'm already homesick.
I was always the kid
that didn't fit in.
Middle child.
Artsy. And I play
the most unpopular
instrument there is...
The jazz clarinet.
You know your way
around a licorice stick, kid.
You blow a mean fish hook
yourself, sister!
- Let's talk normal now.
- Thank you.
You know, today
I was hoping I would meet...
- A lifelong friend?
- Yes!
Here I am.
730 verbal, 790 math,
800 telekinesis.
740 verbal, 780 math,
and I speak fluent cat!
I have a friend!
Maybe more than a friend.
After that day,
I never looked back...
except for all the time
I just spent looking back.
But I never doubted
that who I am was good enough.
Light! Light...!
Sweetie, you're one year old,
and you're already the most
amazing thing I ever did.
Daddy happy.
Daddy very happy.
Daddy euphoric!
She's making up words.
Boy, the way Nirvana played
Steroids caused a hit parade
Beanie Babies had it made
Those were the days
And we had real heroes then
Like Jar Jar Binks
and Qui-Gon Jinn
Mister, we could use a man
Like Richard Simmons again
Watching films
like Gilbert Grape
Then rewinding all the tape
Gee, our modem
dialed up great
Those were the days...
Very nice.
See you in court.
Light! Light! Light...!
Autumn.