The Simpsons
D'oh!
If you ask me,
Muhammad Ali
in his prime
was much better
than anti-lock brakes.
Yeah.
But what about Johnny Mathis
versus Diet Pepsi?
I cannot listen
to this again!
Guys, I just ordered
my wife the greatest
anniversary present.
A koi pond!
A koi pond?
Yeah. A meditative
lily pond with big,
beautiful fish that
fry up really good.
That's the perfect gift.
Yeah. You don't even
have to feed the fish,
'cause squirrels drown in it.
You got this
husband thing down, Homer.
Yeah. You must be
some kind of marriage
super genius.
How about a few tips?
Certainly, Lenford.
Make every day
a celebration
of your love.
Surprise her
with a pasta salad.
Put a mini-beret
on your wang.
This stuff is gold.
Happy marriage,
here I come.
This'll really help
with my speed dating.
I got 400 no's.
I can't wait to
see my surprise!
Hey, hey, hey!
No peeking!
Happy anniversary, Marge!
A koi pond!
It's beautiful!
Oh, you sweet,
wonderful man-child.
I finally have
a peaceful place to sit
and hear my own thoughts.
How much money
did he piss away on this?
What was that?
What the hell
is that noise?
That caterpillar
is screaming.
The poor thing's
in pain.
What he needs is a visit
from kindly old Doctor Foot.
Hold it right there,
Doctor Foot.
You're about to kill
an endangered species,
the screamapillar,
which has chosen
your yard as its home.
Fine, I won't kill it.
Finish the job.
Mr. Simpson, allowing
an endangered species to die
is a federal offense
under the Reversal of
Freedoms Act of 1994.
You are now
legally responsible
for the safety and well-being
of this screamapillar.
Everything you need to know
is in this pamphlet.
Wow. Look at
all this stuff.
"Without constant reassurance,
it will die.
"It's sexually
attracted to fire. "
Are you sure God doesn't
want it to be dead?
Hey, what's God gonna do?
Make my wife leave me again?
What does he want now?
If he wants to sleep
with us, forget it!
Put him down, boy!
Put him down!
"Once upon a time
there were three bears.
"The end. "
Oh, fine! I'll go
back to the beginning!
Oh, no!
I crushed that horrible bug!
What should I do?
Bury it, quickly,
before anyone finds out.
I'm gonna tell!
The hell you will!
Now we're in it together.
There's no going back.
Yeah!
Stop what you're doing!
Why don't I hear
any screaming?
He's sleeping!
Then why don't I hear
any sleep screams?
Well, the thing
about that is...
Woo-hoo! He's alive!
Now you can't punish me.
Homer Simpson,
for attempted insecticide
and aggravated buggery,
I sentence you to 200 hours
of community service.
Next case. Duffman v.
Duff Brewing Corporation.
Duffman's pension
has been mismanaged!
Oh, yeah!
Objection.
That party-hearty
attitude is a registered
trademark of
the Duff Corporation.
Whatever happened
to fair use?
Lousy community service!
Meals on Wheels!
Eat it up or I go to jail.
Didn't these meals
used to have a cobbler?
They discontinued
the cobbler.
You smell like cobbler.
Now let's not get into
who smells like what.
Come in.
Oh, I can't let you
leave now.
Safe and sound.
That's better.
Thank God I'm out of matches!
Oh, no. Here's another one.
Please don't kill me!
I won't tell anyone
about the skeleton!
And I could bring
you more victims!
Like Lenny!
He'd go great
with wild rice!
Oh, don't be such
a nervous Pervis.
That's not a real skeleton,
it's a Halloween costume.
But what about the ax?
Oh, don't be silly.
I just use that
to chop through
those tough Meals
on Wheels steaks.
Oh, I couldn't
possibly eat all this.
Please join me.
You're the shut-in.
So I threw
the SuperBall so hard
it hit the ceiling twice,
then broke a lamp!
Oh, Homer, I feel like
I'm talking to Bennett Cerf.
Yeah, I've gotten a lot of
compliments about my talking.
Before you go,
would you mind opening
this jar of butter pickles?
My pleasure.
Oh, my.
You're as strong
as you are handsome.
And I can ride
my bike real fast.
Aren't you a wonder?
Can I call you
the next time I need
a muscular he-man?
Hey!
I'm not running an employment
service, you old...
Oh, you mean me?
I'd be delighted.
Yello? Hi, Mrs. Bellamy.
No, I'm not doing anything.
I can mow your lawn.
Cover for me.
Hello? Uh-huh.
Yes, Mrs. Bellamy.
I'll be right there.
That woman is
taking advantage of you.
And we need you to do
things around here.
The oven light is out.
And you never finished
filling up the aquarium.
Marge, I can't say no
to a helpless old lady.
They put spells on you!
Fine. I'll go talk to her.
Homer's family
needs him, too.
And that's that!
Oh, Marge,
you're such a good woman
to care so much
about your husband.
All I have left
of my Chester is his
tattered old Army jacket.
Let me sew that
up for you.
Make sure
you double stitch.
Then do these socks.
Darn her socks?
I say darn her!
I'll do them and
then I'm out of here.
Did you hear that
Gertie had a terrible fall
outside the thrift store?
Oh! She would fall there!
Hey, who do I have to
gum to get a refill?
Freshen your drinks,
ladies?
Laxative?
Yeah.
Mother,
may I read a magazine
while I wait in the car?
Don't you read enough
at school, bookworm?
I am so sick of
doing her dirty work.
She's taking
advantage of us, Homer!
The Missus prefers
you call me Simpson.
She's got a set
of lungs on her.
Are you all right?
That man took my
diamond necklace.
Don't worry.
You're gonna
be just fine.
Okay.
Oh, my gosh.
She's dead!
So let me get this straight.
This mysterious man
with braces
just stabbed the old lady
and disappeared?
Without a trace.
Found her will, Chief.
It was just changed
to leave the Simpsons
$50,000.
So it's a good
thing she died,
from our point of view,
financially.
Well,
I'd like to thank you both
for cooperating with...
Did you do it?
Chief Wiggum!
Homer and I are innocent!
I'm sorry, Marge.
I can't believe
I tried to trick you
with such an...
Did you do it?
No!
Now if you'll excuse us,
we'll just be...
Does that ever work?
No. No, never does.
Book him, Lou.
Yeah, sure. Go ahead.
I'll be back on the streets
by dinnertime.
You'll see.
And the elephant that
couldn't stop laughing
was put to death.
Speaking of death,
octogenarian Myrna Bellamy
was brutally murdered
last night.
The top suspects,
her disgruntled servants,
Homer and Marge Simpson.
Hmm?
Top suspects?
Oh, dear.
Now everyone will think
Homer and I did it.
The real killer is
the man with the braces.
Yeah.
If Dad killed everyone
he talked about killing,
would any of us be here?
You'd be dead
a million times.
Do you really think
Homer could be a killer?
I just can't believe
a man we sat and drank
with all these years
could do such
a horrible thing.
Well, we've all got
that voice in our heads
telling us to kill.
You just have
to drown it out.
I've been
working on the railroad
all the livelong day
Yeah, that's better.
Oh, man. What a day!
I'd kill for a beer.
Right away, sir.
I don't want no trouble.
Mmm.
I'd stab somebody
for a pickle.
Give me some peanuts.
You didn't say
you'd kill me.
I'll kill you if you don't
give me some peanuts.
Here you go, mister.
Today's readings
come from Matthew,
Mark, Luke, and John.
Well, maybe just
Matthew and Mark.
Amen!
Next on the
Springfield Death Tour
is the home of Marge
and Homer Simpson,
also known as "H-Diddy
and his Murder Ho. "
Go away!
Wait, wait!
That's a suggestion,
not a threat.
Homer!
What? It goes
right by our house.
This is ridiculous.
You've been through
my delicates, my silkies,
my dainties,
and my unmentionables!
I insist on
searching every inch
of this home personally.
Here's my underwear drawer.
Where's that robot?
Hey, Chief.
You better get in here.
Mrs. Bellamy's necklace!
Homer and Marge Simpson,
you're under arrest for
the murder of Myrna Bellamy.
Homer,
what are we going to do?
You know, Chief,
if you let us go,
there's a diamond
necklace in it for you.
I hope you're
not suggesting
that I would take that
necklace as a bribe.
Think again, dirtbag.
Because I can
just swipe it later
from the evidence locker!
Yeah, your wife's gonna look
pretty good in that, Chief.
Yeah. She's a super lady.
I can't believe
we've been arrested
for murder.
Don't worry, Marge.
I'll cut us
a deal by becoming
a jailhouse snitch.
I know who
stopped up the toilet.
Now don't worry, kids.
You'll be placed with
a caring foster family.
Young'uns, meet your new
brother and sister.
They's worth five dollars
a day county money.
I'm Bart.
And this is Lisa.
Them's city names.
From now on,
you're Dingus Squatford Jr.
and Pamela E. Lee.
But I like my old name.
You hush up, Dingus!
They hated the victim.
Her death earned
them $50,000.
And the necklace was
found in their home.
Does the defense have
any closing remarks?
Well, not at this time,
Your Honor.
This is the only time.
Well, then no.
Mr. Foreman,
have you reached
a verdict?
Verdict? Is that what
we were supposed to do?
Well, in all my
years on the bench...
'Cause that's what we did!
You juries.
Gonna be the...
How do you find?
We find
the defendants guilty.
Homer and Marge Simpson,
I sentence you to death
in the electric chair!
But we're innocent!
It was the man
with the braces!
Can't you do anything?
Surprise witnesses?
Evidence tampering?
Play the race card!
Play it!
We appreciate your
coming to comfort us.
But we're not Catholic.
Oh, dear, dear, dear.
Well, then I hope you enjoy
your stay in hell.
Nice dress.
Oh, go home and have
sex with your wife!
That's it. Bring it on!
Why you little...
Come on, you sainted...
How can you have
such an appetite
at a time like this?
Let's just say
I'm planning a little
surprise for the execution.
This cannon is gonna
be full when I go off.
Ka-boom!
You know,
this is our last night
and our cells
are side by side.
It's hard to get
in the mood
with all those
murderous eyes
staring at us.
Just think of them
as twinkling stars.
Homie, I'm sorry.
I can't.
I just keep thinking about
everything we're gonna miss.
The kids growing up.
Grandchildren.
I want to confess.
I killed and robbed
the old lady all by myself.
Marge is completely innocent.
The only thing
she's guilty of
is loving too much.
The murder I did.
Congratulations,
Mrs. Simpson.
Your husband
confessed to everything.
You're free to go.
Oh, my love.
You saved my life.
Now you do it for me.
Dead man walking
on the green mile!
Give me your hands, boss.
I'll kill you!
I killed them other people,
and I'll kill you, too!
You want some cornbread,
Mr. Jingles?
Well, you can forget it.
Because I'm gonna kill you!
Hello?
Yes, Governor!
No, Governor.
It's not too late.
Yes, Governor.
I'll tell him right away.
The governor says he hopes
you're a twitcher!
Oh, yes!
Oh.
Chin up, Homer.
We've gotta put
an electrode there
to ground the brain stem.
Thank you.
Goodbye, Marge.
I'll always love you.
You're on Frame Up!
That's right.
Homer Simpson,
you're the latest victim
of the new reality show,
Frame Up!
It's the man
with the braces!
I'm also your host.
Now let's meet a ghost.
Mrs. Bellamy?
There never was
a Mrs. Bellamy.
Only me,
Carmen Electra!
I knew it!
And I'm some
actor they hired!
Frame Up is
Fox's latest hit,
right after
No Pants Island
and Fart Date!
This whole thing
was a joke?
I've never been
so relieved!
Relieved and angry.
So wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
You tied up
the judicial system,
costing the city
millions of dollars,
just for a TV show?
Yes.
And I'm gonna be
in the show?
Yes!
Can Eddy and Lou
have producer credits?
Yup!
Now what are
your last names?
We don't have them.
We're like Cher.
Oh, Homie.
I'm so lucky
to be married
to such a selfless
and loving man.
Mom, Dad!
Thank God you're okay!
We were in the greenroom.
I had so much shrimp.
Well, I'm glad
everyone's all right.
But I think you
should be ashamed.
Toying with a human life
for TV ratings.
Uh, Homer.
My face is up here.
I've made my choice.
ENGLISH - US - PSDH