♪ The Simpsons ♪
(TIRES SCREECHING)
D'oh!
(EXCLAIMING)
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
(WHISPERING)
Call the police.
I need change for a dollar.
No change
without purchase.
What's the cheapest thing
you've got?
A 2-ounce bag
of chips, $5.99.
$5.99? What a rip-off!
Someone should shoot you.
Aw! I was hoping
we'd miss the 3:00 holdup.
I don't know
what to do for
dinner now.
Maybe we could
shop somewhere else.
There's a farm stand
next door.
(CHICKENS CLUCKING)
Interesting.
It's like a corndog
without the dog.
Put whatever you want
in this burlap sack.
You may not.
That's my baby carrier!
They so traumatized,
I'm taking 'em for
a walk in they's stroller.
(CHILDREN YELL)
(ALL COOING)
Well, I think this family
should try more
vegetarian meals.
We'd feel better
and live longer.
Vegetables,
you've been promoted
from side dish to entree.
I don't miss meat at all!
This Portobello mushroom
eats like a steak.
A rubbery,
fungus-like steak.
(RUMBLING)
Oh, Marge, I'm giving
birth to a food baby!
(RUMBLING)
Oh!
I feel like something
crawled inside me
and took a crap.
Bart, don't use
that word... (GASPS)
Crap!
(ALL GAGGING)
(ALL SHIVERING)
I brought you some
weak tea and dry toast.
No fair.
Lisa didn't get sick.
It's 'cause your bodies
are so used to processed food,
it's a shock
when you eat vegetables
full of vitamins, minerals,
and trace amounts
of bug feces.
Uh...
Hmm.
I think it's staying down.
It's staying down!
It's not staying down!
Wait, yeah. It's staying down!
Oh, no! It's not!
Yes, it is.
No, it's not! Yeah.
No! Yep! No! Yep! No!
Yep, no, yep,
no, yep, no.
Stop it!
You'll all feel better
if you get a little sleep.
Now, close your eyes.
(SIGHS)
(MOANS)
Where's my bucket? Oh.
♪ Hush, little baby
don't say a word
♪ Mama's gonna
buy you a mockingbird
♪ And if that
mockingbird don't sing
(HUMMING)
♪ And if that
diamond ring turns brass
♪ Mama's gonna buy
you a looking glass ♪
HOMER: Lisa sings so sweetly.
And Bart is my pillow.
Everyone's good for something.
(YAWNING)
Looks like you
guys are on the mend.
Yeah, 'cause we're through
with vegetables.
From now on,
I'm only eating food
that I know had a soul.
KRUSTY: (ON TV)
Hey, hey, kids!
Do you have what it takes
to be a singing sensation?
A dynamite voice?
Ruthless, pushy parents?
A void in your self-esteem
that can only be
filled by applause?
Oh, God. I know that void.
Then you were born to enter
Krusty's Li'l Starmaker
Singing Competition!
ANNOUNCER: Not affiliated
with American Idol.
We've never even
heard of "American Idol."
The winner will be animated
into an "Itchy &
Scratchy" cartoon.
So, enter today,
especially if you're
a funny-looking kid
who doesn't know he sucks!
I'm a comin', Krusty!
Lisa, you should
enter that contest.
You've got a great voice!
It made us
all feel better.
Thanks, Bart.
That's really sweet.
(SIGHS) I think I puked up
all of my meanness.
Ow!
Praise the Lord!
I'm on the road to recovery!
I hope we didn't
camp out here
for nothing.
It's like every kid
in Springfield showed up.
Don't worry about
the competition, sweetie.
Whenever I enter a contest,
I tell myself
I'm going to win.
Because sometimes,
if you believe hard enough,
God cuts you a break.
After all, he works for us.
Our prayers pay his salary.
And if I win, I'll be
on Itchy & Scratchy.
Ha ha! En garde!
Parry! Thrust!
Nicely done,
Wind Dancer.
(LAUGHS)
But seriously,
cruelty to animals
is no laughing matter.
You can make
a difference.
Spay and neuter your pets!
And remember!
Save the violence
for cartoons!
(BOTH SCREAMING)
For details,
log onto peta.org.
(MOANS)
(LAUGHS)
(GASPS)
All right, kids.
Let's do this quick.
After this,
I gotta record 27 seasons
of DVD commentaries.
And I remember nothing!
Today,
we'll pick the lucky children
who will get to
compete on the air.
I was going to be
your celebrity judge.
But then I realized,
I'd have to pay attention.
So, instead, we'll use
the Applause-O-Meter.
Huh? Huh?
Now, let's get this over with!
(GUFFAWING)
(SIGHS)
♪ A, B, C, D, E, F, G
♪ How I wonder what you are ♪
Thank you.
I can't believe
I used to date him.
Lise, you're a shoo-in.
♪ Hush little baby
don't say a word
♪ Mama's gonna buy
you a mocking bird
♪ That's gonna sing
♪ Yes it is, y'all
(ALL CHEERING)
♪ And if that mocking bird
don't sing
♪ Mama's gonna
buy you a diamond ring
♪ That's gonna shine, shine
♪ Oh, it shines so bright I
(ALL CHEER)
Lisa, that sounds
like a fancier version
of the song
you're going to sing.
And she's giving us
the emotional experience
of a lifetime.
(SOBBING)
Thank you for
this angel, Lord.
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, yeah, yeah, no ♪
(ALL CHEER)
This contest is moot!
A li'l star has been made!
When she sings a C, it's a C!
Unlike a certain glee club
I've wasted my life on!
Well, I may not know much,
but I do know talent
when my producers
point it out to me.
We have our first contestant!
Clarissa Wellington!
(ALL CHEER)
Oh, there's no way
I'm gonna beat her.
Why? Just because
she sings
like Whitney Houston
brought to life?
(SIGHS)
Don't lose hope,
sweetie.
I'm gonna write
you a song so great,
you can't lose.
And that's not
just the beer talking.
Your father's in here, too.
(PLAYING PIANO)
♪ When a man
loves a woman ♪
Which one are you?
The man or the woman?
Questioning the kid's
sexuality? Well done. Ha!
Ha!
(FEEDBACK)
Here you go, honey!
Sing this.
How did you write
a song so quickly?
Much of the tune
is plagiarized.
Now, go, go, go!
♪ I've been to
Paris and London
And Tokyo town
♪ But one crazy burg
Has 'em all beat hands down
Jacksonville?
♪ I'm talkin' Springfield
You can buy chimichangas
♪ Talkin' Springfield
The chicks have big gazongas
♪ There's tires on fire
A guy named Apu
♪ And Skinner, and Grampa
and old Disco Stu
Did I forget to mention you?
You? That's me!
♪ I'm talkin' Springfield
♪ Where nobody sucks
♪ Except for Flanders ♪
(ALL CHEERING)
(BEEPING)
(SCREAMS)
I get it!
I get it! She's good!
Looks like they love ya, kid.
And the audience
is always right.
I wish I could say the same
about my stockbroker.
(GUFFAWS)
Ah, what do you jerks know?
That's a quality joke.
You did it, sweetie!
No! We did it, Dad!
She's right. It was all me.
I really do like
working with you, Dad.
Will you keep helping me?
Of course, sweetie.
You and I
are gonna write
and sing our way
out of this
godforsaken hellhole.
But your song said
you liked Springfield.
I wrote it about Shelbyville,
then changed the names.
♪ La, la, la
la, la, la, la, la ♪
Good job, sweetie!
Every time you hit
that note, I'll shoot
a glass with my BB gun.
I really appreciate you taking
such an interest in me, Dad.
Honey, our time together
is precious to me.
I didn't want
to say anything
but I don't think
I'm gonna be
around much longer.
Really? What's wrong?
Well, Moe's getting
a big screen TV in February.
Just in time for the Pro Bowl.
Maybe this time
my beloved blue shirts
will win.
Is it possible
to get a green spotlight?
MAN: Sorry, sweetie.
We don't have green.
Let Daddy
go talk to the man.
(HUMMING)
May I have
a word with you?
(DOOR CLOSES)
(MAN GROANS)
Is that green
enough for you, sweetie?
Because I can make it greener.
No, it's fine.
♪ Alas, my love
you do me wrong
♪ To cast me off
discourteously ♪
(SCREAMING)
That's Cameron.
Girls go crazy
over him.
He's cute,
unthreatening,
And his smile
brought a puppy
back to lfie.
(SCREAMING)
Don't worry, honey.
The song I wrote you
is so schmaltzy,
it'll make Moon River
sound like
a farting orangutan!
♪ My kitty died
on Christmas Eve
♪ Daddy told me to be brave
♪ But instead
of singing carols
♪ I was digging
Snowball's grave ♪
(SOBBING)
ALL: Oh!
Oh, God.
I miss Lisa's cat
so much.
All right, you know
how it works.
Every week
we eliminate
one contestant
based on the votes
cast by you, the audience.
ANNOUNCER'. Disclaimer.
All ballots were lost
and vote totals made up.
The first contestant
eliminated is
Katie Anderson!
(SOBS)
(LAUGHS)
Katie, you were
the first victim of
the Buzz Cola trap door.
Fall into the flavor hole!
And the next contestant
to be eliminated
is Clarissa!
(SOBS)
Yeah, it's you, honey.
Please don't cry.
(WHISPERS)
Keep crying.
It's dynamite.
(INHALING DEEPLY)
Sweetie, tonight
you were perfect!
Marge, Lisa and I
were just discussing
how to improve
tonight's performance.
Now, you're confusing her
by telling her
she was perfect.
Mr. Simpson,
I brought those Twizzlers
you asked for.
My little girl likes
Red Vines! You little...
(SCREAMING)
Mr. Simpson, please stop!
You think
I can't kill you?
There's a hundred
little punks graduating
from Syracuse this year
that would beg
to kiss my ass!
Get outta here!
(WHIMPERING)
He's crazy!
Hey, these are Red Vines!
There you go, sweetie.
Daddy got you your candy.
Homie, I'm worried
you're turning into
some kind of super
cuckoo stage mother.
Yeah. For once,
couldn't you just turn
into a good father?
Would that be
so hard?
Hey, give me a break.
Living through Lisa
is the healthiest thing
that ever
happened to me.
But, Dad, you don't need
to help me by
humiliating people!
(SCOFFS)
You love sausage,
but you hate
to see it getting made.
I don't love sausage!
Then would you like
to see it getting made?
Dad, you're fired!
Fired? Me?
Everything I did,
I did for you!
(DOOR SLAMS)
Dad, I'm sorry you're hurt,
but you left me no choice.
You were obnoxious
at a level
not even permitted
in show business!
Do you know
the hours I worked?
The people
I had to yell at?
The tires
I had to slash?
No one asked you
to yell and slash!
It's called "schmoozing!"
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Bart, you want to go
to the video arcade?
Hell, I'll even go
shoe shopping.
Hey! Come back!
I'm calming down!
We'll have
family fun!
Family fun!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Hey, everybody,
I brought a guest.
Someone who appreciates
my in-your-face
management style.
Ha! Smart move!
Soon the whole world
will be lining up
to suck my nose
after I make
my new client a star.
♪ Hey, Simpson family ♪
How can I touch
your hearts tonight?
(GROANS) You're working
with Cameron now?
His name isn't
Cameron anymore.
He's now Johnny Rainbow.
Mr. Simpson,
about that...
I'm not Mr. Simpson!
That ship has sailed.
I'm Colonel Cool!
And I'm the captain
on this rocket to the stars!
So, are you
a colonel or a captain?
Neither, I'm both.
All right,
I'm gonna teach you
a little something
about jazz hands.
(SCATTING)
Now, don't stop
until it's as natural
as breathing.
Dad looks so happy.
Actually, I think
your father's
still upset
about the way
things went down.
Marge, Bart, Maggie,
Santa's Little Helper...
(SOBBING)
Lisa.
Dad, I don't want things
to be awful between us.
I made you some cookies.
I don't think
cookies are gonna
make me feel better.
Oh! Oh, God! Oh! Mmm.
They're delicious!
Mmm. Oh.
So happy!
Oh, God, they're...
They're gone.
(SIGHS)
Hi. This lighting's
a little bright.
And could I get
a red wash
in the background?
Sorry, hon. This is
all we got. Who's next?
We are.
Okay, Morty, give me
a rose-colored spot,
tight to the mid-chest,
And an aqua background
with an astronaut
on a surfboard.
Sure. Sure thing, Mr. S.
Lisa. Um...
At the end of your song,
remember to look
into the spotlight.
It makes your eyes twinkle.
Aw.
Thanks, Dad.
You're welcome.
This is our final night.
Thirty contestants
have already fallen
Through our Buzz
Cola trap door.
(CHILDREN MOANING)
BOY: Let us out!
Hey, you're supposed
to clean this out
every night!
What do you mean,
"Talk to your shop
steward"? Bah!
Now, let's welcome
the first of
our two finalists,
Lisa Simpson.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I have a confession to make.
I didn't have
my usual songwriter tonight.
So, I took a stab
at writing my
own song.
Something that expresses
what's really in my heart.
Bernie, if you please?
♪ I'm in the final two
♪ I should be happy
♪ But all I want to do
♪ ls spend more time
♪ With my pappy
♪ Now that you're gone, Dad
♪ I miss you so much
♪ And your threats
against teamsters
and techies, and such
♪ Your management style
is like Attila the Hun
♪ You were vicious, malicious
but you got the job done
♪ I'm sorry I hurt you
♪ But please don't be sad
♪ You're no longer my coach
♪ But you're always my dad ♪
(ALL CHEER)
(SOBS)
Even the Applause-O-Meter
is crying.
Oh, God!
That's battery acid!
(SCREAMS)
Dad, you know,
the best part about
this whole thing
has been the time
we've spent together.
I don't care if I win
just as long as
you're in my corner again.
I always was, honey.
Look! Cameron's about
to sing the song
I wrote for him!
He's about to learn
the most important lesson
in the music business.
Don't trust people
♪ I'm a privileged boy
It's great, I gotta tell ya
♪ Privileged boy
My dad can buy and sell ya
♪ It really doesn't matter
that you're on the list
in front of me
♪ I'm gonna get your table
'cause I always
tip the maitre d'
♪ And then I'll go to Yale
because I am a legacy
♪ I'm better than you ♪
(AUDIENCE BOOING)
You suck, Johnny Rainbow!
I believed in you!
(GROANS)
No!
(SOBBING)
You sabotaged
Cameron for me.
Sure did.
I'd do anything
for you, honey.
Especially if it's easy.
Well, I think
you're the sweetest dad
in the whole world.
I'll always be there.
Not even death will stop me.
Now, you're getting creepy.
How about,
I love you, honey?
Good.
(SCATTING)
(SHUSHING)