(SINGING) The Simpsons
(SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
D'oh!
(SCREAMS)
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
(ALSO SPRACH
ZARATHUSTRA PLAYING)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Cool!
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
Happy 3:00 in the morning,
everyone.
In a mere five hours,
We'll be gazing at
Springfield's most exciting
glacier, Springfield Glacier.
I hope you're all wearing
glacier-appropriate clothing.
Hey, check out my T-shirt.
It's wicked relevant.
It's part of my Things Suck
line of clothing.
(CHUCKLES) Yes, well,
while I disagree with
your T-shirt's assertion,
I do encourage anything
that raises glacier awareness.
Busward to adventure.
(ALL GRUMBLING)
So, Lise,
ready for your trip?
Sure am. (GRUNTS)
See you next fall.
(LAUGHS)
(SCOFFS) You make
those same stupid jokes
every field trip.
Eh, you work in the
business as long as I have,
you're bound to
repeat yourself.
(GRUNTS)
Ha! See you next fall.
(LAUGHS)
(SIGHS HAPPILY)
(CHILDREN GROANING)
So, Edna, I, uh...
(CLEARS THROAT)
I wrote up some possible
discussion topics
for this trip.
Oh, here's one.
I'm still in love
with you. Discuss?
Oh, Seymour, I've moved on.
Our romance is in the history
books and there's nothing
worth highlighting. Ha!
The Skin-man doesn't
give up that easily.
(TIRES SQUEALING)
Ooh, these icy roads
are getting pretty gnarly.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
CHILDREN: Woah!
Whoa!
Oh, I'm not worried.
(GASPS) My indemnity waivers.
Stop the bus.
We'll just use the chains.
(ALL STRAINING)
l feel like
I'm in Fitzcarraldo.
That movie was flawed.
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
SEYMOUR: Behold,
children, the majesty
of Springfield Glacier.
Crane your necks skyward
to behold its icy glory.
(FROG CROAKING)
What happened to the glacier?
It's nearly melted.
(GASPS) This must be
due to global warming.
Young lady,
the federal government's
position on global warming
is that it does not exist.
This glacier's
doing just fine.
No, it isn't. It's a lump
of slush. Look at it.
(LAUGHS) I have a little girl
just like you at home.
(OMINOUSLY) That's where
she stays. At home.
Oh, I just love it here.
So many things,
and so many things
of each thing.
Welcome to Sprawl Mart.
Can I get you a cart
or a basket?
Grampa, you're a greet grater.
I mean a great greeter.
Now look who's senile.
(CHUCKLES)
(GROANS)
I'll take a cart.
All right.
(GRUNTING)
Darn thing's stuck.
I'll give it a good yank.
(SCREAMS)
Gnomes!
(GRUNTS)
(BOTH GASPING)
(BOTH PANTING)
Oh, Dad. How I'll miss your
cap, your walking stick,
your plaster base.
ABE: I'm down here, you idiot.
Dad! Where's your base?
Don't worry about that.
Someone's gotta
greet the customers.
Ah, they'll be fine.
No. They're helpless
without a greeting.
Look at them.
(SOBBING)
Make me proud,
or at least less ashamed.
I'm gonna get a glacier
postcard and send it
to my nana.
She'll be like, "No way!"
Score.
I'm going to exchange this
beach towel I bought at
Sequoia National Park.
I learned too late
that it implied tumescence.
(MECHANICAL GROWLING)
Ah, pre-modern man.
If these wise
warriors could speak,
what would they tell us?
They left a message
right here.
(BART LAUGHING)
(ALL LAUGHING)
Actually carved into the rock.
Nice work, Simpson.
Feel free to make
a rubbing.
(HUMMING)
(GROANS)
Welcome to Sprawl Mart.
Pimple cream
in aisle five.
Buenas nachos.
Ask about our
señor discount.
Hey, Rabbi . Jesus loves you .
(CHUCKLES) Just kidding.
Son, you are on fire .
A million times better
than that worth less
old coot you replaced .
That coot happens
to be my father.
Please continue.
How would you like
to be a full-time
Sprawl Mart greeter?
Is there a chance
for advancement?
No.
Whoo-hoo!
No pressure.
Evidence suggests
that this Ice Age
female was alone
when she fell
into a crevasse.
Dying alone, huh?
Terrible fate to befall
any woman, Ice Age
or modern day.
Seymour, I will now
demonstrate how over
you I am.
See that man?
Take note of how
he's not you.
Now watch.
So, is there a
Mrs. Park Ranger Johnson?
No, ma'am. I'm married
to the glacier. But, uh,
it's an open marriage.
Then bring it, fool.
(KISSING)
(GIGGLING)
Oh, for goodness sake.
You've moved on, have you?
Well, so have I.
Hmm.
(MOANING)
Mmm. Just play along.
(CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY)
LISA: Listen, people.
How can you stand
there eating snacks
and being children
when the world's
glaciers are vanishing?
We have to do
something about it.
Glaciers are nature's
alarm clock, and it's time
for us to wake up.
Can there be any doubt that
the culprit is greenhouse gas
produced by man?
(FARTING SOUND
ON WALKIE-TALKIE)
(ALL LAUGHING)
The only gas is
coming from Lisa's butt.
(ALL LAUGHING)
People, please.
I'm talking about
toxic vapors.
(FARTING SOUND
ON WALKIE-TALKIE)
(ALL LAUGHING)
Emanations.
(FARTING SOUND
ON WALKIE-TALKIE)
(ALL LAUGHING)
Miasmas.
(BLOWING RASPBERRY
OVER WALKIE-TALKIE)
CLANCY: Hey,
whoever's doing that,
get off the frequency.
We're combing the woods.
There's a killer loose
out here.
Aw, let him do it, Chief.
It lightens the mood.
Oh, my God!
LOU: That used to be a face.
(SCREAMING) Bart!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(SCREAMS)
Help. I'm sinking
in the lake.
You mean you're
walking on the glacier.
Whatever.
Check it out.
That frog has
a nerd on its butt.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Bart, you are
the meanest, nastiest
little boy that ever lived.
Hey, there's a dog
in the next car
looking at me.
Hey, dog.
You don't even care
how upset I am!
This time, you have
gone too far.
What are you gonna do,
tell Mom and Dad?
They're powerless
figureheads.
You'll see.
(MENACINGLY)
Oh, you will see.
Good morning, world.
Eat my shorts.
CLANCY: There'll be no shorts
eaten today, young man.
Bart Simpson, this
is a restraining order.
From now on, you must stay
at least 20 feet away
from your sister.
Restraining order?
Bull spit.
No piece of paper
keeps me from waling
on my sister.
(KISSING)
So you see what happens
when you don't obey
your restraining order?
Yes, Chief Wiggum.
And, Snake, do you see
what happens when you
kidnap the President?
(SIGHS)
Yes, Chief Wiggum.
And, Lou, do you see
what happens when my
coffee comes back cold?
Chief, you ordered
an ice coffee.
No, I said a nice
coffee. Nice.
(GRUNTS)
Lisa, you took out
a restraining order
against your own brother?
Yes. The clerk also gave
me this bench warrant
for Dad's arrest.
Aw, damn it.
Chief, how are we supposed
to live with our kids
constantly separated?
Hey, I don't make the laws,
I just something with them.
Look, this videotape
should answer all your
questions.
(NARRATOR READING)
Hi, I'm Gary Busey.
(LAUGHING)
I'm here to explain
about restraining orders.
The answers to all your
questions are in this video.
(NARRATOR READING)
GARY BUSEY: Meet Joe.
Last name, Spaghetti-O.
One night, Joe went to a party
and fell in love with a girl
named Mary.
(LAUGHS)
Man, I've been there.
At first, Joe
felt discouraged,
but then he remembered
what his father taught him.
"Never say die,
quitters never prosper,
and no means yes."
(SINGING IN SPANISH)
(GASPS)
Oh! (SOBBING)
The next day,
Mary got a restraining
order against Joe.
(LAUGHING MANIACALLY)
Oh! (GROANS)
Now Joe can't come
within 500 feet of Mary.
He also can't call her
or burn his name in gas
on her lawn.
I'm going to let you
in on a little secret.
Joe is me.
And Mary is a composite
of 12 different women
and a small independent
film company,
all of whom couldn't deal
with me because I'm too real.
(GROANS) I always hoped
we wouldn't be one of those
restraining order families.
How am I supposed to know
if I'm 20 feet away?
Don't worry, son.
No one's going to
make you count to 20.
I have a more humane solution.
This 20-foot pole will make
Bart's restraining order,
oh, so easy to enforce.
And I used my Sprawl Mart
employee discount to buy
this fancy pole cover.
It'll keep your pole
looking great, poke after
poke after poke.
Poke.
(YELPS)
Hey, this really works.
(YELPING)
Homer, why did you
put the screwdriver
at the end?
Show you what it's like
in the real world.
Bart, because of your
sister's restraining order,
there is no place
in this school you
can legally occupy
without violating
your order.
Observe.
A.M. kindergarten
made the Bart doll.
P.M. kindergarten
made the Lisa.
(CLATTERING)
The point is, we're not
allowed to have you
in this building.
Well, I've never been
one to break the law.
So long, Seymour.
Give me a jingle sometime.
(CHUCKLES) I Will,
but there is one place
on school property
That falls outside
all laws of man or God.
No, you don't mean...
Oh, this place smells,
and something's
dripping on me.
The smell is manure,
and the dripping's manure.
Now turn to chapter one
of Math Safari.
But we're already
on chapter seven.
(MENACINGLY)
Then you'll be
teaching Willie.
(WHIMPERS)
(DON'T STAND SO
CLOSE TO ME PLAYING)
(YELLING)
(ALL LAUGHING)
I'm afraid your arm
has sustained extensive
nerve damage.
The only cure is
this anti-poking potion.
(GRUNTS) OOPS!
Missed the vein.
(GRUNTS)
Dang, missed it again.
Sorry, I'm distracted.
My housekeeper is suing
me for sexual harassment.
She hung the mistletoe.
What was I supposed to do?
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
I like eating here
with you, Dad,
especially without,
"Don't have a cow, man."
(LAUGHING)
Yeah, he's all,
"Cowabunga, dude."
(LAUGHING) I mean,
what's that mean?
Nothing, I bet.
(SLURP S)
Oh, need more soda.
Homer, would you be
interested in the position
of executive greeter?
Woo-hoo! That's been
my dream ever since
I heard it existed right now.
What do I get?
You get to work overtime
without us paying you extra.
I won't do it.
If you don't,
we'll ship you right
back to Mexico.
But I'm a US citizen.
Uh-huh.
How sure of that are you?
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
I can't take it anymore.
Every time I try
to relax, she...
Ow! My neck.
(YELPING) Can't I even
finish my milk?
(SIGHS)
(GASPS)
Please lift this
restraining order, Judge Harm.
It's poking our family apart.
Bart, do you have
anything to say?
My sister has
no sense of humor.
I'm sure you understand.
It's why you became a judge
instead of finding a husband.
I have a husband.
What is he,
blind and deaf?
From now on, the restraining
order is set at 200 feet.
(ALL GASP)
(GASPS)
That's 61 meters.
ALL: Oh!
Sacrebleu!
Sorry, boy.
This is the only place
that's 200 feet from Lisa
but still on our property.
(MOANING) Oh!
It's pretty scary
out here, Dad.
Dad?
(DOOR CLOSES)
(LOCK CLICKS)
Well, I bet they miss me.
(PLAYING UPBEAT MUSIC)
Hmm. Well, could be worse.
MARGE: Bart,
Lisa went over to Janey's.
Quick, run inside
and go potty.
Hmm.
Why should I go inside?
The world is my toilet now.
Hey, Why'd you
lock the door?
We're still inside.
It's a chance for you
to catch up on all the
work I'm assigning you now.
I never worked
all night, never.
And I worked at
an all-night diner
for three years.
I slept on the grill.
See this?
It's the bathroom key.
(GULPS)
See you in the morning.
You monster!
(SCREAMING)
We placed a compliance chip
in the back of your neck
during the company physical.
(LAUGHING)
That's it, mister.
l am disgruntled.
And up until now,
I was relatively gruntled.
Oh, better increase the juice.
(SCREAMING)
Wait. (GRUNTING)
I did it. I pulled it out.
And with no brain damage...
(STUTTERING REPEATEDLY)
Now we'll get all your
chips out, go to the police
and shut this place down.
Homer, we took our
chips out years ago.
Really?
Then why do you
still work here?
We've learned to accept
the things we cannot change
and steal everything
that's not nailed down.
(GRUNTS)
I hope you won't
judge us harshly.
I'll be back for
tall kitchen bags.
(GLASS SHATTERING)
(LAUGHING)
(GROANS)
Lisa, don't you
think your brother's
suffered enough?
Mom, I don't mean to be mean,
but every time I think about
forgiving him,
I remember
all the bad things
he's done to me.
He's done good
things for you, too.
Name three.
Mmm. He brought home
your homework when
you were sick.
Yes, but he thought
that was a bad thing.
Let's count it anyway.
Hmm.
He did try to cheer me up
when my hamster died.
Homer, you forgot
to eat your hot dog.
Mmm.
Hotdog.
(CRACKING)
Ow!
(SOBBING) Ow! Ow!
What the...
(CRACKING)
(SOBBING) Ow! Ow!
(GIGGLING)
(CRACKING)
(SOBBING) Ow!
I just don't understand
what the problem is.
(GIGGLING)
Okay, that's two,
and that's it.
If I think of another one,
I'll let him back in.
(GROANS)
(GROWLING)
Stupid, selfish Bart.
Like he's ever going to do
another nice thing for me.
(GASPS)
LISA: He's building a me.
Well, I mean, it's a little
American-primitive,
but who am I to
dismiss outsider art?
It shows he misses me,
and this is the third thing.
(LISA PANTING)
Lise, just let me be.
Look in your heart.
I'm begging you,
look in your heart.
Bart, don't worry.
I'm relinquishing
the poke pole.
What does that mean,
you're sharpening it?
Look in your heart.
I'm begging you.
I'm not sharpening it.
Are you putting
feces on the tip?
No, I'm giving it up.
I've realized
how much I missed you,
and I can see from this
magnificent Lisa statue
that you felt the same way.
Oh, uh... Yeah.
When you're right,
you're right. Let's eat.
Yo, Bart,
we're ready to torch the
Wicker Witch of the West.
Jimbo, the real one's here.
Oh, man. This is every
effigist's worst nightmare.
Bart, you were going to burn
the third nice thing
you've ever done for me?
Well, you see,
the fire represents
your musical ability.
Oh, Bart, I missed your lies.
And I was kind
of a pill, I guess.
Lisa, you just
poked my feelings.
I'm sorry, too.
Give me that torch.
(PLAYING UPBEAT MUSIC)
(MEOWS)