CHOIR: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
MARGE: And here's a marble
for Lisa for cleaning her room,
and a marble for Bart
for not trashing Lisa's room.
The jars are full,
so you've earned
your Saturday Surprise Dad Day!
BOTH: Yay!
This Saturday, from the dad
who brought you cemetery paintball
and go-karts on real roads,
comes the greatest activity yet...
BOTH: Video game convention!
-(cameras clicking)
-(murmuring)
(crowd gasps)
(crowd cheering)
And check these out.
BOTH: VIP passes!
Is there any better feeling
than cutting in line
because a plastic badge
says you're special?
(drools)
(Bart and Lisa drool)
(all gasp)
-BART: GTS!
-HOMER: So many games.
-LISA: Ah.
-HOMER: Wow.
BART: Whoa.
(gasps) W.O.K.?!
HOMER: Ooh, the Flying Tomato.
BART: Ah! TMTOLO!
DL2L-to-D!
Oh! ACSOL! HC1?!
Whoa!
Guts of War Two:
Entrails of Intestinox!
Colon slash!
Rectum kill!
We've made a game
that'll reward the hardcore gamer
with hundreds and hundreds of hours of--
-Finished it.
-Huh?
(fanfare plays)
But working on this game
cost me my marriage.
I-I have twins I've never met!
Well, when you meet them,
tell them your game's too easy.
This game has all the best
college marching bands.
From the precision footwork
of Ohio State
to the lame,
dead-on-arrival humor of Stanford.
-(crowd cheering on game)
-("Stars and Stripes Forever" playing)
Uh-oh, I'm losing the crowd!
(grunting)
GAME ANNOUNCER:
Level cleared.
Next level: study for chemistry test
on 12-hour bus ride home.
(giggles)
This is the funnest game ever!
Man, how many quarters
does this game take?
Dad! Funtendo is unveiling
their new system in three minutes,
in Hall G!
And we're in Hall D.
Three halls, three minutes.
No problem.
-HOMER: Out of my way! Move it!
-(people screaming)
Geeks must yield to normals!
(grunts)
(panting heavily)
(cash register dings)
-(chewing)
-(ascending beeps)
-Room's full.
-HOMER: Hmm.
Aha!
(laughs)
BOTH: Yay!
(fanfare plays)
Whoo-hoo!
-(humming)
-(tires screech)
Conventions rock!
Fun Dad rocks!
I need a nap!
(Bart and Lisa laugh)
You kids have had a big day.
Head up to the tub
while I deflate your toys.
Save us, Fun Dad!
(laughter)
(Rod and Todd grunt happily)
The kids sure had
a good time with you.
Yeah, I was on today.
Scary on.
How come they never
call me Fun Mom?
Look, honey,
a family's like a team.
And on every team,
you have the slam-dunking megastar
and the referee.
It's not fair.
Moms want to be fun,
but we're stuck with all the mom stuff.
Okay, okay, how about this--
next week, you take the kids
on a Saturday Surprise Dad Day.
What if...
we roll pennies
and go to the dollar store?
That's good, Marge!
Get all the terrible ideas
out of your system.
Oh.
I've got it!
Your Saturday Surprise Mom Day
is the X-Games!
BOTH: Yay! X-Games! X-Games!
All right!
That isn't an "X," Mom.
Welcome to the Cross Games, Simpsons.
A Christian fellowship expo!
Are there at least games here?
Oh, no, "games" stands for
Gathering of American Messengers
for Evangelical Sports.
-Sports?
-(chuckles)
"Sports" stands for Strict Parental
Oversight Rather Than Sports.
(both groan)
Come on, kids,
fun comes from inside.
It isn't about what we actually do.
Yes, it is! That's all it is!
You're right, you're right, you're right.
Let's go.
Thank the Lord!
Two children to play debtors
in the Parable of the Unjust Steward.
All the other kids are at
something called the X-Games.
(Bart and Lisa groan)
I'm sorry, gang. I blew it.
(groans) I hate it
when grown-ups call kids "gang."
Don't worry about it, Mom.
Dad will take us
on a great outing next weekend.
(sighs)
(engine clanks, rattles)
Why do old squirrels
always crawl into my engine to die?
(groans)
Guess we'll be making
an unscheduled pit stop, gang.
We're not a gang!
Gangs are cool!
(tires screech)
-Uh, Mom, where are we?
-Nowhere scary.
(engine hissing)
Everything's fine.
We'll just wait here
for the tow truck.
That newborn has earrings!
-Mom, we're hungry.
-(groans)
I guess we could make a sprint
for one of these local establishments.
(Marge groaning)
They're using pancakes as spoons.
Ooh, let's see what else
they do wrong.
(groaning)
Ew! Ugh!
They're selling CDs in the restaurant!
-Back to the car!
-What can I get you?
Oh, I'll just have a side salad.
We have no side salad.
-Back to the car!
-Relax, Mom.
-Be adventurous.
-Yeah, just have fun.
Dad would.
(sighs)
What's the craziest thing on the menu?
(chuckles)
She means the most authentic.
Well, that would be
the Zelzel Minchet Aletcha Wat.
-Then I'll have that!
-(all gasp)
Okay, Marge, you test-drove
a convertible once, you can do this.
(lively Ethiopian music playing)
(taste buds gasping,
murmuring excitedly)
Holy casserole-y!
That's good gloop!
Mmm. Mmm.
I wish I lived in Ethiopia!
Exotic, vegetarian,
I can mention it in a college essay.
Mom, this is amazing!
(all chewing noisily)
Wait, wait, wait,
what is she eating?
They've never served me that dish,
and I wear indigenous
beaded headgear.
Oh, this?
It's just a little
Zelzel Minchet Aletcha Wat.
It's all I ever eat here.
(gasps)
They have prepared her a dish
-from the non-translated page!
-(gasps)
So grab a pancake
and slurp some slop!
Foodies, heed my call!
Commence ripping and dipping!
(all chewing noisily)
So, did all of your cars break down?
Mom, they're here on purpose.
They're foodies.
Indeed. Our passion is to seek out
interesting foods,
savor their exotic flavors,
then blog about them.
Yes.
We discovered Korean barbecue
in this town.
Uh, before the Koreans?
Oh, sure they cook it,
but they don't get it.
"When you stick a pancake into
a friend's mouth, it's a goorsha."
Everybody goorsha!
ALL: Goorsha!
BART and LISA: Goorsha!
Goorsha! Goorsha! Goorsha!
-Goorsha! Goorsha!
-Goorsha!
-Marge, the kids are acting ethnic!
Relax, Homie.
Have some leftover
Galalalalalalalalah.
(grunting)
Oh, no.
I don't eat anything new
unless I've eaten it before.
Aw, come on, Dad, be a foodie.
You're already a fatty and a drunkie.
I don't want to think about food,
I want to like it.
Why drive across town
to savor a bowl of mystery mush
when there's four different
Krusty Burgers
we can see from our house?
Oh, and here's my favorite restaurant--
La Fridge.
It's open 24 hours a day
and there's no dress code.
What kind of American man
doesn't want to explore
global food culture?
And then brag about it
on the Internet.
We should start our own food blog.
(gasps)
The Three Mouthketeers.
Three?
You mean, one, two... me?
(gasps, grunts)
♪ We're blogging a food blog ♪
♪ Marge and Bart and Lisa ♪
♪ As one now ♪
♪ We're having fun now ♪
♪ Throwing down mad foodie game ♪
♪ Knowing all the chefs' names ♪
♪ Rolling into K-town,
bibimbap and bulgogi ♪
♪ The hotties that I chill with
sriracha and kimchi ♪
♪ Give me house-made terrines,
my duck is always confit ♪
♪ I braise with a billion more
BTUs than I need ♪
♪ Cook Thanksgiving turkey
in a trash bag, sous-vide ♪
♪ A fumatore in Brindisi
FedEx me salami ♪
♪ Don't scoop gelato
unless it's got umami ♪
♪ I'll be frank like Bruni,
ruthless like Reichl ♪
♪ Wiley like Dufresne
when I take the mic out ♪
♪ Rhyme about radicchio ♪
♪ Criticize Colicchio ♪
♪ Every pub is gastro ♪
♪ All my beef carpaccio ♪
♪ Throw it in the pho, yo ♪
♪ And don't you call that pho pho ♪
♪ Talk about broth-squirting dumplings ♪
♪ Dumplings, dumplings, dumplings ♪
♪ We're blogging a food blog ♪
♪ Uploading pics with our Fun Mom ♪
♪ Fun Mom, Fun Mom ♪
People are loving our list
of Springfield's top 99
Afghan restaurants.
I feel bad for all those places
that didn't make the cut.
All right, food nerds, reality check.
All the food in those pictures
is poop by now.
Minds blown, you're welcome.
Oh.
I'll remind you kids what real fun is.
Hey, hey, kids! (laughs)
Krustyland has a new ride.
The Eyeballs of Death.
It only passed the safety panel
by a three-to-two vote.
And that third vote didn't come cheap.
(laughs)
And I've got tickets
for the grand opening Saturday night.
-Whoa!
-(gasps) Cool.
Uh, kids, don't forget about
our special plans Saturday night.
Oh, sorry, Dad.
Our blog is so popular,
we got an invitation
to the most exclusive restaurant in town.
Kent Brockman himself
could only get a reservation
at 5:30 or 9:30.
(giggles)
It's called El Chemistri,
and they use science
to make the food.
Behold... pine needle sorbet.
(moaning)
Pine needle... sorbet?
Pine needle sorbet?
My kids do not eat sorbet--
they eat sherbet.
And they pronounce it "sherbert,"
and they wish it was ice cream.
Sorry, Dad,
this is our thing now.
Fine, blow off Fun Dad
and go eat your walrus mustaches
and deep-fried pixie wangs.
Don't be so jealous, Homie,
just because the kids are finally
having fun doing something with me.
Aah! Jealous? Me?
(chortles)
That is to laugh.
The very idea.
If anything... (laughs)
-you're the one who's jealous.
-Of what?
Of how much fun
I am to be around!
(sobs)
It's always a party
with Fun Dad!
(sobbing)
Too sad to walk.
Too sad and fun to walk.
-What are you doing?
-When I'm sad,
I make baseball bats.
Homie,
I don't want you to feel excluded.
Would you like to come with us
to dinner at El Chemistri?
Really?
You'd let me in on your thing?
Even though I think it's stupid?
Of course.
-Hand me that saw, Marge.
-Why?
When I'm happy,
I make birdhouses.
Kids, guess what.
Mom invited me to your fancy dinner.
-Cool.
-Awesome!
I guess Fun Dad is a foodie now.
BOTH:
Food Dad! Food Dad! Food Dad!
(groans)
(groaning)
I'm food bad boy Tony Bourdain.
There's nowhere I won't go
and nothing I won't eat,
as long as I'm paid in emeralds
and my hotel room has a bidet
that shoots warm champagne.
I'm here at a Singapore
street-food market
with famous blogging family,
the Three Mouthketeers.
Marge, you've got to try
some of this hang hir kuay chap.
Ooh, triple spicy barbecued stingray
stuffed with pig organs.
Fun Dad is a foodie now!
(munching loudly)
(swallows)
This is my thing
and always will be.
(munching loudly)
Food Dad! Food Dad! Food Dad!
Everything's more fun with Homer.
(speaking faux Swedish)
But this was all I had.
BRITISH MAN:
Stop your bloody whinging, Marge.
Aah! Gordon Ramsay!
You (bleep) it up,
big blue, didn't you?
Why did you invite Homer?
He stole your bloody thunder.
You're not as (bleep) fun as him,
and you never will be.
(crying)
Darling, darling, crying's not fun.
Homer's fun.
-Now, get out of my dream.
-It's my dream.
Not anymore it's not.
Ramsay, awake.
What in the hell was that?
(gasps, sighs)
Fun me. Fun me. Fun me.
Kids, I was thinking,
was it really such a great idea
to invite your father to that dinner?
Relax.
Dad will be the life of the party.
He'll be the fourth Mouthketeer.
But there weren't four Musketeers.
Yeah-huh. Athos, Porthos,
Aramis, and d'Artagnan.
D'Artagnan wasn't a Musketeer.
He only had a letter of introduction
to the captain of the guards--
which he lost!
You know, I'm pretty excited
about this far-out dinner.
-Maybe I'll like it.
-Oh, I doubt it.
You sit at communal tables
full of hipsters.
Well, actually,
I've come around on hipsters.
Takes a lot of guts
to all wear the same hat.
And the food
will all be weird foams--
cooked with chemicals
or served in a test tube.
It's too crazy for you.
So it's weird.
Don't worry, I'll make it fun.
Yeah, you always do.
Well, here's where to meet us.
1501 W...
East Oak Street.
East Oak Street. Is that it?
Uh... yes.
Yes, East Oak Street.
That's where you should go.
See you there.
Don't you judge me.
Ah, save it for the sitter.
Welcome to El Chemistri.
Pease place these mints
in your mouth,
and when your table is ready,
they will vibrate.
Ooh.
(dog howling)
Here it is-- 1501 East Oak.
No name on the door--
very trendy.
What do you want?
Is this the chemical kitchen place
where you do the crazy cooking?
Quiet, man.
The experience begins.
Where's Dad?
Uh... I don't know.
Probably changed his mind
and stopped off for doughnuts.
(chuckles)
Before you is
a deconstructed Caesar salad--
romaine lettuce gel, egg yolk ice,
crouton foam, and anchovy air.
You eat it like this--
gel, ice, foam, air,
foam, ice, gel, foam, air.
Just like Marge said--
chemicals and test tubes.
The open kitchen is a nice touch.
I guess I'll get started
before my family gets here.
How much for a taste?
You know, just to get me going.
-50 bucks.
-Ouch.
This place is fancy.
The next course is Regret.
(delighted moans)
(moaning)
(chuckling) Hipsters.
Too cool for school.
You don't look like
the kind of guy who does this.
Well, my wife thinks
it's too crazy for me,
but I'm going to prove her wrong.
(chuckles)
I'm doing this for my family.
All right, Breaking Baddies,
drop the meth.
Pick up the meth!
(gasps)
This better be dinner theater!
And now, pork chops 100 ways.
(diners oohing)
100 pork chops!
I can't believe Dad is missing this.
Sure, your dad's great,
but I'm fun, too.
Look at me eat, huh?
(munching loudly)
D'oh. D'oh. D'oh.
Who am I kidding?
I'm not enjoying this.
Even the foam tastes like nothing.
(sighs)
I'm calling Homer.
(cell phone chimes)
HOMER (on phone):
Marge! This isn't a food restaurant!
-It's a meth restaurant!
-(gunshots)
A meth-taurant! Aah!
(gasps)
Foodies, help me!
My husband's in danger!
-Oh, we can't leave now.
-We haven't had the root vegetables
cooked in the perfect vacuum
of outer space.
They say you can't even
understand parsnips
until you had zero-g parsnips.
(groans)
How dare you walk out on me!
Your dessert is in this doggie bag
woven from the silk of
a blueberry-fed spider.
Take it and go!
-(sirens whooping)
-(police radio chatter)
Ah, shucks.
We get the family dressed up
to go to our favorite meth lab,
and it's all raided out.
-(children groan)
-Oh, honey,
I always liked
your home-cooked better anyways.
Aw.
Uh, where do you think
you're going?
A wife needs to tell her husband
she was wrong.
And in you go.
(whimpering)
Sorry.
Everything you've done here
has created problems.
(grunts)
(gasps)
I've got to save him.
Ooh. My dessert.
Eat deconstructed apple pie!
(grunts)
(swallows)
(sighs)
Merci, Maman,
pour la tarte tatin à la mode.
(sighs)
Oh, Marge,
you saved me
from the danger you put me in.
I am so happy and angry.
I'm sorry.
I guess I just wanted
the kids to look at me
-the way they look at you.
-Aw.
Wow, Mom!
That was awesome.
We ate mad-scientist food
and broke up a meth lab
in the same day.
Fun Mom! Fun Mom! Fun Mom!
Now, that's my kind of foam.
This is nice.
A family fun day.
Here's 50 bucks.
For the next two hours,
I don't want to know you exist.
(laughing)
Family fun day.
(lively Ethiopian music playing)
♪ We're bloggin' a food blog ♪
♪ Settin' up accounts for our users ♪
♪ Usin' computers ♪
♪ Post tweets every day ♪
♪ Yo, yo, tweets every day, y'all ♪
♪ Never give it four stars ♪
♪ Ain't never give it four stars ♪
♪ Maybe two, maybe three ♪
♪ Moderatin' the comments ♪
♪ Checkin' the page views,
page views, page views ♪
♪ Duck fat ♪
♪ Truffle oil, yo, yo, yo ♪
♪ My food is art, my food is art ♪
♪ It comes right from the heart ♪
-(crowd murmuring)
-Shh!
Subtitled by A. Vandelay