-CHOIR: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
-Take that, kite-eating tree.
(exclaiming)
(school bell ringing)
Morning!
-(whistle blows)
-(yells)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
(tires screeching)
-(horn honking)
-(exclaiming)
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
(groans)
(jaunty melody playing)
(horn ooh-gahs)
(upbeat orchestral melody playing)
♪ ♪
(sighing, groaning)
(laughing)
HOMER:
♪ Go to sleep ♪
♪ Little Marge ♪
♪ Close your eyes ♪
♪ Start to yawn ♪
♪ You will wake up
with the dawn ♪
(sucking)
♪ Dawn... ♪
Large fries.
Yes, sir.
♪ Dawn... ♪
(sucking)
MARGE (loudly):
Did you get the baby to sleep?
-(sucking)
-D'oh!
Oh, no.
Oh, I can't read that again.
I hate to see
a wolf get punished
for having normal appetites.
I'll tell you a story
that'll put you to sleep.
It's one your mother told me.
Luann Van Houten
uses flavored Crisco
instead of butter
for shortbread cookies.
(yawning)
Which is, apparently, flakier,
but at what cost?
(yawning)
And she... (muttering)
(snoring)
(Homer muttering)
HOMER: Wh...? Huh?
What the... ?
Okay, sweetie, I got a story
about another little girl
who got lost in the woods,
but it wasn't a girl,
and it wasn't the woods.
(sucking)
Suck, suck, indeed.
And it all happened
once upon a time,
before you were born,
and my chances for a man cave
went out the window.
(sucking)
Bless you all for sacrificing
your Saturday afternoon
to help us clean up skid row.
When God came for Sunday,
I said nothing.
Now he comes for Saturday.
Homer Simpson, it's one thing
to moan and groan on the bus,
but in front of these unfortunates,
well, (scoffs)
that just curls my 'stache.
Hey, Flanders,
why don't you take some advice
from your Bible and zip it?
Oh, where does the Bible
say "zip it"?
It's the first thing
the burning bush said to Moses.
Thank you for teaching us Scripture.
Thank you.
You know, all this helping others
is giving me
the most satisfying feeling ever.
So satisfying.
Uh, Lenny...
Oh, huh.
I get why they do it.
Totally get it.
(whimpers)
Hey, Carl, you want to buy
all my stuff for five dollars?
(dog howling in distance)
Well, thank you all for spending the day
thinking of others
instead of yourselves.
Saturday.
It was a Saturday.
Now, a reward
to the most selfless cleaner:
a family vacation
to the Grand Canyon.
The winner: Ned Flanders.
Surprise, surprise.
The guy that did the best job wins.
NED: Mm-hmm!
But this gift certificate
is for two families.
Hey, Reverend, we'd love it
if you and Helen would join us.
Um... uh... uh...
Mm...
Of course we'd love to join you,
but I've noticed that you and Homer
haven't been
the friendliest "neighboreenos,"
if you get my diddly.
Uh, well, Ned, I think
the Lord would want you
to take the Simpsons
on this trip.
Our Lord?
Yes. Our Lord.
For would it not
indeed be glorious,
if in visiting a natural chasm,
two quarrelsome neighbors
would bridge the chasm
of their own discord.
Well, I guess if Job
could accept his burdens.
Um, in America,
it's pronounced "job," Flanders.
(laughing) We can settle it
when we're zipped up
together in a sleeping bag.
(groans)
Welcome aboard.
Oh, oh, we'd love to go,
but is it such a good idea
to travel with another family?
It's fun.
We travel with the Hibberts all the time.
We ran into you once,
in Cincinnati.
And we had dinner.
We slid our tables together.
We were in a booth
we could not get out of.
(groaning sadly)
Homie, we should go.
You and Ned
need to learn to get along.
You said the same thing
about me and Bart.
No. The judge said the same
thing about you and Bart.
Judges.
If they were any good, they'd be lawyers.
Okay, we'll go.
But if Flanders gets so annoying
that I can't take it anymore,
the code word is "octopus."
Can it be something else?
I don't like things
with hidden beaks.
Octopus or nothing.
Okay.
So we took eight-year-old Bart,
and six-year-old Lisa.
After ten hours of driving,
I finally saw
the most glorious site.
(engine revs, tires screech)
(groaning)
HOMER:
Ah... ah... ah...
Ah... ah...
Ahhh...
(growls)
Ah, ah, ah...
Ah... oh... oh, oh, yeah.
Ah... ah... yeah.
(hums)
(loud swallowing)
(whimpering)
Ah.
MARGE:
Oh.
It's like Disneyland for thin people.
Did you know that the Grand Canyon
was created by erosion?
And before 1871,
it was called Big Canyon?
Okay, that's it.
We're on vacation.
-(crying)
-Why, you little...
(rattling)
(both grunting)
(both laughing)
Whoa.
Keep 'em coming, boy.
Oh, ooh.
That one stung me.
(laughing)
Ow.
That's enough.
HOMER AND BART:
Aw.
We're here to enjoy ourselves.
If you just turn your head slightly,
I think you'll be
pleasantly surprised.
-No time.
-Homer.
(Grofé's "Sunrise" from
The Grand Canyon Suite playing)
HOMER:
Wow. Wow.
And they say we're running out of room
for our garbage.
(shudders)
NED:
♪ Go tell it on the mountain ♪
♪ Over the hills and everywhere ♪
♪ That Jesus Christ is born ♪
♪ Born, born, born, born ♪
♪ Go tell it on the mountain ♪
Octopus. Octopus.
Oct-ar-pus.
A vacation with Flanders?
That's like telling you
a bedtime story without a beer.
(sighs)
Now, where were we?
-Thank you, ma'am.
-Eh.
-Thank you.
Mm-hmm.
Am I such a terrible mother
that my son doesn't even know
to say thank you to a waitress?
Come on, honey.
What do you say?
You want me to lie and say
I'm thankful for chicken and veg
when I wanted whiskey-battered
bourbon bangers?
Just say thank you.
My boy never said thank you.
Now he's on death row.
(electricity crackles)
Was on death row.
(faint snoring)
(snoring)
Daddy, when will the noise stop?
Hmm. Take these.
Ugh. Those were earplugs.
(boys groan)
♪ ♪
Wow, I never thought there'd be something
I'd want to stare at longer
than that car wreck on the way here.
We've got to hurry before
they run out of mules.
Ooh. Is that what they're
serving for breakfast?
(Marge groans)
HOMER:
How about donkeys?
MARGE:
No.
Huh? That's odd.
Enjoying your moon view, Homer?
Why you little...
Two can play at that game.
(squeaking)
(groaning)
-(Bart laughing)
-Stupid kid.
So embarrassing.
I'm a little nervous
with all these waivers
we have to sign.
Marge, this is a national park.
People are completely safe here.
Now let's do my favorite thing:
go downhill.
Whoa. You're 180?
My blood pressure is.
Okay.
Uh, let's get you a mule, dude.
Oh...
(loud braying)
Get me El Gordo.
Gordo here used to carry
200-pound granite blocks
up from the canyon.
(Gordo groaning)
(Grofé's "On the Trail" from
The Grand Canyon Suite playing)
This has got to be
the most beautiful thing
we've ever stole from the Indians.
(engines roaring)
What is that?
A billionaires' retreat.
Yeah, the heads of America's
most powerful media companies
have come to enjoy nature.
DRIVER:
Put up the cell phone tower.
MAN:
I said I wanted a Tom Cruise type,
not Tom Cruise.
DRIVER:
Burn down the cell phone tower.
I can't stand rich people.
Can I name my mule?
We prefer you don't.
Is there a name for this trail?
I'm sure there is.
Is this a fun job?
Not at the moment.
Do you count as a grownup?
My parents don't think so.
You're a grownup to me.
Thanks.
Here, have a piece of the canyon.
Are you sure it's okay?
Hey, it only makes the canyon grander.
BOTH:
Aah! Aah!
Aah!
I don't know where
your son gets it, Marge.
I'm only going to say this once,
but I think you're
a little checked out.
(echoing)
Checked out. Checked out.
Checked out.
Well, your kids aren't exactly perfect.
Yay! We can improve.
Let's think about it quietly.
(groans)
(sniffing)
Boy, I bet that mustache
smells really bad, huh?
Oh, don't you rip on my lip strip.
(sniffs)
I smell candles
and-and pew polish.
We're near a church.
(sniffs)
Catholic, if I don't miss my guess.
(organ playing)
Hmm.
A little Popeish for my taste,
but I did come here for adventure.
Geez, Flanders,
you find God in everything.
God is in everything.
He's omnipresent.
You mean, if I check
into the Omni Hotel right now,
he's there?
As a matter of fact, he is.
Then, from now on, we're staying
at the Hyatt Regency.
You're banned there, Dad.
Not as Hagwar Swanson.
(with Scandinavian accent)
I love this country.
(shudders)
Are you sure this is safe?
Totally. You're with State Farm, right?
Where's our guide?
Where's the trail?
(squawking)
(humming)
Aw.
(shrieks)
Big Maggie.
I'd like to hear the rest.
I still have my piece
of the canyon.
Ugh.
(growls)
Okay. It was looking rough...
Oh, no bars.
You mean, on your phone?
Hey, you're right.
Oh, more bad news.
Oh, most of the food
was on the guide's mule.
I sure am glad somebody
packed all this whitefish salad.
I'm willing to eat some.
And if I die, you know it's bad.
Homer, it's time for you and me
to go out and get help.
Please be careful,
Uncle Ned.
I will, Bart.
Please, please be careful.
Don't worry.
If you don't come back,
I'll be so sad.
Excuse me?
What about over here?
Right.
(grunts)
Please, please be careful.
(braying)
Please.
Let's go, Flanders.
(groans)
(whining)
Oh, no. The poor thing
gets night terrors.
I forgot to say,
"God bless the mailman."
He's not awake,
but he's not asleep.
Do your kids get these?
I will now that I know
what they are.
Other kids say
I'm in their nightmares.
I'm not your puppet, Bart.
I'm not.
(grunting)
You ever seen stars this bright,
Homer?
Blessed is the beauty of our Lord.
♪ ♪
(sighs)
(gunshots)
(clicking)
Amen. Listen, Flanders.
This trip has given me
time to think.
If I die here,
you're welcome to live
in my carcass for warmth.
I'm not living in your carcass.
Oh, come on.
You make it sound
like a bad thing.
Look, we're saved!
We just go down there,
get some food and help
returning to civilization.
GUARD (over megaphone):
Attention, people talking.
Unless you are here
to dispose of our poop,
we will start shooting
in five minutes.
(dance music playing)
(animals screeching)
How is that even camping?
'Tis easier for a camel
to pass through
the eye of a needle
than a rich man
to get into heaven.
(sighs)
Sometimes I just don't get it.
What I'm saying is,
the eye of the needle
is very small, and a camel...
No. I mean down there.
They have everything
we need to survive,
but they won't share.
Maybe if I look through
these binoculars one more time,
I'll-I'll see something better.
(gasps)
We've got to go in
and steal what we need.
Well, thou shalt not steal.
But if I don't steal, that's coveting.
That's bad, too.
Look, Flanders,
we tried things your way,
and it failed.
Now let's try mine.
Okay.
W-Wait!
We never did things my way.
Too late. (voice fading)
I'm already rolling downhill.
Ow, sharp rock.
Ooh, cactus!
(screams)
More scorpions.
Is that all you can do? Sting?
(yells)
Now they're pinching.
(whispering)
Easy, Flanders, don't make a sound.
-Okay, here.
-(Ned grunting)
Come on, take this.
(both grunting)
Oh, I got it.
Oh, it's heavy.
(brays)
(whispers)
Ready to go.
(gunshots)
Uh, we're too heavy.
Toss off what we don't need.
(grunting)
(gunshot)
Fine.
We can do without salad forks.
Whoo-hoo!
♪ No sugar tonight for the coffee ♪
♪ No sugar tonight for their tea ♪
♪ We took all their fancy cheeses ♪
♪ And their tasty charcuterie ♪
(growls)
Trout solo!
♪ Ba-da-ta-da-da-da-da-da-da ♪
♪ Ba-da-ta-da-da-da ♪
♪ Da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da ♪
♪ Da-da-da-da
da-da-da ♪
(together)
♪ Ba-da-da-da-da-da-da-da ♪
-♪ Ba-da-da-da-da-da ♪
-♪ Ba-da-dee-doo-da-da ♪
Grand Canyon! Yeah!
(air whooshing)
You know, Homer,
we make a good team.
Homer?
HOMER:
Breakfast time.
Come and get it!
(echoing)
Come and...
Ugh. Not again.
Tablecloths.
Caviar.
Bacon!
(munching)
Bacon.
No, this was before
Lisa was a vegetarian.
That's right.
I had the arteries of a 20-year-old.
I'm gonna miss you, pal.
(neighs)
(chuckles)
Well, Homer,
you think this
will be one of those vacations
where the friendship we made
will last forever,
or start eroding the minute
we enter our cars?
Flanders, like all friendships
between men,
in the end,
it's up to our wives.
Mm-hmm.
NED:
That was a nice story, Homer.
You know,
sometimes I wish this
(chuckles)
grand canyon between us,
uh, wasn't so large.
The offer still stands.
You can live in my carcass.
There's room in my legs
for the boys.
Maybe we could just
store old clothes in you.
I'd like that.
And you know what, Flanders?
I think we owe you guys a trip.
♪ ♪
Always wanted to visit
the postcard museum.
Thank you.
My pleasure.
I wonder if they sell postcards
in the gift shop.
We don't.
(Grofé's Grand Canyon Suite playing)
Shh!
Subtitled by B. Everdene