Hey there, chief.
Look, your mailbox
hasn't been emptied in weeks.
Oh, no, not the mail.
What if I'm missing out
on coupon packs,
or perhaps a jury summons?
How will I live
without my paper e-mails?
I get it.
But be a pal, pally.
Empty it out.
It has been baking
in the sun for a while.
I think it's done.
Mail loaf!
Carve that mail.
Carve it good.
Who wants an end piece?
I'm invited to a birthday party
at Addy's.
Addy?
I don't know that friend.
What subject does she teach?
It's a kid! I know kids.
It's a sleepover
at Addy's house.
Addy.
I met her at the library.
Library, Marge.
We were the only ones
who loved this old series
of books, Gallop Girls.
Old book smell.
New friend smell.
What is the deal
with girls and horses?
Is it 'cause boys took
all the good animals,
like dogs and ninjas?
Horses are nature's triumph.
They have the perfect
combination of power,
grace and braidable hair.
Dumb, dumb, stupid.
Legs don't move.
Pink?!
Once cars were invented,
why didn't they just
kill all the horses...
with the cars?
Beat it, Summer School.
Horse-a-copter attack.
Its plops are bombs.
Let her go. She's a rescue
and uneasy around men.
My paddock!
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
No horseplay.
Horseplay!
Marge, guess what I said.
Fight on.
Why? Why do you always wreck
the stuff I care about?
Big brothers are supposed
to be helpful and a little nice.
I wish I could un-brother you.
Not if I un-sister you first.
Fine. By the power
of safety scissors,
I hereby sever the sibling bond.
Snip.
Look at that house.
I bet they use
their garage for cars.
Horsey birthday!
Your house is huge.
Yeah, it's kind of embarrassing.
My dad's the exclusive
ketchup distributor
for stadiums and megachurches.
She's obviously lying.
Ketchup is free.
Play along.
Hi, I'm Marge.
Lisa's really been
looking forward
to your daughter's party.
Oh, no, I'm the party planner.
The mother's
on a photoshopping retreat
to get her son into USC.
Have fun.
We'll see you tomorrow.
10:00 a.m. pickup.
Goodbyes and gift bags.
They're so rich,
they know the future.
Well, I just finished
the Gallop Girls book
where George Washington's horse
exposed Benedict Arnold's horse
as a traitor.
I kind of wanted it
to be a surprise.
We kind of own horses.
You know, Lisa has a sleepover,
Grampa's with the other ones,
and we are near the marina.
I'm not looking
for your lost sunglasses.
It's been six years.
They're gone.
You are always saying how
I never make plans for us.
Well, how about a sunset cruise?
I only ever read about those
in Sunset Cruise magazine.
There's even live music.
This is the band that was gonna
play Lenny's wedding reception
if he didn't get
pepper-sprayed at the altar.
I forgot how handsome you are
when you make
the slightest effort.
Don't worry.
If you get thrown, your vest
will automatically inflate
so it breaks your fall.
Now use the reins.
Sunflower wants you to lead her.
What's the matter, Addison?
You didn't like my post.
Is your thumb broken?
Thumb broken?
Tessa Rose, you are brills.
Completely brills.
Literally, that was
the funniest thing ever.
I can't stop laughing.
Addison, why is she
staring at us?
Addison?
Is that what you like
to be called?
This is my crew.
You probably know them all
from social.
This is Bella-Ella.
She's from old money.
Myspace.
Sloan. British.
And, of course,
beauty icon Tessa Rose.
Don't you just hate her?
Oh, right, guys,
this is Lisa.
She's... her.
Nice to meet you guys.
You need to calm down.
I am calm.
Stop yelling.
I'm not yelling.
Look, matchy-matchy...
I don't need drama
from someone whose shirt
is a spoiler for her pants.
You're hilarious.
I will never stop laughing.
Your friends seem
different than you.
That one keeps saying
things are funny,
but she's not laughing.
Oh, she can't.
Her mom got too much Botox
when she was pregnant.
Ugh, so lucky.
I know they seem cliquey
and stuck-up and...
- Awful?
- Yeah.
But once they accept you,
you'll see that, deep down,
they're... nice.
Oh, good, good.
So they're not mean.
Oh, I almost judged them.
That was close.
These will totally hide
my kombucha hangovers.
I got them in the city.
The city is New York.
New York City?
I'll make a note, in a book.
A notebook.
A phone case.
It's for the new MyPhone.
There's no buttons,
and the camera only faces you.
It's literally unusable.
What about my gift?
Look, it's got a little
straw hat
that fits right over his ears.
She got her a toy.
Does it come with a nappy?
Oh, my God,
I'm laughing so hard,
I can't even breathe.
Does it dispense bronzer?
Bronzer remover?
What does it dispense?
How is it makeup?
But you like it,
don't you, Addy?
Oh, it's adorable.
For a widdle baby.
You're breaking up, honey.
How's the party?
It's not fun.
I don't want to stay.
I want to go home.
It's fun.
I don't want to
go home.
Thanks for the uneventful
update.
How's Lisa?
Having fun and not wanting
to go home.
Sounds like fun.
You're right.
Daddy understands completely.
That's what daddies do.
I'm trapped. All night.
With them.
What do you mean the
Taylor Swift lookalike canceled?
Now who are the girls gonna
throw cupcakes at?
Finally.
You're the only adult here.
I want to go home.
Can you help me?
Oh, no, this sleepover
has got to get
100% engagement.
I can't go back to working
at Bubba Gump Shrimp.
It's not shrimp.
Hey, lady bosses,
who wants to visit
the perfume lab
and start your own fempire?
What are you wearing,
Desperation by Thirsty Grandma?
I'm 26.
Let's binge the new season
of Thank God I'm Dead.
T.G. I'm D.
is literally massive.
Leandra's funeral is so
on my vision board.
I'm not allowed
to watch that show
'cause it glamorizes
inappropriateness.
It'll be okay.
Just close your eyes.
We get it, warnings,
this show is awesome.
Now that she's gone,
she's finally popular.
I'm gonna ask her ghost
to the prom.
Someone's about to go viral.
Baby videos are super popular.
I think I could stay here
for the rest of my life
Please don't ever
make me go home
What are you doing in here?
This is the caterers' bathroom.
This Japanese toilet
is the first kind voice
I've heard all night.
Addy, why did you invite me to
this party? Just to torture me?
Okay.
Full disclosure, I invited you
because those other girls
are always so mean to me.
But then they were mean to you
instead and let me join in.
Oh, thanks for making this
the best birthday ever.
Wait, no aw. That's horrible.
No, don't you see?
Next time, you bring a Lisa.
Someone from band camp
or science club or whatever,
and then we'll all turn on her
and you'll be part of the squad.
No, no. No, this can't
be who you really are.
Let me whiten your teeth, Lisa.
I've got strips.
Strips, Lisa! Lisa, come back!
I've got whitening strips!
And it's the Old-Man-apolis 500,
but he spun out
into Dead Man's Crack.
Grampa, it's Lisa.
- I need your help.
- What's the matter, loser?
Did a horse bite your head off,
and now you're crying
because you don't have a head?
Called it.
The girls at this party
are so mean,
there's no one else to help me,
and I just want to go home.
Oh, I would love to help,
but you un-brothered me.
Now all I am is a stranger
who magnetized your saxophone.
Please, somewhere inside you
there is an ember of connection
between us.
This is me asking you
to fan that ember.
Call me back and say it
in a normal way.
Get me out of here!
Look, the rando's talking
into a phone.
Phones are for
looking at, rando.
Bart, they're taking my phone.
They're even meaner than you.
Are you Juan Starnotip?
Just drive.
So, Juan, going somewhere
this evening?
The entered address.
I like you, Juan. You're clearly
comfortable in your own skin.
Can I interest you
in a room-temperature
sparkling water?
I requested no conversation.
Hey!
Give it back!
Ew, this phone
is made by Subway.
My dad had to eat
a thousand footlongs for that!
Hey.
Quit hitting on my wife,
you crooning sex pirate.
Whoa, that chick behind that
blue-haired lady's your wife?
Way to go, man.
Oh, right.
I'll just get out of your way.
This is for not
hitting on my wife.
The set list!
Our banter was on there.
What songs do we know?
Without the booze,
it's just a cruise!
Dude, you killed the music.
And the vibe.
Time of death, 10:13 p.m.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Now let's get out of here
before they realize I'm gone.
This sleepover isn't over.
No, yes, it is.
When we leave, it's over.
Look, I didn't come here
to rescue you.
If you run now,
you'll never stop running.
What do you mean?
There's one present you still
have to give those rich girls.
- Revenge.
- Revenge?
Revenge.
Okay, right. Revenge.
Right. I can do that.
- What do I do?
- I can't tell you.
True revenge can only come
from the hate in your own heart.
Hate.
If you do it tight enough,
it's just like a face-lift.
Oh, my God.
I could pass for six.
I know just what to do.
Hi, Mom.
I saw you called a bunch
of times. Is everything okay?
Yeah, everything is great.
I love you, good night.
At least she's having fun.
Your Mos Eisley fracas
has utterly harshed
my Arrakeen spice buzz.
That's right,
a two-reference complaint!
My wife and I have been looking
forward to this for months,
and you ruined our plans.
Plans? Yeah, we all
love to make plans, don't we?
Dinner and a movie,
couples' karaoke, game night
where the hosts are really just
trying to sell Amway.
We're all so eager
to get out of the house.
But why?
To stand in line
to have your picture taken
holding a mustache on a stick?
And all these magical plans are
supposed to lead up to romance.
But when you get home,
you feel tired and gross
and a thousand years old.
So you make plans
for another night and another,
and the cycle continues
until the only time
you touch your wife
is when you don't notice
she's on the toilet at 4:00 a.m.
and you sit on her.
I didn't ruin this cruise.
I saved your life.
Now return to your homes
and never make plans again.
That egghead rando
messed with our hair.
We look like her!
Don't worry.
I have a car waiting.
An airport pickup
during surge pricing?
So long, dot matrix printer,
hello, bubble jet.
This way.
You go ahead.
You don't hate horses.
You're afraid of them.
No, I'm not. I just hate
any animal that works with cops.
No creature
should be that jacked.
You didn't let me quit
when I was scared,
so I'm gonna help you see
that this majestic creature
has a gentle soul.
Not behind her!
She'll kick your face off!
We're gonna destroy you
on Insta, TikTok and Postmates.
You'll be a total outcast
and you'll have
to pick up your own sushi.
Ugh, no Wi-Fi?
Does your horse even have
a mobile hot spot, Addison?
Addison, can I talk to Addy,
my book buddy?
I have to be Addison.
Addy's just a little girl.
Don't you remember
when we were reading this?
We were just kids,
sharing something we loved.
Addison, she's trying
to influence you,
and she's not even
monetizing it.
I'm so going to swat her house
on Christmas morning.
Don't let that rando upset you.
Have a Klonopin gummy.
Be the girl I know you are.
Old book smell.
Stop holding a book, Addison.
You're acting like a rando.
My name is Addy.
Oh, my...
Go!
Come with us. There's nothing
left for you here.
It's my house.
All my stuff is in it.
Oh, right, right.
Well, all right.
Maybe I'll see you
at the library.
Lisa?
You were my best gift.
Addison, are you
out of your mind?
Netflix should make a series
about your social life,
because it just
committed suicide.
She is so mean.
I want to be her friend.
Literally.