GROUNDSKEEPER WILLIE:
I can't see!
-CHOIR: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
-(engine sputters)
(theme music playing)
(exclaims)
(school bell ringing)
(belches)
-(whistle blows)
-(yells)
(beeps)
♪ ♪
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-(tires screech)
-(grunts)
(sad music playing)
♪ ♪
(dramatic music playing)
(gunfire)
(groans, gasps)
(whimpers)
(chuckles)
Hmm?
(sad music playing)
(gasps)
(theme music playing)
Uh... (clears throat)
-Sir?
-Yes?
Uh, well, tomorrow is Valentine's Day.
Ah, yes, the day
of the great Chicago massacre.
Uh, and our employees have requested
to leave early
to be with their loved ones.
Of course, uh, I'll be with you.
(coughs)
Ooh, Smithers. More face hardener.
-(skin squeaks)
-Never!
Well, if you want to tamp down
a potential rebellion,
might I suggest a party after work.
A sweethearts dance, if you will.
Sweet... hearts?
Mmm... tasty.
-Excellent.
-(hearts beating)
Oh, I don't want candy.
It's not candy. It's baby hearts.
MR. BURNS: Ah...
A sweet hearts dance it is.
(arrows whooshing)
(gunshot)
Hey, Brandine!
You know how to Shake 'N Bake cherub?
Cletus, you know I can fry up
whatever you can shoot down.
Oh, Brandine,
of all the cousins I coulda married,
you was my sister. (chuckles)
(bird caws)
(dance music plays)
Carl, this is Mandy.
Mandy, isn't Carl
everything I said he was?
Okay, Lenny,
time to stop talking about Carl.
Why don't you to ask me
to stop breathing?
Oh, Marge, it's so great to combine
the two loves of my life--
goofing off and you.
Hey, listen, there's one fantasy
I've always wanted to indulge in.
If you're willing.
(moaning, kissing)
(Marge gasps)
What are those frisky hounds up to now?
(shrieks)
(yells, grunts)
Wait a minute.
That contractor said
this was a bottomless pit!
I'll have his license!
Hey, Professor!
I didn't know you worked
here at the plant.
I consult.
Sometimes they listen, sometimes not.
People have died.
You didn't hear that from me.
So, who are you here with?
Well, no one as yet.
But I haven't turned on
the old Frink charm.
Hello there, voy-vy.
Well, there's, uh,
no mistaking that message.
(bird caws)
-(cell phone ringing)
-GRAMPA (on phone): Hello, Homer!
D'oh! What is it, Dad?
It's Valentine's Day. I'm alone.
And that cat who can smell
if you're dying is staring at me.
-What are you looking at?!
-(meows)
(whispers) Son, I'm scared.
This cat has taken five this year.
People in their 90s
don't just suddenly die for no reason.
Please come.
Okay, Dad. We'll come over.
Can you pick me up a pack of diapers?
Oh, for--
They always think they're for me.
Fine. I'll just take
a large drum of butt ointment.
-(meows)
-Hurry!
-(screeches)
-Uh-oh.
Happy Valentine's Day, everybody.
I don't see why, unless you found
that missing puzzle piece.
How 'bout I put on some music?
♪ I... never... ♪
♪ Smiled again... ♪
Oh, I used to dance
with my Auggie to that tune.
Yeah, me and my Bubbeleh
made love to that song.
Creating a kid who never visits.
ANNOUNCER: And now back
to Prairie Home Companion.
-(screaming)
-MAN: Pull the plug!
No, on me.
Okay, time for some Valentine's candy
for our swinging seniors.
Don't patronize us. We know it's pills.
But it's a new brand
and they're oh so pretty-- look, green.
Like M&M'S with hope.
Oh, it's starting to kick in.
Much... better.
Suddenly, I don't want to kvetch.
I want to kvell!
I can feel all the tension
going out of my beard.
-Oh...
-(relaxed moans)
Oh...
♪ ♪
(barking)
Mona? I thought you were gone.
Nonsense, Abe.
I didn't leave you
and I'm never going to leave you.
That doesn't sound like the Mona I knew.
I'm the Mona that lives in your memory,
with all the anger
turned to honey by nostalgia.
So what you're saying
is this is really happening.
(laughs)
(big band music playing)
(no music playing)
Do you think it's okay
to leave them here?
Marge, all we ever do is leave them here.
(scoffs) I just think
there's more we should do.
We could visit your mother.
No. No, you're right. Let's go home.
HOMER: Check it out, guys.
CVS stands for Cheap Valentines' Surplus.
You get a box! You get a box!
Haven't forgotten about you,
suspicious Iranian coworker.
(Iranian accent)
Please, call me Dennis.
(Frink groaning)
Oh, my gurvy is muh.
-Oi...
-Professor?
Professor, come on, this is a workplace.
Ooh, dregs!
Oh, wow.
Oh, my egg head is pickled, muh-oyvic.
Did you sleep here all night?
Yes, you are right, I did.
Valentine's Day, you see,
is quite difficult for me.
I saw that Stephen Hawking movie
and all I could think is,
"He's got a girl?"
Give me a frickin' break.
-Two girls.
-Oh, I'll never win,
and I'll always have to only be looking.
Listen, pal, I've had plenty
of experience with one woman.
And I can tell you,
relationships are just trial and error.
Like anniversaries.
First I tried "don't remember,"
then "remember too late,"
then I happily settled on
"make Lisa remember."
And my relationship with Lisa
has never been better.
Yes, you say trial and error, eh?
My good man, that is nothing
more than the scientific method.
(bell dings)
Well, now, that's a little wasteful.
-(bell dings)
-Ah, much better.
I shall use science to uncover
the secret to women.
Homer, scientific research
can solve anything
except for cold fusion, quasars,
the interior of black holes
and what preceded the big bang.
But everything else can be solved,
including love.
Pish-posh, Professor.
What makes a guy and a girl click
isn't science.
It's chemistry!
-Which is science.
-What?!
(dog howls)
See, I have asked an enormous
cross-section of women
one single question--
what attracts you to a man?
Let us listen and learn
and have some lemonade,
which I just squeezed nicely.
(overlapping voices)
...the most important
thing that I look for...
I like it when they're tall.
-Blue eyes!
-Definitely wants kids.
Hmm, I didn't hear the last one.
First I'll replace
these Coke bottle glasses
with invisible blue contacts.
Mm-hmm.
Next, of course, is shoe lifts for height.
Make you much taller,
look down upon people.
It's wonderful. Whoa, whoa...
Hey, look at me.
I'm Herman Munster! (laughs)
Actually, he had Lily,
who was quite a dish.
So, do you, uh, find me attractive?
-Sorry, but no.
-Oh, curse the luck!
And this is an android that I programmed
to say nothing but "yes."
(electronic whooshing)
Why? Why? Why?
What am I over-look-ing?
Uh, Professor, don't be offended.
Do you think it might be your voice?
Why, what's wrong with my voice,
with the up and down
and the extra words
and the terminal nonsense
in the hoyven clyven wayen.
Oh, my God, it's the voice.
Duh.
MARGE: Hello.
We're here to see Abe Simpson.
-I brought him a homemade card!
-I brought me. That's enough.
-Oh... what the...
-(woman humming)
Gee, I thought
they'd be over this by now.
(humming)
Wow, they are really out of it.
There must be some way
to take advantage of them.
You're telling me!
Eh.
This little device,
which fits under the tongue,
will change everything.
(deep, sexy voice)
This voice is an amalgam of great voices
(like Clark Gable)
from Clark Gable...
(like Walter Cronkite)
to Walter Cronkite...
(like Rush Limbaugh)
to Rush Limbaugh!
(deep, sexy voice)
I don't agree with his politics,
but his body is a natural echo chamber.
Wow. That does change everything.
You turned me on.
Oh, it's time
for a little field test, I see.
Any other advice, Homer?
Yep-- hang out at yoga classes.
That's where the ladies are.
(normal voice)
How would you know about yoga class?
Uh, I thought it was yogurt class.
21! Dealer wins again.
Now, here's our headliner, Dolly Parton.
(banjo playing)
Oh, she's good.
-Bart!
-Ay, caramba!
You're taking advantage of these people
who don't know where they are.
I'm taking them back where they belong.
Oh, no, you don't.
He just comped me a suite!
-Fantastic!
-(clattering, thud)
-(meows)
-(gasps)
You can't keep pumping powerful drugs
into people who can't
even bite into a peach.
Mrs. Simpson, it's a fact.
If these seniors aren't medicated,
I can't binge-watch Boardwalk Empire.
Nucky dies at the end!
Yeah, well, screw you.
I'm going to report you to the state.
-I really don't care.
-(groans)
Wha... You broke me.
I'm going to say something
I've never said.
How can I help you?
Um, I'll wait outside
'cause they might make me do something.
I've changed my height,
I've changed my eyes,
my relationship status--
I-I don't know why
I put "unavailable" there.
That certainly did not help matters.
But now it is time to change my voice...
(clears throat) Oyce... Voy...
(deep, sexy voice)
And the hoyvin and the flayvin
are now "hasta la vista, Frinky."
-Ooh.
-(hums)
Mm...
(chuckles softly)
(scoffs) I'm always next to the jerk
who comes here to meet women.
Hey, look, I get you.
You broke up with a long-time
high school boyfriend
'cause he just wasn't going anywhere.
Then you play the field,
but it's all losers
who just want to take from you.
Now you're just hoping beyond hope
for a man you can hug
who'll organize the wires behind your TV.
And believe you me, sweetheart,
I can organize every wire you have.
Now I'd like to show you a picture
of my new puppy.
Yeah, his name's... (sneezes)
(normal voice) Logarithm.
(clears throat)
(deep, sexy voice) I mean Larry.
Aw... Here's my number.
And to prove it's not a lie...
(cell phone ringing)
-Yeah, baby.
-(both giggling)
Call me!
Man, you're reading page three,
and the next thing you know,
you're finishing the last article, hmm.
-(normal voice) I got all their numbers!
-Boy, you are smooth.
Carl smooth. Now I'd better get home.
And in case Marge is mad,
can I borrow that chip?
Oh, sure thing, pal. I have extras.
(sniffs)
-(low voice) Chitter, chitter, baby.
-(chitters)
I was so worried.
Where have you been?
No, don't tell me.
I don't want to hear
one of your stupid lies.
(deep voice) Marge, my dear,
you are the pork chop with gravy on top,
and I'm the applesauce
that brings out your flavor.
Oh, Homie.
(Homer coughs)
(deep voice) What the hell was that?
(normal voice)
What the... You're not my wife.
Which I find intriguing.
Suit yourself. (laughs)
So, Professor,
tell me all about last night.
Dish-dish-dish!
Uh, yes, well, I can't talk now.
I'm on a date. And then I have a date.
And then another date.
Is there such a thing
as too much of a good thing?
This is my cousin, Nookie Kwan.
I'm number one on the east side.
(quietly) Oh, gah-layvin.
-Have any of you seen John Frink?
-He ain't here.
But his hover-tronic
Frink-a-ma-car is parked outside.
Hey, if I say he ain't here,
he ain't here.
Hey, Moe,
there's a rat floating in my beer.
It ain't there.
-(door closes)
-Thank you, my good man,
but, uh, I saw some
terrible things down there.
Like for one, Moe is pantsless.
Hey, it's apron-only Tuesday.
Oi...
You're a lucky guy, Frinky.
Got all the chicks you want
while I can't find a single woman
to put up with me
and my domesticated wolverine.
-Lucky Frink.
-I got nothin'.
Some guys get all the breaks.
Let me see here.
Uh, needy men...
plus lonely women...
I-I just bring them together!
Hey, that's some nice thinkin' there.
Now, how 'bout a beer and a baked potato.
Ah, that sounds nice.
We don't serve baked potatoes.
What happened?
Everyone is incredibly depressed.
-(groans)
-(sighs)
(electronic sigh)
I admit the hallucinations
were getting out of hand,
so I stopped the meds.
And hid them in the one place
they'll never look-- the library.
Well, there's one thing
you didn't count on--
I go there because it's the only room
in this building with heat.
(Marge gasps)
Grampa, you're not allowed
to take dangerous drugs
unless they're in a little paper cup.
Listen here. Every night I watch
my roommate cry himself to sleep.
Yesterday I found out it was a mirror!
I'm gonna find my Mona!
(grunting)
There's a lesson here--
never visit Grampa.
(gasps)
My old car.
Oh, that's some fine hallucinatin'.
To the good ol' days
before polio was cured!
♪ ♪
Hot diggity!
It's America the way I liked it,
before we went to the moon
and discovered how boring it was.
(laughing)
I found the one happy moment
in 80 years of life,
and I ain't leavin' it.
Oh, this ain't right.
(snaps) That's better!
This ends right now!
She's not real. None of this is real.
Imaginary cigarettes?
Nonexistent candy?
(stammering)
Get outta here, Marge!
Unescorted women like you
aren't allowed in this era!
I'm not getting out, I'm cutting in.
You can't live here.
You have people
in the real world who love you.
Two are standing right over here.
If you live in the past,
you'll never have us.
And what's more precious to a grampa
than his grandchildren?
Particularly his grandson.
Aw, your sexist argument has won me over.
We women will have our day.
-Attaboy.
-(groans)
Good-bye, Mona.
And good-bye,
pack of cigarettes for a quarter.
I think I'll miss you the most.
(gasps)
So what, uh, all that dancin' around
with me meant nothin'?
(chuckles)
Oh, I'll be back to steal a kiss later.
And as for you...
I've got more involved plans.
(groans)
So, Frink is finally
going to announce which woman
he's chosen to be with
at the Springfield Planetarium.
It's like an episode of The Bachelor,
but you drive there
and pay six dollars for parking.
Why are we both explaining it
if we all know what's happening?
I like talking to you.
(normal voice)
Ladies, please pay attention here.
(groaning, murmuring)
You see, I, uh... I thought
I was the only one who was lonely.
But I have learned
that loneliness is everywhere,
like superhero movies.
How many times can Batman begin?
I have reworked my algorithms
to make you not like me,
but to find the man that will
make each of you happiest, yes.
Uh, release the bachelors!
I hope they enjoy it.
(gasping)
(impressed murmuring)
Duffman would love to be taught
how to speak in the first-person.
(chuckling) Everyone's paired up.
Almost everyone's paired up.
Professor, what about you?
Where's your match?
For me, my true love
is intellectual conquest,
the-the music of the spheres.
(owl hoots)
Well, sometimes it's good
just to be alone.
♪ And now the purple dusk
of twilight time ♪
♪ Steals across the meadows of my heart ♪
("Stardust" continues)
♪ High up in the sky ♪
♪ The little stars climb... ♪
ELDERLY WOMAN:
What are you doing with my daughter?!
Why did I build a mother?
Oi, goy-vick.
Wait a minute,
how come we're all back here?
I flushed the rest of the pills
down the toilet.
Looks like they made their way
to the reservoir.
-We should really try to wake up.
-Are you kidding?
There's a full buffet,
and Dean Martin's here.
Eh, that's right, pally.
Here, try the shrimp.
Some have gone bad,
but, uh, most are fine.
(slurps)
(theme music playing)
-(crowd murmuring)
-Shh!
Subtitled by A. Vandelay