(SlNGlNG) The Simpsons
(TlRES SCREECHlNG)
D'oh !
(SCREAMlNG)
(BRAKES SCREECHlNG)
Bart, l got it!
l ran here as fast as l. . .
Bart, that creepy kid
is here.
(VULTURES CAWlNG)
Hey, Milhouse!
Oh, what's this?
(READlNG)
Oh, wow! This'll look
great on my bike.
Flame decal for
the chain guard,
Marine Corps tassels,
bullet-proof seat,
and a rub-on tattoo
for that special someone.
That's me.
(READlNG)
Oh !
MAN: (SlNGlNG) Why don't you
come with me, IittIe girI
On a magic carpet ride
Now to turn on
the moto-mimic.
(BlKE MlMlCS
MOTORCYCLE ENGlNE)
lt sounds like
a motorcycle gang.
And we don't have backup!
We'd better lay low.
But Chief,
what if they like pizza?
Way ahead of you, Lou.
That is one bitchin' bike.
Daddy said a cuss word !
Lighten up, Roddy.
NELSON: Ha-ha!
lt's the baby bike brigade.
Hey, Bart. l used to
have a bike like that.
Back before l was born.
Oh, no.
They've got big boy bikes.
Thanks for the tassels.
My mom can wear these
on her boobs at work.
(LAUGHS)
Hey, give those back!
Gentlemen, first gear.
(GROANlNG)
Oh, man, l sure wish
l had a ten-speed bike.
A ten-speed bike?
What did your mother say?
She said, "Yes."
MARGE: l said no!
l'm confused. Which is it?
MARGE: lt's no!
His old bike is fine.
Yeah,
the kitchen lady's right.
No new bike while
your old one still works.
l see. So if my
old bike didn't work,
l would automatically
get a new one?
That's right.
No questions asked.
(LAUGHS)
Boy, l'm really
gonna miss you.
We've really
had some great. . .
Ooh ! A Mercedes!
DR. HlBBERT:
What the Halle Berry?
Yes!
(GASPS) My bike!
My crappy, crappy bike!
l'm very sorry, Bart.
l'll pay for a new bike.
(LAUGHS)
This was a wakeup call.
From now on,
l'll keep my eyes
on the road
and off my Kool &
the Gang air freshener.
Celebration's over, boys.
(CAT SCREECHlNG)
(THUD)
(GASPS)
Snowball !
(SOBBlNG)
Snowball ll,
l can't believe you're gone.
l wrote this poem for you.
lt's called "Cat Math."
"Four paws, plus one tail,
"plus nine lives
equals one special cat.
"One special cat
minus nine lives equals
one sad little girl."
l know how you feel, Lise.
No kid wants to
outlive their pet.
Oh, sweetie,
when l was your age,
l lost my
guinea pig, Cinnamon.
And l thought the pain
would never. . . (GASPS)
Oh, Cinnamon !
lt should've been me
who chewed through
that extension cord !
There, there,
you're both right.
Son, would you like to ride
your new bike
out of the store?
Can l? For true?
For true, Son.
Hey, pally. l don't want to
downshift your enthusiasm
but that's a floor model.
Your bike is in here.
l could put it
together right now
for a small assembly fee.
Here we go.
Now it starts
with the fees.
l'll assemble it myself.
Dad, no! Think of the bike!
l can make a bike.
l made you.
Yeah, great workmanship.
Hey, that's gonna win you
a lot of bar bets someday.
Man, this is so confusing.
What the hell is this? Oh !
(GASPS)
Bike's over there.
You actually did it.
You're the coolest, Dad.
(CHUCKLES)
Look what my dad
just built for me.
ALL: Whoa!
Hey, guys.
This butt's for you.
Oh, no!
No one does this to Dolph !
No one!
(LAUGHS)
Uh-oh ! Whoa!
l'm riding a unicycle
with my pants down.
This should be
every boy's dream.
Ha-ha! Your dad's not handy.
Son, are you okay?
l brought a homemade
first aid kit!
lt's spring-loaded
for quick access.
(SCREAMlNG)
Oh. . .
ANNOUNCER 1 ON TV:
We now return to Robot Rumble
on the Testosterone Network!
AII right!
ANNOUNCER 2 ON TV:
Congratulations to our
winning father and son team,
who will receive
a free appetizer
at Fuzzy ZoeIIer's
Green Jacket Steakhouse.
"And you won't be teed off
when you come in
"because our steaks
are cooked to par-fection.
"Our leader bar is filled
with scrumptious..."
Two more pages?
I'm not reading this.
(AUDlENCE APPLAUDlNG)
Hey, boy.
What do you say
we build a robot?
Face it. You're not
the most mechanical guy
in the world.
But you're good
at other things
like eating while driving !
That's something !
And nobody gets
madder at the news!
First of all, thank you.
Secondly. . .
My son thinks l'm an oaf.
Mom, l'm not sure
l'm ready for a new cat.
When Bad Things
Happen to Cute Children
says that a new pet
will pull you out of
your sorrow cycle.
That book doesn't
know how l feel.
Oh, it's very wise.
lt's written by a Rabbi,
who surfs!
All right. l'll look.
Too fluffy,
too Siamese,
too needy, too stuck up.
lnfected eye,
clearly a skunk.
(GASPS) Meow!
Welcome to the family,
Snowball lll.
There's nothing
worse than the look
on a boy's face when he says,
"Dad, l don't think
you can build a fully
functional robot."
(SCREAMS)
Robot, l command you,
do something cool.
Oh.
l could quit now,
but then my son will
never look up to me.
Oh, why was l born a dad?
Why do l suck?
Wait a minute.
What is it my dad
always said to me?
lf you can't build a robot,
be a robot.
That's it!
(KRUSTY CLOCK LAUGHlNG)
KRUSTY CLOCK:
It's Tuesday, the first.
If you Iive in Krusty Brand
Iow-income housing,
your rent is due!
(YAWNS)
(SCREAMS)
"Dear Bart, if this robot
doesn't prove l love you,
"then you can
both go to hell."
(GRUNTS)
Hey, it didn't fall apart.
Cool ! Now stop!
(GASPS HAPPlLY)
Smash this six-pack!
(CHUCKLlNG)
Oh, awesome.
l gotta tell Milhouse!
Oh, the beer's gone.
l'll have to
suck it out of the shag.
(SlNGlNG)
You pIop the cat food down
You toss the tin can out
You drop the worm piIIs in
And you stir it aII about
You add a lot of lovin'
and you serve it to your cat
That's what it's all...
Snowball lll?
(GASPS)
(SOBBlNG)
Oh, Lisa. Honey, it's okay.
You're a Buddhist.
So you know your cats
are now reincarnated as
a higher form of life.
Like a dog or a snowman.
Ashes to ashes,
dust to dust.
We gotta go fight
some robots!
Come on, Homer.
How long does it take
to go to the bathroom?
Huh?
"Dear Bart. . ."
HOMER:
I'd Iove to be with you.
But I just remembered
an oId Army buddy
has come to town.
WiII meet you Iater.
Love, Dad.
Well, l wish Homer was here.
But don't worry.
l've got a name all
picked out for you.
Chief Knock-A-Homer,
let's win this one for Dad !
(HOMER BLEEPS)
ANNOUNCER 1 :
In this corner, operated by
Frank Murray and
little Frankie Junior,
Buzzkill!
And in this corner,
the chaIIenger.
Chief Knock-A-Homer!
There's no love lost between
these emotionless devices.
Robots rumble!
Go, go, go!
Go! Go!
Oh, jeez.
l'm the only one in
the audience over 1 5.
Are you here with
your children, sir?
Yeah, my two kids,
Screw and You.
(SCREAMlNG)
ANNOUNCER 2: What's this?
Knock-A-Homer has
dropped his hammer.
Doin' it for the boy.
Pain is love.
To bleed is to care.
ANNOUNCER 2:
Can robots feel pain?
lf so, we are horrible,
horrible people.
He's killing him
softly with his saw.
Killing him softly?
With his saw.
(AUDlENCE CHEERlNG)
Woo-hoo! l mean, beep-beep.
Mom, l'm not sure
if l'm ready to open
my heart again.
But this kitten's
name is Coltrane.
Maybe it's a sign.
Coltrane?
Lisa, l'm glad
you're ready to love again.
But a kitty
needs a proper name,
like Whiskers
or Paws Skaggs.
Well, l think it's only
fair l get to name him.
You got to name me.
You should be glad l did.
Your father wanted
to call you "Bartzina."
Coltrane, would you
like to hear some music
written by your namesake?
(PLAYlNG JAZZ MUSlC)
(SCREECHlNG)
(THUD)
Coltrane!
"Coltrane, you were
with us only briefly
"but we will always
have the ride home
from the shelter."
And, um, l guess that's it.
Amen.
And Lord,
if you think l'm making
lemon bars for
your bake sale Sunday,
you better stop
killing our cats.
Mom, l'm not sure
God responds to threats
and intimidation.
lt's the only way
to talk to bullies.
Then Knock-A-Homer
did three victory laps
and pretended
to drink a beer!
(LAUGHS)
Pretended.
Dad, what are
all those cuts?
Various bug bites and wounds.
Now stop
interrupting your brother.
ln my day, mechanical men
had funnel heads
and showed respect!
Then it all changed
when they got the vote
and started
tinkering with our memories.
There he sits with
a pen and a yeIIow pad
What a handsome lad
That's my boy
B-R-L-F-Q spells
mom and dad
Well, that ain't too bad
'Cause that's my boy
WeII, you can have your TV
and your nightcIubs
And you can have your
drive-in picture show
ANNOUNCER 1 :
Well, if you ever want to see
a mailbox shoot a boy,
that's about as close
as you're gonna get.
Dad, it was so great.
Knock-A-Homer
really took a pounding
but then he won !
(GROANS)
Not so rough, Bart.
Daddy can't handle so
much love right now.
This robot's
the greatest thing
you've ever done for me.
l can't believe you've
never seen him fight.
Well, l've been busy, Son.
They really need me
over at the nuclear "plank."
Well, the next match
is Saturday.
Can you come then?
l don't think so, Son.
But on the other hand,
l may be closer
than you think.
Oh. So much metal in my eye.
Ladies and gentIemen...
Who am I kidding?
Just gentIemen,
join us next week
for our title bout
when Knock-A-Homer
wiII try to unseat five-time
defending champion
Smashius Clay,
AKA Killhammad Aieee!
(CROWD APPLAUDlNG)
Our robot can kick
that robot's ass.
Right, Dad? Dad?
(SHUDDERS)
Oh, no.
My recurring nightmare
is coming true.
There are many people
l'd like to thank
for this award.
My wife Anjelica Houston.
This is for you, Angie.
We did it!
ROBOT:
Speeches cannot be longer
than 30 seconds.
(SCREAMS)
Now, a tribute to those
who have left us
this past year.
(WHlMPERS)
BART: Sure he's tough
but he's never
come up against
a wooden mallet.
Listen, Son.
There's something
l have to tell you
about our robot.
(DOORBELL RlNGlNG)
There it is! The thing that
makes us respect Bart.
(ALL EXCLAlM lN WONDER)
You guys are just in time.
My dad's about
to tell me something
important about our robot.
Uh. . .
l just installed a chip
that makes it 1 0 %
more bloodthirsty.
All right!
And if anything
happens to me,
l want you bullies
to take care of my boy.
Don't worry.
l'll raise him like
the mean streets raised me.
l wish l had bullies
like you growing up.
Hey, hey!
These cats'd rather
take their chances
in the back room
than go home with you.
(CATS HlSSlNG)
My job was to keep
Lisa's hope alive.
But instead,
she's really depressed.
You think you got problems,
look what l just
pulled out of my arm !
(GASPS)
That's what
we in the business
call a "biggie."
Business? What business?
The business of being a dad.
Can you hand me that magnet?
Sure.
(CLANKlNG)
Can you do my back?
l guess l'm not meant
to own a cat.
l'm much happier
petting this leaf.
(EXCLAlMS)
(SHOUTlNG GlBBERlSH)
Wait! You don't want
me to have this cat!
(SHOUTlNG GlBBERlSH)
Look, you don't
want to get involved
with a girl like me.
My cats have a nasty habit
of waking up dead.
Now go.
Cough me out of your life
like a bad fur ball.
(GASPS)
You're not hurt.
You're a good luck kitty.
All right,
old Gil's gonna collect big
from insurance.
l'll be eating food tonight.
(HUMMlNG)
(EXPLOSlON)
l'm keeping you.
You're Snowball V.
But to save money
on a new dish,
we'll just call
you Snowball ll
and pretend this whole thing
never happened.
That's really a cheat,
isn't it?
l guess you're right,
Principal Tamzarian.
l'll just be
moving along, Lisa,
Snowball ll.
(EXPLOSlON)
Okay, l've been
studying Frink's robot.
And l've discovered
he has one small weak spot.
This goes here. . .
Yeah.
Oh-oh. His weak spot is
now his strongest point.
(HOMER MOANS)
That moan sounded
almost human.
HOMER: The hell it did.
(BELL DlNGS)
ANNOUNCER: End of round one,
230 rounds to go.
(SlNGlNG)
B-R-L-F-Q spells
mom and dad
But that ain't too bad,
because that's my boy
You look a little sluggish
out there, boy.
l better open you up.
(GASPS)
Dad?
Bart, l'm sorry.
l could never build
a robot this awesome.
l'm a fraud !
So you fought
all those robots?
Affirmative.
That is so cool !
You really think so?
Yeah ! Any Poindexter
can throw some nuts
and bolts together.
You risked your own life.
Even though
you're the sole provider
for a family of five!
l am the luckiest
kid in the world !
And l am the luckiest. . .
ANNOUNCER: Round two!
Oh, no! Dad !
(SlGHS)
(ALL EXCLAlM)
That robot has
given birth to a man !
Hey, what gives?
He's not killing me.
FRlNK:
l'll tell you what gives.
l'm afraid he is subject
to lsaac Asimov's
laws of robotics,
with the sci-fi
and the so many books,
not too many good.
My robot
is programmed never to
harm humans, you see?
Only to serve them.
Mmm.
He knows just how
l like my martinis.
Full of alcohol.
Go, go, go!
Now's your chance!
(CHUCKLES)
Bart, all that button
ever did was
send a mild electric shock
up my backside.
Why did you
make it do that?
To keep me focused.
And the winner
is nature's greatest
kiIIing machine,
man!
(BOOlNG)
Show me where in
the ruIebook it says that
a human can't be a robot.
Right here. Rule One.
Well, then...
Join us next week
for more inconclusive
action on Robot Rumble!
l concur!
(BOOlNG)
Son, did you ever
suspect it was me?
Well, you did disappear
a lot but l've gone
whole summers
without seeing you.
(LAUGHS) Yeah.
l'm pretty unreliable.
l like you, Son.
l like you, too, Dad.
English - US - PSDH