CHOIR: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
-Ay-ay-ay!
-(bees buzzing)
(theme music playing)
(birds chirping)
Oh! Looks like our birdhouse
is benefitting
from positive word of beak.
(laughs)
(eagle screeches)
A bald eagle!
It is!
(screeches)
Maybe he's giving those
little baby birds some food.
(screams)
-(screeches)
-(gasps)
Homer, quick!
Get your shooing broom.
Marge, an eagle is our country's mascot!
Fighting him is like
kicking George Washington
in his wooden nuts!
Aah! (grunting)
(screeches)
(grunts)
Ow. Ow.
This means war!
Boy, bring my toupee.
Go ahead, boy.
MILHOUSE: It's working!
It's definitely working!
For once, we're finally
gonna catch that mouse.
(screeches)
-Got you!
-Ha-ha! Stupid eagle!
It wasn't the mouse we were after.
It was you!
Marge, preheat the oven!
-(grunting) You.. get...
-(screeching)
I got him cornered, boy!
Bag him up!
-(screeching)
-(grunting)
(laughing)
Not so majestic in a trash bag,
are you?
Oopsie. (puffing)
Seems almost a shame
I'm gonna have to bang you
against the wall
-till you die.
-No!
Let's take the eagle
to Shelbyville Animal Rescue
where you took
that injured hummingbird
you found on the front lawn.
Uh...
um...
Or maybe we can nurse him
back to health
and set him free in the wild.
Okay, Bart, think of a name.
Make it great--
insanely, unbelievably great!
-Squawky?
-Perfect.
Just like when we let you name Maggie.
(humming)
Squawky, until I met you,
I never thought I could
love something bald.
-(screeches)
-Bye!
We love you.
(all gasp)
Oh, my God.
Brace yourselves, family.
We're about to meet a being
with intelligence far beyond ours.
Boy, give me my baseball bat.
-Hello. I'm Elon Musk.
-HOMER: Die!
-What the...
-Dad, no!
Elon Musk is possibly
the greatest living inventor!
You're the guy
who put wheels on luggage?
Oh, bless you! Bless you!
(crying)
I'm-I'm not that guy.
His company perfected electric cars
and then gave away the patents!
He changed the way Hollywood drives!
And now he's landed in our yard.
On my son's bike
and on our mailman's leg.
Honey, guess who crushed me?
I'll give you a hint.
His first name is Elon.
Ah! That's right!
So, what brings you to Springfield,
Mr. Musk?
What does bring me to Springfield?
Well, to start with, I'm an idea man.
It's my raison d'être.
Mmm.
Raisin Detra.
I've hit a dry patch. I'm blocked.
In my personal drought,
I'm traveling the country
quietly by spaceship,
looking for... inspiration.
That's so sad.
Maybe we're the same.
Two lost ships in the intellectual sea.
Each of whom could inspire
the other to reach...
Hey, Elon, if you're interested,
you could come to the nuclear plant
where I work tomorrow.
-I am and I will!
-Great.
And if anyone asks where I am,
just cover for me.
-Homer!
-Fine!
We'll both go,
and if anybody asks you
something you don't understand,
just say protons.
So... do you get satellite radio
cheaper in space?
Homer, if we're gonna carpool together,
there's one thing you have to know.
Ass, gas or grass--
no one rides for free.
It's as old as the Bible.
No, it's that I don't talk to anyone
unless they provide
the mental stimulation I seek.
Ditto.
(Lisa giggles nervously) Hi.
I didn't want to miss one more chance
to spend time with Mr. Musk.
It is such an honor.
He is. And may I save that paper?
LISA: "No ideas." (gasps)
That's sad.
(gasps) That's even worse.
-(Elon sighs)
-(Lisa gasps)
Aw, man, I wish those were
white meatballs.
(triumphant orchestra music playing)
Oh, my. That's an idea!
White meatballs-- synthetic meat
that you can print in your printer.
Say something else.
Please! Now!
Uh... don't tase me, bro.
Chocolate rain!
Tase, bro, chocolate rain.
Use electroplating to remove
metal ions from rainwater,
-making it suitable for drinking.
-What about the chocolate?
We'll make the device
a soothing chocolate color-- brilliant!
He's taking your Homerisms
and turning them into
his own great ideas!
This is the most inspirational
moment of my life, but...
unfortunately, this is my stop.
Bye.
Well, come on,
keep throwing things at me.
Um... (grunts)
Oh, this is a break.
We're-we're taking a break!
-(grunts)
-(laughs)
(both laughing)
I got you!
-MUSK: You're fun.
-Well, duh. (laughs)
Why don't we have fun like that, Lou?
(huffing)
Ah, Chief!
Did anyone ever tell you
there's a safety on that gun?
-What do you mean this thing?
-(grunts) That's the trigger!
What are you writing?
Share, buddy.
Suggestion for the suggestion box.
Can anyone make a suggestion?
Be my guest, but I seriously doubt
the old man ever reads them.
Suggestion 8,432.
Nix!
Hmm, technically an order,
not a suggestion.
"Installing an MHD generator
would allow the plant to operate
at a higher temperature
without the tyranny of moving parts
using conducting plasma
as the moving conductor"?
Excellent.
Clearly the work of Lenny.
That's the white one, right?
-Is this your suggestion?
-No.
No, mine was rubber mats
in the decontamination showers.
Also, water in
the decontamination showers.
Never!
-Mm-hmm. Mm.
-Good Lord!
Sir, you know who that is?
The man who's revolutionized
the car industry.
Henry Ford, good to see you.
As healthy and vibrant as Detroit itself.
No, sir, this is Elon Musk.
For some reason, he's sharing
a console with Homer Simpson.
His mind is as rich
as an Italian wedding soup.
-Homer, what are you thinking now?
-Uh, Pittsburgh 35, Dallas 31!
(triumphant orchestra music playing)
Pittsburgh steel, Dallas Cowboys...
Robotic cattle herding!
Thank you, Homer.
(gentle music playing)
Sorry, that's something I'm working on
so that I don't have to display
-facial expressions.
-(electrical crackling)
Young man,
I look at you and I see myself.
How much would you charge
to work for me?
I don't care about the money.
The whole monetary system is
just a series of interconnected
heterogeneous databases.
Could you repeat that first part?
I don't care about the money.
Once more... with feeling?
Now, let me feel the vibrations
of your lips.
(muffled)
I don't care about the money,
and I want you to get
your fingers out of my mouth!
Smithers, there's something
strange in his mouth.
It's called moisture.
Hmm, I see.
Okay, Musk, what do you propose?
Well, you'll need to increase
the capacity of your plant.
You cover the costs,
you get 100% of the profits.
Careful, Elon,
he's not as kindly as he appears.
(creaking)
Now, Burns, what if everything in town
not powered by electricity
were powered by electricity?
The electricity you sell them.
Imagine that.
(gasps) My doctor says
I'm not allowed to imagine,
so I hired someone to do it for me.
Send in the imaginer.
(humming)
Oh, that's fabulous.
Oh, my goodness,
I can see everything.
I'm in.
Oh, by the way, Mr. Burns?
I haven't been paid in a while.
Here you go. Imagine.
Ooh, Swiss francs!
Time to take my wife
for a night on the town.
Hey, wait a minute!
(sniffs)
So, what kind of lunch do you pack?
Wow, Elon, you're like Willy Wonka
without the underpaid munchkins.
Uh, I'd like to offer you something.
But all I got is coffee.
With cream!
Come on, I want cream.
Give it up. (grunting)
D'oh!
Cream and sugar
are one thing too many!
(triumphant orchestra music playing)
Exactly, exactly!
What if we made
the cream cup out of sugar
so it dissolved in the coffee?
Wow. Wow!
Between your genius and my nothing,
we make a great team!
Come on, give me a hug.
Sorry, I'm not one for hugging.
Well, I'm not one for just talking.
(violin playing romantic melody)
Does that drone do date nights
with the wife?
My partner, Montgomery Burns...
-ALL: Boo!
-We hate him!
-...and I...
-Hooray!
have exciting news.
Springfield Nuclear has electric solutions
to all of your energy needs.
The Springfield Hyperloop.
Electrifying the school
to replace the old power source,
Willy pushing a wheel.
(drumming rhythmically)
And my passion project,
the Glayvinator.
You have a Glayvinator, too?
Is it, um, uh, patent-pending?
Patent granted.
All the years of Glayvining
in my basement for naught!
I'm a failure.
Ah, yes, everyone's been there.
-You have those feelings, too?
-Of course not.
If I knew how to make a fist,
I'd hit you.
This is wonderful, Smithers.
For once in my life,
something's going my way.
I'm not so sure.
Oh, another visit from Mr. Worrywart.
I don't trust Musk.
Anyone with that much money
has a darkness in his soul.
Says you.
(sighs)
SMITHERS: Mr. Burns?
Mr. Burns?
Sir, Musk's ideas sound great--
too great.
We're meant for wretched lives.
We should pass on this.
And before you reply, remember,
I've never let you down.
-You know what I'm going to say, right?
-Release the...
I was going to say "Get out,"
but your idea sounds better.
(sighs) Can you give me
a ten-second head start?
Of course. One, two, three!
(barking)
Not on my carpet.
Attention, fans of The Little Rascals.
The last of them died today
in Palm Springs.
Now it's time for traffic with Arnie Pye.
Nothing to report, Kent.
Since Elon Musk gave everyone
self-driving cars,
there hasn't been a single accident.
(chuckles)
Well, you be careful up there, Arnie.
No need.
Mr. Musk gave me a self-flying chopper!
Where's Arnie?
Now I can get as loaded as I want,
which is pretty damn loaded.
Oh, boy.
♪ Elon, Elon, you're my guy ♪
♪ Since you came down from the sky ♪
-(gulping)
-(glass shatters)
Car, go park at work
so people think I'm there.
(horn honks)
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Force of habit.
Car, wake Grampa.
-(zapping)
-(Grampa groaning)
GRAMPA: Thank you.
Mm. (muttering)
Bart, what are you doing?
Disable auto drive.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Enter password.
Foolish boy.
You'll never guess
Elon Musk's master password.
Musk rulez, with a "Z."
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Password verified.
Manual control enabled.
(laughs)
(tires squealing)
Welcome, friends.
I have invited you here to share
in our first quarterly profit report.
I'm sure you're all eager to hear
how much richer I am.
Now, to end the suspense, Elon?
Thank you, Monty.
-At our current rate...
-Yes?
-...assuming a linear growth model...
-Of course!
...we are losing roughly
$50 million a quarter.
Just remember, our purpose is
to show the planet how to save itself.
Oh, the planet.
I adore the planet.
Do you know my favorite part
of the planet?
Gravity!
There are no trapdoors
on this podium, Burns.
You just started
the PowerPoint presentation.
♪ ♪
No, no, no!
Musk, you tricked me.
Not a trick. We sacrifice now
to take care of the future
in a way totally determined by me.
(groans) All I wanted
was to make obscene profits
in the last year of my life
and leave it to no one.
Why does God hate dreamers?
(bird caws)
Due to recent fluctuations
in my judgment,
and the once in a lifetime mistake
of trusting another human being,
I am saddened to announce
massive layoffs.
Who will pay
for my radiation sickness treatments?
Not my concern.
But Musk was our savior!
Your so-called savior isn't interested
in saving anything but the world. Bah!
Burns' layoffs have thrown the city
into a new depression,
marked by the singing of songs
from the old depression.
If you're old enough
to have suffered then and now,
why don't you sing along?
♪ Now the rain's a-fallin' ♪
♪ Hear the trains a-callin' ♪
♪ Whoo-ee ♪
♪ My mama done told me ♪
♪ Hear that lonesome whistle ♪
♪ Blowin' cross the trestle ♪
♪ Whoo-ee ♪
♪ My mama done told me ♪
♪ A-whoo-ee ♪
-♪ A-whoo-ee ♪
-(clopping hoofbeats)
♪ Oh, clickety-clack
and it's echoing back ♪
♪ The blues in the night ♪
My final invention.
A pill that removes all grief.
-(chittering)
-Ah...
-(groans)
-(chittering)
Oh, my God, it attracts women, too.
You're welcome,
you're welcome, you're welcome.
(distorted)
You're... welcome.
(whistles)
You really came back
from that Tommy John surgery.
Tell Musk there's more
where that came from.
More of what? (groans)
Smithers, the hounds feel terrible
for what they did,
and good news,
one pooped out your ear.
We'll dip it in iodine,
and it's just like new.
(groans)
Also, I'm sorry,
I couldn't find the records
of the shots the hounds
had which, in turn,
led to all those painful injections
in your abdomen.
(groans)
Now, the reason I'm here...
I've made the calls.
I'm going to have Elon Musk killed,
and I'll give you
a little extra morphine, friend.
(screaming)
-(dogs snarling)
-Oh, right, that's a trapdoor.
(groans)
What's wrong, Homer?
Is it that all your friends
are out of work,
and it's kind of your fault?
(scoffs) No, it's Elon.
I don't care how much he likes me.
I don't want to be friends
with him anymore.
None of his pie in the sky ideas
ever work out.
Sky pies are lie pies.
Of all the planets in the universe,
why did he have to come to this one?
How do you break up with a guy?
Here's what you do.
You just take his hand,
look in his eyes, and say,
"I don't want to be with you anymore."
Wow, you're good at that.
It's gotten me out of
a lot of gym memberships.
♪ ♪
Sir, I have my concern
about the team of hit men
you've assembled.
-They seem a little long in the tooth.
-Nonsense.
Just because a man can't see
or hold his hands steady
doesn't make him
any less of a marksman.
A yoga mat that rolls itself up.
Silent Velcro, baseball tickets
that guide you to your seat.
(gunshots)
Sweet Columbian Exposition!
Musk lives.
But, uh, three of your hit men don't.
The recoil was pretty bad.
Oh, my God, Oh, my God.
You saved my life!
Which is gonna make what
I'm about to say even more awkward.
Whatever you want,
we'll make it work, right, Homer?
Elon, Elon, Elon,
I want to say something to you,
and I don't want you
to be inspired by it.
I want you to listen.
No!
I don't want to be with you anymore.
Can I ask why?
I could say it's the being shot at,
or the flat,
emotionless way you talk,
or the fact that PayPal was my idea,
and I was just about to do it
when you came out with it,
but really it's that this town
isn't ready for you.
-And neither am I.
-It's okay. I'll be fine.
(gentle music playing)
It's on your face, too.
Well, I did save you one last prize
from the Cracker Jack box
that is my brain.
Use it as you will.
On the Miami Dolphins helmet,
the little dolphin
is also wearing a helmet.
Why are they always the most beautiful
just when they're breaking up with you?
I think it's time to tell
my luggage to self-pack.
Good-bye, Elon.
Our town will never forgive you.
Thanks for the real working lightsaber.
(whooshing)
Ay, caramba!
(giggles) I just wanted to see
if there was a better life,
even for a little bit.
When you're 16,
I'll drive you to Cincinnati,
and you'll see what there is to see.
Mr. Musk, before you go,
is there anything you could do
to give a little girl hope
that the world of the future
won't be as grim
as all our current movies forecast?
I guess humanity wants its change
one birdhouse at a time.
Hmm, for a man who likes electric cars,
he sure burns a lot of rocket fuel.
-(moans)
-What's wrong, Dad?
Nothing.
Elon's log, Earth date, 25 January, 2015.
I have left Springfield forever,
but there are some things
I will definitely miss.
The little dolphin
is also wearing a helmet.
Wearing a helmet. Wearing a helmet.
I never thought I'd say this,
but sometimes holograms
miss the point.
♪ There's a starman ♪
♪ Waiting in the sky ♪
♪ He'd like to come and meet us ♪
♪ But he thinks he'd blow our minds ♪
♪ There's a starman ♪
♪ Waiting in the sky ♪
♪ He's told us not to blow it ♪
♪ 'Cause he knows it's all worthwhile ♪
♪ He told me ♪
♪ Let the children lose it ♪
♪ Let the children use it ♪
♪ Let all the children boogie ♪
♪ There's a starman ♪
♪ Waiting in the sky ♪
♪ He'd like to come and meet us ♪
♪ But he thinks he'd blow our minds ♪
♪ There's a starman ♪
♪ Waiting in the sky ♪
♪ He's told us not to blow it ♪
♪ 'Cause he knows it's all worthwhile ♪
♪ He told me ♪
♪ Let the children lose it ♪
♪ Let the children use it ♪
♪ Let all the children boogie ♪
-(crowd murmuring)
-Shh!
Subtitled by Jimmy Boots