D'oh!
- No electricity.
- D'oh!
Hardest test in the world?
Who'd want to do that?
Oh, hey, Bart.
What you doing?
They say this one single test
can tell if you're
a genius or not.
Looks pretty simple to me.
It says only one
out of every 400 people
has the spatial reasoning
to solve this maze.
Elon Musk and Anjela Merkel
both got perfect scores.
Angela. Angela.
Oh, if you're so smart,
let's see you solve the maze.
Let me at it!
Okay, got through the first one.
Next one's a little harder.
Just gonna focus.
You passed the test, genius.
Epic sister fail!
You better not post that!
And... post.
You scared me and
denied me a genius test!
Well, when you got
an opportunity to prank,
you gotta take it.
Gotta take it.
And the likes are pouring in.
Whoa! Sideshow Mel retweeted it
to all his boneheads.
Are you almost done?
You have your office.
This is mine!
I don't know how,
I don't know when,
but I super know why I'll get
revenge on you, Bart Simpson.
Will you be wearing my
underpants when that happens?
And post.
Post. Post. Post.
Unpost! Unpost!
And post.
The internet is down!
I don't know the score.
I don't even remember
who's playing.
Okay, no internet.
We can do what we did
in the olden days,
when I was a child.
You better not be suggesting
a board game.
I'm not playing anything
with you ever again.
Okay, fine. No board games.
Dumb. Useless.
Piece missing.
So flammable.
Okay, look, the TV still works,
and I know we've seen
all our DVDs a hundred times,
so this could be
the perfect time to break out...
Daddy's VHS collection.
Classic moments from a time
when people used to
tape the shows they loved,
then never watch the tape again.
Family Matters?
It certainly does.
The Tracey Ullman Show?
Well, I've had my fill.
Saved by the Bell?
The hit show
that launched no one's career.
Now for the simple task
of hooking up the VCR.
Okay, I need to connect
magenta to magenta,
set the tracking.
Marge, did I record these
in long play or extended play?
- What's the difference?
- Long is shorter.
Gross!
The remote has a cord on it.
My first remote.
Coincidentally,
the same time I got fat.
What is that noise?
It's rewinding.
Listen to it speed up
as it gets closer.
Well, that was fun.
Good night.
No, now we play it.
Ri-cola!
I used to love that commercial.
Remember when I went as
the horn for Halloween?
Ri-cola!
Let's get physical, physical
I want to get physical...
No worries.
We just have to find
a VCR repair store.
I'll look online, which I can't
because there's no internet!
Damn it!
Lisa, solve this.
I've solved
enough puzzles today.
Well, Flanders' network
is working.
Maybe we could ask him
for the password.
You can't just ask someone
for their password. That's rude.
Come on, boy,
let's go borrow his router.
How come all our father-son
activities involve
getting a TV back on?
What about the time I watched
you get out of that thing?
- You mean when I was born?
- That was fun.
If I die before I wake,
I pray the Lord
my soul to take. Amen.
That's right, boys.
Think about your possible deaths
as you go to sleep.
Now let's look at my plans.
Who's this ladder
made for, babies?
D'oh!
- You'll have to climb it, boy.
- I'm a little scared.
Scared? What do we give you
those meds for?
So you can do less parenting?
Babysitter in a bottle.
Now climb the ladder.
So beautiful.
Almost there. You just need
to go up the last rung.
That's not a rung, it's the top.
- The top is a rung.
- No, it's not!
- Let me check on Google.
- We don't have internet!
Maybe if I keep refreshing,
it'll come back.
Refresh. Refresh. Refresh.
Oh, this is pointless.
Ooh! No.
Refresh. Refresh. Refresh.
You guys need jackets!
No, we're fine! D'oh!
The internet's back on!
Doctor, is he gonna
be all right?
Millions of volts
coursed through his body.
But it was the amps
that really messed with him.
But he should be fine.
According to his chart,
Bart's had more comas
than he's had hot breakfasts.
Well, I can't cook
every morning.
Until he recovers,
just talk to him.
Lightning victims
are highly suggestible.
Your kind words could turn
his coma into a trip to Hawaii,
or a golf excursion
to St. Andrews,
which is where I'm heading now.
Well, when you got
an opportunity to prank,
you gotta take it.
Gotta take it.
But you're in a coma.
Fine, I'll get revenge.
You're gonna see dragons
with pools of blood.
Oh, right, you like that.
Okay, scratch the dragons.
You're gonna see the one thing
everyone's afraid of, death.
And dead people.
That's right, buddy.
Right and left
And right and right and left
Left, left, left,
right, right, right
It's Bart's
unconscious brain!
Okay, Bart,
your nightmare begins.
What happened?
How long was I out?
Maude Flanders!
I thought you were dead!
I am.
Sweetie, we're gonna
get something to eat.
- You want to come?
- I'd rather stay with Bart.
In fact, I'd like to stay
with him all night.
- Such a sweet girl.
- So sweet.
Someone's not happy.
You know, that sign
should be unnecessary.
I'd better cheer him up.
I'm going to add to your dream
the worst thing I can imagine!
Let me see. Let me see.
Wazzup...?!
Milhouse.
What's going on, Bart?
Are you into God now?
I always was.
Look at those abs.
The secret is less loaves,
more fishes.
I don't believe in
some dopey religion.
This is to keep out ghosts.
Oh, this looks just like
my first apartment with Ned.
I'm never leaving!
Milhouse, have you ever
been haunted?
Once, my hamster died
and then came back.
Actually, my parents
bought a new one
and thought I wouldn't know.
Then my dad's check bounced,
and they repo'd the hamster.
You've got to talk to me, Bart.
Leave me alone.
Leave me alone!
The power of Homer's socks
compels you!
Maybe you could use this,
my therapist.
If you see him,
can you give him this?
Don't tell him
I forgot to bring it back.
He'll say I kept it
to get attention.
I don't need attention, Dr. Sam!
I knew it was Milhouse.
I knew it!
What's on your mind, son?
I'm scared to say.
You'll toss me in the loony bin.
Bart, these days,
there are no more loony bins.
All those people
are on the streets.
- So how can I help you?
- I've been talking to a ghost.
I know, you think I'm
the nuttiest kid you've seen.
Oh, please, I can't tell you
what a relief it is
to not be talking to Milhouse.
Are you allowed
to say stuff like that?
No, but screw it.
My mom found
my dad's other cell phone,
boo-hoo.
So you don't think I'm crazy?
No. Take a look
behind the couch.
You're dead too?
Yeah, I killed myself five
minutes before you got here.
Why would you kill yourself?
Oh, I want my patients to think
it's all their fault.
Oh, if you'd been on time,
you might've saved my life,
but, you know, whatever.
Why is this happening to me?
I don't know,
but you have a gift!
You can see the dead, Bart.
Why am I waiting for a bus?
I can appear and disappear
whenever I want.
And it's late.
That's far enough.
And, Bart, you can
help us ghosts move on to
what comes next.
By telling your family
you love them?
Which family?
I've led a complicated life.
No, to move on, I need you
to get revenge on Dr. Morton,
with whom I share the office.
What have you got against him?
He won't shut up
about his Tesla.
Yes, yes, just as smart
as I always thought I...
Thank you, Bart.
Now I can move on.
Wow, helping him
felt really good.
- Help us, Bart.
- Help us.
Settle our beefs.
Beefs!
Please help me get vengeance
against all jet engines
And then I will go to hell
Didn't anybody finish
their business before dying?
All I want to do
is return this hatchet.
Fine.
Okay, I want you
to whack Johnny Tightlips,
ice Fat Tony and put a hit
on Joey Doublecross.
Who would've figured
he'd rat me out?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Next.
You can't keep ignoring me!
Doctor, shouldn't he have
woken up by now?
Yes, he should.
Unless someone's been
telling him bad things.
- What do you mean?
- Anything negative someone says
could do permanent damage
to his brain function.
It could even kill him.
But you said he'd be fine!
I said he'd be fine
if you told him
he was at
a dolphin encounter on Maui.
But those dolphins aren't fine!
They try to kill themselves!
I said he'd be fine,
not the dolphins.
Bart! Bart. I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I'll watch everything I say.
I had to walk
nine blocks to get this.
I am dead.
- Dad, no!
- Nine blocks.
I am dead.
Dead, dead.
Dead, dead, dead.
Finally, you get to me.
Yeah, yeah, what's your
unfinished business?
Revenge, against the man
who caused my death.
Hey, T-shirt, T-shirt, T-shirt!
Fire!
Ooh, a bobby pin!
You mean the guy
who invented the T-shirt guns?
- No.
- The guys who built the stadium
- with a really low back wall?
- No.
You, for standing up?
No, your father,
your stupid, stupid father!
You know, some people grow
when they die. Not you.
See you, guys.
That was fun, getting every
answer in Jeopardy! wrong.
All that saying good-bye
really made me thirsty.
Maude Flanders says hello.
Hello.
Let's move!
Oh, thank you, Bart.
I'm finally at peace.
You know, Ned remarried.
He what?!
Well, that's it.
All the ghosts have been helped.
Except one.
Dad, you weren't
supposed to die.
It was, it was just
supposed to scare you.
Oh, don't worry.
Patricide is just
a part of life.
Ooh, your vocabulary
really goes up when you die.
Dad, I am so sorry I killed you.
It's cool.
I feel no pain.
Ooh, I was wrong.
It feels worse than in life.
Get away, you stupid cat!
D'oh!
Oh, I can't believe you're dead.
But at least
I can still see you,
while I help you
with your unfinished business.
Well, I wanted
to lose some weight,
but I'm light as a feather now.
All that's left is for me
to go into the light.
You know how much
you hate walking.
Stay with me.
Stay with me, Bart.
Oh, Homie.
It's not your fault.
You were doomed when
they started putting cheese
into pizza crust.
What's next, plugging
Swiss cheese with cookie dough?
Peanut butter and hot dogs?
Why isn't anyone
writing these things down?
I can't watch this.
I'm gonna go check in on Moe's.
I don't know what's wrong.
I served them lager.
I should go, son.
I leave this world
without a care,
knowing I raised two great kids,
plus the one who murdered me.
No, Bart,
you have to stay with me!
No, Dad,
No, my time has come.
Man was not meant to live
beyond the age of 39.
You have to stay.
If you leave,
Mom will marry someone else.
I want her to be happy.
And someone else
will raise your kids!
Sucker.
And someone else
will ride your mower.
That bastard!
Still, it's time
for me to move on.
Oh, my God.
It's so beautiful!
Dad!
Why you little life-saving,
heaven can waiting...!
Bart, I'm so sorry
if I was ever mean to you,
because even though
you started it, you...
Sorry, sorry, I'm past that.
I love you,
and I want you back,
Bart Simpson.
Lisa?
He's awake!
- Thank God.
- Lisa?
Have you been by my side
this whole time?
I have.
Were you putting
those bad dreams in my head?
Yes.
- Can you teach me how to do it?
- I guess.
And can you help me
put Dad in a coma?
No.
Oh, man, this is great.
But how do I know
this isn't a dream too?
Because you're not
wearing the sweater.
Oh, yeah, of course.
Wait a minute.
How did he know
about the sweater?
Bart, did you see anything else
when you were under?
Just how we're all gonna die.
- Want me to tell you?
- Not really.
Well, I'm gonna tell you anyway.
Ouch
I have lost myself again
Lost myself
and I am nowhere...
I knew it was a sandwich.
Yeah...
Lost myself again
And I feel unsafe
Be my friend
Hold me
Wrap me up
Unfold me
I am small
I'm needy...
Oh, my God!
Now I realize, this has
all been a waste of time.
And breathe me
Be my friend
Hold me, wrap me up
Now I'm the evil king.
Unfold me
I am small
I'm needy
Warm me up
And breathe
Me