D'oh!
Hmm?
Number two.
Aw...
Oh, I thought we were
going to breakfast.
First we're
visiting Grampa.
No fair!
We just went to church!
Yeah, so we've already heard
stories
from thousands of years ago
about stuff that didn't happen.
Oh!
I have an important
announcement to make.
I've had a lot of time to think
since my hands got too shaky
to play cards. D'oh!
It's not your
fault, Grampa.
These cards are
too slippery. See?
Damn it!
Anywhen, I've decided to give
you all your inheritance now.
Are you sure about that, Grampa?
I just want to see
the look on your faces
when I share with you the fruits
of a lifetime of labor.
50 bucks each?!
That's your life savings?!
This won't even cover the vig
on what I owe!
Well, I lost the rest
investing in a Broadway musical
based on the real-life story
of Eddie Gaedel,
the midget who had one
big league at-bat.
I even wrote a song for American
League president Will Harridge!
♪ What do I do with this
damn little man? ♪
♪ His strike zone's the size
of a tuna fish can! ♪
of a tuna fish can ♪
Now remember what Grampa said:
you can spend the money
any way you want.
I just paid some
loser 50 bucks
to walk up the down escalator
all day.
I bet it's 11:00.
I bet it's 11:00!
Oh, 9:15?!
Hmm, I think I'll look
for a new handbag.
Ooh, so many celebrities have
their own label:
Princess Penelope, Booberella,
The Real Housewives of
Ogdenville, even Scratchy.
Oh... I wonder how much
that one is.
Gotta look without looking
like I'm looking.
Yes!
I'd like this bag, please.
Marge Simpson!
Are you buying a Marc Fredericks
signature handbag?
Why wouldn't I?
Well... those bags are
pretty pricey.
Hey, my husband makes
good money,
and we can
certainly afford...
That'll be $500.
Oh, I didn't realize...
What's the matter, Marge?
Just remembered
your husband's not a doctor?
Oh, my God,
you are so burned!
I'll take it!
Ooh!
Well done, Marge.
If you're looking for a bag hag,
I'm your man. Okay?
But stay on my good side,
girlfriend.
Or... uh-oh!
$500?!
That's, like,
ten dead Grampas!
Some of us stuck
to our limit, Marge.
And I would've loved to rent
this carpet cleaner another day!
Is that the cat
in there?!
Well, it's a cat.
I'm not sure it's the cat.
Don't worry, Homer,
I'll return the handbag
first thing tomorrow.
You know what, honey?
Just because we can't afford
to keep that handbag
doesn't mean that
you two can't have one night
at the most glamorous
place in town.
Right this way.
Well, at least it's a good place
to see celebrities.
It's not what
you think!
I'm researching a movie
where I play myself.
Wait a minute.
Is that bag Marc Fredericks?
Mm-hmm.
You know, a much nicer table
just opened up!
Hmm!
After Bart,
that bag's the best
mistake we ever made.
I'm gonna go, uh,
study the menu.
Heh.
So, I want to honor Grampa
by giving my inheritance
to charity.
But which one?
Ooh, what's this?
Most banks are for the haves,
not the have-nots.
I'm sorry, but we simply
can't accept your collateral.
I am just a goat,
but even I know that a peasant
in an emerging economy
can't get a break.
She needs a microloan.
A guilty first-worlder lends
$50 or more
to the Microloan Bank,
who uses it to help my owner
finance her business.
Working together,
we can help people
help themselves!
And now, apparently,
I am a girl.
Mmm...
Hmm.
Come on, Marge,
let's hit the buffet.
You go ahead; I'll stay here.
If I get something
on this handbag,
I won't be able to return it.
Oh, you don't want to
wait for that buffet.
Wiggum's making
his move!
I need backup, Lou.
Get two plates and follow me.
Uh, Chief, not now;
I'm undercover.
Oh, it's like
that, huh?
The minute you
go undercover,
you act like you
don't even know me!
He'll turn on you, too,
Fat Tony, you just wait!
Mm, I suppose I should
get something to eat.
Hey!
Waah...!
Oh, thank God!
I can take that for you.
Homer, take me home!
Sure, sure!
Let me just
grab one more shrimp.
Boy, I bet that looked cool
in super slow motion.
Too bad we saw it
in regular motion.
Yeah, I got bigger
problems, Chief.
I'm in love with
the don's daughter!
But which me
does she love?
I don't know.
Hmm...
Thank you so much
for clicking on me.
I am Muhammad Yunus,
founder of the Grameen Bank,
and, oh yeah, I'm also the
winner of the Nobel Peace Prize.
To find an entrepreneur you want
to lend to, click on my nose...
if you can catch it.
It's up here!
Now down here!
Too slow!
Okay, I'll hold still.
No, I won't.
Ha-ha!
Got it!
Good-bye!
Let's see, I could help someone
in any impoverished
area on Earth.
Bangladesh.
Bolivia.
East Springfield?
My name is Nelson Mandela Muntz.
Nelson?
And my dream is
to make and market
custom bicycles.
Nelson! My dream is
to make enough money
so's I can get the rest
of this tattoo removed.
Sorry I wasted your time.
No fool would take a chance
on a loser like me.
I will. I'll take a chance
on you, Nelson Muntz.
Nelson, I gotta take this
computer to the pawn shop,
so's we can get White Castle
for your birthday.
So, Nelson, I see
you started a small business.
Yeah.
Some anonymous dude
sent me 50 bucks.
Probably someone cool like
Famous Amos or Ba Ba Booey.
And I'm gonna justify
his faith in me.
Well, whoever your
mysterious donor is,
he, or she, really
wants you to succeed.
Ding-dong!
Ooh, your
first customer!
Be nice.
Right. Nice.
Good day, Mr. Barf-Breath.
Good day to you.
Let me be frank:
Everyone thinks you're a wuss.
So, we'll change
the pink to black,
elevate the seat--
trust me, it's slimming--
and change this wicker
basket to no basket.
Do you like it?
Oh, I love it!
Hmm!
Wow, my first job.
Tonight I'm having
peanut butter and jelly.
No more PB or J for me.
Stay cool, Marge.
Stay cool.
I'd like to return this handbag.
Unused.
I believe this stranger!
Well, here's your refund.
Check and mate.
Thank God!
I will never do that again.
Wait a minute, Marge.
Don't you realize
what just happened?
You got to enjoy that bag
for nothing!
We can buy stuff
we can't afford,
temporarily own
the hell out of it,
and then indignantly bring
it back for a full refund.
Hide a sandwich in this hat.
"Mary Poppins" myself to work
with this umbrella.
Homie, you know what happens
when you push your luck...
Yeah, the luck
lasts longer!
Thanks to the power of returns,
this store is our closet!
Ooh, a message
from my small business person!
Dear anonymous investor:
Here is my update
on my small business.
I'm making money fist over face!
Dingus!
Great timing!
Awesome!
No way I can look nerdy
on this bike.
♪ Hot cross buns,
hot cross buns ♪
♪ One a penny, two a penny ♪
♪ Hot cross buns ♪
And, with the money I'm making,
I can treat my mom
the way she deserves!
This place is so fancy, Nelson.
The ketchup packets
are made of glass.
Ma, please.
You're not at work.
Come in. Come in.
Don't wipe
your feet.
Whoa, look at
all this stuff!
Did you find a mouse
head in your Cuppa-Soup?
I wish.
What the hell are you doing?!
With this protective plastic
overlay, I can't tell
if I'm watching an old Seinfeld
or an old Old Christine.
Now, everyone
onto the hot tub.
Come on on.
The cardboard's fine.
Hi, Nelson.
Here again, huh, Lis?
I guess now
that I'm a success,
you want to get
back together with me.
Dolph called it.
No, but there is something
I can't hold back anymore.
I'm your microfinance donor!
You're L-Simpson-Jazzgirl?
Oh, my God.
I owe you everything.
Well, I didn't do this
for thanks,
but if you want
to thank me,
I can stand here and listen
for as long as it takes.
I'm sure
you can.
Lisa, if it weren't for you,
I never would have achieved
the kind of success
that has allowed me
to quit school.
You're quitting school?!
Dropping it like a melon
off an overpass.
But don't you know that people
who don't go to college
make three percent less
than people who do?
Lisa, thanks to you,
and Nobel laureate
Mohammad Yunus,
I can do... this!
Spelling, meet F-Y-R-E.
Principal Skinner,
I need to convince Nelson
to come back to school.
Seriously? Why?
With Nelson gone,
lunch money's finally making
its way to the cafeteria.
Nurples are returning to
their natural, non-purple hue.
Besides, I hear he's doing quite
well with his bicycle pimpery.
He is. He's paying people
$11 an hour to work for him.
$11 an hour?
That's night watchman money.
Maybe I should have
a chat with him.
Which of these ties
says confidence?
Isn't that a Christmas tie?
It's a conversation starter!
Lisa, this conversation is over.
It's not you I'm trying
to impress, it's Nelson.
I know
he likes the sleeveless look.
Skinner!
Oh. Oh, so you also heard
about the, uh, $11 an hour.
I heard about it first.
Yes, well, you see
the thing about that is... Blah!
Good afternoon.
I'd like to return
this merchandise.
"Wrong size, wrong color,
not asictured,
and other reason
please explain."
Sir, this suitcase has
an airline tag on it,
these ping-pong balls have
been served and volleyed,
and this hot
plate's still warm.
Yes, uh... maybe
I'll just come back
during someone else's shift.
Is Claire working today?
She's a real sucker.
Let me get my supervisor.
Hello, Homer.
How do you know my name?
I'm Chris Hansen
from To Catch a Credit-Whore.
We know you've been returning
used items all over town.
Oh, it's not what you think...
I came here to warn them-- yes,
to-to warn them about, um...
People like you?
Yes! I mean no! I mean...
You'll never get me!
I have to sign a release so
you can broadcast this, right?
Initial there,
and... Never!
Can you tell me when
this is gonna be on?
I'm thinking
of having a party.
Lisa, why did you
bring me here?
Oh, I don't know.
I thought one
of these super-successful people
might tell you how important
it is to stay in school.
Why, look. It's Mark Zuckerberg,
the founder of Facebook!
Mr. Zuckerberg, I'm Lisa,
and this is Nelson.
S'up, Zuck?
"Mark Zuckerberg is...
happy to meet new friends."
That's great,
Mr. Zuckerberg,
but I was hoping
you could tell us
how education was
instrumental to your success.
Well, the truth is...
I dropped out of Harvard.
You did?
Better earnin' than learnin'!
Hell, yeah! I'll get
the best kind of degree--
honorary, baby!
Well, clearly,
you're an exception.
Am I, Lisa?
Bill Gates-- dropout.
Virgin Airlines'
Richard Branson-- dropout.
Well... didn't anybody here stay
in school?
I did. Graduated
magna cum lade.
There, you see?
I'm afraid
I haven't done
too well for myself.
But I can certainly appreciate
the irony of it.
So, how did everyone do
with their $50?
Well, I learned
a valuable lesson
about wanting more
than I could afford.
Marge, you couldn't have fun
if you were a monkey
on a banana boat!
I used Grampa's money
to try to help someone in need,
but it didn't go the way
I expected.
Aw, sweetie, money
can't change people.
It can just help them
be who they are.
I gave a bum a dollar once,
and he used it to buy
an Ellery Queen mystery.
But there was one mystery
Ellery Queen couldn't solve--
why a man was named Ellery.
But my point is,
whatever I said before I started
talking about Ellery Queen.
Nelson, I just wanted to say
that I realize now
you can't be anyone else other
than who you are, and... Huh?
Look, everyone,
just chill out!
My Wizard of Oz bike
fell apart
in the middle
of the Pride parade!
What kind of pride?
Never you mind what kind!
Fix my bike!
I want my money back!
Fine. Here's exactly
what you paid me.
Thank you!
Oh! Why is this happening?
Uh, this epoxy you've been using
is water soluble,
which means it's not
weather-resistant.
Dumb it down for me.
Um... bike... sticky...
water go bye-bye?
Some sticky water stay-stay?
All bye-bye.
Oh!
Hi, Nelson.
Lisa, I've been
thinking and...
It fell apart when I was trying
to impress this cute girl.
My gramma!
Maybe I could use a
little more school.
You can't
break us up.
We're like a
family here.
Kearney and I are
having brunch on Sunday.
If I'm up.
Listen, what say
we go back to the school?
I'll help you out with a little
micro-financing of my own.
$50! I can buy paint
for the art class,
instead of those crushed-up
berries I find in the woods.
And Lisa, I've got a little left
that I'd like to spend on you.
This is really fun.
But we're still just
friends, right?
Right. Friends.
Can I hold your hand...
for balance?
Sure... for balance.
Haw-haw!
Sorry.
Oh!
Whoa! Oh!
"Mark Zuckerberg is..."
- Haw-haw!
- Sorry.