♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
(grunting and chattering)
(excited chattering)
♪♪ ("Also Sprach
Zarathustra")
Ooh!
(snoring)
(hooting like an ape)
-(phone ringing)
-(hooting like an ape)
Ooh, ooh, ooh--
Yello?
Dad, I'm calling about
the school talent show...
Don't worry.
I know it's tonight.
No. Dad, I broke my last
saxophone reed,
and I need you to
get me a new one.
Isn't this the kind of thing
your mother's better at?
I called her.
She's not home.
I also tried Mr. Flanders,
Aunt Patty, Aunt Selma,
Doctor Hibbert,
Reverend Lovejoy,
and that nice man who caught
the snake in our basement.
Wow. And after them
out of all the people
in the world,
you chose me.
Uh-huh. Yeah.
Number 4 1/2 reed. Got it.
Well, you're in for
a whale of a show tonight.
I'd like to point out that
the doors are now locked,
so you parents can't
sneak out of the show
after your own child
has performed.
Oh, and let me
caution the people
in the first five rows--
you will get wet.
(panting)
Just in the nick of--
Mmm. Beer.
(smacking lips)
Hurry. Moe, hurry.
I've only got five minutes
till the music store closes.
Well why don't you
go there first?
Hey, do I tell you
how to do your job?
Sorry, Homer.
You know,
if you tip the glass,
there won't be so much
foam on top.
Sorry, Homer.
♪♪ ("Sabre Dance")
(feeble applause)
This is a whole lot
of nothing.
I'd rather be watchin'
the boilers.
Make sure you return those
chairs to the cafeteria, Kim.
I'm not kidding.
Ah... finished,
with 15 seconds to spare.
(whistling)
Ah!
D-ohhh! D-ohhh!
What's the matter, buddy?
The moron next door
closed early.
I happen to be that moron.
Oh, me and my
trenchant mouth!
(spooning sounds to
"Sweet Georgia Brown")
Oh, terrible,
just terrible.
You know, they seem to
get worse every year.
(laughs)
Wonderful!
You know, I think this is
the best batch we've ever had.
I really do.
And now, here's Bart Simpson,
the boy of
a thousand voices.
I'd like to open
with my impression of...
Principal Skinner.
(dopey voice)
Duh, look at me.
I'm Principal Skinner.
(kids cheering)
That young man
just became
the boy of a thousand days
detention.
Hey, it's Lunch Lady Doris.
I wonder what she's
got for us today.
(nasal voice)
Today's special is refried
dog poop.
(chuckling)
(kids cheering)
Please! You've got
to open that store.
Let me think about it.
Uh... no.
Okay, okay, but I want
you to see a picture
of the little girl
you're disappointing.
Well, I don't have one.
Come on, Jer.
Open up. Be a pal.
Remember when I pulled you
and your wife out of that burning car?
Okay, okay,
but now we're even.
What does your daughter need?
I'll have you know
I wrote it down.
"Number--
number 4 1/2..."
Stupid gum!
"Number 4 1/2 reed."
Whoo-hoo!
Mm-hmm. And, what instrument
does she play?
I don't know.
♪♪ ("Cancan")
Mom, where is he?
If I don't get that reed,
I'll sound terrible.
Don't worry, honey.
I'm sure your father is...
(thinking)
maybe...
No.
That's a long shot.
Bingo.
Don't worry.
He'll be here.
-Clarinet? Oboe?
-No.
-Saxophone?
Wait a minute.
What was that last one again?
-Saxophone.
-Hmm...
Lisa, stop playing
that stupid...
saxophone!
Yes, that's it!
-Alto or tenor?
-D-ohhh!
♪ My ding-a-ling ♪
♪ I want you to play
with my ding-a-ling ♪
This act is over!
Well, ladies and gentlemen,
I'd like to put this filth
behind us
and let's all enjoy
Lisa Simpson's rendition
of "Stormy Leather."
Uh, "Weather."
(applause)
(playing off-key)
(murmuring)
Ha, ha!
Sounds like that gopher
I caught in me lawn mower.
Ew, I'd hate to be
that kid's father.
(gasping)
Uh-oh.
-That will do.
-It's not my fault.
It's the reed.
Oh, yes, of course.
Let's hear it
for Lisa Simpson
and her wacky sax.
HOMER: Yeah!
Whoo!
Whoo, yeah...
(groaning)
Okay, who ordered
a Mount Bellyache?
I ordered it
for my little girl. Heh heh.
I'm done.
Oh! That cost $88!
I'm sorry, Dad.
I don't feel much like eating.
Look, I let you down
and I apologize.
I know that
doesn't make it right.
But I hope you can
find it in your heart
-to forgive me.
-I forgive you.
D'oh!
You didn't mean that.
-No, I didn't.
-(sighs)
(cooing)
MARGE: Look, Homer.
Lisa's taking
her first steps.
-You're taping it?
-Yes.
I'll watch it later.
The plane,
the plane!
No, my freakish little friend.
That's a seagull.
Hmm.
Da-da.
MARGE:
Did you hear that, Homer?
Marge, please--
I'm busy.
No wonder she hates me.
Oh, I never even noticed
she was alive.
Homer, if you want
to make up with Lisa
just spend some
time with her.
Ohh! Okay!
(sipping noise)
(boys laughing)
Aah!
(grunting)
(thud)
Maybe I should just
cut my losses, give up on Lisa,
and make a fresh start
with Maggie.
Homie, you've got to
stop looking for the quick fix.
If you keep spending time
with Lisa, she'll forgive you.
Marge, if I spend any more time
doing these girl things,
I'm gonna, you know,
go fruity.
No, you were right
the first time
with that quick fix idea.
Let's see--
quick fix, quick fix.
Ahh. I'll buy her that pony
she's always bugging me for.
We can't afford
to buy a pony.
Marge, with today's
gasoline prices,
we can't
afford not to buy a pony.
That's ridiculous.
Marge, I've gotta
get her a pony.
When I look in Lisa's eyes,
I don't see love anymore.
That's no reason
to buy a pony.
See, even when you yell at me,
I can see love in your eyes.
Stick to the subject.
(singsongy)
Ha, ha, you love me.
(groans)
Let's be realistic.
A pony is very expensive,
and we have enough trouble
paying bills as it is.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You sound like you're
going to buy a pony.
-Promise me you won't.
-Hmm.
What was that?
Was that a yes or a no?
-Baa.
-Those aren't even words.
-Sna.
-(groans)
Oh, my, what is that smell?
Oh, it's you.
Excuse me.
Do you sell ponies?
Uh, sure, pal.
Right here.
"Scottish Deer Hound."
Hey, this is a dog.
Ooh, my friend, you're smarter
than I gave you credit for.
I suggest you try
the Boney Farm on Route 401.
Merely take a left
at the rendering plant.
Now, lady, I'm buying a pony
for my little girl,
and I don't care
what it costs.
Very good.
That stunning creature
over there
is half a million dollars.
Half a million dollars?!
He was sired by Seattle Slew,
-and his mother won the Kentucky Derby.
-HOMER: Wow.
His likeness
graces a stamp in Tanzania.
-I'll take it!
-Mr. Simpson...
do you have
half a million dollars?
Uh, sure, let me
write you a check.
Hmm.
Mr. Simpson,
this check is dated
January 1, 2054.
Is there a problem
with that?
Our ponies start
at $5,000... cash.
Isn't there like a pound
where you can pick up
cheap ponies
that ran away from home?
I sincerely hope not.
I-- I'd like
to borrow $5,000.
Sorry.
I can't approve
a loan that size myself.
(rings bell)
-Hello.
-(scream)
"Simpson," eh?
How can I help you?
Mr. Burns,
you do this personally?
It's a hobby.
I'm not in this for any
personal gain. Heavens no.
By the way, are you
acquainted with
our state's
stringent usury laws?
-Usury?
-Oh, silly me.
I must've just made up
a word that doesn't exist.
Now, what is the purpose
of this loan?
I want to buy a pony.
Isn't that cute?
Smithers, he's planning
on joining the horsey set.
That is it, isn't it?
You're not planning to eat it?
No I need to get it
for my little girl because
she doesn't love me anymore.
-Shut up, Simpson.
-Sorry.
You have any collateral?
Oh, Smithers,
let's not be so cold.
His spirit
is my collateral.
Just sign this form
and the money will be yours.
(diabolical laughter)
Sorry, I was just thinking
of something funny
Smithers did today.
I didn't do anything
funny, sir.
Shut up.
Mr. Simpson,
are you quite sure you know
how to take care of a pony?
Of course.
Simpson, you've done it again.
(screaming)
I love you, Dad!
(groans)
I am very upset with you.
Sounds like someone's
angling
for a pony of her own.
(gasping)
Hey, how come Lisa
gets a pony?
Because she
stopped loving me.
I don't love ya' either,
so gimme a moped.
I know you love me,
so you don't get squat.
Snowball II,
Santa's Little Helper--
this is Princess.
Please don't exclude her
because she's different.
Homer, just where were you
planning to keep this horse?
I've got it
all figured out.
By day, it will roam free
around the neighborhood,
and at night,
it will nestle snugly
between the cars
in our garage.
-Dad, no!
-That's illegal.
That's for the courts
to decide.
Marge, she loves me.
Dad, I think Princess
belongs in a stable.
Stable?
That sounds expensive.
This is what love costs
a month?
These are standard
stable fees, Mr. Simpson.
Plus, I'm teaching your daughter
riding, grooming,
and at no extra charge,
pronunciation.
(with British accent)
Father, you've made me
the happiest girl
who ever lived.
Oh, nuts.
GRANDPA: What do I do?
What do I do?
Grandpa, if you want
to go right,
move the joy stick to the left.
Yes. Move the--
What's a joy stick?
You didn't tell me--
Here comes a Xylon cruiser!
Woah, woah woah!
Go into hyperspace!
Ready, hit it!
Wait!
Where's the hyperspace?
Grandpa, you're the spaceship,
not the--
I'm the what?
I thought I was this guy.
Oh!
Game's over, Grandpa.
I got down on the floor
for this?!
Wait, Dad.
I've got something for you.
I was hoping
it would be money.
Oh, dear. We're
in serious trouble here.
We're just going to have
to cut down on luxuries.
Well, you know we're always
buying Maggie vaccinations
for diseases
she doesn't even have.
Actually, I was thinking
we could cut down on beer.
Nah, we're not going
to be doing that.
Then I'm afraid
there's no choice
but to give up the pony.
First you didn't
want me to get the pony.
Now you want me
to take it back.
Make up your mind.
Homer!
Marge, Lisa loves me.
The pony stays.
Alright. You got us
into this.
-You get us out.
-Fine, I will.
There's plenty of money
out there
for a guy who's
willing to work for it.
Do you have any jewelry
you don't need anymore?
(groans)
You're so beautiful.
Oh, look, you haven't
touched your salt lick.
Num-num.
Good salt lick.
HOMER:
Need money. Need money.
One scratch-for-cash, please.
Here you go.
Liberty bell.
(gasps)
Two liberty bells.
Come on,
come on, come on...
Oh.
Yes!
Whoo-whoo!
Three liberty bells!
That will be
$10,000, Apu.
Congratulations,
Mr. Homer.
Thank you.
If I could just see
the ticket...
There it is.
Please to be removing
your thumb.
No.
Yes, please.
I must insist.
No. No.
-You can't see--
-Yes, I must--
No! Let go!
You're ripping it.
(gasps)
A cherry.
Oh, Mr. Homer,
what has reduced you
to such cheap chicanery?
Oh... I need money.
Well, if you need money,
you should have at least
jammed a gun in my ribs,
or better yet,
you could inquire
about my help wanted sign.
You're looking for help?
Yes, we need someone
for the demanding
yet high profile
midnight to 8:00 a.m. shift.
I'm your man.
-You're hired.
-Whoo-hoo!
Always I dreamed the day
would come
when one of you would
be working for me.
-(clapping)
-So pretty.
She certainly tamed
that horse.
Yes, but what man
can tame her?
APU: I won't lie to you.
On this job,
you will be shot at.
Each of these bullet wounds
is a badge of honor.
"Badge of honor..."
Here's a pointer.
Try to take it
in the shoulder.
Now, these hot dogs have been
here for three years.
They are strictly ornamental.
There is only one bozo
who comes in and buys them.
But I eat-- Oh.
(Homer yawning)
The perfect crime.
Homer, where have you been
all night?
I was so worried.
Marge, can we go
in the other room?
I did something last night
I'm not proud of,
and I don't want
the kids to hear it.
Busted.
I'll work
midnight to 8:00,
come home,
sleep for five minutes,
eat breakfast,
sleep six more minutes, shower.
Then I have ten minutes
to bask in Lisa's love
then off to the power plant
fresh as a daisy.
(thud)
Oh, my God,
she killed him.
(snoring)
Mmm. Salty.
Homer!
Are you stealing Squishies?
No, sir.
This next song is also
about a girl and her pony.
It's called "Wildfire."
♪♪
WOMAN: Come on, Apu, honey,
loosen up.
APU: Ohh!
I'm sorry, baby.
While I'm here
pleasuring you,
-my store is going down the tubes.
-(sighs)
(snoring)
Three dollars and 51, 52, 53 cents.
(chuckles)
Homer, you are asleep
at your post!
Now go change
the expiration dates
on the dairy products.
Yes, sir.
Sorry, baby.
Date's over.
-(thud)
-(gasps)
(snoring)
♪♪ (soothing)
(alarm rings)
Homie, how long do you
plan to do this?
I don't know.
How long
do horses live?
30 years.
D-ohhh.
HOMER: Mustn't sleep.
Must monitor core.
(snoring)
(phone ringing)
Yello?
I just called
to say I love you, Dad.
Thanks.
When is she going
to stop loving me?
(snoring)
I just heard Milli Vanilli
was arrested
for impersonating
a McNugget.
Well, it's still fun
to be up late.
Hey, Homer,
where you going?
Going for...
eight-hour walk.
-(car horn blares)
-(snoring)
Homer. Homer?
Homer sleep now.
What's wrong with Dad?
He's just exhausted.
Lisa, do you know how much
it costs to keep a pony?
-No.
-Well, it's a lot.
In fact, your father had
to take a second job.
The poor guy.
Where's he working?
The Kwik-E Mart.
(laughing)
Lisa, I hope
you realize
that your father
can't keep this up.
You're gonna make me
give up Princess?
Lisa, we can't make you
give up that pony.
I can make her.
Just give me five minutes
alone with her.
No, Bart.
No one's going to make her.
This is something Lisa
has to decide for herself.
All the years I've lobbied
to be treated like an adult
have blown up in my face.
Hey! (whistles)
Pink hat!
When I ordered
that blueberry squishy
I meant today.
Coming right up, sir.
And fill it to the top
this time.
Yes, sir.
(sighs)
She likes a little carrot
after her oats,
and she really likes it
when you scratch her
behind the ear.
And if you're playing the radio,
she likes contemporary
adult in the morning
and easy listening at night.
Please take good care
of my Princess.
Although there is no change
in my patrician facade,
I can assure you
my heart is breaking.
I'll never forget you.
What the--?
You call this melted cheese
receptacle clean?
The young man you replaced
is rolling over in his grave.
Dad, you don't have
to do this.
Yes, I do.
You see, Lisa,
grown-ups have
a thing called money...
Dad, I understand the sacrifice
you've made for me.
That's why
I gave up the pony.
-You did?
-Mm-hm.
There's
a big dumb animal
I love even more
than that horse.
Oh, no, what is it,
a hippopotamus?
I mean you, you dummy.
Aw.
Apu, you can take this job
and restaff it.
(laughing)
Giddy-up, Dad!
(whinnies)
He slept, he stole,
he was rude
to the customers.
Still, there goes
the best damned employee
a convenience store ever had.
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.