(eerie music plays)
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
(grunts)
Hmm? (gasps)
(clattering, Homer groaning)
-(bell ringing)
-Whoa!
(all groaning)
(ringing continues,
Homer groaning)
♪♪
Oh, I love going
to aquatic parks.
Sure, they have worse rides
than amusement parks,
less fish than aquariums--
but the parking is ample!
(Marge humming)
Now to seal you
in for safety.
Oh, there's so many photo ops,
but I already filled up
my camera in the parking lot.
Parking lot C sign, the tram,
a license plate from Canada,
a bird eating potato chips,
my feet walking,
that boy who got sick
on the tram,
Grampa talking
to a mermaid hedge,
the park rules in Spanish,
a fat baby,
Grampa telling a story
to a trailer hitch.
-(ding)
-Oops! I erased them all!
I want to do that!
(mechanical whirring)
(gasping)
I'm going to take stuff
from the lost and found!
(humming)
(chuckles)
(people screaming)
My feet hurt!
My left ear's freezing!
My right ear's burning!
I got fish smell in my wrinkles!
(grunts)
ANNOUNCER:
Attention, exploro-nauts!
That's us!
In one minute,
we'll be starting
our rock-quatic roll-tacular!
Hurry! If we don't get a seat
in the splash zone,
I've worn my bathing suit
under my clothes for nothing!
GRAMPA:
A splash-'em-up show?
Reminds me of the time
I high-dived into a damp sponge
for the amusement of Federal
Reserve Chairman Paul Volcker.
Grampa, no stories!
You can come with us,
or sit here on the shark bench.
You know, I did sit
on a shark once...
Dad, bathing suit!
(grunts)
Oops! No bathing suit.
♪♪
Let's give a wet
and wacky welcome
to Springfield's oldest
performing mollusk...
Get to the show!
This is the show!
Here's the original Octomom:
Slimu!
♪ Whoa! ♪
♪ I feel good ♪
(applause, cheering)
♪ I knew that I would... ♪
Slimu! Did you get my letters?
Slimu wasn't expecting company,
so he's got some
cleaning up to do!
♪ ...I wouldn't now ♪
♪ So good ♪
(muffled laughter)
Slimu looks kind of
uncomfortable.
Wouldn't you be if you
were a saltwater fish
in a freshwater aquarium?
The country has its first
black president.
Maybe it's time
for the first octopus president!
("Hail to the Chief" playing)
And when it comes
to signing bills,
he can provide his own ink!
Ahh, oily!
(cheering and applause)
They'll cheer a dancing octopus,
but not an old man
complaining about everything.
Excuse me, sir.
Is this seat taken?
Well, not for a pretty girl
like you!
(chuckles nervously)
Well, this is the first time
I ever sat on a shark.
Not me-- sat on
a real one once!
-Tell me more!
-More?!
(gasps)
Play it cool, Grampa.
Play it cool!
It was back in World War II.
I was a Seaman First Class
on the USS World War I.
We were minding
our own business
when we were attacked
by a heat-seeking torpedo
we had fired the day before.
(explosion)
(men screaming)
(gasps)
Don't worry about
the sharks, boys.
Just play possum
and they'll leave you alone.
GRAMPA: Unfortunatley,
sharks love possum.
Hey, boys, these sharks can't
bite us if we're on their backs!
(grunts)
Yeah.
It's like riding the Cyclone
back at Coney Island!
Whoa!
It's like riding a dust devil
back in Yuma--
like I read about in a book
back in Boston!
GRAMPA: By the time
the rescue planes came,
we had those sharks
trained pretty good.
♪♪
I still keep in touch
with all those men
and some of the sharks.
Why, here's us
in Hawaii last year.
Good times.
Sir, my name is
Marshall Goldman.
I'm a newspaper columnist
specializing in human
interest stories.
You're in the newspaper
business?
(chuckles)
Something that's gonna die
before I do!
You have any other stories
you'd care to tell me?
Someone's listening to me!
Now I know how a radio feels!
(school bell ringing)
Well, class, it's
Friday afternoon.
That means it's time to find out
which one of you gets
to take Larry the Lamb
home for the weekend.
-(all sigh)
-Oh! Oh! Oh!
And don't forget,
the lucky student gets
to add his or her page
to Larry's personal journal.
Just like Martin did last week.
Ha!
-I want him first!
-No, me!
Oh, not that stupid
stuffed lamb again.
This isn't learning!
Do you want to learn?
No, no, no. I'm just saying...
This weekend,
Larry will go home with...
(all gasp)
Please, God, I need this.
...Bart Simpson.
(all groan)
Oh, cruel irony!
Hey, the only thing I bring home
are notes to my parents,
and those do not arrive
the way that they left.
Hmm.
Oh, what a nice note!
I'm not sticking my hand
in that can again.
You're getting the lamb.
Not so fast.
Tell the diary how special
he makes you feel!
More adjectives!
That's an adverb!
(grunts)
(sizzling)
Top of the morning,
Homer.
Seen the paper?
No, I get my news
off the Internet.
(laughing)
Well, sir, it looks like
your dad is a quotable notable.
Huh?
That's a... It's funny.
It's poignant...
It actually happened!
My father is interesting?!
The whole world's upside down!
That must mean Cathy is funny.
Nope.
Abe, I never knew
you were so full of...
-(speaking Yiddish)
-What does that mean?
It's like
(speaking Yiddish),
but with a pinch more
(speaking Yiddish)
Yep, I may just be
the best known Abraham
in history.
So, Abe, what else
you got for me?
Hmm, well, let's see.
Ooh, I was working
as a shoeshine boy
at Springfield Union Station.
♪♪
Every Monday, the
Tinseltown Starliner would stop
at 1:17 p.m. on its way
to Hollywood.
I never rode that train,
but I'd palaver
with the movie stars
when they got out
to stretch their legs.
Hiya!
(clicking)
But none was more
memorable than...
Clark Gable!
Looks like someone
has seen my work
as an extra in Du Barry,
Woman Of Passion.
I sure have, Mr. Gable.
How come you ain't
a star yet?
Maybe my ears are too big.
I don't know.
(laughs)
-Hey, what you
reading there?
-Oh, it's called
Gone with the Wind.
You can have it.
It's only got one swear word,
and not a very good one.
Gone with the Wind, eh?
Well, let's see:
garbage, garbage, my line.
Garbage, garbage, my line.
Atlanta burns, nice dresses.
I like it!
Thanks, kid.
Don't tell this story
to anyone for 60 years.
(train whistle blowing)
"Clark Gable owes me a book.
And he never paid me
for the shoeshine.
But his big blue eyes
could melt the butter
you kept in your pocket
for lunch.
Lunch butter we called it."
How come Grampa never shared
those stories with us?
He does all the time.
You just never listen.
Marge, my brain is
like a computer,
and I file away Grampa's stories
in a very special place.
(clicking)
(crunching)
Hmm, while I'm up there.
(clicking)
(crunching)
(dings)
(chuckles)
(beeps)
Uh-oh.
(dog barking)
-(growling)
-That's it, boy!
Go for the nards!
Bart!
If you're not gonna
take care of him right,
then give him to me.
How come you don't get mad
when I torment real animals?
I do! It enrages me!
I thought you Hindus were
supposed to love everybody.
I'm a freaking
Buddhist!
A Buddhist!
Larry, please don't judge
our whole family by Bart.
He's the black sheep.
I mean, not that black sheep
are in any way inferior
to white sheep.
I do not judge wool
by its color--
only by how itchy it is.
(chuckles)
Ooh, look!
Jazz!
Larry, what sub-genre
of jazz do you like?
Fusion? Neo-bop?
Afro-Cuban?
(gasps)
Larry!
Gotcha! (screams)
(water splashing)
Larry? Oh, Larry?
Larry?
Larry?!
You're coming off
desperate, honey.
That's how I got my idea
for a suitcase with wheels,
from watching a commercial
about a suitcase with wheels.
(all sigh)
Hey, Abe,
great stories.
I'm Mitch Albom,
author of Tuesdays with Morrie.
Never heard of you.
Yeah. Sure you haven't.
Take a hike, Hollywood.
I've already got
a college boy
to turn my every word
into syndicated gold.
Yeah, beat it, sports page.
And what if I don't?
(grumbling)
(groans)
Clouds are God's sneezes.
Ooh, I like this kid.
(humming)
Oh, Dad, I got you some Scotch.
One of those fancy ones
the checkout lady had
to unlock the cabinet to get.
Well, well, well,
look who decided to visit me
twice in one year.
This man's more of a son to me
than you've ever been.
What the...?!
Well, he's more of a father
to me than you've ever been!
I don't think that's true.
Stay out of this, Dad.
Uh, no. O-Okay.
You only care about me now
because I'm famous.
That's it.
Here's your ring back.
Ring? What ring?
It's a father-son
commitment band
that I bought
and never told you about.
(sobbing)
And now
I'm telling you.
Okay, I need
the stupid lamb back.
He's in here,
safe and sound.
Let me just staple
that bag for you.
(panting)
Hmm.
This isn't Larry.
It's just cotton balls
on toilet paper rolls.
Where's the real Larry?
Well, what do you care?
You don't even like him.
Of course I don't,
but other people do.
Hey, Bart, can't wait
to see Larry again.
Um, what if someone
were to lose Larry?
They'd see a dark side of me
no one knows about.
♪ Nelson loved a little lamb ♪
♪ Little lamb, little lamb ♪
♪ He kept me nice and sane. ♪
(beep)
ABE:
You've reached Abe.
MARSHALL:
And Marshall.
Abe can't come
to the phone right now.
ABE:
And if this is Homer,
you're too late for my love.
(beep)
Stupid Grampa.
I try to end the
cycle of neglect,
and he hits me with
some super neglect.
Maybe you're not
really mad at Grampa.
Maybe you're mad
at yourself
for taking him for granted
all these years.
Marge, how can anyone
be mad at himself?
It's impossible. Watch.
Why, you little...
(gasps)
Oh, I can't.
When I look at those beautiful
chubby cheeks.
Come here, you.
Ow!
Ow! I'll kill you,
you son of a ...!
Oh. No, no,
don't-don't look hurt.
Okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
I'll show Grampa.
I'll find my own
surrogate father
full of heartwarming stories
I can share with the world.
And that's how you win
an opium war.
Oh, great stuff.
And the life lesson is?
The Yangtze River swallows
all secrets.
Hmm.
I'm just gonna put
"Haste makes waste."
Yes, although, these days, I can
make neither haste nor waste.
You know, Simpson,
this has truly been
a lovely afternoon.
Release... a hound.
Isn't that cute?
He thinks he's a pack.
-(barking)
-(yells)
Where'd you get
this rope?
Swiped it
from gym class.
Climb that rope!
There is no rope.
Well, you better get
to the ceiling somehow!
(panting)
-Ceiling, ceiling, ceiling!
-(grunts)
(groaning)
Bart, I'm losing my grip.
Put the rope in your teeth.
What will that do?
It'll shut you up.
(grunts)
Hmm.
Larry?
Larry the Lamb?
There you are,
you piece of crap.
-(growling)
-(yells)
There's rats
in my pants!
Chief, my brother fell
in the storm drain!
Um, I'm strictly an
above-the-ground policeman.
What you need is
the sewer cops.
Fine. What's their number?
Lisa, you're old enough now
that I can tell you
the truth.
There's no such thing
as the sewer cops.
It's just something we tell kids
to make them feel safe.
What about Bart?
Well, if you miss him,
yell into a toilet.
BART (echoing):
It's dark down here!
I have a column
I'd like to submit.
Pay me whenever.
I'll just take this
to our editor.
(shredder whirring)
Hmm.
What?
Pulitzer Prize application form?
"When I rode with Abe Simpson
on the Tinseltown Starliner,
I never dreamed his first
voyage would be his last?
At 3:00 on Monday,
Abe passed away peacefully
in his sleep."
How would he know
Grampa was going to die today?
Unless he was going to kill him!
But would someone
really kill a man
just to win a Pulitzer Prize?
(music plays dramatic sting)
(gasps)
All aboard the final run
of the Tinseltown Starliner,
the last ride
into a nostalgic past.
Anyone without a ticket
will be beaten
by classic railroad bulls.
♪ Old Dan Tucker
was a fine old man ♪
ALL:
♪ He washed his face
in the frying pan ♪
♪ He combed his hair
with a wagon wheel ♪
♪ And died of the toothache
in his heel. ♪
You don't get a beatin'
like this traveling by plane.
Ow!
I'm finally riding
the Tinseltown Starliner.
I could die a happy man.
(grunts)
(panting)
D'oh!
Drink up, Abe.
Live each moment as if
someone's about to kill you.
I mean,
as if it's your last.
Sorry, my hearing aid's
on the fritz.
The only word
I heard was "kill."
(Homer whimpering)
Hey. Aah.
Look at that.
They've recreated the '30s.
Tent cities,
failing banks.
No, those are real.
(mutters)
(whimpering)
Oh!
HOMER:
Beware of Marshall Goldman!
What was that?
Um, an elephant
on a circus train
bellowing for
his mother.
Oh, I remember the first time
an elephant tried to eat me
like a peanut.
I was on the set
of a Warner Brothers cartoon.
Jack Warner came by
and said...
(whimpering)
Hey, Slimu!
(yelling)
Huh?
(laughs)
Yeah, you'd better run!
-(loud mewing)
-(gasps)
Sewer cats!
(yells)
(whimpering)
Larry?!
(grunting)
(yowling)
Larry, you saved my life!
You're the most wonderful
stuffed lamb in the world.
I'm sorry
about the mean things I said,
and we'll have the rest
of the weekend to...
Whoa!
(grunts)
Huh?
Larry!
(sobbing)
Man, everybody
loves this guy.
Give him my number.
I'll teach him things.
Things he can use.
(train whistle blows)
The older I get,
the more I like the taste
of hot water.
(snoring)
(to "Here Comes the Bride")
♪ Here comes the prize ♪
♪ Pulitzer Prize ♪
♪ I'll finally be successful
in my mother's eyes. ♪
A little lower...
A little lower.
Drop that pillow!
(yells)
It gets worse.
-Ow!
-Yeah.
(grunts)
See you tomorrow at yoga.
Jane is sick, so
Tricia's filling in.
As long as it's not a dude!
(both grunting)
(choking)
How can you stand up
to this punishment?
I'm the toughest
S.O.B. there is--
a biweekly human
interest columnist.
And your father's
gonna make me a fortune.
Pathetic old fool.
Maybe so, but I know
how to play possum.
-(grunts)
-Um...
(laughs)
(brakes squealing)
(groans)
So many hat boxes.
Dad, I don't have
the right words
to say how I really feel
about you,
but at least I know
how to beat up a guy who does.
Well, at least
you never tried to kill me.
Just with indifference.
You did good, kid.
This is for the shoeshine.
It's a ghost quarter,
but you'll be able
to spend it pretty soon.
So, Grampa,
you really saved Dad's life?
I sure did.
But why don't we let Homer
tell the story?
Really? Me? You mean it?
I think you're ready
for your first ramble.
Oh, I've been waiting
for this day for so long.
The year is 1946.
In a war-torn world,
a single flower blooms.
And that flower is an angry
Japanese monster named Godzilla.
How am I doing, Dad?
I'm hanging
on every word.
Fortunately, there was
one man who could help--
Colonel Tom Parker.
The Colonel took this monster,
cleaned him up
and put him onstage
under the name
The Rolling Stones.
The first concert was a sellout
with many, many,
many people eaten.
But those that survived raved
about the undeniable harmonies
and brutally honest lyrics
of what they had just seen.
And out of the wreckage
of that concert,
crawled a woman, who would
later give birth to me.
Not once but four times.
'Cause in those days,
if they didn't like
the way you looked,
they would send you back in
to bake a little longer.
After four times, they just
decided to cut off my tail.
But you can still see it...
in the British Museum,
which, interestingly enough,
is in France.
Not the France
you're thinking of.
But a much better one,
filled with palm trees
and leprechauns.
But I digress.
In fact, I used to be
a professional digressor.
But I don't want
to get off the tracks
so I'll tell you
about the time I was
a professional digressor.
The year was 2021,
and I had just returned
from a brief vacation...
where I'd eaten more
than my fill of tacos.
Not the tacos
you're thinking of.
Did I ever tell you
about the time
I started Gracie Films?
Shh!
HOMER:
Hey, shh yourself!
Enhanced by Fotokem