♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
D'oh.
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
(playing classical music)
(glass clinking)
My friends,
tonight, we unveil my most
diabolical creation--
Swank.
Ten times more addictive
than marijuana.
ALL:
Ooh!
To human misery.
(rumbling)
(gasping)
Huh?
Ice to see you.
McBain!
Ah, McBain.
So glad
you could make it.
Have a salmon puff.
All right.
(groaning loudly)
(evil laughter)
That is one evil dude.
It's just a movie, son.
There's nobody that evil
in real life.
(evil laughter)
-(window cleaner yelling)
-Smithers, where's
that union representative?
He's 20 minutes late.
I don't know, sir.
He hasn't been seen
since he promised
to clean up the union.
Oh!
What the hell?
Well, let's look
at the contract
ourselves, eh?
Benefits, perks,
a green cookie on
St. Patrick's Day. Ho ho.
It didn't use
to be this way, Smithers.
No, it didn't use
to be this way at all.
Come on, come on,
crack those atoms.
You, turn out
those pockets.
Atoms. One, two,
three, fo...
six of them.
Take him away.
You can't treat
the working man this way.
One day we'll form a union,
and get the fair and equitable
treatment we deserve.
Then we'll go too far,
and get corrupt and shiftless,
and the Japanese
will eat us alive.
The Japanese?
Those sandal-wearing
goldfish tenders?
Ha ha! Bosh. Flimshaw.
If only we had listened
to that boy
instead of walling him up
in the abandoned coke oven.
Well, I am going
to avenge my grandfather.
We'll take
on that greedy union
and we'll get back our...
dental plan.
How often do you brush, Ralph?
Three times a day, sir.
Why must you turn my office
into a house of lies?
You're right, I don't brush.
I don't brush.
Let's look at a picture book.
That's enough!
Dr. Wolfe likes to pull kids'
teeth so he can sell them.
To who?
Know that rattle
when you shake up spray paint?
That's a kid's tooth.
(whimpering)
Maggie's teeth are coming
in crooked.
Has she been sucking
on a pacifier?
Um, not to my knowledge.
Liar!
I'm also afraid
little Lisa is going
to need braces.
Oh, no. I'll be
socially unpopular.
More so.
Are you sure, doctor?
Well, judge for yourself.
Here's Lisa today.
Without treatment,
here's what she'll look like
at age 11...
age 14...
age 17...
and finally, age 18.
(gasps)
Cool. She'll be a freak.
Bart!
We can stick
her in a trailer,
drive around the south,
and charge
two bits a gander.
ANNOUNCER: Now, stay tuned
for professional wrestling
live from the Springfield
Grapplarium.
Tonight, a Texas Death match--
Doctor Hillbilly
versus the Iron Yuppie.
One man will actually be
unmasked and killed in the ring.
I hope they kill
that Iron Yuppie.
Thinks he's so big.
Homer, Lisa needs braces.
Don't worry.
We won a dental plan
in the strike of '88.
That's where I got this scar.
What do we want?
ALL: More equitable treatment
in the hands of management!
When do we want it?
ALL: Soon!
Where's my burrito?!
Ow!
Then I got this scar
sneaking under the door
of a pay toilet.
CARL: Welcome brothers
of local 643.
As you know, our president,
Chucky Fitzhugh,
ain't been seen lately.
We're all praying he'll
turn up soon, alive and well.
(derisive laughter)
All right, all right,
but seriously...
we have to vote
on Burns' new contract.
It's basically the same deal,
except we get a free keg
of beer for our meetings.
(cheers)
And in exchange for that,
we have to give up
our dental plan.
So long, dental plan.
-LENNY: ...dental plan.
-MARGE: Lisa needs braces.
-...dental plan.
-Lisa needs braces.
Bull's-eye!
Thanks a lot, Carl.
Now I've lost
my train of thought.
LENNY: ...dental plan.
MARGE: Lisa needs braces.
...dental plan.
Lisa needs braces.
If we give up
our dental plan...
I'll have to pay
for Lisa's braces!
People, stop! We can't
give up our dental plan.
Lenny, without
that dental plan,
you wouldn't have that
diamond in your tooth.
Yoink!
Hey!
And Gummy Joe.
Where would you be
without that dental plan?
(Walter Brennan voice)
I wouldn't have old chomper here
that's for sure.
You know what I think
of this contract? This!
(growling, straining)
Who is that firebrand,
Smithers?
That's Homer Simpson, sir.
Simpson, eh? New man?
Actually sir, he thwarted
your campaign for governor.
You ran over his son.
He saved the plant
from meltdown.
His wife painted you
in the nude.
Uh, doesn't ring a bell.
(chanting)
Homer! Homer! Homer!
I move that Homer Simpson
be our new union president.
All in favor?
ALL: Aye!
All opposed?
MAN (with nebbish
voice): Nay.
Congratulations, Homer.
(cheering)
Hey, what does this job pay?
Nothing.
-D'oh!
-Unless you're crooked.
Whoo-hoo!!
President of the union!
I'm so proud of you, Homie.
This is your chance
to get a fair shake
for the working man.
And make lifelong connections
to the world of organized crime.
Mmm, organized crime.
Don Homer, I have baked
a special doughnut
just for you.
Mmm.
Grazie.
Don Homer, my son, he has
trouble with the, uh...
Eh-eh-eh-eh-eh...
Molto bene.
That's-a nice-a doughnut.
Do you think you can get
the dental plan back?
Well, that depends on
who's a better negotiator--
Mr. Burns or me.
Dad, I'll trade you
this delicious doorstop
for your crummy
old Danish.
Done, and done.
(chuckling)
D'oh!
Lisa and Marge,
these braces
are invisible, painless,
and periodically release
a delightful burst
of Calvin Klein's
Obsession for teeth.
(sniffs)
Mmm!
Doctor, we don't have
a dental plan right now
so we'll need something
a little more... affordable.
These predate stainless steel,
so you can't get them wet.
(coughs)
He's a worthy foe.
Look at him, Smithers--
Exercising away
while the others are off
at the candy machine.
(grunting)
Hey, Lenny, can you get
this Sugar Daddy
off my back?
Okay, but it's
the last time.
We don't have
to be adversaries, Homer.
We both want
a fair union contract.
HOMER: Why is Mr. Burns
being so nice to me?
And if you scratch my back,
I'll scratch yours.
Wait a minute.
Is he coming on to me?
I mean, if I should slip
something into your pocket,
what's the harm?
Oh, my God.
He is coming on to me.
After all, negotiations
make strange bedfellows.
(snickers)
(clicks tongue)
Ahh!
Sorry, Mr. Burns,
but I don't go in for these
backdoor shenanigans.
Sure, I'm flattered,
maybe even a little curious,
but the answer is no.
(sighs)
Lisa, so you won't be scared,
I'll show you some
of the tools I'll be using.
This is the scraper,
this is the poker,
and this happy little fellow
is the gouger.
Uh-huh.
Now, the first thing
I'll be doing
is chiseling some teeth
out of your jawbone.
Hold still while I gas you.
('60s music playing)
(cockney accent)
Look, fellas.
It's Lisa in the sky.
No diamonds, though.
Look out for the campy drawing
of Queen Victoria!
All: Oh, no!
For the love of God,
help us!
-Help us!
The mirror.
The mirror!
(evil cackling)
Honey, you look fine.
(barking)
(yelping)
(doorbell rings)
Who is it?
MAN: Goons.
HOMER: Who?
Hired goons.
Hired goons?
(sinister laughing)
Ah, Homer. I hope Crusher
and Low Blow didn't hurt you.
You know, you could
have just called me.
Oh, yes, but the telephone
is so impersonal.
I prefer the hands-on touch
you only get
with hired goons.
Hired goons?
This is the largest TV
in the free world.
Aiee! Un gato malodoro!
(shivering groan)
This is a thousand monkeys
working at a
thousand typewriters.
Soon, they'll have written
the greatest novel
known to man. Let's see.
"It was the best of times,
it was the blurst of times!"
-You stupid monkey!
-(chattering)
Oh, shut up.
(footsteps trudging)
And this
is my basement.
Gee, it's not as nice
as the other rooms.
Yes, I really should stop
ending the tour
with it.
Now, let's get down
to business.
HOMER: Oh, man,
I really have to go
to the bathroom.
Why did I have all that beer
and coffee and watermelon?
Now, Homer, I know
what you're thinking,
and I want to take
the pressure off.
It doesn't take a whiz to see
that you're looking out
for number one.
Well, listen to me
and you'll make
a big splash very soon.
Which way to the bathroom?
Oh, it's the 23rd door
on the left.
Nope.
Ah, he wouldn't even
hear me out.
(grunting)
Find the bathroom
all right?
Uh... yeah.
Well, you've won
this round, Simpson.
But I'll grind you
into the earth like a bug.
(maniacal laughing)
(screaming)
Simpson, be a dear
and rub my legs
till the feeling
comes back.
A bug, I tell you!
A bug!
(maniacal laughter)
(groans)
(sighs)
I'm going to resign.
I don't know why they made
me union president
in the first place.
Because they love you
down at the plant.
Yeah, you're right.
Guys are always patting
my bald head for luck,
pinching my belly to
hear my girlish laugh.
Hmm. That doesn't sound like
they like you at all.
You know,
I think you're right.
First thing tomorrow morning,
I'm going to punch Lenny
in the back of the head.
Hmm. (grunts)
Batten down those cowlicks.
Straighten that part.
Uncross those eyes,
mister.
But I can't!
Oh, sorry, Quigley.
Come on, honey, smile.
I bet you've got
a beautiful smile.
Why don't you share it
with the world?
(gasping)
There is no God!
Fellow workers,
I've been meeting
with Mr. Burns day and night
and I've had enough.
(chanting)
Strike! Strike! Strike! Strike!
All in favor of a strike?
ALL: Aye!
All opposed?
MAN (with nebbish
voice): Nay.
Who keeps saying that?
(nebbish voice)
It was him.
Let's get him,
fellas.
(angry muttering)
(chuckling)
(guitar strumming softly)
♪ Come gather 'round,
children ♪
♪ It's high time ye learns ♪
♪ 'Bout a hero named Homer ♪
♪ And a devil named Burns ♪
♪ We'll march till we drop ♪
♪ The girls and the fellas ♪
♪ We'll fight till the death ♪
♪ Or else fold like
umbrellas... ♪
(shouting and grunting)
Ah, this is the life.
Smithers, get me
some strikebreakers.
The kind they had
in the '30s.
We can't bust heads
like we used to.
But we have our ways.
(murmuring in agreement)
One trick is to tell
them stories
that don't go anywhere.
Like the time I caught
the ferry over to Shelbyville.
I needed a new heel
for my shoe,
so I decided to go
to Morganville,
which is what they called
Shelbyville in those days.
So I tied an onion to my belt,
which was the style
at the time.
Now, to take the ferry
costs a nickel,
and in those days,
nickels had pictures
of bumblebees on them.
"Give me five bees
for a quarter," you'd say.
Now, where were we?
Oh, yeah.
The important thing was
that I had
an onion on my belt,
which was the style
at the time.
They didn't have
white onions
because of the war.
The only thing
you could get
was those big,
yellow ones.
(shouting angrily)
Full power, Smithers.
(screaming)
♪ So we'll march
day and night ♪
♪ By the big cooling tower ♪
♪ They have the plant ♪
♪ But we have the power ♪
Now do "Classical Gas".
(playing "Classical Gas")
Ooh, look at him strutting around
like he's cock of the walk.
Well, let me tell you.
Homer Simpson
is cock of nothing.
Hmm?
Why, you and I can run
this plant ourselves.
(upbeat music playing)
ROBOTS: Crush, kill, destroy.
Tonight on Smartline:
"The Power Plant Strike--
Argle-bargle or Foofooraw?"
With us tonight
are plant owner
C.M. Burns,
union kingpin
Homer Simpson,
and talk show mainstay
Dr. Joyce brothers.
I brought my own mic.
Yes, well...
Homer, organized labor has been
called a lumbering dinosaur.
(screams)
Uh, my director's telling me
not to talk to you anymore.
-Whoo-hoo!
-Uh, Mr. Burns,
you mentioned you wanted
an opening tirade?
Yes, thank you, Kent.
15 minutes from now,
I will wreak a terrible
vengeance on this city.
No one will be spared!
No one!
(chuckles)
A chilling vision of things to come.
Oh, for God's sake.
(whines)
Good-bye, Springfield.
From hell's heart,
I stab at thee.
(plant powering down)
♪ So we'll march
day and night ♪
♪ By the big cooling tower ♪
♪ They have the plant ♪
♪ But we have the power ♪
♪ So we'll march
day and night ♪
♪ By the big cooling tower ♪
♪ They have the plant,
but we have the power ♪
Look at them all
through the darkness
I'm bringing.
They're not sad at all.
They're actually singing.
They sing without juicers.
They sing without blenders.
They sing without flunjers,
capdabblers, and smendlers.
Dooh...
Tell Simpson
I'm ready to deal.
All right, Homer.
You can have the dental plan
on one condition.
You must resign
as head of the union.
Whoo-hoo!
(hooting loudly)
Smithers, I'm beginning
to think that Homer Simpson
was not the brilliant
tactician I thought he was.
(hooting)
We're going back to work.
STRIKERS: Yay!
(plant powering up)
(sultry music plays)
(splurting)
All: Yay!
Oh, honey, you can hardly
see your new braces.
And that's the tooth.
Oops.
I left the gas on.
(laughing continues)
♪♪
Shh.
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.