♪ The Simpsons ♪
(chalk screeches)
(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(tires screeching)
(horn honks)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
♪♪ ("The Flintstones" theme)
(whistle blowing)
Yabba dabba doo!
♪ Simpson, Homer Simpson ♪
♪ He's the greatest guy
in history ♪
♪ From the town
of Springfield ♪
♪ He's about to hit
a chestnut tree ♪
Aah!
What do they do with these
after we seal them?
I hear they dump 'em
in an abandoned chalk mine
and cover 'em with cement.
I hear they're sending them to
one of those southern states
where the governor's
a crook.
Either way,
I'm sleeping good tonight.
Well, sir, where shall
we dump this batch?
-The playground?
-No.
All those bald children
are arousing suspicion.
To the park!
(Smithers and Burns
straining)
I think it's full, sir.
That's ridiculous.
The last tree
held nine drums.
(chittering)
Agent Malone,
Environmental Protection Agency.
Some Boy Scouts stumbled
on your little game
of "hide the ooze."
JUDGE: Mr. Burns,
in light of your unbelievable
contempt for human life,
this court fines you
$3 million.
Smithers, my wallet's
in my right front pocket.
Oh, and I'll take
that statue of justice, too.
Sold!
(chuckling)
Oh, Andy Capp,
you wife-beating drunk.
Heh heh heh heh.
Ooh, there's going to be
a town meeting
to decide how to spend
Mr. Burns' money.
Oh, what a boon it could be
for our underfunded
public schools.
Children, it's time
for your history lesson.
Put on your
virtual reality helmets.
Mmm, excellent.
Hello, Lisa.
I'm Genghis Khan.
You'll go where I go,
defile what I defile,
eat who I eat, hmm?
Come on, Lis, we both know
how this money should--
nay, must be spent.
(electronic beeping)
Gaa! Oh...
Bart, we'll do anything
you want.
Just call off
your giant mechanical ants.
Whoa!
(evil laughter)
Well, I think we should
spend the money on something
the whole town
can be proud of.
Like a giant billboard
that says, "No fat chicks"?
No.
Ooh, it looks like everyone in
Springfield showed up for this.
-(glass breaking, alarms ringing)
-Ha ha!
Could this town
be any stupider?
Order. Please rise
for the Pledge of Allegiance.
Get to the money!
In a moment.
First, let's review the minutes
from our last meeting.
-Get to the money!
Get to the money!
Very well.
We will now hear suggestions
for the, uh, disbursement
of the, uh, $2 million.
Don't you mean $3 million?
Of course.
How silly of me.
Excuse me.
We could use the money
to hire firemen
to finally put out that blaze
on the east side of town.
Boring!
Hello.
My name is Mr. Snrub,
and I come from, uh...
someplace far away.
Yes, that will do.
Anyway, I-- I say
we invest that money
back in the nuclear plant.
I like the way Snrub thinks.
(grumbling)
Pardon me, but I would like
to see this money
spent on more police officers.
I have been shot
eight times this year,
and as a result,
I almost missed work.
Crybaby!
My name is Marge Simpson
and I have an idea.
It may sound a little
boring at first.
Chat away.
I'll just amuse myself
with some pornographic
playing cards.
Oh.
Well, surely
you've all noticed
the terrible condition
Main Street is in.
Many of us have destroyed it
by leaving winter chains
on our tires
and carrying
too much weight.
Woo-hoo!
Look at that pavement fly.
MARGE: And those potholes
are becoming a real nuisance.
Now hold on just one minute.
Sure, we could fix up
Main Street.
We could put all our eggs
in one basket.
(cheering)
Shut up!
I wasn't done yet.
I'm just saying,
we could blow all our money
on a stupid little street,
but--
(cheering)
Oh, I ain't fer it.
I'm agin' it.
ALL (chanting):
Main Street! Main Street! Main Street!
All those in favor
of Grampa Simpson's plan
for rebuilding Main Street,
please--
(whistling)
You know, a town with money
is a little like
the mule with
a spinning wheel.
No one knows how he got it,
and danged if he knows
how to use it.
(laughter)
Heh, heh... mule.
The name's Lanley,
Lyle Lanley,
and I come before
you good people tonight
with an idea.
Probably the greatest--
Oh, it's not for you.
It's more of
a Shelbyville idea.
Now, wait just a minute.
We're twice as smart as
the people of Shelbyville.
Just tell us your idea
and we'll vote for it.
All right,
I tell you what I'll do.
I'll show you my idea.
I give you
the Springfield monorail.
(all gasping)
I've sold monorails
to Brockway, Ogdenville,
and North Haverbrook.
And by gum, it put them
on the map.
Well, sir,
there's nothing on earth
like a genuine, bona fide,
electrified, six-car monorail.
-What I say?
-Monorail!
-What's it called?
-BOTH: Monorail.
That's right, monorail!
ALL (chanting):
Monorail! Monorail! Monorail!
♪ I hear those things
are awfully loud ♪
♪ It glides as softly
as a cloud ♪
♪ Is there a chance
the track could bend? ♪
♪ Not on your life,
my Hindu friend ♪
♪ What about us
brain-dead slobs? ♪
♪ You'll be given
cushy jobs ♪
♪ Were you sent here
by the devil? ♪
♪ No, good sir,
I'm on the level ♪
♪ The ring came off
my pudding can ♪
♪ Take my penknife,
my good man ♪
♪ I swear it's Springfield's
only choice ♪
♪ Throw up your hands
and raise your voice ♪
ALL:
♪ Monorail! ♪
♪ What's it called? ♪
ALL: ♪ Monorail! ♪
♪ Once again ♪
♪ But Main Street's still
all cracked and broken ♪
♪ Sorry, Mom,
the mob has spoken ♪
ALL: ♪ Monorail ♪
♪ Monorail ♪
ALL: Monorail!
Mono--
D'oh!
(chanting)
Monorail, monorail, monorail.
I still think we
should have spent the money
to fix Main Street.
Well, you should have written
a song like that guy.
(grumbles)
Thank you for coming,
Mr. Lanley.
I'm Miss Hoover.
Miss Hoover?
That is hard
to believe.
Oh, you.
Now I'm here to answer
any questions
you children may have
about the monorail.
CHILDREN:
Me! Me! Me!
-Can it outrun The Flash?
-You bet.
Can Superman
outrun The Flash?
Uh... sure. Why not?
Hello, little girl.
Wondering if your dolly
can ride the monorail
for free?
Hardly. I'd like you
to explain why we should build
a mass transit system
in a small town
with a centralized population.
(laughs) Young lady,
that's the most
intelligent question
-I've ever been asked.
-Really?
Oh, I could give you
an answer,
but the only ones
who'd understand it
would be you and me,
and that includes
your teacher.
(giggling)
Next question.
You there, eating the paste.
ANNOUNCER: Coming soon, it's
"Truckasaurus: The Movie."
Starring Marlon Brando
as the voice
of John Truckasaurus.
BRANDO: You crazy car.
I don't know whether to
eat you or kiss you.
ANNOUNCER: Celebrity voice
impersonated.
-LANLEY: Are you stuck in a dead-end job?
-Maybe.
Are you squandering
the precious gift of life
-in front of the idiot box?
-What's it to you?
Are you on your third beer
of the evening?
Does whiskey count as beer?
Well, maybe it's time you
joined the exciting field
of monorail conducting
by enrolling at
the Lanley Institute.
ANNOUNCER: Actual institute
may not match photo.
Marge, I want to be
a monorail conductor.
Homer, no.
It's my lifelong dream.
Your lifelong dream
was to run out on the field
during a baseball game,
and you did it last year,
remember?
Oh, yeah.
LANLEY:
Good evening.
Before we begin,
is anyone here
an investigative reporter?
I am and she is.
Well, I'd like you
to please leave.
Should we take
our hidden camera?
-Would you?
-Let's go, Phil.
"True or false:
You can get mono
from riding the monorail."
Mmm... false.
No, wait.
Maybe it's true.
No, you were right.
It's false.
Wow, you really are
gonna be
a monorail conductor.
That's right, boy.
You know, I used to think
you were stuck
in an emasculating,
go-nowhere job.
(chuckles)
Kids.
But now, I want to follow
in your footsteps.
Do you want to change
your name to Homer, Junior?
The kids can call you Hoju.
I'll get back to you.
Come on, keep it coming.
Over.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
Hi, Homer!
Oh, I hate that sound.
According to this book,
the monorail goes
over 150 miles an hour.
What if something
goes wrong?
What if?
What if I'm taking a shower
and I slip on a bar of soap?
Oh, my God, I'd be killed!
It frightens me
that you want to work
on something
that's so unsafe.
We monorail conductors
are a crazy breed--
half in love with death,
gobbling up danger
like ordinary men eat peanuts.
Am I turning you on?
-No.
-What if I undo this button?
Good night, Homer.
(deepens voice)
What if I talk like this?
What if I sing to you?
♪ I gave my love a chicken
that had no bone... ♪
Mmm, chicken.
(licking lips)
So, then, mono means "one,"
and rail means "rail,"
and that concludes our
intensive three-week course.
Hey, wait, man!
Who gets to be conductor?
Oh, right, that.
Well, I've been monitoring
your progress closely,
but this gentleman here clearly
stands out above the rest.
Who, me?
-Yeah, sure.
-Woo-hoo!
After an exhaustive search,
Springfield has found
its monorail conductor--
Homer Simpson.
This is the snack holder
where I can put my beverage,
or, if you will, cupcake.
Wow, Dad, you really
know your monorails.
(hissing)
Homer, there's a family
of possums in here.
I call the big one Bitey.
Mmm. I'm going to
see Mr. Lanley.
Mr. Lanley?
(gasps)
Oh!
How much did you see?
Uh... nothing incriminating.
-Good.
-Well, bye.
I don't know why
I leave this lying around.
I've sold monorails
to Brockway, Ogdenville,
and North Haverbrook.
Is there a chance
the track could bend?
I call the big one Bitey.
I've sold monorails
to Brockway, Ogdenville,
and North Haverbrook.
Is there a chance
the track could bend?
I call the big one Bitey.
(cackling laughter)
WOMAN: Go away.
There ain't no monorail,
and there never was.
(screams)
Excuse me, miss.
You asked
about the monorail?
Who are you?
My name is Sebastian Cobb.
Lanley hired me
to build his monorail.
He cut corners everywhere--
bad wiring, faulty brakes,
and the celebrity on
the maiden voyage was Gallagher.
This is all that's left
of one of the crappiest
trains ever built.
Mr. Cobb,
what can we do?
You just better have
a damn good conductor.
I locked my keys
in there.
Get a rock.
Ladies and gentlemen,
nothing brings out the stars
like the maiden voyage
of a monorail.
Everyone's here--
from recently-outed
leading man Dash Calhoun
to Krusty the Clown.
Hey, hey!
Krusty, why won't you
answer my calls?
You've never even
seen our son.
(babbling)
Here's one of those lovable
high schoolers
from TV's
"Springfield Heights, 90210."
He's cool.
He's sexy.
He's 34 years old.
Let's hear it
for Kyle Derin.
(women screaming)
And here's
country singing sensation
Lurline Lumpkin,
fresh from her latest stay
at the Betty Ford Clinic.
(crowd cheering)
What you been up to,
Lurline?
I spent last night
in a ditch.
How about that, folks?
Now I'd like to turn things
over to our grand marshal,
Mr. Leonard Nimoy.
Heh heh. I'd say this vessel
could do at least warp five.
(laughter)
And let me say,
"May the force
be with you."
Do you even know
who I am?
I think I do.
Weren't you one of
the Little Rascals?
Mr. Lanley!
Aren't you gonna ride
the monorail?
Little lady, I'd love to,
but I have to catch a plane.
But the ride only takes
a minute.
Yeah, well, my plane leaves
in less than one minute.
All aboard!
(electricity crackling)
We're too late!
I shouldn't have stopped
for that haircut. Sorry.
(jazzy lounge music playing)
Actually, you see, the doors
on "Star Trek" were not mechanical.
We had a stagehand
on either side
who would pull the door open
when he saw you approach.
Uh-huh.
Stick your head
out the window, boy.
It's the greatest.
Yee-ha!
BOTH: Aah!
(alarm blaring)
Can't you stop it,
Dad?
I'm trying my best.
(electronic tones)
WOMAN'S VOICE:
The lever you have pulled--
"brakes"--
is not in service.
Please make a note of it.
How fast are they going?
(Homer screams)
Well, judging by your
husband's cowardly scream,
-180 miles an hour.
-HOMER: Yee!
(distant shouting)
Ugh. It's making me dizzy.
I'm gonna take a nap.
All right,
I'm in charge here.
Oh, run along, Quimby.
I think they're dedicating
a phone booth somewhere.
Watch it, you talking tub
of doughnut batter.
Hey, I got pictures
of you, Quimby.
You don't scare me.
That could be anyone's ass.
Now beat it.
I'm calling the shots.
I think that sash is cutting
off the air to your brain.
The town charter says that
in an emergency, I run the show.
Well, we'll just see
about that.
Let's go to town hall.
Fine!
Should we take one car
or should I follow you?
(screaming)
Hey, according to the charter,
as chief constable,
I'm supposed to get
a pig every month.
"...and two comely lasses
of virtue true."
QUIMBY: Keep the pig.
How many broads
do I get? Hey.
Hey! Hey, let go,
you're ripping it!
-No, you are!
Let go.
That's the charter.
(screaming)
Wait a minute.
We can just shut off
the power.
No such luck.
-It's solar-powered.
-Solar power.
When will people learn?
A solar eclipse.
The cosmic ballet goes on.
Does anyone want
to switch seats?
(engine powering down)
(cheering)
I did it.
D'oh!
Folks, this is
your captain speaking.
Our non-stop flight
to Tahiti
will be making
a brief layover
in North Haverbrook.
North Haverbrook.
Where have I heard that name before?
Oh, no.
Oh, no!
There he is.
Seat 3-F.
(angry shouting)
-(angry shouting)
-(Lanley grunting)
Krusty wants out.
No.
The world needs laughter.
Are we gonna die, son?
Yeah, but at least
we'll take
a lot of innocent
people with us.
MARGE: Homer? Homer?
-Yello.
-Homer, there's a man here
who thinks he can help you.
-Batman?
-No. He's a scientist.
Batman's a scientist.
It's not Batman!
I think I have a way
to stop the train.
You need to find an anchor
of some sort.
Think harder, Homer.
(gasps)
I'll take that.
Uh, Dad...
(screams)
Now,
separating Siamese twins
is a long
and costly procedure.
Aargh!
You call that an anchor?
Huh?
Donuts.
Is there anything
they can't do?
Dad! You're a hero.
Yes, son.
I'm the best mono-thingy guy
there ever was.
(cheering)
Well, my work
is done here.
What do you mean,
your work is done?
You didn't do anything.
(chuckles)
Didn't I?
MARGE:
And that was the only folly
the people of Springfield
ever embarked upon...
except for the
popsicle-stick skyscraper...
and the 50-foot
magnifying glass...
and that escalator
to nowhere.
Whoa!
Wha!
Aah!
MAN: Whoa!
WOMAN: Aah!
♪♪
Shh.
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.