♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
(whistle blowing)
(beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
-I need one 29-cent stamp.
-That's $1.85.
-I want $2.00 worth of gas, please.
-$4.20.
-(bell dings)
-How much is your penny candy?
-Surprisingly expensive.
-MARTIN: What a rip-off!
-(door chimes)
-This is what I think of your store!
-(grunting)
-(door chimes)
Silly customer!
You cannot hurt a twinkie!
(sniffing)
Jiminy Cricket!
Whoo! Expired ham.
Well, this time I've gone too
far. No. No one will fall for--
Woo-hoo! Cheap meat!
Ooh, this one's open.
(gobbling)
-Ooh! Stomach churning!
-(stomach grumbles)
Bowels clenching.
-Not much time.
-(thuds)
Must finish.
(gobbles)
(alarm blaring)
Well, sir, Homer's illness was either
caused by ingesting spoiled food
or some sort of voodoo curse.
Hey, we've just been
working the eyes.
-(door chimes)
-Your old meat made me sick!
Oh, I'm so sorry. Please accept
five pounds of frozen shrimp.
(sniffing) This shrimp isn't frozen,
and it smells funny.
-Okay. Ten pounds.
-Whoo-hoo!
(alarm blaring)
(barking)
-MAN: Brought to you by--
-(barking continues)
That dog can sell anything.
Good evening.
Here's an update on last week's
nursing-home exposé,
"Geezers in Freezers."
It turns out the rest home
was adequately heated.
The footage you saw was
of a fur-storage facility.
We've also been told to apologize
for using the term "geezers."
Now, coming up next, "The case
of the cantankerous old geezer."
-Ohh! Urp!
-(stomach grumbles)
Rancid meat attack!
Stupid parasites!
Is there no way
I can find justice?
If you have a consumer
complaint, just call this number.
Boring.
Dad, you should blow
the whistle on the Kwik-E-Mart.
BROCKMAN: And now a message from
the Church of Latter-Day Saints.
(dog barking)
-Dad, are you listening to me?
-Shh! Lisa! The dog is barking.
All right. Are you willing to go
undercover to nail this creep?
No way, man! No way, man!
Get yourself another patsy, man!
No way am I wearin'
a freakin' wire.
All right, all right, all right.
Would you be willing to wear
-a hidden camera and microphone?
-Oh, that I'll wear.
We've come up
with a camera so tiny
it fits into this
oversized novelty hat.
(groaning)
Now go get us some
incriminating footage.
And remember, you have to get in
and out in 10 minutes,
-or you'll suffer permanent neck damage.
-He's not kiddin'.
(groaning)
(footsteps clattering)
(door chimes)
-Huh?
-Don't be alarmed, Apu.
Just go about your daily routine
like I'm not wearing the hat.
Your headgear seems to be
emitting a buzzing noise, sir.
Perhaps you have
a bee in your bonnet.
Bee?
(screaming)
(panting)
Homer, that hat's been
with the station for 20 years.
He had one day left
till retirement.
♪ La la la la la ♪
Well, time to
replenish the hot-dog roller.
♪ La la ♪
Oops!
Oh, no.
It is encrusted with filth.
Oh, well.
Let's sell it anyway.
Now, this is just between me
and you, smashed hat. (chuckling)
Hot diggety dog!
We've got him, Mr. Simpson.
Now, let's-- Mr. Simpson?
One hot dog, please.
(dog barking on TV)
Apu, will you ever stop
selling spoiled meat?
No. I mean, yes.
I mean-- Uh-oh.
-I think I come off very well.
-Monster! Run, children!
(panicked shouting)
Apu Nahasapeemapetilon,
you have disgraced
the Kwik-E-Mart corporation.
But, sir, I was only following
standard procedure.
Ah, true. But it's also
standard procedure
to blame any problems
on a scapegoat or sacrificial lamb.
Uh-huh. And if I can
obtain for you these animals?
I'm sorry, Apu.
I have no choice.
-You can no longer wear this name patch.
-(gasps)
And you can no longer tell
people about our fried pickles.
Now, turn in
your pricing gun.
Oh!
The other one too.
Oh! Fired after all these years
of loyal service.
-I don't want to live anymore! Oh!
-Give me that wiener!
-No! I don't want to live, sir!
-(grunting)
-No, Apu! It's not worth it!
What do I do now?
I've been drummed out of my profession.
I'm a disgrace.
Even this babbling brook sounds
almost like mocking laughter.
(laughter)
Who needs money
when we got feathers?
(chittering)
Hmm.
(thunderclap)
This is all because
of Homer Simpson.
-(laughing)
-(laughter on TV)
Oh, oh, stop!
Yo, check this out.
Black guys drive a car like this.
-♪♪ (scatting)
-(audience laughing)
Yeah, but white guys, see, they drive
a car like this. ♪♪ (scatting)
-(laughter, applause)
-It's true! It's true! We're so lame.
It is time to settle the score.
Huh?
(thunderclaps continue)
Aah!
(screaming)
No! Don't kill me! I didn't know
there was film in that camera in that hat!
I was unaware!
Mr. Simpson,
you misunderstand me.
In my village, this is
the traditional pose of apology.
-Oh.
-You know, now that I think about it,
it may be a little confusing.
Many have died needlessly.
I have come to make amends, sir.
At first, I blamed you for squealing.
But then I realized
it was I who wronged you.
So I have come to work
off my debt. I am at your service.
You're selling what now?
I'm selling only the concept
of karmic realignment.
You can't sell that!
Karma can only be
portioned out by the cosmos.
-He's got me there.
-(metal scraping)
-HOMER: Is he still out there?
-Yes. He's raking leaves.
What? That's your job!
If he starts doing
Lisa's wood chopping--
If he wants to make it up to you
so badly, I think you should let him.
Okay, okay. I'll let him.
But then I get a Chipwich. Okay?
It is an honor to begin
repaying my debt to you.
Back in Rahmatpur,
I was considered quite the gourmet.
Hmm. It certainly is exotic.
-(panting)
-Oh, Lisa, is that too spicy for you?
I can see through time.
(gulping)
Stop being such babies.
You can't be afraid
to try new things.
For instance, tonight I'm using a--
Apu, what do you call this thing again?
-A napkin.
-(chuckling) Outrageous!
All right. Why do you want
to become a part
of the Kwik-E-Mart family?
Because I like people,
and I need a place
where I'll be out of the sun.
-Thank you.
-(belches)
Hmm. He's head and shoulders
above everyone else.
-Wait. There's one more applicant.
-Name?
-James Woods.
-Previous job experience?
Ooh, uh, gee, True Believer, uh, Salvador,
Onion Field, The Hard Way.
Wait-wait a minute!
Those aren't convenience stores.
that sounds like the resume
of a Hollywood movie star.
Uh, yeah, well-- Hmm.
(both gasp)
James woods!
Why would you want
to work at a Kwik-E-Mart?
(chuckles) Well, uh, to be honest,
in my upcoming movie...
I'm gonna be playing this tightly wound
convenience-store clerk,
and, you know, I kinda like to research
my roles and really get into it.
For instance, True Believer. I actually
worked in a law firm for two months.
And in the film Chaplin--
I had a little cameo in that--
I actually traveled in time
back to the '20s where--
-Well, (chuckles) I've said too much.
-Welcome aboard.
♪♪ (humming)
Hm? Hm? Hm? Hm?
-Good morning, sir.
-(screams)
Relax, please. You do not have anything
I have not seen before.
-What the--
-Uh, I like to keep a lollipop there.
-♪ La la la la ♪
-(groans)
Apu, we usually store
our cans in the cupboard.
Well, they'll never move
that way.
Mmm! Corn!
Haven't had that in a while.
Yeah! Delicious corn.
-TOGETHER: Bye.
-Hm.
Oh, we're low on milk for Maggie.
You wanna come with me to the Kwik-E-Mart?
Please, Mrs. Simpson.
I-- I cannot go there. That is
the scene of my spiritual depantsing.
Umm, well, I guess we could go
to that new Monstromart.
♪♪ (Muzak)
Ooh! That's a good price
for 12 pounds of nutmeg.
Ooh! Great selection and
rock-bottom prices. But where is the love?
MAN (on P.A.):
Attention Monstromart shoppers.
Just a reminder that we love
each and every one of you.
-(shoppers) Aww!
-Hm!
Excuse me, ma'am.
Where are the lampshades?
-Ma'am?
-(liquid pouring)
Oh! I've killed her!
It's all happening again!
-(sobbing, screaming)
-Mm-hmm.
(both gasp, scream)
Help me! Help me!
(gurgling)
Mmm! It's cran-tastic!
Uh, Mrs. Simpson, the express line
is the fastest line not always.
That old man up front,
he is starved for attention.
He will talk
the cashier's head off.
Ah, there's an interesting story
behind this nickel.
In 1957, I remember it was.
I got up in the morning and
made myself a piece of toast.
I set the toaster to three--
medium brown.
-Let's go to... that line.
-But that's the longest.
Yes, but look-- all pathetic single men.
Only cash, no chitchat.
(rapid cash-register sounds)
Mmm!
Seventy-five, 85, 90
and a dollar.
Thank you and come again.
Hey, wait a minute! Hey!
Uh, eh, could I just
ask you a question?
Did you-- huh! Did you believe that?
I mean, the way I gave you the change?
Did I sound like a real Kwik-E-Mart,
you know, kinda guy?
Actually, I thought
it was a little labored.
You gotta lose yourself
in the moment, man.
Yeah. Like-- Yeah! Great. Okay. Let-let's
just try that again. Okay? Come on.
Hey. Come on. Hey-ey-ey! Hey, get over
here! Okay. Now, you're you, I'm me.
-I'm me?
-Hey, don't jerk me around, fella.
(all gobbling, gulping)
-Pass the chutney.
-Apu, you've been so helpful.
If it weren't for him, we'd
still be in line at the Monstromart.
-And he taught me how to play the shehnai.
-♪♪ (shrill notes)
(shudders) That's even worse than
the album Grampa released.
And he taught me how to do this.
(grunting)
I got out of school, 'cause I told 'em
I was mangled in a car wreck.
-Thank you all for the kind praise.
-Well, you deserve it.
All these vegetables are really clearing
the cholesterol out of the old heart.
(beating)
(electrical crackling)
(slowly)
Ahh. Apu friend me good.
I think what my father's saying is
you're like a member of the family now.
I feel that way too. You see,
whether igloo, hut or lean-to...
or a geodesic dome,
there's no structure I have been
to which I'd rather call my home.
Hello. Aah!
♪ When I first arrived
you were all such jerks ♪
♪ But now I've come
to love your quirks ♪
♪ Maggie with
her eyes so bright ♪
♪ Marge with hair
by Frank Lloyd Wright ♪
♪ Lisa can philosophize ♪
♪ Bart's adept
at spinning lies ♪
♪ Homer's a delightful fella ♪
-♪ Sorry 'bout the salmonella ♪
-Heh-heh! That's okay.
-Aah!
-♪ Who needs the Kwik-E-Mart ♪
♪ Now here's
the tricky part ♪
♪ Oh, won't you
rhyme with me ♪
♪ Who needs
the Kwik-E-Mart ♪
♪ Their floors
are sticky-mart ♪
♪ They made Dad sicky-mart ♪
♪ Let's hurl a bricky-mart ♪
♪ The Kwik-E-Mart is real-- ♪
D'oh!
ALL:
♪ Who needs the Kwik-E-Mart ♪
-♪ Not me ♪
-♪ Forget the Kwik-E-Mart ♪
♪ Good-bye to Kwik-E-Mart ♪
♪ Who needs the Kwik-E-Mart ♪
♪ Not me ♪
Ahh. Everything really wrapped up nicely.
Hmm. Much quicker than usual.
I guess we've learned that happiness
is wherever you find it.
And we've all found happiness,
every one of us.
-(Apu crying)
-(TV clicks on)
Hey, what's that sound?
(crying continues)
♪ Who needs
the Kwik-E-Mart ♪
♪ I do ♪
Hey, he's not happy at all!
He lied to us through song!
I hate when people do that!
I can't lie to myself, you know.
I do miss my Kwik-E-Mart.
Isn't there anything you can do to
get your job back?
I must go to the head office
and appeal my case.
I'm coming with you!
I got you fired.
It's the least I can do.
Well, the least I can do is
absolutely nothing.
But I'll go you one better
and come along.
-But, sir, the head office is in India.
-Okay.
-Dad, that's over 10,000 miles away.
-I'm aware of that!
-That's over 16,000 kilometers.
-D'oh!
I'm sorry we couldn't take a cab, but I
spent my last dollar on the plane tickets.
-HOMER: Are we in India yet?
-APU: No.
-Are we in India yet?
-No.
Oh, wait... now we are.
T-Tony, T-Tony,
y-you're my agent.
You have to do something
about this.
Uh! How can it be the same movie
if they've changed my character
from a tightly wound convenience-store
clerk to a jittery Eskimo firefighter?
Uh-huh. Uh-huh. Mm-hmm.
Well, actually, that's--
that's a pretty good explanation.
Now this is gross-- this'll be gross
points, right, on this new-- okay.
Yeah, 'cause those monkey-- yeah. Okay.
Great. Okay. Look. Book me a flight,
rent me an igloo, and tell those dorks
at the Kwik-E-Mart
that, boom, I am out of here.
I'm a dot. I'm gone. Okay? What do you
mean, I gotta give two weeks notice?
Why, you damn, frickin', no good
mother-- (beeping) cheese!
No, not you.
I'm just talkin' to my oven.
♪ If you're saved and you know it
clap your hands ♪
-♪♪ (continues, indistinct)
-Oh, great. Christians.
MAN: Attention, passengers. Dinner
is now being served in the dining car.
(all clamoring)
(both panting, grunting)
-Ooh-ooh!
-There she is.
There she is, the world's first
convenience store.
-This isn't very convenient.
-Must you dump on everything we do?
(bell chimes)
♪♪ (Indian Muzak)
He is the benevolent,
enlightened president and C.E.O.
of Kwik-E-Mart,
and in Ohio, Stop-O-Mart.
-(slurping)
-He is the one I must ask for my job back.
Approach, my sons.
(slurping continues)
You may ask me
three questions.
That's great,
because all I need is one.
-Are you really the head of Kwik-E-Mart?
-Yes.
-Really?
-You?
-Yes.
I hope this has been
enlightening for you.
-But I must--
-Thank you. Come again.
-But--
Well, that was a big bust.
Is he really the head
of the Kwik-E-Mart?
-(angry groan)
-No need to apologize, Apu.
It was as much my fault
as it was yours.
-(growling)
-(gagging)
Okay, Apu!
I accept your apology.
(both screaming)
TOGETHER:
Dad! Dad!
What'd you bring us?
What'd you bring?
-How did it go?
-Fine! Oh, I mean, not good.
I'm sorry, Apu. But remember--
♪ Who needs the Kwik-E-Mart ♪
Do you mind?
I'm not in the mood.
Apu, if it'll make you
feel any better,
I've learned that life is one
crushing defeat after another...
until you just wish
Flanders was dead.
Yes, yes. You are right, sir.
I've got to accept my fate.
I have feared it
for long enough now.
I'm going to go down to the Kwik-E-Mart,
and I am going to face my demon!
Oh, that'll work out great!
We're out of Lucky Charms.
-(door chimes)
-(delighted gasp)
Ah, my old Squishee machine.
And my scum bucket with flies.
And the hot-check list.
Hey, hey, you're Apu Nahasapeemapetilon,
aren't ya? I mean, you're the--
God, you're-- you're like the guy!
You're a legend around here.
Can I ask you-- is it true you once
worked 96 hours straight?
Oh, yes.
It was horrible, I tell you.
By the end, I thought I was
a hummingbird of some kind.
Oh, yeah! You know, I studied
your old security tapes.
Fee-ee-ee-ee.
In a few minutes,
I try to drink nectar
out of Sanjay's head.
All right, you! Hand over the cash,
and don't try any funny stuff!
Hey, pal. I assure you. If I tried any
funny stuff, you would be in hysterics.
-Hey, you're James Woods!
-Oh, thank you. Yes, yes. Thank you.
Well, Mr. Woods,
your new song is gonna be
-number three with a bullet.
-(gun cocks)
-Uh, I'm not a singer.
-Shut up!
-(frightened gasp)
-No!
-Apu!
-Oh!
The searing kiss of hot lead.
How I've missed you.
I mean, I think I'm dying.
-Uhh.
-Oy.
(Dr. Hibbert chuckling)
Well, you are
a very lucky man, Apu.
You see, the bullet ricocheted
off another bullet
that was lodged in your chest
from a previous robbery.
Apu, you saved my life.
And as a small token of
my appreciation,
I got you your job back
at the Kwik-E-Mart.
Oh! Oh, Mr. Woods, you're--
but as for me, I'm off to battle aliens
on a faraway planet.
-That sounds like a good movie.
-Yes. Yes, a movie. Yes.
Hey, let's all hug Apu.
-SIMPSONS: Aww.
-Ooh!
Hey, there's still time.
Let's hug him again.
-Aww.
-Mm!
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.