(SlNGlNG) The Simpsons
(TlRES SCREECHlNG)
D'oh !
(SCREAMlNG)
(BRAKES SCREECHlNG)
(GET SMART THEME PLAYlNG)
(FLOOR CREAKlNG)
Okay. Mother's Day gift check.
Let's see what you got.
l picked Mom a bouquet
of Erigeron eIatiors.
Daisies.
Flowers!
Hmm?
Oh. . . Yeah.
Lise, your stupid present
will only last a week.
Mine will sit in
the closet for years.
Bart, we made her
the same thing.
Oh ! This is even worse
than you think! Look!
Kids, we're going
Mother's Day shopping.
l'm glad this holiday
only comes every four years.
Let's see,
what would
she like?
Twenty on the trifecta?
Her wedding china back?
(GASPlNG)
l could get Marge a new
window just like this one!
Hey, Dad, why don't
we try the Sprawl-Mart?
Yeah, l love Sprawl-Mart.
They've got everything.
Even Christian videos
with talking vegetables.
Mighty Yamses, we are weary
of buiIding your food pyramid.
Let my pickIes go!
Mmm ! Moses.
(DROOLlNG)
Welcome to Sprawl-Mart!
Grampa?
You have a job?
How dare you challenge
my perceptions of what
old people can do!
l'm a greeter.
l'm here to make
every visit special.
And to size up
potential shoplifters.
Like l can't
shoplift with
my mouth.
Ha-ha!
Wow. Look at
all this stuff.
Oh, look, Jaclyn Smith has
her own line of axe heads!
Yeah, it's impressive.
But l still haven't found
the perfect gift for Marge,
only imperfect stuff for me.
Hey, look.
lt's "Hairy Ass" Tubman.
(LAUGHlNG)
Well, well, if it isn't
Fatty and Smell-ma.
Your names
can't hurt us.
(MOANS)
Aunts Patty and Selma,
can you help us pick out
a Mother's Day gift?
You can give her
one of these, the
Kitchen Carnival.
We got one when we
appeared on an episode
of The Price is Right,
which the network
refused to air.
Apparently,
we're not "TV pretty."
Wow! lt's a machine that
makes carnival food at home!
"Endorsed by the
American Carny
Association."
Wow.
l never thought
l'd say this,
but you slags
are all right.
All this attention.
l feel like a secretary
on Administrative
Professionals Day!
Marge, you're gonna
love my present.
lt is so thoughtful,
it makes the kids'
gifts look like crap.
(BOTH GRUMBLE)
Kitchen Carnival !
l love it!
Thank you, Homie.
Oh, Marge,
get a room !
(HUMMlNG)
(CARNlVAL MUSlC PLAYlNG)
Only my hairdresser
knows for sure.
Hmm.
Dare l pour caramel
over the cotton candy?
(LAUGHlNG NERVOUSLY)
(LAUGHlNG MANlACALLY)
(THUNDER CLAPS)
(MANlACAL LAUGHlNG CONTlNUES)
l'm gonna pour
caramel on my clothes.
And then finally,
l can eat my shorts!
BOTH: Ahhh !
What is that?
This is 85 pounds
of tooth-melting
sugar. Dig in.
(SUCKLlNG)
That's it, kids.
Suckle daddy's sugar ball.
Chief, that guy
shouldn't be in
the car pool lane.
His passenger is just
a big piece of candy.
l wish mine was.
What?
Nothin'.
Homer, are you
spooning that snack?
(SCOFFS)
That's my old lady.
(SNORlNG)
Ants!
Birds!
Cats!
Flandereses!
(CRYlNG OUT lN PAlN)
(SOBBlNG)
l was saving sugar
for my wedding night!
Homie, it's time you
got rid of that thing.
All that candy is
rotting your brain.
(lN A SlNlSTER VOlCE)
l think you
should get rid of her.
Then we can be
together forever!
Maybe you're right, Marge.
Or maybe you're right,
Candy Ball. No, Marge!
Then again. . .
No, Marge!
Definitely Marge!
Goodbye, old friend.
l'll think of you whenever
l have a stroke
or a heart attack.
D'oh !
(GROWLlNG)
(ROARlNG)
Oh, my God !
l'm gonna be
killed by a bear!
Well, l guess l don't have
to worry anymore about
the dangers of smoking.
Smooth.
(ROARlNG)
(HOMER WHlMPERlNG)
Homie, what
happened to you?
Marge, please.
l'm too upset
to talk about it.
But seeing you like this
is more than l can bear.
Bear! Ahhh !
The angry president woke up,
crawIed out of his grave
and went back to work.
(CHlCKEN CLUCKlNG)
That sound can mean
onIy one thing.
lt's time for another
installment of
"Kent's Cowards."
Today's cIip comes straight
from the Springfield Dump.
Dad, you got
attacked by a bear?
l did a lot of stuff today.
l went to Starbucks.
But you didn't
see that on tape.
(WHlMPERlNG)
(PANlC-STRlCKEN SOBBlNG)
(CHUCKLlNG)
That hiIarious footage
was shot by IocaI hunter,
Grant Connor.
Not with a gun,
but with a camera!
That's right, Kent.
I often get guns
and cameras confused.
One time, tragically,
at a wedding...
l don't care if they think
you're a coward, Dad.
You did the right thing
hiding and crying.
Yeah. We'd rather
have a live sissy
mincing around the house
than some
dead hero any day.
Choke on your candor!
You can strangle Bart,
but you can't strangle
your humiliation.
lt's a deal !
(CHOKlNG)
Hey, Simpson, l heard
your dad's afraid of a little,
old, giant grizzly bear.
The only thing my dad's afraid
of is paying child support.
My dad once beat up
six employees at KFC.
And he'd been up
for three days.
SMlTHERS: Homer Simpson,
report to Mr. Burns' office
immediateIy.
Ahhh ! (WHlMPERlNG)
(ALL LAUGHlNG)
What a delightful
practically-based joke.
Hello? Anyone home?
Marge? Maggie?
Ahhh !
(READlNG TlTLES)
Oh, Goldilocks.
And the three bears!
Oh, God,
they're in our food !
Teddy Grahams,
Gummi Bears!
Are you a Care Bear?
l'm an lntensive Care Bear.
Why does a bear
need a crowbar?
l don't like to
get my hands dirty.
(FESTlVE MUSlC PLAYlNG)
Ahhh !
(BEARS GROWLlNG)
(WEEPlNG)
Crying in the corner, huh?
Mind if l join ya?
No, go ahead.
(BOTH WEEPlNG)
All right,
that's enough,
Fraidy Sue!
Here's what
you gotta do.
Find that bear
that whupped ya
and whup him back!
Can l fight
human-style
by slowly poisoning his
environment until he loses
his fur and becomes sterile?
You cowardly Swede! You face
that bear like a man or l'll
never speak to you again !
But how will l find out
what you had for lunch
in 1 928?
l have a web site!
ABE: WeIcome to my
home page. Why don't
you visit more often?
Mr. Simpson, if you want
to find that bear that
attacked you, use this.
lt tracks an electronic tag
l stuck in the bear's ear.
lt's the same technology
they use to keep tabs on
Gary Busey.
Finally, science has
joined forces with revenge.
Now listen.
The bull grizzly
is seven feet tall, weighs
more than a Mazda Miata
and can tear through a tree
like a Jewish mother
through self-esteem.
Next time you face him,
you better have some way
to protect yourself.
(CRUNCHlNG)
It's the eye of the tiger
it's the thriII of the fight
Risin' up to the chaIIenge
of our rival
And the...
Lookin' good.
And l did it all without
wasting money on one of
those stupid welder's masks.
(SlZZLlNG)
Behold the ultimate
in anti-bear technology!
The Bear Buster 5000!
Available wherever
fat men dream.
(DRAMATlC MUSlC PLAYlNG)
Oh, dear Lord.
Check it out, ladies. A suit
that makes me completely
invulnerable to bear attacks.
(GASPlNG)
Homer, there's no
rear on that thing.
l know. lf l get
really scared, l don't
want to ruin the suit.
Now look here, mister.
l forbid you to fight
a bear.
What kind of an example
would l be if l didn't
take revenge on things?
Dad, you can't take
revenge on an animal.
That's the whole
point of Moby Dick.
Lisa, the point of
Moby Dick is be yourself.
You're not going
and that's final.
D'oh !
Fine! But do you
know how ridiculous
you look right now?
(SOFTLY) Marge,
are you awake? Marge?
(CHUCKLlNG)
(THUDDlNG)
(CLANGlNG)
(CREAKlNG)
Hmm. (CHUCKLlNG)
Marge is sure gonna
be steamed when she
finds you missing.
Or dead.
Gentlemen, sometimes
a man must put
his marriage at risk
for reasons that are
confusing even to him.
You're sneaking out
to fight that bear.
l want to go, too!
No way! lf something happens
to me, you have
to carry on the Simpson name.
Screw that. When l grow up,
l'm legally changing my name
to Joe Kickass!
That is so cool !
All right, you can come.
Lisa, l think your
father just left!
And Bart's
missing, too!
l've got a bad feeling
about this. Let's check
the suit closet.
Zoot suit,
astronaut outfit,
southern belle,
Renaissance dandy,
country-western octopus. . .
(GASPlNG)
lt's gone!
That man
and his foolish pride.
We've gotta go follow him.
Hmm.
(GlGGLES)
l just wanted to see
what it was like.
(lN SOUTHERN ACCENT)
Howdy, y'all.
lf you don't like my song,
l'll spray you with ink!
(CHUCKLlNG)
l never realized
how hot this suit is.
l'm sweating out
all my bloodlust.
Why don't you take
a bath in the river?
This bear tracker stopped
beeping a half hour ago.
Sweet!
Hey, the batteries are
missing from this thing.
Yeah. We borrowed
'em for the radio.
BOTH: (SlNGlNG)
Skyrockets in flight,
afternoon deIight
Rub-a-dub-dub,
I'm washing the fIub
(ROARlNG)
Oh, my God !
Lenny! Carl ! Bart!
ALL: (SlNGlNG)
Rubbing sticks
and stones together
Makes the sparks ignite
And the thought of Ioving
you is getting so exciting
Skyrockets in flight
(HOMER SCREAMlNG)
Mr. Connor,
thank you for helping
find my husband.
l don't want my last
words to him to be,
"Clip your toenails,
they look like Fritos."
Mom ! Mom !
Stop the car!
Dad went to take a bath,
and the bear carried him off!
Yeah. lt almost
wrecked the whole trip.
Ma'am, l will find
your husband before
that bear kills him.
But first, a snack.
(FlRES GUN)
l guess this is it.
lf l'm gonna die,
l'm gonna die a man.
(ROARlNG)
(ELECTRlClTY CRACKLlNG)
(WHlMPERlNG)
ls this thing
hurting you?
Hmm.
(CRACKLlNG)
Ahhh !
(PANTlNG)
Okay, it's probably the tag.
But just to be sure.
(CRACKLlNG)
(YELLlNG)
Hey, you're not mean.
lt was just this tag
that made you go ape-scat.
We're not so different.
Gimme a hug !
Jeez, l don't know
why bear hugs enjoy
such a great reputation.
I guess that's so,
we don't have a lot
But at least l'm sure
of aII the things we got
Babe
(GlGGLlNG)
I got you babe,
I got you babe
Funny.
(GUNSHOT)
Oh, no. The hunter
has become the hunter.
He must be following
this thing.
Well, l'm gonna
make sure it never harms
another living creature!
(ELECTRlClTY CRACKLlNG)
MAN ON RADlO: A kiIIer
bear is on the loose
in Springfield Forest.
And IocaI Iaughingstock
Homer Simpson is missing
and presumed mauIed.
(CHUCKLlNG)
Wrong again,
liberal media.
MAN ON RADlO: A bounty has
been pIaced on the rogue bear
in the amount of $1 0,000.
Don't worry.
l'll find you
someplace safe.
The bear is no longer
wearing his tracking device.
(MOCKlNGLY) And it looks
like he's headed toward
that wildlife sanctuary.
ls there any sign
of my husband?
Hmm.
Your husband appears to be
traveling with the bear.
Either as hostage
or as what we call
a "forest bride."
Ew!
Okay. You want
to go over there.
Hold on. Something
doesn't feel right.
(GROWLlNG)
Wait, stop. l know bullets
can be scary sometimes.
But l have an idea.
First, we pull off
all your fur.
(ROARlNG)
All right, all right!
l'm still thinking.
They're looking for
a male bear, right?
(GROWLS)
Oh.
lt's so easy to condemn,
so hard to create.
Okay, boys. That bear's gonna
make a dash for freedom,
unless we take him down.
(COCKS GUN)
Yeah. All the way down.
What you said didn't
really add much.
(COCKS GUN)
l know. l just
wanted to belong.
(COCKS GUN)
Well, we all feel
that way sometimes.
(COCKS GUN)
(GUNS COCKlNG)
lt's Homer!
Don't shoot!
Go! Go!
lt's that bear!
Aim for the holes
in the colander!
He made it! He's finally
protected from man.
Yeah. But now he's being
attacked by an elephant!
(TRUMPETlNG)
Well, l'm proud
of you, Homie.
You set out to
fight an animal,
and you ended up
saving its life.
What can l say?
l love nature.
Circle of life.
English - US - PSDH