♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
(all yelling)
Hello? Hello?
-We're here for the field trip.
-(siren wails)
Sorry. Sorry.
Boy, it's getting
harder and harder
to make it here by 10:00.
(coughing)
We'll start the tour
in a second.
I've just got to check
the answering machine.
(beeping)
Oh, can't anybody in this town
take the law into
their own hands?
(beep)
Gather around, kids.
We're about to enter
the museum--
-(kids groaning)
-Oh, man.
...of crime.
(cheering)
Now, what I am
about to show you next
may shock and educate you.
Hold on to your values
as we step through
the looking glass
into a hippie pot party.
While Johnny Welfare plays
acid rock on a stolen guitar,
his old lady has a better idea.
(switch clicks)
-(all gasp)
-That's right.
She's got the munchies
for a California cheeseburger.
NARRATOR:
So the next time
you're walking on the beach
enjoying an hourglass
or making cheap
low-grade windshields,
think where we'd be
without sand.
♪ Sand, sand ♪
♪ Sand ♪
Okay, that was the sand movie.
Now, it'll just take me a second
to set up our next movie.
Oh, Miss Hoover,
movies are a nice break,
but couldn't we be doing
something a little more
challenging?
Probably.
NARRATOR:
The moon--
for several years,
she has fascinated many.
But will man ever walk
on her fertile surface?
Democratic hopeful
Adlai Stevenson says so.
I have no objection
to man walking on the moon.
NARRATOR: By 1964, experts say
man will have established
12 colonies on the moon--
ideal for family vacations.
Once there, you'll weigh
only a small percentage
of what you weigh on earth.
Slow down, tubby.
You're not on the moon yet.
The moon belongs to America
and anxiously awaits
the arrival of our astro men.
Will you be among them?
(film reel flapping)
Miss Hoover, the movie's over.
Where's Miss Hoover?
Hey, her car's gone.
Maybe she drove to the moon.
It's not my nature to complain,
but so far today,
we've had three movies,
two filmstrips,
and an hour and a half
of magazine time.
I just don't feel challenged.
Of course, we can make things
more challenging, Lisa,
but then the stupider students
would be in here complaining,
furrowing their brows
in a vain attempt
to understand the situation.
(groans)
We're now in
the Communications Room
or the Com Room.
Uh, this is a police radio--
the single most important piece
of equipment in the Com Room.
As you can see,
some of the boys like to put
their banana stickers
all over it.
There's Chiquita.
There's Del Monte.
There's a Banana Co.,
Gorilla's Choice.
Now, everyone follow me
to my chair,
where I just need to get
off my feet for a few minutes.
Ahh!
Ah... I won't be
getting up soon.
Testing.
(louder)
Hmm.
Hey.
(devilish laughter)
(buzzing)
Testing!
(voice echoing)
Testing, testing, testing...
-(parrots screeching)
-PARROTS: Testing, testing...
(echoing continues)
(screams)
(loud ringing)
You've really done it this
time, Bart!
You're in for the punishment
of a lifetime!
When do you expect
the ringing will stop?
In about ten to 15 seconds.
I certainly hope so!
-(ringing stops)
-Ooh! That's better.
(pops)
Now, about your punishment,
young man.
I know. I'll go to my room
and think about what I did.
Oh, no. Your room
is full of toys.
You're going
to the, uh, garage.
You're the boss.
I tell you, Chief,
I just don't know what
we're going to do with him.
You know,
you do have options.
For example, there are
behavior-modifying drugs.
How wedded are you
to the Bart you know?
-Not very.
-No. No drugs.
Bart just needs
a little discipline.
Hey, what about military school?
It set my brother straight.
Now he owns and operates
a famous cave.
Hmm. You know,
maybe Chief Wiggum is right.
Military school is a good idea.
-(motor whirring)
-(siren yelps)
Wow! I can't believe
we're going to Disneyland.
Hey, where's all your luggage?
-Hurray!
-Oh, yeah!
You dream about this day
for so long.
Then when it comes,
you don't know
what to say.
Shh, shh, shh.
Edna, your tears say
more than words ever could.
(choking)
Military school?
You lied to me.
Well, I'm sorry
if you heard Disneyland,
but I distinctly said
military school.
And that's how
we'll mold your boy
into a productive
member of society--
through an intensive program
of push-ups
and formation marching.
Well, it certainly
was nice of you
to accept Bart
in the middle
of the semester.
Fortunately, we've had
a couple of recent freak-outs.
So that freed up
a couple of bunks.
-Freak-outs?
-If that happens,
are we still charged
for the entire semester?
Our high standards
challenge students
to reach their full potential.
Look at how disciplined
they are.
They're just like
the terra-cotta
warriors of Xian.
They sure are.
Ow!
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
That's not
so disciplined.
They're just children,
Mr. Simpson.
Pww! I guess.
Truth is beauty,
beauty truth, sir!
(gasps)
They're discussing poetry.
Oh! We never do that
at my school.
But the truth can be
harsh and disturbing.
How can that be
considered beautiful?
Oh, they sure sucked
the fun out of that poem.
Please don't make me stay, Dad.
I'll do anything you say.
I'll find religion;
I'll be good, sometimes.
-Let go of my leg.
-No!
Son, for the last time
you're staying
at military school.
And so am I.
(gasps)
This school has everything
I ever wanted.
Lisa, no!
This place is just
a jail for children.
No jail can hold me.
All right, let's go
over this one more time,
just to make sure
I understand the situation.
(clearing throat)
You're a girl?
-Yes.
-Oh, gosh darn it.
I just don't understand
the situation.
(clearing throat)
You're a girl.
All I want is a chance
to prove myself.
Hmm.
In our 185 years, we have
never had a female cadet.
Oh, but that seems
to be the way
the wind is blowing
these days.
After all,
we have female singers...
female motorists.
Hmm.
Welcome aboard.
Lisa, if you ever want
to quit and come home,
I'll be here in half a jif.
I want to quit and come home.
Oh, honey,
I heard you the first time.
(kisses)
Atten-hut!
Gentlemen, we now have
a girl cadet among our ranks,
so we're going to have
to make a few changes.
First of all, Franklin,
you are no longer
the girliest cadet here.
Well, we'll see about that.
Second, this is now
the girls' barracks.
So pack your things.
You're moving in
with company "L."
Company "L"?
But they smell.
Yes, we've all
heard the chant.
Now, fall out!
Sorry. Sorry.
I know we'll be friends.
Talk about getting off
on the wrong foot.
(nervous chuckle)
I can't believe
they let a girl in.
Don't worry. We'll drive her
out of the academy.
That is why God created hazing.
(thunder rumbling)
(grunting)
What's the matter?
Don't girls like doing
push-ups in the mud?
Is there any answer
I can give
that won't result
in more push-ups?
(all whispering)
No.
Hey, look,
it's the school motto.
"I'll die before
I surrender, Tim."
Who's Tim?
Apparently, Tim was somebody
who was with the general
moments before he was shot
in the head.
Cleaning graffiti
off a statue
makes a mockery
of everything I stand for.
I don't think I can
survive here, Lise.
That's how they want you
to feel.
But if you just hang
in there,
they'll eventually
accept you.
Get to work!
I want to see my face
in that horse's ass.
Okay, that's long enough.
Let's see how they're doing.
Had enough?
(both groaning)
What's say you, men?
Has this lowly maggot
passed the test?
Congratulations, Bart.
You made it.
Hey, what about me?
I'm a lowly maggot.
(gunfire)
Well, since you attended
public school,
I'm going to assume that
you're already proficient
with small arms.
So we'll start you off
with something
-a little more advanced.
-(nervous chuckle)
Four out of five, Simpson--
impressive.
But you missed your last target.
Did I?
Ha-ha!
You're a born
soldier, Simpson.
Too bad it doesn't run
in your family.
Uh, could someone help me?
It's stuck on "auto fire."
-Brad, you hear anything?!
-No!
(gun clicking)
(panting)
Maybe you should
just learn to use this.
If there's a war,
just blow on it,
and I'll come
help you.
(touch-tones beeping)
I am just calling home.
I am not asking to come home.
(phone ringing)
(ringing)
Marge! You got that?
-Marge!
-(yelps)
Hey, go on, boy.
Go get it.
Answer the phone.
D'oh!
There's got to
be something
on this thing
for that thing.
-(ringing stops)
-Ahh.
-(groans)
-(phone ringing)
-Simpson.
-Hot diggity!
I don't care if it's bad news.
Oh, Grampa,
you're not busy, are you?
Well, you're really asking
two questions there.
The first one takes me
back to 1934.
Admiral Byrd had just
reached the pole
only hours ahead
of the three stooges.
And I guess
he won the argument,
but I walked away
with the turnips.
The following morning,
I resigned my commission
in the Coast Guard.
The next thing I heard,
there was civil war in Spain.
And that's everything
that happened in my life
right up to the time
I got this phone call.
Uh-huh. So, anything else
you wanna talk about?
Oh, I'm afraid I'd just be
repeating myself, honey.
(groans)
Anyway, other people need
to use the phone.
ALL: Mm-mmm.
I've already talked to her
for 20 damn minutes.
(groans)
Hmm? Oh!
(laughing, chattering)
BOY: You're all right.
Shh.
What is it?
Bart, I got a cassette
from Mom and Dad.
I thought we could listen
to it together.
Ah, gee, Lise,
I'd love to
but this really
isn't a good time.
-Bart, who you talking to?
-Uh...
Lisa. You're talking to Lisa.
I'm talking to...
No one.
All right, lights out!
(thud)
Ow! Damn it!
Lights on. Lights on.
Lights out. Lights out.
(door slams)
MARGE:
And don't worry, sweetie.
It's very common
to be homesick
when you're so far away from
the people who love you.
Okay,
I'm not going to give up.
Solitude never hurt anyone.
Emily Dickinson lived alone,
and she wrote some
of the most beautiful poetry
the world has ever known--
hmm-- and went crazy
as a loon.
(tape rewinds)
MARGE:
♪ You are my sunshine,
my only sunshine ♪
♪ You make me happy
when skies are gray ♪
♪ You'll never know, dear,
how much I love you ♪
♪ So don't take
my sunshine away ♪
Sorry I froze you out, Lise.
I just didn't want
the guys to think
I'd gone soft
on the girl issue.
I'm tired of
being an issue, Bart.
Maybe everyone would be
better off if I just quit.
But if you quit,
it'd be like
an expert knot-tier quitting
a knot-tying contest
right in the middle
of tying a knot.
Why'd you say that?
I don't know.
I was looking at my shoelaces.
Look, the point is
you're going to make it, Lise,
and I'm gonna stick by you.
Don't do that.
Why should we both be outcasts?
Then I'll just stick
by you in secret
like a sock-maker secretly
working on a top secret sock--
will you stop looking
at your feet?
Well, cadets,
it's been a great year.
You've all worked
very hard developing
academic skills
and general killing skills.
My killing teacher says
I'm a natural.
But these skills are nothing
without courage and stamina.
Traditionally, the academy
tested these virtues
by pitting you
against each other
in a two-day Battle Royale.
-(all gasp)
-That was prior to 1957.
Thank you very much,
State Supreme Court.
Consequently now, no cadet
can receive a passing grade
for the academic year
without first conquering this.
Meet "The Eliminator."
That's a 150-foot
hand-over-hand crawl
across a 60-gauge hemp-jute line
with a blister factor of 12.
The rope is suspended
a full 40 feet
over a solid British acre
of old-growth Connecticut Valley
thorn bushes.
Gentlemen,
welcome to Flavor Country.
This wasn't in the brochure.
(overlapping chatter)
Hey, Bart, come on over here.
There's plenty of room.
"Meet me at the Eliminator
after lights out.
"P.S.--
The cadets are planning
to throw their meatballs
at you."
Hmm.
(groans)
That's it, Lise.
Now start crawling.
Oh, it's too hard.
My hand is slipping.
(screams)
I can't do this, Bart.
I'm not strong enough.
I thought you came here
looking for a challenge.
Duh. A challenge I could do.
It was worth
sneaking into town.
That was some good corn.
Uh-oh.
Uh, hey, Simpson.
What are you doing out here?
-Nothing.
-Nothing?
Doesn't look like nothing.
Oh, yeah?
Well... um...
What are you doing out here?
Uh... also nothing.
Well.
Okay.
-Okay.
-Then carry on.
All right, we will.
(sighs)
That was close.
Bees.
BART: Bees? Aah!
-(screaming)
-(body thuds)
Gentlemen,
I regret to inform you
that the State Supreme Court
has determined
that forcing cadets
to cross the eliminator
is a barbaric
and malicious practice.
-Yes!
-Hence, you will be
the last class
to be subjected to it.
Anderson, you're up.
(yelling)
Son of a...
Jeez.
-(sighs)
-Good job, Simpson.
Although that's more cursing
than I like to hear
from a cadet in peace time.
Last up...
Simpson, Lisa.
(playing "Taps")
(shouting insults)
Well, at least
they're talking to me.
(gasps)
(crow caws)
Oh.
(sighs)
If only I were in Springfield,
all my friends would be
cheering me on.
Oh, God, I'm delirious.
-(screaming)
-(cheering)
-(chanting)
-(straining)
Drop, drop, drop,
drop, drop, drop,
drop, drop, drop...
(chanting continues)
You can make it, Lisa.
I know you can.
Come on,
I know you can do it.
Just get your hands
back on the rope.
It's just a little further.
Come on, just a little bit more.
You're doing great.
That's it. Come on,
just a little bit more.
I know you can do it!
I believe in you!
Yes!
You thought I couldn't,
but I could, I did,
and I could do it again.
Let's do it again!
Lisa, it's over;
you made it.
You can put your arms down.
I can't. They're stuck.
We're going to make
your life a living hell
for the rest of the semester.
But graduation's in three hours.
Oh, we better go change.
-♪♪ (fanfare plays)
-The wars of the future
will not be fought
on a battlefield or at sea.
They will be fought in space--
or possibly on top
of a very tall mountain.
In either case,
most of the actual fighting
will be done by small robots,
and as you go forth today,
remember always,
your duty is clear,
to build and maintain
those robots.
-Thank you.
-(cheering)
Well, Bart...
(nervous chuckle)
Did you make sure
to return all the guns?
Sir, yes, sir.
Luckily I am now trained
in six additional forms
of unarmed combat, sir.
-Well, he's got more confidence.
-Uh, yeah.
I've always said the boy
could use more confidence.
Lisa, before you go,
I want to present you
with this.
A medal?
Thank you, sir.
Hmm.
"For satisfactory
completion
of the second grade."
-Oh.
-Well, kids,
we're so proud of the way
you completed military school,
we thought this time,
we'd take you to Disneyland
for real.
-Yay!
-Hey!
(laughing)
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.