♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-(screams)
-(tires screech)
(screams)
Tonight on
"Eye on Springfield"--
Opening day at the world's
first two-story outhouse.
MAN: Oh, God! Stop!
A comedy nurse who's laughing
all the way to the blood bank.
Okay, how many of you are here
for shoulder surgery, huh?
(people groaning)
Gotcha!
But first,
move over, Baltimore.
Springfield
has stolen your idea.
I'm walking
on the waterfront--
Once the center of a thriving
squid-gutting industry,
now abandoned by all
but a few longshoremen
and allied tradespeople.
But the decades of rot will end
with the opening
of the South Street Squidport,
an upscale
shopping promenade
with authentic
maritime theming.
And to kick it all off in style
area merchants will host
a black-tie gala Saturday night.
Ooh, that sounds
fabulous, Homer.
Stores throw
the best parties.
You like parties, huh?
Well, I just remembered
they're having a big one
down at the waterfront
this weekend.
You didn't
remember that.
You just saw it on TV.
The important thing
is I didn't imagine it.
I can't get enough
of "The BabySitter Twins."
They arrested
the counterfeiters,
rescued the president
and made four dollars.
I love everything about
the world of baby-sitting--
The responsibility,
the obligation, the pressure...
And full refrigerator
privileges.
That's a trust, Janey,
a sacred trust.
jeez, lighten up, Lisa.
(organ plays)
LOVEJOY:
That concludes our service.
All right, I have
two announcements.
Friday you will have the chance
to party down
in the church basement
to the Jesus rock
stylings of Testament.
That's Friday,
6 p.m. sharp.
All the best bands are
affiliated with Satan.
Also, anyone in need of a reliable
and affordable baby-sitter
should call
Lisa Simpson.
Mention the topic
of today's sermon
to get a dollar off.
(man coughing)
(clearing throat)
The topic was love.
Why hasn't anyone called?
Maybe people don't want an
eight-year-old baby-sitter, honey.
Parents need to be sure
their sitter can handle
anything that might happen.
That's why they hire teenagers.
But, but I'm very
mature for my age.
People often
mistake me for nine.
(doorbell chimes)
Homer, I've got a Fozzie
of a bear of a problem.
That Maude and her mother
were visiting Tyre and Sidon,
the twin cities
of the holy land.
They must have kneeled
in the wrong place
and prayed to
the wrong god
because, well, they're being held prisoner
by militants of some sort.
Militants, huh? Well, if I were you,
I'd kick their asses.
Well, any hoodily-doodle,
the embassy says
it's just a routine
hostage taking
but I have to drive
to Capitol City,
fill out some forms
to get them out.
Could you possibly
watch the kids tonight?
Oh, gee, I'd really love
to want to help you, Flanders
but, uh... Marge was...
Taken prisoner in, uh...
Holy land, and, uh...
I'll do it!
I'll baby-sit!
Well, I don't know, Lisa.
You're awfully young,
and the boys
can be a handful.
Todd's been pinching
everyone lately.
But I'm smart and responsible
and my parents
will be right next door.
Well, what do
you say, Homer?
Can Lisa baby-sit
for my kids?
Please, please,
please?
Well, I'll have to ask her.
Where are the dice?
Daddy says dice are wicked.
We just move
one space at a time.
It's less fun that way.
-Moth! Moth!
Moth-moth-moth!
Don't worry.
A moth is no more harmful
than a ladybug.
-A ladybug?
(both screaming)
Uh, they're going to get
eaten alive in middle school.
And thank you
for sending Lisa
to protect us
from the bug you sent.
And please make Lisa
tell us a bedtime story...
about robots...
named Rod and Todd.
Amen.
Once there was
a robot named Todd...
Did he have a brother?
Yes, he had a brother
robot named Rod
who was two space
years older than him.
I don't like this story!
Oh, imagine that:
sleeping quietly
after a bug attack
and Todd's as
dry as a bone.
Lisa, you're a wonder.
I'm going to recommend you
to everybody.
So long, Lisa.
If anything goes
wrong, just dial 911.
Unless it's an emergency.
LISA:
Okay, chief. Enjoy Bob Saget.
Ha! It's Bob Seger.
Aw, crap.
Now, put your left leg
into the left side
of the pants
and you're done.
I dressed myself.
Hey, Dad. How come you're
wearing a tuxedo?
Going to that fancy
waterfront party tomorrow.
Why are you wearing it now?
It's like a rent-a-car, son.
You get all the mileage you can,
then ball it up
and cram it through
the mail slot.
(car door slams)
LISA:
Thanks for the ride.
You did a first-rate
job of baby-sitting.
I've never seen such
a responsible young lady.
Thank you, Dr. Hibbert.
Your trust means so much to me.
I only wish my Volvo
mechanic were as reliable.
(chuckling)
Good night, Lisa.
You made all that money
for sitting around and
watching TV and eating food?
There's a lot more
to it than that, Bart.
I don't just baby-sit.
I sell peace of mind
for a dollar an hour.
Two dollars after 9:00.
Man, if I was making
that kind of money
I'd be out of
here so fast...
(giggles)
LISA:
You look so glamorous, Mom.
Oh, and you smell
like vanilla flowers.
Dad, you look
totally classy.
You could be Abe Lincoln's
father's boss.
Can you see the pie stains?
It'll be dark.
So, when's Grampa getting here
to baby-sit?
Mmm, Grampa's not coming.
Oh, not Patty and Selma.
Actually, Bart, Lisa's
going to be in charge tonight.
-What?
-I know she's young,
but Lisa has proven herself
mature and dependable.
Dad, help me out.
Take it like a man, boy,
and do everything
your little sister says.
This is an outrage.
I am two years and 38 days
older than she is!
This is the greatest injustice
in the history of the world!
Well, we have to run.
I'm sure you kids
will work things out.
Good night.
Make sure he brushes
his teeth, Lisa.
Bart, I know
you're not wild
about having me
for a babysitter
but I'm not some ogre.
I think you will find me
fair and fun.
You're dead.
You should wash up for dinner.
To make it fun,
you can use the Mr. Bubble.
It'll be like giving
your fingers a bubble bath.
You are so dead.
(clattering)
Ah, I love this
pedestrian mall.
It's practically
no traffic.
(honking horn)
(gasping)
Mmm. I don't think
we should be driving here.
The mayor's yelling at us.
MAN:
Stop, you idiots!
All right, all right.
Jeez.
Okay, honey, remember
where we're parked.
May I have some more
lima beans, please?
Certainly.
More than that.
More.
Maybe you should eat
the ones you have.
I didn't say I was
going to eat them.
I just wanted
to look at them
because they're
so gross.
What's for dessert?
Bart, if you don't want
to have a baby-sitter,
maybe you should stop
being such a baby.
Oh, I'm a baby, huh?
Well, then,
I'll act like a baby.
Ga-ga-goo-goo.
Even babies know how to open
and close their mouths.
You need a bib.
Oh, baby hate bib.
Waah! Waah!
Waaah! Waaah!
(crying)
Oh, look, Bart.
Now you got Maggie
all upset.
Relax. I'll give her
some ice cream.
(slurping)
Bart, that's
coffee ice cream.
It has
caffeine in it.
Well, I guess that'll make
things more interesting
for you now,
won't it?
Ooh! It's so beautiful.
This is what I imagine
Paris must be like.
You've never been?
I'm so honored that Springfield
has been chosen
to host all these
upscale chain stores.
I guess this makes us
yuppies, huh, Homie?
Nah, I'm really
more of a slacker.
Ooh!
Malaria Zone.
That's where all
the explorers shop.
Look, Marge!
A restaurant owned
by celebrities.
I always wanted
to be a celebrity.
Ha-ha! Yes, it's true.
The entire menu was personally
approved by my secretary.
Isn't that clever?
It looks like a Cadillac
drove right into the building.
Help me.
Wow. Even Moe's moved
to fancy new digs.
Hey, this isn't
faux dive.
This is a dive.
You're a long way
from home, yuppie boy.
I'll start a tab.
Maggie, if you come down,
I'll give you some more coffee.
Lots more coffee.
(fast sucking sounds)
Are you getting ready
for bed, Bart?
I am!
That's right.
I want the 25-foot
Italian party sub.
And don't skimp
on the vinegar.
It's time Lisa learned
what baby-sitting Bart Simpson
is all about.
Um, yes, I'd like to host
an A.A. meeting.
Tonight if possible.
Come on, Maggie.
Good Maggie.
The talcum powder's
not to play with.
(coughing)
(groaning)
Ohh...
Okay, Bart now it's really time
for you to go to bed.
(grunting)
Why do you have
to make this so hard?
I'm using nonviolent resistance.
The idea that you would compare
yourself to Mahatma Gandhi...
-Who?
-(doorbell chimes)
I'll answer it.
You go to bed.
Good evening
there, miss.
Here's your giant sub
swimming in vinegar
just the way you like it.
It's going to be
$225 plus tip.
What? I didn't order
any giant sub.
(doorbell chimes)
Hey, hey!
Are you ready to get rowdy?
Excuse me?
Somebody hired me for an emergency
bachelor party.
Well, there's been a mistake.
Well, I'm not leaving
till I get paid.
I get 500 just
for "Hey, hey."
(siren wailing)
Who called for an emergency
sisterectomy?
(growls)
(shutter clicks)
(doorbell chimes)
We got a report
that a Lisa Simpson
spotted a U.F.O.
I didn't see any U.F.O.!
That's right, miss.
You didn't.
I'm here to pick up
the ambassador from Ghana.
Well, he's not here!
Nobody's here!
None of you
should be here!
You've all been tricked!
Why would the ambassador
do such a thing?
This is ridiculous.
I'm going to
bill them later.
Bart, you are going to be
in so much trouble when
Mom and Dad get home.
Now, go to bed!
You're the boss.
(groans)
I thought I told
you to go to bed.
Yeah, right. Bread.
You said go to "bread."
I said go to bed.
Yeah, go to "bread."
B-E-D! Bed!
Oh... Bed.
Oh.
Well, anything
you say, sis.
You didn't say which bed.
Go to your bed!
-Make me.
-I'll make you.
If you want me,
you got to catch me.
(snarls)
-Almost.
-(snarls)
-Oh, so close.
-Bart!
(grunting)
Son of a--
Oh, my God.
Okay, we'll call it even
if I can just have some
of that big sandwich.
Oh...
I'll come back.
Bart, are you okay?
Ohh. Yeah, I think so.
It's just a bump
on my head.
Ew, your arm.
It's got extra
corners.
Yah! Oh, cool.
It must be dislocated
or something.
We have to get you
to the emergency room.
And get this fixed?
What's the rush?
Don't you want
everyone to see
what a responsible
baby-sitter you were?
Stop it. Stand still.
Maybe I can pop it back in.
No, I'm going to preserve
the evidence
until Mom and Dad get home.
And you'll never
baby-sit again!
(door slams, locks)
You know, honey
when I think of all the good
times we've had together...
Yeow!
Did you see that, Marge?
Oh, my God, you walked
into the fountain.
Get out of
the fountain!
(shrieking)
I can't get out.
Just stand still
and I'll get someone.
I can't get out.
(sobbing)
(crowd laughing)
Don't laugh at me.
I was once like you.
Bart, you need first aid.
Let me in.
I'm afraid
you'll hurt me again.
Bart, if you come out,
I'll let you eat
raw cookie dough.
I'll let you...
ride the lawn mower
through the house.
Come on, open the door!
(pounding)
What are you doing now?
BART: I'm banging
my head.
I'm going to make
the lump even bigger.
(chuckling)
No! As your baby-sitter
I order you to stop hitting
your head on the wall!
(thump)
Bart?
Did you stop
because I said to?
If so, thank you.
Bart?
(whimpering)
(gasps)
(beeping)
WOMAN: 911.
Hello, this is Lisa Simpson...
Simpson? Look, we've already
been out there tonight
for a sisterectomy,
a case of severe butt-rot,
and a leprechaun bite.
How dumb
do you think we are?
(dial tone)
Oh.
Wait. Dr. Hibbert.
Hmm...
Dislocated shoulder,
bump on the noggin.
My diagnosis?
Bad baby-sitting.
Well, near
as we can tell,
the boy was
studying quietly,
when the girl,
drunk on her
own sense of power,
beat him silly with a block of
frozen lima beans.
It's true!
Young lady, you will
never baby-sit again.
I am so disappointed.
(echoing)
Oh, well, I guess
I don't have a choice.
"Complete confidentiality"?
Oh? And I'm sure
he's as good as Dr. Hibbert.
It says so
right in his ad.
What's
the matter, Marge?
I thought you loved
Jell-O shooters.
(slurping)
Oh, I do.
I'm just a little concerned
about the kids.
Maybe I should call.
Oh, come on,
Marge, relax.
Lisa's in charge.
She's
the responsible one.
(grunts)
Hold on, Bart.
Everything's going
to be just fine.
I'm going to get you
to a doctor.
He will fix you up.
And by this time tomorrow,
we'll all be a happy family.
Happy, happy,
happy family.
(babbling)
Maggie!
Please, Maggie.
Please go to sleep.
Yo, um, I must have, like,
fallen on a bullet,
and it, like, drove
itself into my gut.
Hey, don't worry.
You don't have
to make up stories here.
Save that for court.
Um, excuse me,
Mr. Smithers.
Bart may be
seriously hurt.
Could we possibly
go ahead of you?
Um... No.
I really would rather
get this taken care of.
Excuse me, little lady.
The wheelbarrow line
is over there.
Ooh, loneliness
and cheeseburgers
are a dangerous mix.
(groans)
(siren blaring)
Hold it right there.
Well, if it isn't
Springfield's
finest little baby-sitter,
Lisa Simpson.
-Hi. How are you?
-Um, I'm fine.
Now, Lisa, when
you're walking
down the side
of the road,
you always want
to be sure
to go with
traffic, okay?
Well, is that with traffic
or against traffic?
No, it's with traffic--
with traffic.
Anyway, good night.
(sighs)
Uh, hold on
a minute.
Let me have a look at
that wheelbarrow, please.
Okay.
Just as I thought.
It's a Yard King.
That is
a quality barrow.
Well, I got to run.
(engine starting)
(car departs)
Oh, God.
Where's Bart?
(gasps)
(Lisa moaning)
(moaning)
(grunts)
Oh, Bart,
I'm so sorry.
This is all
like a bad dream.
(switch clicks)
Citizens of Springfield,
I officially declare this--
What the hell is that?
Why, it's Lisa Simpson
and look what she's doing.
(crowd gasping)
MAN:
I don't believe it.
She's murdered her brother.
And she's trying to dump
the body in the harbor.
Well, duh.
And as a grim finale,
she intends to drown
that poor caged baby.
What's happening?
Where am I?
And she's on drugs!
Give me the drugs, Lisa.
Dad, I am
not on drugs.
I was just
trying...
Oh, his arm!
Oh, my special little guy.
Are you okay?
Hmm. Dislocated shoulder,
bump on the noggin.
My diagnosis?
A rather nasty fall...
caused by bad baby-sitting!
(crowd gasping)
Hey, Bart.
-How's your arm?
-It's all right.
I was hoping they'd give me
one of them steel claws,
but what are you going to do?
Hmm.
I'm... I'm sorry
I was such a jerk last night.
I guess I sort of ruined
your baby-sitting business.
Yeah, well, that's okay.
I can always sell seeds.
Do you want some seeds?
-No, thanks.
-Oh.
(ringing)
Hello.
World's worst
baby-sitter speaking.
DR. HIBBERT: Lisa,
I'm glad I reached you.
Are you available
to baby-sit tonight?
Aren't you afraid
I might take drugs
and injure your children?
Yes, that is a concern,
but it's so hard
to find a sitter,
and I've got judo tonight.
-(beep)
-Um, okay.
I'm sorry.
Can you hold on, please?
Hello.
FLANDERS:
Lisa, Ned Flanders.
You available tonight?
Didn't you hear
I almost killed my brother?
FLANDERS: You did?
Just a minute.
(muffled conversation)
What time
can you come over?
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.