♪ The Simpsons ♪
-(chalk screeches)
-(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(tires screeching)
(horn honks)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
Uh... Chief Wiggum,
Archbishop McGee,
distinguished guests,
I am pleased to dedicate
this emergency warning system.
In the off-chance
of a nuclear disaster
this sign will tell you,
the good citizens of Springfield
what to do.
HOMER:
The joke's on them.
If the core explodes,
there won't be any power
to light that sign.
And now, I would like to present
the man who made this sign possible
by dropping the last of his
obstructionist legal challenges,
Montgomery Burns.
Mr. Burns is never late.
Something must be
terribly wrong.
There better be. Nobody leaves
Diamond Joe Quimby holding the bag.
(gasping)
Must turn over.
Got to greet dignitaries.
Oh, no! Mr. Burns!
We've got to get a doctor.
Absolutely not.
No quack Sawbone's is
going to apply
his leeches to me.
As long as there's
an ounce of strength
-left in me, I--
-(body thuds)
Mmm.
Mr. Burns is suffering
from what we medical men
call hypohemia.
In laymen's terms, it's quite
simply a lack of blood.
Damn it, doctor, I'm no idiot.
I know what hypohemia is.
What I want to know is
what can we do about it?
Well, at this point,
our only hope is a transfusion.
How long does it take
to sterilize a needle?
-A few seconds.
-Oh, skip it!
Just leave me enough
to get home.
(chuckling)
I'm afraid it's not that simple.
His blood type
is double-o-negative.
-It's quite rare.
-But I'm b-positive.
Damn my common gutter-blood
in my veins.
Smithers, don't feel so bad.
After all, the kidney
you donated to me
really hit the spot.
SMITHERS:
Attention all employees!
Our boss and inspiration,
Mr. Burns,
is at death's... death's door.
-(scoffs)
-If you have type double-o-negative blood
I implore you to report
to the Bloodmobile outside.
That is all.
I'd give him my blood
except for one thing.
-What's that?
-I don't want to.
-(laughing)
-I can't believe you guys.
There's a human being
out there
with millions of dollars
who needs our help,
and you don't want
to cash in?
That's why you losers are stuck
in this crummy dead-end job.
-You know, Homer, I am your supervisor.
-Sorry, sir.
Maggie, look.
What's that?
Lee-mur.
Lee-mur. Zebu.
-Zeee-booo.
-What are you doing, honey?
I'm trying to teach Maggie that nature
doesn't end with the barnyard.
I want her to have all the
advantages that I didn't have.
Lisa, we did the best we could.
What's a zebu?
It's like an ox, only it has
a hump and a dewlap.
Hump and dewlap.
-Marge! What's my blood type?
-A-positive.
Aw, nuts! Extremely rare blood,
and I don't have it.
You know his blood type?
How romantic.
A mother knows everything
about her family.
-Oh, yeah? What's my shoe size?
-4-B.
-How many teeth do I have?
-16 permanent, eight baby.
-Earmuffs?
-XL.
-Ring?
-I don't want you wearing rings.
It looks cheap. But three.
-Allergies?
-Butterscotch
-and imitation butterscotch.
-And?
-Glow-in-the-dark monster makeup.
-Ooh, impressive.
How many hairs on my head?
Without looking.
Oh, Homey, you have
lots of hair.
Why did you want to know
your blood type?
Old man Burns is gonna
kick off if he doesn't get some
double-o-negative blood,
but nobody at the plant has it.
-Bart does.
-Whoa! Yes! All right! Whoo!
Congratulations, boy!
You've got a date
with a needle.
Hey, wait a minute.
I don't have to give blood.
I have rights, you know.
Yeah, you have the right
to remain silent.
Bart, you have to help
someone in need.
-It's the only decent thing to do.
-D'oh!
Bart, it's not like I'm asking you
to give blood for free.
That would be crazy. You're a little
young to understand this,
but when you save
a rich man's life,
he showers you with riches!
Don't you know the story
of Hercules and the lion?
-Is it a Bible story?
-Yeah probably.
Anyway, once upon a time,
there was a big, mean lion
who got a thorn in his paw,
and all the village people
tried to pull it out,
but nobody was strong enough.
So, they got Hercules.
And Hercules used
his mighty strength
and bingo!
Anyway, the moral is
the lion was so happy
he gave Hercules
this big thing of riches.
How did a lion get rich?
-It was the olden days.
-Oh.
Hey! Let's go!
Emergency!
Life or death here!
-Just a sec, man.
-Whoa, Otto, man.
-You work here?
-Oh, yeah.
During the day,
all my friends are in school,
so I got a job as a certified
bloodletting tech dude.
Now, let's get this
show on the road.
Okay. Let me wash up.
(humming "Iron Man"
by Black Sabbath)
Homer, brave young Bart...
I don't know
which one to hug first.
Uh, the boy.
-Eww.
-(tires screeching)
(humming tune)
-Oop!
-(bell dings)
We're ready with
the transfusion.
Smithers,
I'm not going to make it.
I want to dictate my epitaph.
-Go ahead.
-Charles Montgomery Burns...
-Mm-hmm.
-American...
-And a patriot American...
Patriot...
Master of the atom...
Scourge of the despot.
Oh, tyrant,
hear his mighty name and quake!
Smithers! I'm back!
BURNS:
Top of the morning to you.
Why, look who's here.
It's... good old... you.
Hi, Mr. Burns.
Oh! Hey, there, Mister...
Brownshoes.
How about that local
sports team?
Mr. Burns-- he's okay.
-Jackpot!
-(glass breaking)
Ay caramba!
(laughing)
Well, that's game.
Hasta mañana, Oswaldo.
Smithers, I'm back in the pink--
full of pith and vinegar.
Just remarkable, sir.
You know, it's funny, Smithers.
I tried every tincture
and poultice and tonic
and patent medicine there is,
and all I really needed was
the blood of a young boy.
-By the way, what was the lad's name?
-Bart Simpson, sir.
-Who?
-He's the son of Homer Simpson,
one of your stiffs
in sector 7-G.
Well, the Simpsons
will be getting
a very nice surprise
in the mail.
Very nice, indeed.
(fiendish laugh)
Bill, bill...
summons, bill...
(gasps)
Wait a minute.
From C.M. Burns.
This is it.
Yes, this is it!
Woo-hoo! Whoo!
Bart, Lisa, Maggie!
Let's do this out in the yard
where the neighbors can see.
Lisa, dim the lights.
No! turn on more lights.
Do something.
Yes, Dad.
It's a little thin,
but that's okay.
It could be a check.
Alright, there's no check.
Just a card,
but don't panic.
I'm sure it tells us
what we're getting
and where we can pick it up.
"Dear Bart,
Thank you kindly for the blood.
Yours truly, Montgomery Burns."
D'oh! It's just a card!
Is that some way
to show your gratitude?
No gold, no diamonds,
no jewelry...
not even a lousy card.
Wait a minute.
There was a card.
That's what got me so mad
in the first place!
You don't do things like that
to be rewarded.
You do them because a fellow
human being needs a helping hand.
Marge, you're my wife
and I love you very much,
but you're living
in a world of make-believe
with flowers and bells
and leprechauns
and magic frogs
with funny little hats.
-Yeah, Mom, we got hosed.
-Bart!
We got exactly what we wanted
out of this!
We gave an old man
a second chance.
I promised my boy
one simple thing:
lots of riches
and that man broke my promise.
Well I've had it!
Bart, take a letter!
Dear Mr. Burns
I'm so glad
you enjoyed my son's blood
and your card was just great.
In case you can't tell,
I'm being sarcastic.
You stink!
Could you read that
last part back to me?
-"You stink!"
-(chuckles) Good.
You are a senile,
buck-toothed old mummy
with bony girl arms,
and you smell like...
An elephant's butt?
(laughs)
An elephant's butt.
But he's your boss. Do you have to
mail it right this minute?
Yup.
You're still angry, Homer.
Why don't you sleep on it?
-Forget it, Marge.
-Please, Homey?
For me?
Oh, all right.
You always do
that hand thing,
and it usually works.
Cheap son of a...
(snoring)
Ooh, pancakes.
Ooh.
Homer, breakfast is ready.
Hmm?
(gags)
Marge, you saved me
from making a big mistake.
You know, I finally understand
the meaning of...
-(unintelligible)
-Meaning of what?
Better half, Marge.
Better half.
-Oh, thank you.
-Where's the letter?
(whistling)
-Where is it?
-(cans clattering)
Oh...
Homer, I don't think it's
in the cornstarch canister.
Well, it's somewhere.
It didn't just get up
and walk away.
-(whistling)
-Bart, have you seen the letter?
-Yep.
-All right, think very carefully.
Where did you see it last?
-The last place I saw it--
-Uh-huh?
-...was in my hand.
-Yeah?
As I was shoving it
into the mailbox.
HOMER:
D'oh!
Why did you do that?
Dad, there were things in the letter
that had to be said.
And I know you.
You're an emotional guy.
Just because you were mad
last night
is no guarantee
you'd be mad in the morning.
I'll show you mad
in the morning!
Homer, you encouraged him.
You should be strangling
yourself.
She's right.
Okay, think, Homer.
Don't panic.
They don't pick up the mail
till noon.
-There's still time!
-(gasps)
Ow, ow.
Give it up, Homer.
It's locked up tight.
Locked, eh?
Well, I just might
have a little surprise
up my sleeve
for old Mr. Lock.
Step aside, boy.
Hey!
I'm with you, Homer.
Fight the power!
-Why the hose, Homer?
-What does it look like?
I'll get our letter so wet,
the ink will run, and no one
will be able to read it.
Yeah, but don't other people
have mail in there?
So a few people won't get
a few letters. Boo-hoo.
You know the kind of letters
people write:
"Dear somebody
you never heard of--
"How is so and so?
"Blah, blah, blah.
Yours truly, some bozo."
Big loss.
Now, Bart, you keep an eye out
for the mailman.
Just give me some kinda signal.
-Dad, the mailman's here.
-That's a good one. We'll use that.
-No, I mean the mailman's here!
-(screams)
Dear God! Are you planning
to water the mail?
I guess it wouldn't do
any good to run,
'cause you're a mail lady and you know
my name and address and everything, huh?
-That's right.
-Well, I'm still going to run!
I want the whole world
to hear the story
of my harrowing struggle
with hypohemia.
Sir, Mr. Roman is one of the finest
ghostwriters in the business.
He's written
Like Hell I Can't,
Up From the Muck,
The Unsinkable
Sadruodin Mahbaradad.
-Excellent.
-All right, first question.
Have you slept
with anyone famous?
Well, Countess Von Zeppelin
and I...
What in blaze!
Now you listen to me,
you bargain-basement Baudelaire.
I'm not some dizzy starlet
who can't string
two words together.
I can write this thing myself!
You're fired!
(imitating Mr. Burns)
Hello. My name is Mr. Burns.
I believe you have
a letter for me.
Okay, Mr. Burns,
what's your first name?
I don't know.
Great plan, Bart.
Ooh, look, Maggie.
What is that?
Dodecahedron. Dodecahedron.
Lisa, I don't know
what you're doing
but it's very strange, and your father's
trying to worry.
BURNS:
Chapter the fifth--
the trip to the infirmary
with most unexpected results.
HOMER: Oops. 28 minutes
till Burns comes in.
Time for operation
"Mail Take."
-Can I help you?
-(shrieks)
Oh, don't be frightened
of this.
It's nothing but a letter opener.
Who are you?
Don't tell him.
Give him a fake name.
-Homer Simpson.
-D'oh!
Simpson, huh?
Simpson, why there's
a letter here from you.
I'll just read it right now.
"Dear Mr. Burns, I'm so glad
you enjoyed my son's blood,
and your card was just great."
Why, Simpson,
you've made my day.
You're a true gentleman.
-Well, I'll be on my--
-Hello, there's more.
"In case you can't tell,
I'm being sarcastic.
"You stink.
"You are a senile
"buck-toothed old mummy
with bony girl arms,
-and you smell like an elephant's butt."
-(nervous chuckle)
Hey! Come on, Joey,
you have to twist my arm?
Homer, I don't tell you how
to do your job, okay?
I could crush him like an ant,
but it would be too easy.
No, revenge is a dish
best served cold.
I'll bide my time until...
Oh, what the hell.
I'll just crush him like an ant.
Senile, eh?
Buck-toothed, am I?
Bony arms, are they?
Liver spots, did I?
-Shameless, will you?
-His pink slip awaits your signature, sir.
Hmm-hmm-hmm.
Now that's odd.
I've just robbed a man
of his livelihood,
and yet I feel
strangely empty.
Tell you what, Smithers,
have him beaten to a pulp.
-But, sir--
-But what?
Nothing, sir.
I've never seen
Mr. Burns this mad,
and he's always
kind of mad.
-(groans)
-Me and my big letter-writing pen.
Honey, what's done is done.
No matter what happens,
we'll pull through.
-We always do.
-Okay, here's the plan.
You can move in with your sisters
and raise the kids,
and I'll die in a gutter.
It's practical
and within our means.
(sobs)
They always told me I was
going to destroy the family,
but I never believed it.
That's okay, Bart.
Nobody really believed it.
We were just trying
to scare you.
-You know Homer Simpson?
-Yeah, nice guy.
Play poker with him
once in awhile.
Mm-hmm.
We, um, need him beaten up.
-You got it.
-Wait.
- What is it?
- Uh... nothing.
-Wait.
-What?
Beat, but don't kick.
-Hold the kicks. Got it.
-Wait.
-What?
-Um...
What did Homey do, anyway?
(sobbing)
He saved Mr. Burns's life.
(thunder rumbling)
In closing, gentle reader,
I'd like to thank you.
What's that you say?
Me thanking you?
No, it's not a misprint.
For you see,
I enjoyed writing this book
as much as you
enjoyed reading it.
The End.
Ah, Smithers,
how did the beating go?
Sir, there was no beating.
What? Well that's a hell
of a thing. Why?
-Because I-- I called it off.
-Judas!
I'm sorry, sir, but I just
couldn't hurt Homer Simpson.
-He saved your life.
-I see.
I know you're mad at me,
but I think it's only fair
to warn you,
I'm going to stand outside
the gate until you forgive me.
No need, Smithers.
As usual,
you've been the sober ying
to my raging yang.
-Put her there, old pal.
-(sniffles)
(sniffling) Sir, while I wish
this handshake would never end,
I'm afraid we still have
the Simpson matter to attend to.
We do indeed, old friend.
We do, indeed.
MOE: Moe's Tavern,
where the elite meet to drink.
BART: Uh, yeah.
Hello, is Mike there?
Last name Rotch.
Hold on, I'll check.
Mike Rotch! Mike Rotch?
Hey, has anybody seen
Mike Rotch lately?
(laughing)
Listen to me, you little puke.
One of these days
I'm going to catch you,
and I'm gonna carve my name
on your back with an ice pick!
(laughing)
What's the matter, Homer?
You're not your normal
effervescent self.
I've got my problems, Moe.
Give me another one.
Homer, hey, you should not drink
to forget your problems.
Yeah, you should always drink to
enhance your social skills. (burping)
BURNS: We'll get the Simpsons
a present--
an extravagant present.
A mad, unthinkable,
utterly impossible present.
A frabulous, grabulous,
zip-zoop zabulous present.
Too practical.
Too cutesie-poo.
-♪♪
-Too cornball.
A pool table?
Are you mad?
I'm not going to turn
his home into a saloon.
Eureka! We've found it.
But, sir, it's $32,000.
Don't you dare sully this moment
with your price taggery.
It's perfect.
Oh, woe is me.
Oh, my, it's Mr. Burns.
(yelps)
Heave-ho, heave-ho.
-Heave-ho.
-Wait, Dad, he's smiling.
Mr. Burns,
you brought us a present.
What did you think
I was going to do,
-have you beaten to a bloody pulp?
-(chuckles)
To show there's
no hard feelings,
please take an advance copy
of my book.
And now young fellow,
I haven't forgotten you.
-Here.
-Wow! A crowbar.
It's to open the crate, stupid.
What did I tell you?
I'll bet it's filled with diamonds,
rubies, sapphires, pearls.
BART:
Wow!
-A big, ugly head.
-D'oh!
Actually, son, it's a big,
ugly, Olmec Indian head.
It was carved by Mesoamerican
Indians over 3,000 years ago.
This gruesome customer
is Ixtapolapoquetl--
the god of war.
Awesome!
No, Maggie, not Aztec.
Olmec. Olmec.
Marge, what does it do?
It doesn't do anything.
Marge, really,
what does it do?
Whatever it does,
it's doing it now.
Well, I'll let you
get acquainted
with Señor Ixtapolapoquetl.
Ta!
Did you see their faces,
Smithers?
Sir, you're my god
of generosity.
HOMER: Save a guy's life
and what do you get?
Nothing. Worse than nothing--
Just a big, scary rock.
Hey, man,
don't badmouth the head.
Homer, it's the thought
that counts.
The moral of this story is,
a good deed is
its own reward.
Hey, we got a reward.
The head is cool.
Well, then I guess the moral is:
no good deed goes unrewarded.
Wait a minute!
If I hadn't written that nasty letter
we wouldn't have
gotten anything.
Well, then I guess
the moral is:
the squeaky wheel
gets the grease.
Perhaps there is
no moral to this story.
Exactly.
It's just a bunch of stuff
that happened.
But it certainly was
a memorable few days.
HOMER:
Amen to that.
(all laughing)
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.