(theme music playing)
CHORUS: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
(whistle blows)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
(jazzy solo)
(chimes)
(tires screeching)
(honking horn)
D'oh!
(screaming)
(tires screeching)
(elephants trumpeting)
"Olive oil"?
"Asparagus"?
If your mother wasn't so fancy,
we could shop at the gas station
like normal people.
I need this candy for school.
-Candy class.
-Well, OK, but get five bags
in case we eat four
on the way home.
My teacher said I need cupcakes.
-Cupcakes to learn.
-In the cart.
(panting)
I'm out of wine.
Cart.
(humming)
We need these
because we have to...
My doctor says and my garage mechanic
agrees that--
-In the cart.
-Woo-hoo!
You know, I always
felt sorry for Marge
having to do the shopping
but this is kind of fun.
Yeah. I wish Maggie had to go
to the emergency room more often.
(Dr. Hibbert laughing)
Hmm, I've never heard of a baby
swallowing a magazine before
and I'm a doctor.
I don't know if it matters,
but it was a Time magazine.
Does that matter?
Uh-oh, this could be dangerous.
What? What?
"Syrian hard-liners
are gaining influence."
(scanner beeping)
Wait, I changed my mind.
Stack it in the order
I'll eat it driving home.
Sir, please!
I've already bagged it
by color and in order of each
item's discovery by man.
The customer's always right.
That's what everybody
likes about us.
Now, mush!
You tell him, Jumbo.
And you, start over.
I want everything in one bag.
Yes, ma'am.
But I don't want the bag
to be heavy.
I don't think that's possible.
What are you,
the Possible Police?
Just do it.
Hey, hey, watch what
you're doing there, sack monkey.
You're bruising my DuraLog.
Hurry up.
I can't stand here
jabbing you all day.
Please, ow! Stop.
Bag boys have feelings,
too, you know.
No, you don't.
Ah, excuse me.
Is there a problem here?
No, I can handle it.
I'll get you, squealer.
Ow!
OK, that's it.
On behalf of Sack Stuffers
Local 199,
I'm calling a strike.
Strike! Strike!
(chanting)
Strike! Strike! Strike!
Strike! Strike! Strike! Strike!
Oh, the bag boys are on strike.
(mock shuddering)
Ooh... I'm shaking.
Mr. Simpson, please,
will you go home?
If I can have this rubber stick.
Pledging to honor
the bag boys' strike
are the Brotherhood
of Fruit Packers and Unpackers,
the Shelf Dusters Union
and the Unattractive Waitresses
of America.
Kiss my grits.
(chuckling) Indeed.
Good luck, sir.
No bag boys are
going to stop Lenny
from hosting a casual
get-together.
Casual?
Ah, I can taste that
get-together now.
-(glass shatters)
-Hey! I was holding that.
Next time I'll knock
your hat off, scab.
(whimpers)
So hungry.
There's got to be
some food left.
Sulfur jerky?
Cream of toast? Where did we get
all this crap?
Most of it was sent by relatives
who couldn't see very well.
Hey, I found some eggs.
The mother abandoned her nest.
(angry squawking)
(screaming)
(moans)
There's got to be something
to eat in this house.
(whimpering)
(sniffing)
Hey, the dog smells something.
Good boy, good boy.
Show us where the food is.
Where? Over there?
Hey!
(snarling)
(sniffing)
Yoink.
-(snarling)
-My old lunch box!
Oh, that Amos Burke
made his own rules.
(humming)
(gasps)
Very old animal crackers!
Mmm. Mmm.
(chomping)
Homer, no!
Those were made in the '60s.
Mmm... turbulent.
-(clank)
-Ow!
What the hell-
Whoa.
A solid gold animal cracker.
"Find the golden giraffe and we'll
send you and your family to Africa."
Africa? They're bound
to have food there.
And on my free African safari,
I wanna do everything on this box.
I want to shoot a lion in the face,
fight Muhammad Ali...
and ride in a convertible
with two happy zebras.
Sir, that contest ended
30 years ago.
We don't even make
animal crackers anymore.
We make household poisons
and Christmas lights.
Your box made promises
of a "vacational" nature...
and I expect you to
live up to them.
We won't though.
Sir, with all due respect, an old box
of cookies is not a legal contract.
Ow! My eye!
-We're in big, big trouble.
-Is that our fault?
-He could sue us.
-It was defective string.
Yeah, and it's got
very sharp corners.
Mr. Simpson, we've decided
to make good on your vacation.
Whoo-hoo!
-(whispering) Hey, mister.
-Yes?
On the plane I'm gonna
need two seats-
for the twins.
-The Simpsons are going to Africa.
-TOGETHER: Yay!
-(drums beating)
-(vocalizing)
-(gasps)
-What is it, Ngongo?
Evil is coming.
-What shall we do, Ngungo?
-Uh-
You are Ngongo now!
Aaah!
Africa looks like
a beautiful jewel.
And these musical garment bags
aren't bad either.
WOMAN (on P.A.):
Attention, passengers.
Please prepare for our
landing in Tanzania.
I'm sorry. It is now called
"New Zanzibar."
Excuse me. It is now called
"Pepsi Presents New Zanzibar."
Hello. Hello, Simpsons.
Welcome to Africa.
-I am your guide, Kitenge.
-Hey, how ya doin'?
-Hi.
-Hello.
Yo, Kitenge.
-Isn't that cute? A bush baby.
-Where?
-Aaah! Shoo! Shoo!
-(chattering)
Oh, man. I just bought
this shirt.
-Who's Muntu?
-He is our leader.
He seized power in a bloodless coup--
all smotherings.
Just like Jimmy Carter.
(brakes screech)
OK. You'll be sleeping
here tonight.
On the ground?
No, Mom.
Ohh.
I will come down for your bags.
That's OK. I got 'em. (grunts)
(all gasp)
(squeaks, hisses)
Eh. Bound to happen.
-(insects buzzing)
-Help! Ugh!
This mosquito net's not working.
No, no. You have it inside out.
There.
When do we get to
see the animals?
In the morning, little one.
Now, good night and don't let
the bedbugs paralyze.
(door closes)
MARGE: Homie, did you remember
to tip Kitenge?
KITENGE: No, he did not.
All right! I got another one.
Hey, you didn't see a warthog.
I'm looking at one right now.
Mom! Bart implied
I was a warthog.
MARGE: Nobody's a warthog.
-What about him?
-(snorting)
-Aaah!
-(laughs)
(gasps) Oh, look, everybody.
(elephants trumpeting)
HOMER: Wow!
It just rolled over to 10,000.
Now we sit quietly
and wait for nature to unveil herself.
(cracking)
(squeals)
Wait. Rhinos don't
come from eggs.
-What did you just see, Lisa?
-I know, but--
-What did you just see?
-Hmph. (gasps)
(braying)
Oh, now, come on.
Look, Mother,
by that tree-- Cheetah.
-(growling)
-Mmm. He doesn't look so fast to me.
(snarls)
-(gasps)
-(yowling)
(Kitenge singing in Swahili)
Take it, Homer.
♪ Glibbie, glop, gloopie ♪
♪ Nibbie, nobbie, noopie ♪
♪ La, le, lo, lo, lo... ♪
-(brakes screeching)
-What? What is it?
Mmm. Poachers.
(growling)
(gasps) That's terrible.
Now, honey, poachers are
nature's way of keeping the balance.
Whenever there are so many species
that people get confused and angry,
a poacher is born.
I don't care. I hate them.
-(all gasp)
-Let's get out of here!
They'll be back.
They left their cargo pants.
This is the earliest known
fossil of a human being.
It's over two million years old.
(blows raspberries)
I've got more bones than that guy.
If you're trying
to impress me, you've failed.
It's not the number
of bones, sir.
-It's the--
-You have failed.
(slurping)
(speaking Masai)
The Maasai chief
welcomes you to his village.
Oh, thank you.
Your ground is so comfortable.
By the way, what kind
of blood is this?
-Cow.
-(all gasp, laugh)
Hey, Mom.
Look what Mbali gave me.
Hey, check it out.
Bart! I told you not to
get your lip disked.
All right.
(voice quavering)
Uh-oh, boh-boh.
-(drums beating)
-(people chanting)
That's it! Get into
a frenzy. Aha!
(whooping)
(playing jazz riff)
This song has been
going on for hours.
Yeah. It's like
the Allman Brothers.
(babbling)
-Homer, no!
-(snarling)
-Aaah!
A hungry, hungry hippo.
(yelling)
Help! Kitenge!
-Now, Simpsons! Run for it.
-(clamoring)
(all gasp) Huh?
(Kitenge groaning)
Good old Kitenge.
(Kitenge screams)
(growling)
(snarling)
Aaah!
Quick! Into the river.
-Hippos hate water.
-No, they don't. They-- Aaah!
(squeals)
Shaka Zulu!
Which way should we go?
Mmm.
Hmm.
Hmm?
-The left! Go to the left!
-(grunting)
It's working. Aaah! Leeches!
-(chomp)
-Aaah!
(sighs)
-(wind whistling)
-uh-oh.
(all scream)
(birds calling)
OK, here's the situation.
We're hopelessly lost
and about to die.
-(roaring)
-(screaming)
Don't worry.
Being eaten by a crocodile...
is just like going to sleep...
in a giant blender.
Wonder where this river goes.
(gasps) I've got a map.
(laughs) Monkey.
Now, according to animal crackers,
there's no river here.
-Eh-
-Stay in the boat, Homer.
(drums beating)
Look.
(speaking Swahili)
Let's just float by quietly.
(grunts)
(both gasp)
(speaking Swahili)
Oh. You think they settled
that bag boy strike yet?
-(rumbling)
-Oh, no. We're headed for Victoria Falls.
Here's why they shouldn't
get anything. One--
(all screaming)
Whoo!
This flower saved our lives.
Oh, no. It's eating us.
HOMER: Not a chance.
Wow, Dad. How did you do that?
It's a flower.
(birds screeching)
BART AND LISA:
Are we insane yet?
I told you, yes. Now--
Now, Bart, go to the top
of that hill
and see if you can
spot our hotel.
BART: Mount Kilimanjaro?
-Go!
-(groans) OK.
-Aaah!
-(chattering)
A chimp.
Hello, little fella.
Hey, maybe he'll lead us
to bananas.
Or more mouthwatering monkeys.
-Ooh! Ooh! Ooh! Ooh!
-HOMER: Overtime for bag boys?
Ridiculous!
(gasps) This is the place
I've read about--
where Dr. Bushwell
lives among the chimps.
Oh, isn't that sweet?
He named it after his wife.
No, Dr. Bushwell is a woman.
Well, now I've heard everything.
It's kind of you
to take us in, Dr. Bushwell.
-Yeah. Thanks for the grub.
-Grubs.
(slithering) Whatever.
Ah, there's a burst of flavor.
Your work has really
inspired me, Doctor.
And I love your sensible
ponytail.
Well, thank you.
See, Jojo? She likes it.
So I notice your home
smells of feces.
-Yes?
-And not just monkey feces either.
Could we talk about
something else?
I-- I love what you've done
with these poles.
(sniffing)
(chattering)
Every day I get up at 5:30,
watch the chimps...
eat a quick lunch of roots and water,
then more chimp-watching.
After dark I come home and think
about chimps until it's time for bed.
You must be the most
boring woman on earth.
Possibly, but--
I mean, I knew scientists
wasted their lives, but geez!
Homer!
-(screeching)
-BUSHWELL: What? What is it, Pointy?
(brakes screech)
Oh, no. It's the poachers.
Give us the chimps,
and no one gets hurt.
Absolutely not!
Will you help me
defend the refuge?
Anything for these
noble animals.
(chattering)
So like us.
(all grunting)
(both grunt)
Huh?
-What?
-Aaah!
(together) Yes! D'oh!
-Somebody light this monkey.
-(chattering)
Aaah! Help! Bad monkey.
(chattering)
(gagging)
Hey! Stop it, you creep.
-Greenpeace?
-That's right.
And we're not leaving
till we rescue every animal here.
Well, if you really
cared about chimps...
you'd know that Dr. Bushwell
is their best friend.
Oh, is that right?
Why don't you tell her
about the diamond mine, Doctor?
Diamond mine?
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about this.
(whistling)
(chattering weakly)
(gasps) The chimps are running
a diamond mine.
Why, what fascinating behavior.
I-- I must document
this new activity.
Dr. Bushwell!
What, these? Well, they were
a graduation present.
Unbelievable.
This shaft must be
five miles deep.
(all grunting)
(excited chattering)
(derisive chattering)
MAN: Oh, for-- Look it.
There's more over here.
Look at this.
She's hidden diamonds everywhere.
Even on the soles of her shoes.
Yep. She's one of the 10 richest
chimp researchers in the world.
Look at me! I'm a scientist.
(laughs, sighs) Africa.
How could you exploit
your beloved chimps like this?
I think we should look at her research
before we condemn her entirely.
I haven't said anything
for a while.
Hmm.
These are just pictures
of monkeys from famous movies.
This is disgraceful, Doctor.
All right, so I snapped.
You don't understand
the crushing loneliness and greed.
Don't worry, Doctor.
We'll get you
all the help you need.
No! Don't put me away.
I'll give you diamonds.
Everybody wants diamonds.
Diamonds will make
everything all better.
Diamonds! Diamonds!
-What a nice lady.
-Very nice.
Hey, Lise, check it out.
Diamond vision.
Buzz off.
Hey, look. Our tour guide
got a new job.
MARGE: Mmm, quite a promotion.
I was wondering
what became of him.
What happened to
President Muntu?
I don't want to talk about it.
(all laughing)
HOMER (laughing):
He got overthrown!
Now he's just a stinkin'
flight attendant.
Hey, where's my pillow?
(theme music playing)
-(murmuring)
-Shh!
Captioned by
Visual Data Media Services