(beeping)
KIEFER SUTHERLAND:
Previously on 24...
I mean The Simpsons:
Behold... our new
state-of-the-art weapon
in the global war
against misbehavior.
CTU...
-the Counter Truancy Unit!
-(kids gasp)
(moaning)
-(screams)
-(Nelson laughing)
(whimpers)
I’ve got something!
The sixth-grade
security camera
shows three
empty desks.
Enhance!
Dehance!
I ran the attendance
protocols.
Here are your three
missing students:
Hmm.
Good work, Database.
MARTIN/MILHOUSE:
We helped.
(alarm blaring)
(siren wailing)
(shouting)
(amplified breathing)
(ticking)
Whoa.
-This is the source
of the stench.
-Hey.
Get your own yogurt.
Vile curd.
Simpson, you can take your
putrid mess
far out of my sight,
you song-less land whale.
Whoo-hoo!
Business trip!
(laughing)
(kids laughing)
Simpson!
I’ll teach you
to make a Poupon "me."
(raucous laughter)
(grunts)
(shoes squeaking)
(groans)
(humming)
If someone did eat
Bart’s shorts,
they’d have a tummy full
of pocket garbage.
Hmm.
Mm.
(gasps)
The school’s having
a bake sale today?!
At 3:00?!
I promised them a cake.
I’ve only got 27 minutes.
The pre-heat is on.
SUTHERLAND:
Or maybe it’s a.m.
Whichever one is the morning
one, it’s not that one.
Apu, I’m returning
a yogurt
I wasn’t a hundred percent
satisfied with.
Mmm?
Ooh. Oh my God!
If a dead fish and a homeless
person had a baby,
and the baby puked,
and a dog ate the puke,
this smells like the rear end
of that dog!
I’ll give you any
yogurt in the store,
just take that thing
with you when you go!
(chuckling)
JIMBO:
Let’s spit
in the coffee pots.
DOLPH:
I call hazelnut.
Truants moving
into the Kwik-E-Mart.
I’ve got a visual.
(sniffing)
Ugh!
That yogurt is toxic.
It’s just what
we’ve been looking for.
Now this crossword’s nothin’
but swears.
(gasps)
We’ve got what
we need.
Milhouse, bring them in.
Roger that.
And Lisa,
if I don’t make it back,
there’s a letter in my locker
I want you to read.
I already read it.
We’ve all read it.
Wait, Milhouse,
hold your position.
Something
doesn’t add up.
Look what the bullies
could have stolen...
Big Chief Rotten Cheeks
Chewing Tobacco...
a take-a-penny tray
with a quarter in it.
So why steal the yogurt?
We have to find out
what they’re up to.
Hmm... Milhouse,
change of plan--
observe and follow.
Permission to buy
a Hostess fruit pie
to keep
my strength up?
Denied.
Hey Milhouse,
who are you spying on?
-Those bullies?
-Huh?
(screaming)
What about the fat guy?
Hey, lay off.
You’re the fat one
of you guys!
I’m bulking up
for football!
(Homer whimpering)
HOMER:
I’m still alive.
You call that playing
to win?
(Milhouse and Homer screaming)
(Homer giggling)
HOMER:
Ooh.
MILHOUSE:
Mr. Simpson,
I’m scared.
HOMER:
This is our life
now, Milhouse.
We’re Dumpster folk.
(static bursting)
I’ve lost Milhouse.
He’ll be somewhat missed.
Who do we send now?
(moaning, whimpering)
Principal Skinner,
you know we have
only one agent
who stands a chance
with those bullies.
(sighs)
My brother.
Lord, give me guidance.
That’s right, the Guidance
Department-- Detention Room.
Thank you, Mrs. Lord.
(grunting angrily)
Hmm?
(grunting)
All out?
I can’t make my famous raisin
sponge-cake without raisins.
Kids love the zing of raisins!
If I help you,
I want full immunity
for all pranks past
and future,
and you have to teach me
a swear word
I don’t already know.
No deal.
Okay, suit yourself.
It’s not like you have any
major events coming up
that the bullies would want
to disrupt.
(gasps)
The bake sale!
Principal Skinner,
as we both know,
but you might need
reminding,
the annual bake sale provides
90% of the school’s funding.
Okay, you
have a deal,
you conniving
little...
-(whispering)
-(gasps)
Wow, that’s a swear?
Used as a noun it is.
Sweet!
Now I’m going to need
some wheels.
Yes, of course.
I think we can wrangle you
a used bicycle.
Do you prefer Schwinn or Huffy?
Bart? Where did he...?
(gasps)
My car keys!
(engine starting)
(tires squealing)
Road kill, burnt hair,
my sister’s retainer case,
six weeks of bottled farts,
possum placenta,
sweat from a walk-around
Goofy suit.
And finally, T.C.B.Y.--
that container
of botulized yogurt.
Okay, everyone, masks on.
(grunts)
(liquid gurgling, hissing)
Gentlemen, we’ve created
the mother of all stink bombs.
(laughter)
Most satisfactory.
(door squeaks open)
Jimbo, sweetie, I have
to run to the bank.
Are you boys going
to be okay alone?
Put a top on, Mom!
Everyone’s seen
your implants.
But the doctor said
the air will help them...
Just go!
(door closes)
Lookin’ good,
Carol!
(squeaking)
(hissing)
(sniffing, liquid hissing)
(squeals)
(beeping)
(both grunting)
I saw it first!
You are such
a liar!
(grunting
continues)
(train whistle blowing)
You give
that to me!
(methodic beeping)
(train whistling blowing,
train chugging)
(crashing)
(train whistle blowing)
(liquid hissing)
(sniffing)
Must... escape.
(wheel squeaking)
(whimpers)
Springfield
Elementary is about
to be Stinkfield
Elementary.
Lisa, they’re going to put
a stink bomb in the school.
I might be able
to stop them,
but I’ll need a schematic
of Jimbo’s house.
Jimbo drew a couple of pictures
of his house in second grade,
but I can’t vouch
for their accuracy.
The teacher gave him
a frowny-face.
(button tones beeping)
I’m so proud
of us.
(Odd Couple theme
ring tone playing)
You got Jimbo.
They’re on to
you, Jimbo!
Get out of there!
Scram... mbled eggs
would be lovely
for breakfast,
Mother.
(whispering):
Just go! Quickly!
We’re busted!
Thanks, mole.
Now make your split-
screen vanish.
Will do!
Ooh!
Damn it, these blueprints
are all wrong.
Where’s the roller coaster room
and the shark tank?
-(heavy door closes)
-Huh?
Ooh.
(grunts)
Son of a beach ball,
they’re gone!
(whimpering)
(phone speed dialing)
I’ve got a man down!
Well, not a man.
A very special boy.
(static on other end)
Chloe, I need those
schematics now!
What? Who is this?
I’m Jack Bauer.
Who the hell are you?
-Me? Uh, I’m...
Ahmed Adoody.
-(rapid gunfire)
Chloe, find out all you
can about Ahmed Adoody.
Does anyone there know
Ahmed Adoody?
Ahmed Adoody, wealthy
Saudi financier.
Disappeared into Afghanistan
in the late 90s.
-Really?
-No, Jack, it’s
a joke name.
You’re being
set up.
Damn it!
(laughing)
Now, let’s see.
20 minutes at 300 degrees
is the equivalent
of five minutes at...
Let’s see...
(mumbles)
1,200 degrees.
Now...
to make the folded index card
that goes in front of the cake.
(loud hissing)
(sniffing)
(explosion)
(hissing)
(groans)
D’oh!
(clock ticks)
No!
Oh. Pink frosting
fixes everything.
HOMER:
Say, is your butt numb
from all this vibrating?
(laughs)
Oh, mine is.
Still, I wouldn’t describe
it as unpleasant.
Well, let’s get
some shut-eye.
Ooh, it’s that
bar I like!
Wait here in the car.
Ow!
Okay, this might
hurt a little.
No problem.
(whirring)
Oh, sweet mother
of Mary!
(whirring)
(groans)
Okay, Milhouse,
what do you want to do?
Well, the school’s having
a bake sale.
Old Betsy’ll get us there.
(grunting)
We are projecting an
effective stink radius
farther than any of us
can kick a kickball.
Sir, we have to call off
this bake sale now!
Yes, yes, yes,
we have to do something.
Although, the basketball hoops
have been retracted.
D.J. Fun-times has already
cashed his deposit,
and Superintendent Chalmers
won’t be happy to hear...
I won’t be happy to
hear what, Seymour?
Um, that, uh, bake sale
revenue projections
are through the roof!
I’m very happy to hear that.
You don’t know me at all.
We have to find those
bullies before the
bake sale starts.
Martin, run a top-down search
on the school security grid.
Will do, and you chose
the perfect person.
(laughs)
(mechanical hum)
(gasps)
The stink bomb!
I can’t let anyone see it!
Martin, anything?
I wish.
This is as boring
as mainstream cinema.
(both laughing)
So true.
(methodic beeping)
Cops. Act natural.
(girly laughter)
(high-pitched voice):
Hello, Officer!
Oh, afternoon,
ma’am.
(sighs)
What is it about a woman
in a Dumpster?
(methodic beeping)
Wait!
(grunts)
Mr. Simpson!
(groans)
(gasping)
My cake!
(grunts)
They’re gonna wish the bake sale
was a nose plug sale.
And it totally isn’t.
(all laughing)
Teens?
In Willie’s hidey hole?
I’ll mop up your blood
from the inside!
(all scream)
(alarm ringing)
We have a fire alarm
in the ventilation room!
I’ll check it out.
(door opens, closes)
(panting)
(sighs)
♪ Skip, skip,
skip to my Lou... ♪
Top of the morning,
Nelson.
And to you, Martin.
♪ Skip to my Lou,
my darling. ♪
Hey, Nelson,
what gives?
Martin just skipped past you
singing "Skip to My Lou,"
and you did nothing.
Can’t a guy enjoy
a catchy tune?
(grunts)
Ow! Ow!
I’m unclear
on what you want!
Is Martin working for Jimbo?
Uh...
Ow!
(groans)
Yes.
Yes what?
Ow!
Yes, sir.
(groans)
Lisa, are you
on a secure line?
I am.
You’re on a Bluetooth
cell phone,
the most vulnerable
device known to man.
But it looks so cool.
Listen, there’s
a mole inside CTU.
A mole?!
Yes, a mole.
Now, I don’t
have much time,
so I’m just gonna come
right out and say his name,
so get ready
to know his name.
His name is
the following: M...
♪ Skip, skip, skip to my Lou. ♪
(overlapping chatter)
Rice Krispie Treats?!
Way to phone it in,
Sarah Wiggum.
Excuse me, excuse me,
I’m in the sale.
Okay, I kept
my end of the deal.
Release my friends.
All here, from
Asimov to Zarathustra.
Where’s Phobos?!
He’s with us now.
(groans)
We’re out of here.
Smell you later.
Three minutes
later, to be exact.
(beeping)
What have I done?
Raisin cake.
Who wants raisin cake?
Don’t worry, it’s not too moist.
Hmm?
(sighs)
Can I have some
more money?
I gave you ten dollars.
All the other moms
gave their husbands $20.
Well, all
the other husbands
don’t come home
dirty from fighting.
I had fight.
Lenny said his dad
is Hulk Hogan,
and I know he’s not.
Here’s five
more dollars.
(gasps)
(laughing)
Bart, are you all right?
Bart?!
Hey, I’m fine.
They haven’t made
a French horn yet
that can hurt me.
Now, I’m sending you
a picture of the bomb.
(grunting)
My God.
That’s a class-five
stench-dispersal unit.
We have to short
out that fan.
"H.D.W."
What’s that?
That’s the main valve
of the hot dog water
recirculation system.
There’s over 30 years
of wiener soakings in there.
Lis, you have
to release that water.
It’s the only way
to short out the fan.
But you and Willie
will drown.
Possibly,
but I can’t risk
Superintendent Chalmers
finding out about...
Finding out about what, Seymour?
Um, about how early press
coverage of the bake sale
is uniformly positive.
Once again, you have thoroughly
misgauged my response.
This is going on
your permanent record.
The hot dog water’s
going to push us into the fan!
And I just sharpened
those blades.
(weakly):
♪ Skip to my Lou...
my darling. ♪
Bart, I’ve got an idea.
As you’re dying,
jam the blades with your spine.
Keep pitching. I’ll be back.
(inhales deeply)
(humming)
(gasps)
Look!
A window to
a child’s watery grave!
Don’t worry,
I’ll free the boy.
(crowd gasping)
(gunshots)
(gasps)
Damn it! This glass
is bulletproof.
There’s nothing
that can shatter it.
MARGE:
Yes, there is!
(beeping)
Huh?
Ooh, a thermos.
With seven cups of
coffee still in it.
Oh, wait, six.
Dad, that’s a bomb!
Here! It’s yours!
(panting)
(gasps)
How do I stop it?
Oh, that’s convenient.
(sighs)
SKINNER:
Thank goodness
this crisis was averted.
Nicely done, Lisa.
Hey, what about me?
I almost died,
and so did Willie.
(grunting)
Oh, leave me be.
I don’t want to live if I
have to clean up this mess.
Oh, my special
little guy.
I’m so glad
you’re okay.
Oh, I’m just glad you
taste like hot dogs.
(crowd gasps)
Good work, Lisa!
What about me?
Bart Simpson,
12 minutes ago,
you made an annoying
prank phone call to me.
All units, move in.
I pulled every single field
agent off all other cases
to track you down
and bring you to justice.
It was a tough decision, but I
think I made the right call.
(explosion)
(all gasp)
It’s okay,
that was Shelbyville.
(all sigh)
(methodic beeping)
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Shh!
Enhanced by Fotokem