♪ The Simpsons ♪
Aah!
Lisa! Lisa, are you
still in there?
What's the problem?
Did you fall in?
Lisa!
- Sorry, Dad. Women and children first.
- What the...
Where the hell are my keys?
Who stole my keys?
Come on. I'm late for work.
Homer, you'd lose your head
if it weren't securely fastened
to your neck.
- Did you check the den?
- The den! Great idea.
Warm. No, cold.
Colder. Ice cold.
Do you know where my keys are?
No. I'm talkin' about
your breakfast.
Did you try the rumpus room?
Rumpus room?
Great idea.
Dad.
- Doh!
- Homer.
Here.
I'm sorry, everybody,
but I've only got two cupcakes
for the three of you.
Well, Mom, one of us
has scarfed down
more than enough cupcakes
over the past three decades to...
- Bart!
- Just take mine.
A simple cupcake
will bring me no pleasure.
- Yeah!
- All right!
All right, class.
From the top.
One, and two, and three, and...
♪♪-♪ My country, 'tis of thee ♪
♪ La da da da da dee ♪♪
♪♪
Lisa!
Lisa Simpson!
Lisa, there's no room
for crazy bebop
in "My Country 'Tis of Thee."
But Mr. Largo, that's
what my country's all about.
What?
I'm wailing out for the homeless
family living out of its car.
The Iowa farmer whose land
has been taken away
by unfeeling bureaucrats.
The West Virginia coal miner,
coughing up...
That's all fine and good,
but, Lisa, none of those
unpleasant people
are going to be
at the recital next week.
Now, class.
From the top.
Five, six, seven...
Every day at noon a bell rings,
and they herd us in here
for feeding time.
And we sit around like cattle,
chewing our cuds,
dreading the inevitable...
Food fight!
Come on, Lis!
What are you waiting for?
Chuck that spaghetti.
I choose not to participate.
Lisa, we are playing
dodge ball here.
The object of the game is
to avoid the ball
by weaving or ducking
out of its path.
In other words,
to dodge the ball.
Listen, missy, just tell me why
you weren't getting out of
the way of those balls.
I'm too sad.
Too sad to play dodge ball?
That's ridiculous.
Now, let's see some enthusiasm.
Play ball!
Come on, come on.
Let's go.
♪♪
In the red trunks
with the record of 48 wins
and no losses,
the undisputed champ
of this house,
Battling Bart Simpson!
Whoopee, whoo!
And in the lavender trunks,
with a record of zero wins
and 48 defeats...
Correction.
Humiliating defeats,
- all of them by knockout...
- Must you do this every time?
Homer "The Human Punching Bag"
Simpson!
Doh! Stupid joystick!
Three seconds, folks.
A new record.
Hey, no. I'm not down.
I'm... Get up, you!
Get off the mat.
Okay. Here we go.
Yo, chump, you back again?
Get outta the way!
How come he's not ducking?
Wait a minute. I can't get my... Get out of
the way, stupid!
- Homer?
- Not now, Marge!
- Get out of the corner!
- They sent a note from school.
What did you do this time,
you little hoodlum?
Oops, get outta the way!
I didn't do it.
Nobody saw me do it.
There's no way
they can prove anything.
No, Bart.
This note isn't about you.
It isn't?
There must be some mistake.
Hey, you're right.
This note's about Lisa.
Lisa?
♪♪
She doesn't look sad.
I don't see any tears
in her eyes.
It's not that kind of sad.
I'm sorry, Dad, but you
wouldn't understand.
Sure, I would, princess.
I have feelings too.
You know, like,
"My stomach hurts."
Or "I'm going crazy!"
Why don't you climb up
on Daddy's knee
and tell him all about it.
I'm just wondering
what's the point?
Would it make any difference
at all if I never existed?
How can we sleep at night
when there's so much suffering
in the world?
Well, I...
Come on, Lisa.
Ride the Homer horsey!
Giddyap. Whee!
Lisa, honey,
why don't we go upstairs,
and I'll draw you
a nice hot bath.
That helps me when I feel sad.
Sorry, Dad.
I know you mean well.
Thanks for knowing I mean well.
Gee, Homer. Looks like
you got yourself
a real problem on your hands.
Yeah, right.
Bart, vacuum this floor.
Hey, man.
I didn't do anything wrong!
In times of trouble you've
got to go with what you know.
Now, hop to it, boy!
Thinks he's some big
stupid Homer. Man.
I'll show him.
He thinks he's so big.
- Enjoy your bath?
- No, not really.
Too bad.
Well, I certainly
had fun vacuuming.
Maybe now I'll get the pleasure
of scrubbing your tub.
So typical of Bart.
All he thinks about is himself.
Hey, don't say stuff like that
about me to Maggie.
She's on my side anyway.
- Is not. Is not.
- Is too. Is too.
- Is not.
- Is too!
Watch.
I'll prove it.
Maggie. Come to the one
you love best.
No, Maggie. Come here, girl.
Come to me.
Come on, Maggie!
The choice is obvious.
No, Maggie.
Don't go for the glitter.
Look for substance.
All right, Maggie,
just go to Bart.
Exactly. Come to the one
you love best.
No! Come on!
Don't let the... Get out of the...
Aaah! No,
not again.
Get over to the... Aaah!
♪♪
Gee, Dad, you're
really bad at this.
I am not.
It's just that I...
♪♪ -Couldn't concentrate
with that infernal racket.
Lisa! Lisa.
♪♪
Lisa, what did I tell you about
playing that sax-a-ma-thing
in the house?
I was just playing
the blues, Dad.
Lisa, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to yell.
Go ahead. Play your blues
if it'll make you happy.
No. That's okay, Dad.
I'll just work on my fingering.
Unless my fingers clacking
on the keys is too loud for you.
Let's hear it.
You just clack
as loud as you want, Lis.
♪♪
I've gotta find that sound.
That was beautiful.
What's it called?
It's a little tune
that I call...
the "I Never Had
an Italian Suit Blues."
Wait, Margie.
Before you go out that door,
let's put our happy face on,
because people know
how good a mommy you have
by the size of your smile.
What the...
Put up your dukes, Homer.
Bart, go easy on me.
I'm your dad.
I am going easy on you,
but you're so old and slow...
and weak and pathetic.
No! Bart, no!
Homer, wake up, wake up.
- Man.
- My.
Here, let me wipe off the drool.
You know, Marge, getting old
is a terrible thing.
I think the saddest day
of my life
was when I realized I could
beat my dad at most things.
And Bart experienced
that at the age of four.
So, why are you still awake?
I'm still trying to figure out
what's bothering Lisa.
I don't know.
Bart's such a handful,
and Maggie needs attention.
But all the while, our little
Lisa is becoming a young woman.
So that's it.
This is some kind of
underwear thing.
Good night, Homer.
♪♪
Now, now low b-flat.
Okay, Lisa.
"Altissimo" register.
♪♪
Very nice. Very nice.
I once ruptured myself
doin' that.
Thanks, Mr. Murphy.
My friends call me
Bleedin' Gums.
Eww. How'd you get
a name like that?
Well, let me put it this way.
You ever been to the dentist?
- Yeah.
- Not me.
I suppose I should go to one,
but I got enough pain
in my life as it is.
I have problems too.
Well, I can't help you, kid.
I'm just a terrific horn player
with tons of soul.
- But I can jam with you.
- Okay.
♪♪
♪ I'm so lonely ♪
♪ Since my baby left me ♪
♪ I got no money ♪
♪ And nothing is free ♪
♪ I been so lonely ♪
♪ Since the day I was born ♪
♪ All I got is this rusty ♪
♪ This rusty old horn ♪
♪ I got a bratty brother ♪
♪ He bugs me every day ♪
♪ And this morning
my own mother ♪
♪ She gave
my last cupcake away ♪
♪ My dad acts
like he belongs ♪
♪ He belongs in the zoo ♪
♪ I'm the saddest kid ♪
♪ In grade number two ♪♪
You know, you play pretty well
for someone
with no real problems.
Yeah, but I don't
feel any better.
The blues isn't about
feelin' better.
It's about makin'
other people feel worse,
and makin' a few bucks
while you're at it.
Which reminds me, if you're
ever in the neighborhood,
I'm playing in a little club
called the Jazz Hole.
Lisa! Get away from
that jazzman!
- But Mom! Can't I stay a little longer?
- Come on.
We were worried about you.
Nothing personal.
I just fear the unfamiliar.
♪♪
Today's fire raced
through downtown Springfield,
gutting Symphony Hall,
the Springfield Museum
of Natural History,
the Springfield Arts Center,
and Barney's Bowl-a-rama.
Officials said the...
No! Marge!
- Marge, are you all right?
- No! I'm very upset.
Then you've heard. God.
What are we gonna do?
The lanes were kinda warped,
but, the food.
I'm upset about Lisa.
- Me too.
- Me three.
- What are we talking about?
- Bart!
Do you think you're being
nice enough to your sister, Bart?
Yeah, easy.
You do love her, don't you?
- Mom.
- Well, you do. Don't you?
Don't make me say it.
I know the answer.
You know the answer.
He knows the answer.
Let's just drop it. Okay?
Okay, Bart.
You don't have to say it,
but you do have to have
a loving attitude.
Be nice to your sister.
- Okey-dokey.
- Go on, Bart.
No time like the present.
- Hi, man.
- I don't want your pity.
- Aw, come on. I'll cheer you up.
- How?
Yeah. Moe's Tavern.
Moe speaking.
- Is Jacques there?
- Who?
Jacques.
Last name Strap.
Hold on.
Jacques Strap?
Hey, guys, I'm lookin'
for a Jacques Strap.
What?
Aw, wait a minute.
Jacques Strap?
It's you, isn't it,
you cowardly little runt!
When I get ahold of you,
I am gonna gut you like a fish
and drink your blood.
Where's your
sense of humor, man?
Lisa, you'll be late
for band practice.
Let's go.
Give me some quarters.
I'm doing my laundry.
Yeah. Right.
- Where's the video boxing?
- It's over there in the corner.
If I were you I really would use
those quarters for laundry.
Wise guy.
- Hey, that kid's pretty good.
- Good? Are you kidding?
Over 2,000 fights,
and he's still on
his original quarter.
Okay, who's next?
- Me, me, me, me, me!
- No, me! No, me!
Listen, can you teach me
to fight like you do?
- I don't think so.
- Come on.
I'll tell you what. I'll do
it if you bark like a dog.
You little...
You got yourself a deal, Fido.
Well, looks like you're
all out of quarters, old man.
That's okay.
With the tips you've given me,
I'm gonna pound the tar out of
a certain little
smarty-pants tonight.
Howie! I thought I told you
to stop wasting your money
- in this stupid place!
- Sorry, Mom.
And you! A man of your age.
You should be ashamed
of yourself.
Excuse me. I think
I hear my wife calling.
Now, Lisa, listen to me.
This is important.
I want you to smile today.
But I don't feel like smiling.
Well, it doesn't matter how
you feel inside, you know.
It's what shows up
on the surface that counts.
That's what my mother taught me.
Take all your bad feelings
and push them down.
All the way down,
past your knees,
until you're almost
walking on them.
And then you'll fit in, and
you'll be invited to parties,
and boys will like you,
and happiness will follow.
Come on.
You can do better than that.
That's my girl.
I feel more popular already.
- Hey, nice smile.
- Thanks.
Hey, what are you
talkin' to her for?
She's just gonna say
somethin' weird.
- Not me.
- You know,
I used to think
you were some brainiac,
but I guess you're okay.
Hey, why don't you come over
to my house after practice?
- You could do my homework.
- Okay.
Five minutes, people,
five minutes.
Now, Miss Simpson, I hope
we won't have a repeat
of yesterday's outburst
of unbridled creativity.
No, sir.
Wow, Mom!
So that's where she gets it.
Lisa, I apologize to you.
I was wrong.
I take it all back.
Always be yourself.
You wanna be sad, honey, be sad.
We'll ride it out with you.
And when you get finished
feeling sad,
we'll still be there.
From now on,
let me do the smiling
for both of us.
Okay, Mom.
I said you could stop
smiling, Lisa.
I feel like smiling.
I'm gonna knock you out
one more time, and that's it.
This is getting boring, man.
Just try not to kill me
too hard, son.
- Whoa!
- Kid, tonight's not your night.
All right, man, you asked
for it. No more Mr. Nice Guy.
Aha! Blocked it.
You missed me.
I got you. Ooh.
Don't try that. I got you blocked.
And the crowd is on its feet
as Hurricane Homer moves in
for the kill!
Boys, I'd like
your attention, please.
Quiet, Marge!
This is my big moment!
Bart "The Bloody Pulp"
Simpson is on the ropes.
He is hoping I'll put him
out of his misery!
Well, you're in luck, Bart!
Here comes my right!
No!
My game, my game!
I could have beat the boy.
Marge, how could you?
I was so close.
I'm sorry,
but this is more important
than that silly, loud game.
You're right, Mom.
I'd just like to
use this occasion
to announce my retirement,
undefeated, from the world
of video boxing.
Calm down, Homer.
Lisa has an idea that she thinks
would be fun
for the whole family.
The next song was written
by a friend of mine,
one of the great
little ladies of jazz.
♪♪
♪ I got this bratty brother ♪
♪ He bugs me every day ♪
♪ And this mornin'
my own mother ♪
♪ Gave my last
cupcake away ♪
♪ My dad acts like
he belongs, y'all ♪
♪ He belongs in the zoo ♪
What?
♪ I'm the saddest kid ♪
♪ In grade number two ♪♪
♪♪
Shh!