♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screeching)
(birds chirping)
(grumbling)
(splat)
Sandwich.
(groans)
(items crunching)
Hmm, underpants.
Hmm?
(groans)
Bowling ball.
More underpants.
-Hi, Mom.
Hi, Mom.
(all chomping, swallowing)
After breakfast, me and Milhouse
are going down to the ravine.
We got a tip
from a six-year-old
that there's a
dead Martian down there.
And I'm going to the park
to jam with the Little
White Girls blues quartet.
-Wanna come with me, daddio?
-I'd love to, honey,
but Daddy has to go to a
beer-drinking contest today.
Think you'll win?
Son, when you participate
in sporting events,
it's not whether
you win or lose,
it's how drunk you get.
Gotcha. Well, gotta go.
-Me, too.
Uh, it's hard for us to leave
when you're standing there, Mom.
-Push her down, son.
-No one's going anywhere.
We're going to clean
the whole house from top to bottom.
-(gasps)
Oh, dear God, no!
(panting, struggling)
I think you'll find
that escape is impossible.
Now, each one of you
take a floor and get started.
-I call the basement.
-ALL: Fine.
D'oh?
D'oh!
(squeaking)
I'm tired. I'm hungry.
Can't we just buy a new house?
Oh, Bart, cleaning
doesn't have to be a chore.
Here, work to the music.
♪ You load 16 tons
and what do you get ♪
♪ Another day older
and deeper in debt ♪
Amen, Ernie.
(sputtering, engine starts)
-All done.
-You're not done.
I want you to throw away
these old calendars and TV Guides.
Are you mad, woman?
You never know when
an old calendar might come in handy.
Sure, it's not 1985 right now,
but who knows what
tomorrow will bring?
And these TV Guides.
So many memories.
"Gomer Upsets Sergeant Carter."
Oh, I'll never forget
that episode.
-Pyle!
-Shazam!
(laughs)
Shazam.
Stop remembering TV
and get back to work.
What's the point
of all this cleaning?
Are we so vain?
(vacuum whirring)
-(jazz playing)
-Hmm?
Hey, Clinton,
get back to work.
Make me.
(sighs) They're having a great time,
and I'm stuck in here.
(sour note plays)
Ooh!
Hmm. "Use only
in a well-ventilated area."
Shove it, buddy.
(grunting)
Whoo! Ahh!
(Homer blabbering)
(popping, squeaking)
Huh? Whee!
(all growling)
(straining)
I must destroy you!
(screaming)
MARGE: Homer, what's going on
down there?
-Nothing.
-Then stop screaming so loud.
Okay.
(quieter screaming)
♪♪ (country music plays)
(groaning)
RADIO DJ: And that was
"Take this job and shove it."
Now let's make another one
of our lucky phone calls.
DJ 2: Okay, just answer
the phone with
the special phrase that pays,
and you'll have your choice
of $10,000 in cash--
(cash register dings)
(laughs)
Or a really stupid prize.
(clock cuckoos)
DJ:
Well, let's make that call.
(rings)
KBBL is gonna give me
something stupid!
GRAMPA:
Bart, I'm having palpitations!
Can't tie up
the line, Grampa.
-(all groaning)
-There. Isn't that a lot better?
Now you can do whatever you want,
but don't mess up the house.
ALL:
We won't.
(groans)
DJ: And now let's try
another lucky phone call.
(rings)
Help! Help us!
They stole our uniforms,
guns and tasers!
-Ooh, fry, piggy.
-(electrical charge)
WIGGUM:
No, no, no, don't!
(electrical charge,
Wiggum yelling)
A little to the left.
-(electrical charge)
-Ahh, that's the stuff.
DJ:
Oh, I'm sorry the phrase is
"KBBL is gonna give me
something stupid."
DJ 2:
Pretty weird.
(laughs)
DJ:
Let's try one more number.
-(phone rings)
-(gasps)
-Hello.
-KBBL is gonna give me something stupid!
-Well, hot dog, we have a "Wiener."
-(alarm sounds)
-Hello?
-I won! I won!
You win your choice of
$10,000 or--
What's our gag prize
this week, Bill?
(Bill laughs)
A full-grown African elephant.
Well, all that money
sounds mighty tempting, Marty,
but I think I'm gonna
have to go with the elephant.
He's taking the elephant
instead of the money.
MARTY:
The kid wants the elephant.
We don't have a damn elephant.
Don't whisper into the mike.
(clears throat)
Kid, the elephant's a gag prize.
Nobody takes the gag prize.
You want the cash.
I want the elephant.
(laughs)
Stick it to the man.
No, wait!
We'll call you back.
Bart, with $10,000,
we'd be millionaires!
We could buy all kinds
of useful things like... love.
Or double-ply windows.
They look just like regular windows,
but they'll save us four percent
on our heating bill.
Well, they will.
You all seem to be forgetting
the most important thing,
which is, that it's wrong
to imprison an animal.
Lisa, go to your room.
(man laughing)
We appreciate you coming down,
but, look, kid.
The thing is, uh--
(chuckles)
We don't have an elephant.
(laughs)
Come on, kid,
just take the money, huh?
Otherwise, we might get fired.
-You don't want us to get fired, do you?
-Eh, either way.
-(both gasp)
-(groans)
We think we know how your mind works,
Bart, so how 'bout this?
We pay your principal $10,000
to pull down his pants
and keep 'em down for
the rest of the school year.
-I'll do it, Bart.
-Um... no.
Okay, okay. What if we use the 10,000
to surgically transform Skinner here
into, uh, some kind
of a lobster-like creature?
Well, now wait just a minute.
That wasn't discussed with me.
Uh, gentlemen, I am not leaving
without my elephant.
-Hey!
-Whee!
Where's my elephant?
-(mellow music plays)
-BART: Where's my elephant?
Where's my elephant?
Hey, they're playing
"The Elephant Song."
I love that.
Reminds me of elephants.
So, isn't that what we're all
asking in our own lives?
Where's my elephant?
I know that's what I've been asking.
(electrical crackling)
Look, our ratings are down,
and the station is being swamped
with angry calls
and letter bombs.
-And it's all your fault.
-Yes, it is, ma'am.
This is the DJ-3000.
It plays CDs automatically,
and it has three distinct
varieties of inane chatter.
MALE VOICE: Hey, hey, how about
that weather out there?
Whoa, that was
the caller from hell.
Well, hot dog,
we have a "wiener."
Man, that thing's great.
Don't praise
the machine.
If you don't get that kid an elephant
by tomorrow, the DJ-3000 gets your job.
(grunts)
Looks like those clowns
in congress did it again.
What a bunch of clowns.
(laughs)
How does he keep up
with the news like that?
-(doorbell rings)
-(yawns)
-(gasps)
-(tires squeal)
(Marge, Homer gasp)
Whoo-ho-ho-ho!
(trumpets)
(elephant trumpets)
(snorting)
Homer?
It looks like
it could gore.
(chuckles)
It does look like Al Gore.
Oh, he smells worse
than anything.
Hey, you, elephant! Lift me up
on your back, man. Whoo!
(Marge gasps)
Bart!
(grunts)
Cool!
(chuckles)
He tried to kill me.
I really think
this is a bad idea.
Marge, I agree with you
in theory.
In theory,
communism works.
In theory.
Look, he thinks
he's people.
(trumpets)
I think I'm gonna
call him Stampy.
(trumpets)
-What's he yelling about?
-He's hungry.
Here you go, Stampy.
Eat it slow. It has to last for--
You ate it too fast.
Maybe if we tied it down so it couldn't
move, it wouldn't get so hungry.
You can't do that, Dad.
It's cruel!
Oh, everything's cruel
according to you.
Keeping him chained up
in the backyard is cruel.
Pulling on his tail
is cruel.
Yelling in his ears
Everything is cruel.
So excuse me if I'm cruel!
(yells)
-(chomps)
-(muffled yelling)
(grunts,
breathing heavily)
Now I've had my head in an elephant,
a hippo and a giant sloth.
(swallowing)
(crunching)
(grunts)
I think you're taking unfair
advantage of my generous offer.
-Shut up!
-(labored breathing)
He can't just eat peanuts, Dad.
He needs plants to live.
Plants, eh?
(squirrels chittering)
Strip the bark now, Stampy.
Hey, any more arboretums
around here?
No!
(Homer gasps) That bird!
He's killing the elephant! Stop him!
No, Dad,
he's grooming him.
Grooming him, eh?
Oh, Homer, there's
a bird on your head.
I know.
He's grooming me.
Mm, elephant fresh.
(several dogs barking)
(Stampy trumpets)
(silence)
(straining)
Good night, Stampy.
(sniffing)
(Bart sighs)
(yawns, grunts)
Uh-- Ahem.
Thanks, Bud.
Appreciate it.
-Hmm.
-Taught Stampy any tricks yet, Bart?
Nah. He doesn't wanna learn,
and I don't wanna teach him.
We get along fine.
-(heavy panting)
-Hey, what's with them?
I think they're trying
to get some attention.
Oh. Good luck!
Look at these bills.
"Chain for elephant."
"Shots for elephant."
"Oversized decorative poncho"!
Technically, it's for a giraffe,
but I think I can let it out a little.
Well, these bills will have to be
paid out of your allowance.
You'll have to raise my allowance
to about $1,000 a week.
-Then that's what I'll do, smart guy.
-(doorbell rings)
-Can we see the elephant?
-We'll pay you money.
For the ninth time, no!
(doorbell rings)
Wait a minute.
This gives me an idea.
Mm, here's
a better sign, Dad.
I don't have time
to read it.
Just give me
the gist of it, son.
(playful chattering)
-(grunts)
-Your kid flew five feet.
That counts as a ride.
Two bucks.
That was never five feet.
That animal of yours
is certainly bad-tempered.
Yeah, well, you'd be
grumpy too
if you were taken out
of your natural habitat
and gawked at by a bunch
of slack-jawed yokels.
Hey, ma, look at that
pointy-hairded little girl. (guffaws)
You guys don't
understand Stampy.
He's just like me.
We're a pair of jokers,
and both of us are wild.
We don't take nothing
from nobody. (sighs)
(laughs)
Smithers!
This reminds me of that fat man
I used to ride to work.
-(groaning)
-(door closes)
Look at this, Marge.
$58 and all of it profit!
I'm the smartest businessman
in the world.
Stampy's food bill
today was $300.
Marge, please, don't humiliate me
in front of the money.
(humming)
(customers reacting
negatively)
(car doors slamming,
tires screeching)
(vehicles departing)
Um, Milhouse saw the elephant
twice
and rode him once, right?
Yes, but we paid you
four dollars.
Well, that was under
our old price structure.
Under our new
price structure,
your bill comes
to a total of $700.
Now, you've already
paid me four dollars,
so that's just $696 more
that you owe me.
Get off our property.
This town
is full of deadbeats.
We can't afford this elephant.
No, Dad, he's my friend.
Sorry, Bart.
I'm gonna have to sell him.
♪♪ (music playing)
(roars)
Well, sir,
I'll be honest with ya.
I need a large African elephant,
and I need it today.
But I'm afraid this just
isn't what I'm looking for.
What do you mean?
It's an elephant, isn't it?
Well, it is and it isn't,
if you understand what I mean.
He likes peanuts.
Our wildlife refuge is the ideal
environment for your elephant.
Thousands of acres
of simulated African savannah.
It's perfect, Dad.
I only have two questions:
How much? And give it to me.
Well, we really can't
offer you any money.
-We're a nonprofit organization.
-So, your bid is zero?
-Well, we'd like to think of it as--
-Thank you.
-You know, I really think--
Mr. Simpson, I think you'll find
this amount more than fair.
Dad, I think
he's an ivory dealer.
His boots are ivory.
His hat is ivory.
And I'm pretty sure
that check is ivory.
Lisa, a guy who has lots of ivory
is less likely to hurt Stampy
than a guy whose
ivory supplies are low.
(growling)
We love... you.
(meows)
-Mr. Blackheart?
-Yes, my pretty.
-Are you an ivory dealer?
-(laughs)
Little girl, I've had
lots of jobs in my day--
Whale hunter, seal clubber,
president of the Fox network--
And, like most people,
yeah, I've dealt
a little ivory.
Dad, you can't do this.
Stampy is my friend.
Don't worry, son.
I'll get you a new elephant.
-I'll take that one too.
-Done.
I'll be back in
the morning to pick up Stampy.
Here's the keys.
-Elephants don't have keys.
-I'll just keep these then.
Don't worry, Stampy.
I won't let Homer sell you
to that ivory dealer.
You and I are gonna
run away together.
We'll keep to the back roads
and make our way south.
Then, if I know my geography,
it's just 12 miles to Africa.
Okay, bud, very quietly,
let's just sneak through--
(grunts)
Stampy!
(trumpets)
(gasps) Oh, it's the four elephants
of the apocalypse.
-That's horsemen, Ned.
-Well, getting closer.
Mom, Dad,
Bart and Stampy are gone!
Oh, my Lord!
I bet it's because of that horrible
ivory dealer, Dad.
He took Bart too?
That wasn't part of
our deal, Blackheart!
That wasn't part!
Piece of cake.
All we have to do is follow
the path of destruction.
Oh, stupid tornado!
(laughs)
Look.
It got Patty and Selma.
(groans) I feel it
all the way up my skirt.
Ditto.
(trumpets)
Whoa!
(chuckles)
Yeah, right, lady.
An elephant ran through
your front yard. Okay.
Wiggum. Yeah, right,
mister. Mm-hmm.
An elephant just knocked over
your mailbox. Okay.
Wiggum.
Yeah, right, buddy.
Liquor store robbery,
officer down. Sure.
And I'm Edward G. Robinson.
Waah!
(cheering)
(trumpeting)
(jeering)
(trumpets)
Whoa!
This is the moment
we've feared, people.
Many of you thought
it would never happen,
but I insisted we spend two hours
every morning training for it.
You all thought I was mad.
Many of you requested to be
transferred to another peanut factory.
-But now, we--
-(trumpets)
Stampy!
Stampy, where are
you, boy?
-(trumpeting)
-Huh?
(panting)
(trumpeting)
FEMALE VOICE: These prehistoric
creatures blundered into the tar pits,
which preserved their skeletons
in showroom condition.
Oh. He's gone forever.
(loud trumpeting)
(gasps)
Stampy!
Mm.
Huh?
Oh, you're lonely for
other elephants, aren't you?
-D'oh!
-A deer!
A female deer.
Son, you're okay!
And you led us
to the precious ivory.
And, of course, your lovable pet,
who it's connected to.
Dad, I can't let you sell him.
Stampy and I are friends.
Ow!
Anyway, I want him to go
to that animal refuge.
Forget it!
That elephant cost me
thousands of dollars.
Dad, how would you like to be
sold to an ivory dealer?
-I'd like it fine.
-Even if he killed you
and made your teeth
into piano keys?
Yes, of course I would.
Who wouldn't like that,
to be part of the music scene?
-Dad, you're sinking!
-Huh?
-Get a rope, Bart.
-No, that's okay.
I'm pretty sure
I can struggle my way out.
First, I'll just reach in
and pull my legs out.
Now I'll pull my arms out
with my face.
Mm.
(gurgling)
-Dad!
-Homey!
Stampy, quick!
Pull him out!
Thanks, Stampy.
Ow!
(gasping)
Ah, I'm alive!
I'm alive!
And I owe it all
to this feisty feline.
Dad, feline means cat.
Elephant, honey.
It's an elephant.
And I'm sure he'll make
a grand piano.
-BOTH: Dad!
-Oh.
I guess it wouldn't be
right to sell Stampy
after he saved my life.
And the boy seems to have some
sort of relationship with him.
-Thanks, Dad.
-On the other hand,
who's to say
what's right these days,
what with all our modern ideas...
and products?
All right. We'll give the stupid elephant
to the stupid animal refuge.
BOTH: Yea!
Uh, Mom,
we're stuck to Dad.
(groans)
This is just what happened
at the caramel factory.
-Ow!
-Ow, my hair!
(grunting)
Mmm, caramel.
(trumpets)
So long, Stampy.
I know you're gonna like it here.
No, Stampy, no!
(trumpets)
(chuckles)
Oh, thanks, boy.
-(roars)
-Whoa! Whoa, boy!
Wh-whoa!
-(grunts)
-(trumpets)
(Bart laughs)
Attaboy, Stampy.
Butt him once for me.
Gosh, I thought he'd be happier
in his true habitat.
Oh, I think he is.
Then why is he attacking
all those other elephants?
Well, animals are a lot
like people, Mrs. Simpson.
-Some of them act badly
-Stampy!
Because they had a hard life
or have been mistreated.
But, like people,
some of them are just jerks.
Stop that, Mr. Simpson.
(grunting)
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.