CHOIR: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(theme music playing)
(exclaims)
(school bell ringing)
(Barney belches)
-(whistle blows)
-(yells)
(beeps)
(playing the harp)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-(tires screech)
-(grunts)
(electric humming)
(shouting)
(robotic voice)
D'oh. D'oh. D'oh. D'oh. D'oh.
Family.
Meet me at...
the kitchen cube.
D'oh. D'oh.
-D'oh. D'oh. D'oh.
-(electric crackling)
(raspy voice)
I am Simpson.
I am Simpson. I am Simpson.
(Bart gurgling)
(distorted)
Don't... don't have cow, man.
-I am Simpson. I am Simpson.
-Don't... don't have cow, man.
(distorted)
All hail the dark lord of the twin moons.
-I am Simpson. I am Simpson.
-Don't have cow, man.
-(gurgling)
-I am Simpson.
-Cow... man.
I am Simpson.
(Lisa babbling)
(sucking)
(low voice)
Make purchase of the merchandise.
-D'oh.
-Don't have cow, man.
I have... memories.
I have.... memor... memor...
(distorted sounds)
(gentle piano playing)
(high-pitched voice)
Still love you, Homar.
(high-pitched, distorted voices)
We are happy family.
(growling sound)
All animals can scream.
(low voice)
Make purchase of the merchandise.
-I am Simpson. I am Simpson.
-Don't have cow, man.
D'oh.
Three feet, nine inches.
That should do it.
Don't you know what kind of animal
we're dealing with?
-Okay, enough theory.
-Hey, Dad. We made popcorn.
HOMER: Whoo-hoo!
Huh? Out of my reach?
(grunts) Must... make... effort.
(grunting)
(bones crack)
Yay.
Mr. Simpson, you earned this.
(quiet grunts)
What's on TV?
Krusty's getting roasted tonight.
Hey.
(grumbles)
Sometimes the language on these
gets a little B-L-U-E.
What?
Oh.
If you don't let us watch,
we'll just go to a house
where some more
permissive parents will.
How permissive?
Chief Wiggum shows us
crime photos at sleepovers.
So this is what a body looks like
after it drops 60 stories.
Uh, come on, Milhouse,
don't pretend you're asleep.
This is the world we live in.
Yeah.
(crowd laughs over TV)
Hey, Krusty, our local deli
just named a sandwich after you.
It's called "The Unfunny Comedian."
(crowd laughs)
You will always be remembered
for your countless appearances
on the Krusty the Clown Show
and your one appearance on
To Catch A Predator.
(crowd laughs)
Hey, I spent a lifetime
making people happy.
Yeah-- plastic surgeons
and divorce lawyers.
I was just about to say that.
Oh, he took my laugh.
Screw it, I'm doing it anyway.
Plastic surgeons
and divorce lawyers.
(man coughs)
What a legend.
Krusty the Clown is to comedy
what Martin Luther King
is to comedy.
(laughter)
We've seen a lot of
top-flight comics tonight,
but that's over, because it's time
to hear from Krusty the Clown.
Welcome, Krusty.
I grew up watching you.
Oh, uh, sorry.
I threw up watching you.
(laughter, applause)
(grumbles)
Sarah Silverman.
I say this with love,
you disrespectful skank.
You've had more... Oh.
Suddenly,
I don't feel like doing this.
(gasps)
Sorry, Mini-ha-ha.
Canceling the bit.
Tell the others.
I thought this night would be fun
for me and my friends.
I don't even know these people.
And I guess I don't have any friends.
My only comfort is the roast is over
and will only be shown four times a day
for the rest of all time.
-Krusty.
-Yeah?
Is your nose red because
it's embarrassed to be seen with you?
-(laughter)
-Oh, nobody warned me
this roast would treat me the same way
as every roast I've seen
and laughed at.
...and the husband says,
"Who paid you a nickel?"
And the wife says, "Everybody."
(laughs)
Oh, sorry, wrong for this audience.
I thought Swapper Jack's
was something else.
Krusty, sorry about the roast.
They had no right to say
those hilarious things.
How could they say
I'm past my prime?
Me-- the voice of Ovaltine.
Krusty, why don't you
talk to your dad?
He'll cheer you up.
He's a rabbi.
He must've learned something from that
giant star scroll he's always reading.
Kid, does talking to your dad
make you feel better?
Well, no, but he's not a rabbi.
More of a flabbi.
(snorts, laughs)
Why, you little...
I'll show you who's a flabbi!
(grunting)
-(muffled) No, you're not a flabbi!
-Yeah, all muscle.
-In Minnesota, I'd be a supermodel.
-Okay, I got it.
So, basically, I came here
so you could tell me the truth--
that I'm great.
As the Torah says--
Judgment belongs to God.
The Torah also says
you can't eat ham,
and I'm the spokesman
for HamCo Ham.
This is why I only call you
on Christmas and Easter.
Wait, wait, wait. Please, Dad.
Do you even think I'm funny?
I'm not gonna lie to you,
for funny,
I prefer Rabbi Rudenstein.
He puts the "ha" in Hanukkah
and the "levity" in Leviticus.
As for you, son,
if you want to know
my honest opinion of you,
you've always been... eh.
Go on.
I've always been "Eh... ntertaining"?
Dad?
Show me nose fog.
Oh, God, he's dead.
And he never lived
to see me be successful.
(sobbing)
A pusten fas hilcht hecher.
"An empty barrel reverberates loudly."
And today, my heart is that barrel.
Even though my father and I
had our difficulties...
(sobs) he was a great man.
And, well, he always...
-Wha...
-Eh.
ALL: Eh.
(continues)
(sighs)
Look, I'm an entertainer.
So maybe the best way to say
how I feel about my dad
is through a song
that someone else wrote
that I hired people to sing.
This is for you, Dad.
(to the Itchy & Scratchy theme)
♪ He fought and fought ♪
♪ And fought for Jewish rights ♪
♪ Wisdom sought, students taught ♪
♪ Rabbi Krustofsky's gone ♪
Yeah, well, it's just...
well, I thought...
Seriously, it can be really tough
to lose your father.
(crying)
Yasher Co-ack.
Let us all please rise.
-(snoring)
-Homer, get up.
Huh? Oh, uh...
(grunting)
Oh! Oh!
Ooh! (panting)
Dad, are you okay?
Yeah, yeah, great. (sighs)
I guess my getting-up days are over.
(gasps)
(Homer humming)
Dad, you're eating too much.
I'm worried about your health.
I don't want to lose you.
(softly) Oh, no.
Krusty, I brought some
homemade chicken soup.
We used the Play-Doh maker
for the matzo.
Uh, thanks,
but I don't really like soup.
But you wear that little spoon
around your neck.
(chuckles)
You really notice stuff, don't you?
Yes. And I can tell
how hard it was to lose your father.
But at least you were there
to share his final thoughts.
-Eh.
-No, no, it's a big thing.
No, that's what he called me. "Eh."
Well, it could be worse.
-Oh, yeah? How?
-I don't know, uh...
how about...
(blows raspberry)
That's a lot worse.
Can you stop comforting me now?
Krusty, condolences on your loss.
So this is the Bob
whose comedic genius
I can never live up to.
Believe me, all of us
have thought about killing him.
(sighs)
Clowns have it tough, Krusty.
I understand.
I was Professor Pickles with
Ringling Brothers for several years.
The elephant and I
had our differences.
So, what brings you here?
And don't say clown car.
I'm a sad, tragic clown.
Like what's his name-- Liberace.
Tell me about your father, huh?
Ah!
Herschel, did you read your Exodus?
Oh, uh, oh, sure.
Really? Then tell me,
what did the burning bush say?
It said, "Ow! Put me out!
How many talking bushes
do you think there are?!"
-(laughs)
-My son,
you are a big needy nothing
that only laughs can fill.
(scoffs) I don't need laughs.
-Ha.
-Oh, thank you. Thank you.
A big needy nothing.
-(sniffles)
-Wow. Wow.
Krusty, would you like a therapy dog?
Yeah. With extra relish!
Hey-hey! I still got it, huh?
Yes, if by "it" you mean
reflexive denial of your inner sadness.
(sadly) Hey-hey.
SIDESHOW MEL:
Shut up, children.
Boys and girls, you know
that we've been dark
for a couple of days because of
a tragic loss in the Krustylu family.
Now put your hands together
for the man who's falling apart
before our eyes,
Krusty the Clown!
(kids cheering)
(jaunty theme music plays)
No monologue. Roll the cartoon.
(swing creaking)
Oh, my God!
Who made this monstrosity?
I did everything!
Kids, I'm experiencing
a crisis of conscience.
(canned applause)
No, no, no, no!
I don't deserve the prerecorded applause
of children long gone.
-(canned applause)
-KID (over recording): I like Ike!
Therefore, I'm quitting the show.
And I know Mel
will be quitting it with me.
Yes, yes, buy the house.
It'll be...
Uh, what?!
Today is the day the pity laughter died.
Krusty the Clown has retired.
For a brief overview
of a half-century of ha-has,
here is Channel Six TV critic
Clive Meriwether.
Krusty the Clown
will perhaps best be remembered
for taking up two spots
in the Channel Six parking lot.
On a personal level,
he used to call me Little Lord Tingaling.
I shan't miss that.
This man's only lasting legacies
are a law in his name
limiting the working hours
of chimpanzees to 14 hours a day
and the invention
of the payment of alimony
by dropping hot pennies
from a helicopter.
I give his life a D-plus.
Good day to you.
What will Krusty do now?
I suppose only time will tell.
Which is true
for all news stories, I guess.
Until anyone realizes,
I'm Kent Brockman
adding no useful information.
And here's another sentence.
You can tell I'm winding it up
because my voice is going up
and down like this.
Well, at least now I have plenty of time
to solve this Rubik's Cube.
All right, what if I did...
Oh!
(Homer snoring unevenly)
(snoring, gasping)
-(quietly) Mom, Dad.
-Yes, Lisa?
(snores) What?
I've been listening,
and Dad stops breathing
for as long as five minutes.
Mind if I sleep with you guys
and keep an eye on him?
Sweetie, you shouldn't have to worry
about such things.
(gasps, snores, wheezing)
The doctor gave us this machine
to help him breathe in his sleep.
Go to bed. I'll take care of him.
No good. No good.
Oh! Ooh! Ah!
-(gasping)
-What do I do? What do I do?
Oh. Breathe, Homie, breathe.
(coughing)
Well, at least Teeny's doing okay.
He's in The Odd Couple
with David Hyde Pierce.
Now, really, Oscar,
would it kill you to use a coaster?
(screeching)
If you're going to go up there,
at least dust!
Finally, done the way
I first imagined it.
I'm gonna prove
you did groundbreaking work.
Krusty, I want you to binge-watch
all the shows you've ever done.
Well, I've never said no to a binge.
(static crackles)
Deuteronomy?
Isn't that the study of deuters?
Hippocampus?
Isn't that another name for
the University of Mississippi?
Okay. I've been on 50 years.
You're bound
to repeat yourself a little.
Unless I wanted to be sat on
by Mama Cass.
Unless I wanted to be
sat on by Dom DeLuise.
...by the cast of
What's Happening!!
...William "The Refrigerator" Perry,
everyone!
...Newman from Seinfeld.
...the whale from Whale Rider.
...Adele! (laughs)
What? She's a guest star?!
(sobbing)
(groans)
(static hissing)
So that's why
all my cameramen have PTSD.
Where's my whiskey funnel?!
(German accent)
Young man, you should go.
When the master is like this,
it is no place for children.
Pour, Helga!
It begins.
(gulping)
(angelic choir singing)
Whoa. Where am I?
Why, you're in Jewish Heaven.
Oh, this place is great.
Why, my necktie straightens itself.
Even Portnoy has no complaints.
And I tell you,
I get so much respect.
Wow. So I made it to Heaven.
(klezmer playing)
(crowd cheering)
This place is amazing!
Schmuck, there's no Jewish Heaven.
Our faith teaches us
that once you're dead, that's it, kaput.
It's dark, it's cold.
It's like that apartment we lived in
before I started doing weddings.
But you, my son, remain...
Eh?! (groans)
Go back to Earth.
Do something with your life.
Help people.
(echoing)
Help people. Help people.
Help people.
Nothing. I'm not getting a pulse.
(gasps)
I got to change my life!
Still no pulse.
I guess I'm just really bad at this.
♪ Someone to watch ♪
♪ Over me ♪
I'm afraid Lisa's getting obsessed
with keeping her father out of danger.
She's gotten our Resusci Annie doll
to breathe on its own.
(wheezes) Why?
In this new shelter,
we provide a home
for animals put out of work
by Cirque du Soleil.
(gorilla growls)
Um, Krusty, have you fulfilled
the promise you made to your father
in the dream
you never told anyone about?
Uh, no.
Somehow a brief act of uncharacteristic
generosity solved nothing.
-Hey, Krusty.
-What?
Have you been going to temple?
Yeah, and I've learned that
all religions are equally boring.
But there's a reason I went.
Come and see.
Kid, there's no way
you can cheer me up.
Not when whiskey,
good deeds, and hookers failed.
Who's a hooker?
Uh, with me, it's easier to say
which ones aren't hookers.
Hmm?
(grunting)
Lisa, what are you doing?
Wrapping you in bubble wrap.
I can't always be around
to protect you, so it will.
But...
-(bubble wrap popping)
-Oh, Lisa, honey,
you can't insulate yourself from life.
Why, I could live till 100
or a bus could hit me tomorrow.
That's why I never plan
more than four seconds ahead.
Oh, I guess you're right.
Now come on.
Give Daddy a hug.
-(grunting)
-(bubble wrap popping)
-Bubble wrap!
Your daughterly love saved me, sweetie.
That's all I wanted,
a tiny bit of control.
Ooh. I suppose we should
exchange insurance information.
-I don't have any.
-Me neither.
Then we have the same company.
They'll work it all out.
(tires screech)
(quietly) Rabbi Rudenstein.
Your father's favorite.
Today's reading is from Deuteronomy,
which I believe is the study of deuters.
(laughter)
Hey, that's my joke.
Eh, must be a coincidence.
Uh, but before we begin,
I'd like to quote the burning bush,
which said, "Hey, put me out.
How many talking bushes
do you think there are?"
Hey-hey.
(laughter)
Me again.
So if Dad loved his jokes, then...
Dad loved my jokes.
(crying) Oh...
Yeah, I guess he just
hated your delivery.
He loved my jokes.
My father respected me
but could never tell me.
That's Jewish Heaven.
♪ Heaven ♪
♪ Jewish Heaven ♪
RABBI KRUSTOFSKY:
♪ We're a father and a son ♪
♪ Who didn't speak ♪
♪ But up here we found
the happiness we seek ♪
♪ And I can't wait
till you join me next week ♪
You!
(music continues)
Uh, just this once, you think you could
turn water into a Bloody Mary?
I'll tell you,
you're all right, you know?
Krusty, let's face it,
you might not be cutting-edge anymore,
but your show still does
really great in that key demo
of people who died with the TV on.
-(laughter)
-Whoa.
Of course, Krusty's responsible for
Itchy & Scratchy,
which is also
what he calls his testicles.
(groans)
♪ ♪
D'oh.
-(crowd murmuring)
-Shh!
Subtitled by C. Noline