(start-up chime sounds)
(man humming)
(groans)
(grunting)
(mouse clicks)
Hmm. Hmm.
Hmm!
♪
Hey, guys.
It's your favorite
YouTube family vloggers:
the Simpsons.
Coinstar bought us a new house,
and we're gonna give you
the grand tour.
Come on in.
Take your shoes off first.
All 50 million of you. (laughs)
♪
Now, we can't tell you
where the new house is located
because we value our privacy.
Which you know if you watched
our last family therapy sesh
where Marge begged me to stop
filming our therapy seshes.
Video link in bio.
This is my favorite room
because the kitchen is really
the heart of a home.
Also, because a robot cleans it.
And check it out.
The refrigerator
blends into the wall.
No more tedious seeing your
refrigerator all the time.
Come on, we want to show you
our favorite room.
(grunting)
This is our screening room.
It's also where
we shoot our confessionals.
It's cool that Dad doesn't have
to work nine to five anymore.
We just have to post
15 videos a day.
After homeschooling,
we're free to do fun kid stuff.
Zoom calls with
our fan club in Dubai,
giving Lamborghinis
to the homeless.
Sometimes I
just chill in my room,
recording Cameo messages
until my voice gives out.
(sucks on pacifier)
MAN: Huh.
(grunting)
M'atchomaroon,
or "Hey, guys" in Dothraki.
Today I'm doing a deep-dive
on the Internet's
current obsession,
The Simpsons Family Channel.
Camera 2.
In case you've been living in a
tauntaun these past four months,
here's the video
that started it all:
"Cute Baby Gets Stage Fright."
Let's take a look.
♪ I have a duckie tail ♪
♪ And a little duckie head ♪
(crowd chuckles)
♪ I quack around the park ♪
♪ And I eat
the old man's bread ♪
Maggie, remember
what we practiced.
Poke Daddy's tummy
and kill the ants.
♪ Honk, stomp, quack ♪
Shake your diaper,
touch the starfish,
open your sandwich,
and Mick Jagger, Jagger, Jagger.
(crowd cheers)
- (Homer shouts)
- (crowd gasps)
(crowd cheers)
No, don't!
- (Homer gasping)
- (crowd gasping)
(crowd cheers)
(crowd oohs)
(crowd laughs, cheers)
Best... origin story... ever.
It deservedly
got 20 million views,
and Homer launched a channel
all about the special bond
between himself
and the youngling Maggie.
(eating noisily)
(Maggie eats noisily)
(dog whines)
(vacuum cleaner running)
Say, Maggie,
do you think our viewers
could enter the code "Aw"
with 15 Ws for a discount
from Toy-Weasel.com?
HOMER:
Mmm.
The Internet fell in love
with the rest of the Simpsons
when they released...
♪ Everybody, yeah ♪
♪ Rock your body, yeah... ♪
(tires screeching)
- (siren wailing)
- ♪ Now throw your hands
up in the air ♪
Whoa, what's going on?
(shouts)
(over radio):
♪ 'Cause we got it
going on again ♪
WIGGUM:
Oh. I love this song.
♪ Am I sexual? ♪
♪ Yeah. ♪
MAN:
Hmm.
- Hmm.
- (mouse clicks)
(theme song plays)
(camera shutter clicks)
Greetings, newshounds.
Today, a retrospective on
The Simpsons Family Vlog.
In case you've been living
in a grammar-rodeo boot camp
these past four months,
here's the video
that started it all.
(fast-forwarding)
Soon each family member
had their own channel.
Marge combined her
love of cooking
and deeply personal questions
for a groundbreaking
interview show.
How you holding up, Krusty?
Ready for number four?
(groans) I'm not gonna lie,
number three feels like
it's not done with me,
but my agent said
this is what talk shows are now,
so... (burps) bring it on.
MARGE:
Next up, The Coagulator.
A tuna melt dipped
in funnel cake batter,
then fried in hot mayonnaise.
It clocks in at 300,000
on the Lethargo Scale.
Oh, I'm really regretting
all those bagels
I ate in the greenroom.
(shouts)
The grease
and the powdered sugar
are forming a paste
in the back of my throat.
Do you think your comedy
is fueled by rage
towards your father
or towards yourself?
Well, I'd rather talk about
my new holiday movie,
A Very Merry Bris-mas.
(gags)
Oh, the batter is in my lungs.
Ow! Why is this a show?!
MARTIN:
And Bart took pranking
to a whole new level
with The 'Gurt Squad.
(stifling laughter)
Can I sample
the strawberry yogurt?
Wait, I'm allergic to strawb...
(imitates vomiting)
('Gurt Squad laughing)
The Simpsons were
YouTube sensations,
and corporate America
lavished them
with sponsorships and lucre.
But Lisa used her newfound fame
to draw attention
to issues close to her heart.
Hey, guys.
I'm here at Needle Beach,
super stoked
to start this clean-up
because, as you can see,
this beach
is pretty messed up.
(gasps) What's that?
Oh! Oh, you poor thing.
Luckily,
I always carry wire cutters.
♪
(mouse clicks)
(distorted voice):
Attention, Internet.
It is I, Truth Wizard.
The Simpsons are not
who you think they are,
and I can't let
these lies continue
for even one more sec...
...and I can't let
these lies continue
for even one more sec...
LUANN:
Milhouse, why are you
sitting in the dark?
You'll ruin your eyes.
Mom.
The doctor said your nose
can't support thicker glasses.
I'm recording a takedown.
Get out.
(door closes)
Okay, fine, it's me, Milhouse.
I was the one filming
every Simpson family video.
Take your shoes off first.
All 50 million of you. (laughs)
Yo, camera-monkey, shoes off.
MILHOUSE: I saw firsthand how
the pressure to create content
- turned them into monsters.
- (Homer growls)
- HOMER: Where the hell
is the refrigerator?!
- (groans) Coming.
(grunting)
You have to tap it.
(grunts)
Oh, who would want this?
- I'm getting a hammer.
- No.
You never let me get the hammer!
Ew, your hand is so sweaty.
Would you tell my scene partner
to be professional?
MILHOUSE:
Uh, Bart? Lisa has a note...
Shut up, Milhouse.
MILHOUSE:
Ow.
And those cool
'Gurt Squad friends
that hype up
Bart's prank videos?
Paid Spucklers.
Hey, guys,
you don't have to go home
just 'cause
we're done filming pranks.
Yeah, we was meaning
to ask you about that.
How is what you do a prank?
This just seems like
a mean-spirited waste of yogurt.
Okay, we'll use pudding.
Great note.
Hey, you guys want
to jump on my trampoline?
I'll take
the safety barrier down.
We prefer to keep our
relationship professional.
I'll... pay you.
(groans) Fine.
Time and a half.
And a basket of eggs.
Our hen is feeling poorly.
MILHOUSE:
Even my off-again, off-again
girlfriend Lisa
fell prey to the siren's call
of Internet fame.
What the hell is this?
This beach is spotless.
MILHOUSE:
Sorry, Lisa. We're on it.
(grunts)
Now where's this thing
I'm supposed to save?
MILHOUSE:
Uh, Gil, how's it coming?
I-I'm trying. Ow!
This little fella's really
good at freeing himself.
CREW PERSON:
That's a rented seal. Catch him.
We're gonna lose our deposit.
(both grunting)
But let's take a look
at the relationship
that started
this whole crazy ride:
Homer and Maggie.
We are so excited
to work with Maggie
on this viral campaign for
Nom-Noms 6:
European Nom-cation.
We got Maggie's room all set up
for the ultimate immersive
Nom-Nom experience.
Uh, one little hiccup.
Maggie's terrified of Nom-Noms,
especially the girl one.
I'm not sure why.
Uh, Bart will do it.
The yogurt kid? No way. No.
Either the Internet baby
goes in there,
or you forfeit
all nom-pensation.
So that's, uh, "nom"-negotiable?
- (chuckles)
- That's not a real word.
Maggie, there's
a cute baby bunny in there,
so put this GoPro
on your head...
Nom-nom-nom-nom-nom-nom-nom-nom.
(Maggie shrieks, cries)
NOM-NOMS:
Nom-nom-nom-nom-nom-nom-
nom-nom-nom-nom-nom-nom...
(Maggie screaming)
(Maggie crying)
Oh...
Maggie, I'm sorry.
(Maggie fussing)
Poor Maggie. Although
I like the girl Nom-Nom.
I like her a lot.
I like the way her glasses
have eyelashes and...
LUANN:
Milhouse,
come do your ear drops.
Mom!
(mouse clicks)
Hey, guys.
Welcome to episode 751 of
The Lenny and Carl Situation.
Back with us
is our frequent guest Moe.
You gonna behave today, Moe?
(chuckling):
Hey, don't cancel me, huh?
Today we're talking about
the Simpson family,
specifically "Super Dad"
himself, Homer Simpson.
Guy's a phony.
Full disclosure:
You go back five, six months,
we were best friends
with the guy
before he got famous
for those baby videos.
Yeah, so many nights getting
blackout drunk with Homer.
I don't remember him
mentioning that baby once.
And I heard Maggie won't make
any more videos with him.
What people been seeing
is all high-tech trickery.
Intern Barney, play the clip.
HOMER: Mmm.
Oh, even fake Maggies
hate me.
(laughing)
You know, I'm thinking about
going on the all-peanut diet.
You heard about this?
Supposed to be great
for the adrenals.
You know, the Aztecs,
that's all they ate was peanuts.
Not like the crap we got today.
Them ancient nuts,
they was full of that, uh, uh,
niacinnamonites. Yeah.
'Cause of the sand they had.
And they lived to be a hundred,
200 years old.
- (man groans)
- MOE: Same thing with
the Mayans and cashews...
MAN:
Uh-uh.
(mouse clicks)
Hey, guys.
We know there have been
a lot of rumors going around.
So we wanted
to formally announce
that we'll be making
a formal announcement
tomorrow night on our livestream
which will address
all the recent controversies.
And we'll Cluck-Stop at nothing
to earn your trust back.
(grunts)
FRINK:
That was nine days ago.
Nobody has seen or heard
from the Simpsons family since.
Over the next two hours,
I will break down my theories
on what might have caused
their dramatic disappearance
on this special edition of...
That's your cue.
This special edition of...
Frinkileaks.
Now play
the suspenseful music.
No, that's a latte macchiato.
(suspenseful music playing)
Well, you might as well
finish my coffee now.
(grunting)
Which brings us once again
to Snowball I,
which... (groans)
Marker fumes. Oh, my.
Hoyvik! Blarvlagin! Ivy.
(clears throat)
I apologize.
Um... in summary, I have
concluded that the Simpsons
are being held hostage
by a major tech company.
Now, I cannot
say which one, but, um,
follow the Google Doodles.
If, uh, you pause
right where the video glitches,
you can see Homer
doesn't look human.
More like an alien wearing
an ill-fitting human suit.
Let me tell you something,
Homer Simpsons has done more
for this country
than Dr. Fauci
and Dr. Pimple Popper combined.
It's not his fault
he has a trash son
with a face
like a lunch bag, okay?
Leave Homer Simpsons alone!
Leave him alone!
(enunciating):
Welcome back to Patty...
And Selma's...
BOTH:
Tingle Palace.
We were going to do part four
of our scalp-delousing
role-play.
(tines riffling)
But, in light of recent events,
we're going to tell you what
we think happened to our
sister Marge Simpson.
(scales rubbing)
It's pretty obvious
that Homer snapped,
ate the whole family.
and is hiding on a houseboat,
in a cloud of belches
that used to be his wife
and kids.
(grunts)
(scraping)
- (man shudders)
- (mouse clicks)
Hmm... hmm.
What's up, guys?
Today we had
a whole cemetery parkour
segment ready to go,
but instead we've got
a big announcement.
The location
of the Simpsons' mansion
has always been super secret,
but we figured out where it is.
We found clues
in all their old videos.
We're talking
regional birdsongs,
town-specific
ice cream truck jingle.
But the clincher:
my mom's dating a guy
who got fired
from the post office,
and he gave us their address.
We're heading there tonight
to get some answers.
But first, parkour.
Parkour. (grunts)
Beloved husband!
Angel-baby!
Jewish guy! Parkour!
- (mouse clicks)
- MAN: Eh...
- Huh.
- (mouse clicks)
Hey, guys, I'm Shauna.
With a freaking exclusive.
I found the Simpsons mansion.
What the hell, Jimbo?
Did you tell her the address?
JIMBO:
Duh. She's my girlfriend. Hey...
(grunting)
MARTIN:
Martin Prince here, now embedded
at the Simpsons family compound.
SHAUNA:
We're about to get
scooped, dumb-wads.
Hey, guys, Simpsons...
(speaking gibberish)
Like and subscribe.
- PATTY: Hey, guys.
- COMIC BOOK GUY: Hey, guys.
- SHERRI AND TERRI: Hey, guys.
- MOE: Hey, guys.
(gasps) It's a vlog swarm.
No, no, no. This is our content.
JIMBO:
Okay, okay.
(Crazy Cat Lady
speaking gibberish)
JIMBO:
But turn on that light.
NELSON:
This way, come on.
(all panting)
Ha! Look at this.
They obviously left in a hurry
without their phones.
Shut up.
I can't hear myself Shauna.
- Move out, people, let's go,
let's go, let's go.
- Come on, guys, let's go.
(gasps)
Huh?
(all shouting)
- Hmm?
- What is this?
(all grunt curiously)
- (Simpsons gasp)
- I found 'em!
Somebody get a pic!
Bart, the door!
- MARGE: Grab it!
- LISA: Get it!
Welcome, Simpson family.
So, nine days
in a panic room. Why?
Well, Opal,
our house had been built
by a company we partnered with
that, at that point,
had only built NFTs of houses.
(chuckles)
They installed
the panic room door backwards.
You could get in,
but you can't get out.
But how did you all
end up trapped there?
Well, we'd been getting ready
for our redemption livestream,
and we were all a little tense.
So I went to the panic room,
where we stored
all of our sponsored crap,
to get some
children's CBD gummies.
But I was already in there
pounding 'em.
MARGE: Then I ran in
and yelled, "Stop fighting.
"You're going to sweat through
your signature line
of slimming activewear."
BART:
But when we tried to leave,
it was locked.
LISA:
I said, "Nobody panic.
There's got to be
a panic button."
HOMER:
Then I walked in, saying,
"Marge, I can't find
the fridge again."
LISA:
We tried to grab the door.
But it was too late.
We were trapped,
and it was all Homer's fault.
What? You said
it was nobody's fault.
That's what
I'm supposed to feel,
but I'm not there yet.
LISA:
We survived on products
we'd been shilling
but had never
actually eaten before.
Luckily, there was
also a huge supply
of single-use hat-toilets.
Uh, I'm pretty sure
those were just hats.
We didn't have any way
to post content,
so we went through
pretty severe withdrawal.
MARGE:
Then, sometime around day four,
I said, "Where's Maggie?
She was just here a second ago."
I moved the table from the wall
and said,
(gasps) "Oh, God. She must've
crawled in the vent."
HOMER:
I said, "Maggie, come back."
That I'd never force her
to do content ever again,
that I wouldn't be
♪Daddy anymore,
I'd just be Daddy.
And then...
LISA:
She'd been in the cabinet
the whole time.
We were so relieved.
MARGE:
Then we realized how high up
she was, and then...
BART:
But Homer made an awesome catch.
And Maggie barfed on him.
(chuckles)
Classic.
MARGE:
After that,
something strange happened.
We started talking
to each other.
BART:
Like texting with our mouths.
LISA:
I'd almost forgotten
I could L-O-L I-R-L.
MARGE:
It felt like we were
coming out of a trance.
LISA:
The only subscribers we needed
were in that room.
Wow. Just, wow.
We're shutting down
the YouTube channel
because "The Simpson Family"
isn't who we are.
We are the Simpsons.
We are completely offline now.
I don't even check
email anymore,
but that's mainly 'cause we
moved back to Evergreen Terrace,
and our neighborino changed
his Wi-Fi passwordily-durdily.
Well, there you have it.
A confusing, nonsense-word end
to the meteoric rise and fall
and disappearance
and reappearance
and return to status quo
for the family
the Internet could not
get enough of
for almost half a year.
Can we go look at your beehives?
Nah, we're all done here.
Well, that's four hours
of my life I'll never get back.
WOMAN:
George R. R. Martin, you better
be working on that new book.
I am.
You said you would finish
it years ago.
I'm gonna.
They already made two TV shows
about it.
I know that.
I went to the parties.
No more parties until
you finish that book.
I'm writing it right now.
I'm... doing research.
(typing)
Oh.
You did not just stick
your hands in the mint bowl.
Girl, use the spoon,
or I'm gonna have to
kick your
Rooty Tooty Fresh 'N Booty.
Bitch, that is
an IHOP reference.
- This is a Waffle House, mama.
- The Waffle House.
♪ Waffle to the House, House ♪
♪ Waf to the kach
to the House, how ♪
- ♪ From the legendary
House of Waffle. ♪
- (chuckling)
Captioning sponsored by
20th CENTURY FOX TELEVISION
and FOX BROADCASTING COMPANY
and TOYOTA.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org
Shh!