♪ The Simpsons ♪
(chalk screeches)
(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(tires screeching)
(horn honks)
(tires screech)
-(screams)
-(tires screech)
Busted my hump all week.
Stupid grass!
Supposed to be the boy's job.
Now, now, Homer
Bart's busy working
on his science project.
You heard the lady, Homer
so please mow quietly.
Genius at work.
1:00, still just a potato.
Hey there, neighbor.
The Lord's certainly given us
a beautiful day today, huh?
-Hello, Flanders.
-Doing a little yard work, huh?
Who told?
Marge, beer me.
Say, Simpson
I've got some
time-released granules
that will get rid of that
crabgrass in just half a jiff.
Crabgrass?
What are you talking about?
-Where?
-Well, there, there...
and there's
a big patch over there.
There's nothing wrong
with crabgrass.
It just has a bad name,
that's all.
Everyone would love it
if it had a cute name
like "elfgrass."
(chuckles)
Well, you may be right.
-Marge, where's the Duff?
-Oh, we're all out, Homer.
-D'oh!
-Would you like some fruit juice?
Don't toy with me, woman.
I couldn't help
overhearing, Simpson.
I've got some ice-cold suds
in the rumpus room
if you'd like to join me.
Well, uh, okay, what the heck?
I've earned a little break.
(gasps)
Holy moly.
It's beautiful.
Say, that's right.
This is your first visit
to the Flanders homestead.
Well, we've
only been neighbors what?
(muttering)
Eight years.
There's my little popcorn ball.
Kissy-kissy.
Oh, hello, sponge cake.
I thought you boys
might be hungry
so I whipped up
some club sandwiches.
Ain't she wonderful, Simpson?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, but aren't we
forgetting something, Flanders?
Oh, your beer.
Uh, is draft okay?
Just put in the tap
last week.
Heh heh.
Here's a tasty little lager
that came all the way
from Holland.
Well, beggars can't be choosy.
-(burp)
-Hey, Dad,
thanks for helping me
with my science project.
-Mwah!
-Oh, my pleasure, study buddy.
Aw, I got the best Dad
in the whole world.
NED: Oh, now, you know
how that embarrasses me.
I know. Toodley-doodley.
(sighs) Kids can be
a trial sometimes.
All right,
knock it off!
Knock what off, Simpson?
You've been rubbing
my nose in it since I got here!
Your family is better
than my family!
Your beer comes
from farther away than my beer!
You and your son
like each other!
Your wife's butt is higher
than my wife's butt.
You make me sick!
Simpson, I'm afraid
I'm going to
have to ask you to leave.
I hope you understand.
I wouldn't stay on a bet!
One for the road.
(Homer moaning)
Homey, quit tossing.
Sorry, Marge.
But it's just that
I'm still steamed up
about that jerk Flanders.
Lousy, bragging
know-it-all, show-off.
What exactly did he say?
Get this.
He said...
No, he said...
Well, it wasn't so much
what he said,
it was how he said it.
How did he say it?
-Well, he...
-Was he angry?
-No.
-Was he rude?
Okay, okay.
It wasn't how he said it either,
but the message
was loud and clear.
Our family stinks!
Homer, I'm your best friend,
but I've gotta say,
I've never seen him be anything
but a perfect neighbor.
Oh, he's perfect now, is he?
Well, he's not perfect,
but he is very...
No, no, Marge,
don't backpedal!
You were right the first time.
He's perfect!
Perfect in every way.
I'm just gonna go take a walk
around the block to calm down.
I got a little excited.
I'm not perfect...
like Ned Flanders.
(concerned groan)
Neddy, you're tossing.
What's the matter?
I feel terrible.
Sometimes I forget
that we have things a little better
than the Simpsons.
I drag him over here,
he has a few beers.
You can't blame him
for erupting and then...
I turn into a snarling beast.
Talk about flunking the old
turn-the-other-cheek test.
Well, Ned, maybe I'm not the one
you should be talking to.
You're right.
Hello, Reverend Lovejoy?
(yawns)
No, this is Mrs. Lovejoy.
Just a minute.
Honey, honey, wake up.
It sounds like Ned Flanders
is having some sort of crisis.
Oh, probably stepped
on a worm.
(clears nose)
Hello, Ned.
Reverend, I'm sorry
to bother you at this hour,
but I threw a man
out of my house today.
I feel like I violated
Matthew 19:19.
-Huh?
-"Love thy neighbor."
Oh, oh.
Matthew 19:19, right, right.
Well, you know, Ned,
the good book says
"A gentle answer
turneth away wrath."
A gentle answer?
Well, that is a jim-dandy idea.
Bless you, Reverend.
"Dear neighbor..."
-HOMER: Flanders!
-Ah!
I don't blame you for
being upset with me, Homer.
I just wanted to give you
this letter.
I'll leave now.
"Dear neighbor...
(laughing)
-"You are my brother."
-(laughing)
-"I love you.
"And yet I feel
a great sadness
in my bosom."
(cackling)
Bosom.
Wait, wait, there's more.
I think that's terrible.
A man opens his heart,
and you make fun of him.
-(giggles)
-(laughter)
"Neighbors forever."
Oh, no.
(laughing)
-"Ned Flanders."
-(laughing)
What a sap.
Read the bosom part
again, Dad.
-Now just a minute!
-Bosom.
(laughing)
Bart!
I wish this family was
as close as the Flanders.
Okay, okay,
all right, all right.
She's right.
Let's do something together.
What does everyone say
to some miniature golf
followed by a round of frosty
chocolate milk shakes?
All right.
Hmm, I was going
to wash my hair.
And I'm studying
for the math fair.
If I win, I'll bring home
a brand new protractor.
Too bad we don't live
on a farm.
Let's go, boy.
Fore!
(laughing)
But I got it in the middle.
D'oh! That was just
a practice shot, boy.
Play it where it
lays, Homer.
Hey, there's Homer Simpson.
What a perfect opportunity
to follow up on my letter.
Aw, give up, homeboy.
There's a six-stroke limit.
I know, I know.
I can still make this for five.
Come on, baby, please,
please, go in, please.
D'oh!
(grunting)
Hi, Simpson.
Having fun?
Flanders,
what are you doing here?
Oh, just playing a little mini-golf
with the Todd-meister.
-Hi, Bart.
-Get bent.
Say, now that we're
all friends again,
why don't we
make a foursome?
-That sounds great.
-Well, okay.
All right.
This will be fun.
Oh, say, you looked like
you were having a little
trouble there.
Well, that shot is impossible!
Jack Nicholson himself
couldn't make it.
TODD: It is difficult,
Mr. Simpson.
The best strategy is
to play conservatively.
Hug the rail.
It won't go in
but you set yourself up
for an easy deuce.
Oh, well... hmm.
It went in.
-Good shot, Toddski.
-Luck.
BART:
Final score, Bart 41.
Homer, let's see...
Six plus six plus six
plus six plus six...
-Never mind.
-Hey, look.
TODD:
Wow! First prize, $50.
Wow! Free balloons
for everyone who enters.
So my little Bartly, thinking
of entering the tournament?
Yeah, he's entering and what's more,
he's going to win, aren't you, boy?
-I guess it's possible.
-Hey, I like that confidence.
But I hope you're not putting
too much pressure on the boy.
My Todd's awfully good.
Oh, yeah? Well, I think
the fruit of my loins
can beat the fruit of your loins
any day of the week.
-Come on, boy.
-Hyuh!
-(Homer slurps loudly)
-But Dad,
I've never won
anything in my life.
Son, this is the only time
I'm ever gonna say this.
It is not okay to lose.
Stay, stay. Good dog.
Now, keep your head down.
D'oh! Not you.
I'm talking to the boy.
Keep your head down.
Follow through.
Okay, that didn't work.
This time, move your head
and don't follow through.
Oh, man.
(concerned groaning)
What are you doing?
That putter is to you what a bat is
to a baseball player.
What a violin is to the...
the guy... the violin guy.
Now come on!
Give your putter a name.
What?
-Come on. Give it a name.
-Mr. Putter.
Oh! You want to try
a little harder, son?
-C'mon, give it a girl's name.
-Mom.
-Your putter's name is Charlene.
-Why?
It just is, that's why.
Now this is a picture
of your enemy
Todd Flanders.
Every day, I want you
to spend 15 minutes
staring at it
and concentrating
on how much you hate him,
and how glorious it will be
when you and Charlene
annihilate him.
-Who's Charlene?
-I'll show you who Charlene is.
Now start hating.
(growling)
Ugh.
Hi, Bart.
Homer, I couldn't help
overhearing you warp Bart's mind.
-And?
-Well, I'm worried
that you're making too big a deal
of this silly little
kiddie golf tournament.
But Marge, this is our big chance
to show up the Flanderses.
I'm sure it is,
but why do we want to do that?
Because sometimes the only way
you can feel good about yourself
is by making
someone else look bad.
And I'm tired of making other people
feel good about themselves.
Hmm.
-(groans)
-Hi, Bart. What are you doing?
Hey Lise, what do you call those guys
in chess that don't matter?
Well, a black-headed bishop
is of little value
but I think you're
referring to a pawn.
Right. I am a pawn.
Hmm, I know.
It's times like this that I'm thankful
Dad has little to no interest
in almost everything I do.
Bart, I think
I can help you.
LISA: Our journey begins here
at the library.
-Hi, Lisa.
-Hi, Mrs. Norton.
-Hey, Ralph.
-Hi, Lisa.
-Hey, gang.
Okay, Bart, this is
the card catalogue.
Let's see. Golf.
Anecdotes, Eisenhower and...
profession, humor,
Japanese obsession with...
Ah, here it is.
Putting.
And finally, the most
important book of all--
The Tao-Te Ching by Lao-Tzu.
Lisa, we can't afford
all these books.
Bart, we're just
gonna borrow them.
Oh, heh heh! Gotcha.
LISA: I want you to shut off
the logical part of your mind.
BART: Okay.
-Embrace nothingness.
-You got it.
Become like
an uncarved stone.
-Done.
-Bart!
You're just pretending to
know what I'm talking about.
-True.
-Well, it's very frustrating.
I'll bet.
Bart, I have a riddle for you.
What's the sound
of one hand clapping?
Piece of cake.
(fingers slapping)
No, Bart, it's a 3, 000-year-old riddle
with no answer.
It supposed to clear your
mind of conscious thought.
No answer?
Lisa, listen up.
(fingers slapping)
Uh, let's try another one.
If a tree falls in the woods,
and no one's around,
does it make a sound?
Absolutely.
(makes crashing noises)
But Bart,
how can sound exist
if there's no one there
to hear it?
Whoo!
It is time.
The basis of this game seems
to be simple geometry.
All you have to do
is hit the ball here.
I can't believe it.
You've actually found
a practical use for geometry.
Bart, what are you doing?
Get down from there before
the neighbors see--
-Hey, Simpson.
-D'oh!
Flanders, I don't care
what this looks like.
Bart's gonna mop the floor
with your son's ugly butt.
Well, sir,
may the best man win.
Ah! "May the best man win."
The mating call of the loser.
Just a minute, Simpson.
I think my son has
a very good chance.
Oh, yeah? Want to bet?
Yeah, well,
I'm not a betting man.
(clucking sounds)
Oh, I'm a chicken, am I?
-That's right.
-All right, how's this for a wager?
A batch of your wife's
delicious blueberry muffins
against one of my wife's
homemade wind chimes.
Wha-- Are you afraid
to make a real bet?
-No, I just...
-(clucking)
You know, Simpson,
you're starting to annoy me.
How about this, henny penny?
If Bart wins tomorrow,
you have to mow my lawn.
All right, and if Todd wins,
-Aah!
-And do a decent job of it for a change!
Better yet, you have
to mow my lawn
in your wife's Sunday dress!
You have yourself a bet,
you... jackaninny!
Read that back to me, Marge.
"The father of the loser
mows the lawn..."
Hey, hey. Just a minute.
Loser is such a harsh word.
Couldn't we say,
"the boy who doesn't win"?
Oh, man. Fine.
"The father of the boy
who doesn't win
has to mow the lawn
in his wife's Sunday dress."
There you go.
Now, I suppose
you both have to sign this.
I hope blood
won't be necessary.
I'm game
if you are, Flanders.
(sighs)
Good gravy,
what have I done?
Keep your
left arm straight, Bart.
-Rotate your shoulders.
-TOGETHER: Dad!
Look, son. All I'm asking
is that you try.
Okay, I'll try.
Anybody can try!
I want you to win!
(screams)
Homer?
Marge?
Give me your honest opinion.
-This or this?
-(groans)
-Aah!
-Good morning, son.
Oh, by the way, today's
the day of the big tournament.
-And you'd better win!
-Dad!
See you downstairs, boy.
Heh, heh, heh.
That crazy Marmaduke.
-Eighth hole.
-Aim for the octopus, third tentacle.
-12th hole.
-Bank it off the pink tombstone.
-Nirvana.
-A state of bliss attained through
the extinction of the self.
MARGE: Here you go, Bart.
A lumberjack's breakfast
for my little golfer.
Mom, Bart is on a strict diet
of complex carbohydrates.
Steak will make him logy.
Well, what won't make
him logy?
-Oatmeal.
-Oatmeal?
Oats are what
a champion thoroughbred eats
before he or she wins
the Kentucky Derby.
News flash, Lisa.
Bart is not a horse.
Eat your steak, boy.
ANNOUNCER (British accent):
Good afternoon, everybody,
and welcome to the finale
of what has already been
a stirring afternoon
of miniature golf.
The cream has risen.
The wheat has bid farewell to the chaff.
And now we approach the championship
match with but two warriors remaining:
the heretofore unknown
Bart Simpson
and Todd Flanders,
one of the most skilled ten-year-olds
to ever take back the blade.
Bart, having never received any words
of encouragement myself,
I'm not sure how they're supposed
to sound, but here goes.
-I believe in you.
-Thanks, man.
NED: Oh Lord,
we beseech thee...
Hey Flanders,
it's no use praying.
I already did
the same thing
and we can't both win.
Actually Simp-son, we were
praying that no one gets hurt.
Oh, well, Flan-ders,
it doesn't matter.
This time tomorrow
you'll be wearing high heels.
-No, you will. Afraid so.
-Afraid not. Afraid not.
-Afraid so.
-Afraid not, infinity.
-Afraid so, infinity plus one.
-D'oh!
ANNOUNCER:
Young Flanders has the honor
and will tee off first.
It's got a chance.
-(ball clanking)
-Yes, sir!
Oh, man.
(exhaling) Tree falling in the woods.
Tree falling in the woods.
Tree falling in...
-(ball clanking)
-(crowd murmurs)
ANNOUNCER: And the battle
is well and truly joined.
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Mercy is for the weak, Todd!
Yeah!
Yee-hee!
Eee, eee...
D'oh!
ANNOUNCER:
If one were to look up "courage"
in the Oxford English
dictionary,
one might very well
come upon a photo
of these two gladiators.
They approach the final hole
in the shadow of
The Great Emancipator
deadlocked at eight strokes
on the happy side of par.
Soon, one man will
emerge triumphant.
He will drink naught
but champagne
while his opponent tastes bitter defeat,
in this oft-cruel game.
(crowd oohs)
It's okay, son.
You can recover.
Come on, Bart.
Remember what
Vince Lombardi said--
"If you lose,
you're out of the family."
-Homer! (smack)
-Ow!
-(gasps)
(gasping)
-Whew!
Neither man showing
his best form.
This sort of pressure
can unhinge
even the steeliest
of competitors.
This is pretty tense,
isn't it, Todd?
Yeah. My knees
are shaking
I got butterflies
in my stomach,
but I guess this
builds character.
Who wants to build character?
-Let's quit.
-Okay.
We decided
we're equally good.
We wanna call it a draw, man.
-Hmm.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we have a draw.
(crowd murmurs)
Forgive an old Brit
for crying,
but this is
the most stirring display
of gallantry and sportsmanship
since Mountbatten gave Egypt
back to the Punjabis.
Put her there, man.
Yeah, all right.
Well, Homer
our kids showed us
something today, huh?
By working together,
we can both be winners.
(chuckles) Thank heaven,
neither of us has to go through
with that silly wager.
Put her there, pal.
Oh, so you're going
to welch on our bet?
What are you talking about?
Neither boy lost.
I got it in right here
in writing.
"The father of the boy
who doesn't win
has to mow the lawn
in his wife's Sunday dress."
Yeah, but neith--
I mean we're both--
I mean,
you have to do it too.
It's a small price to pay
to see you humiliate yourself.
( whistles, jeers and laughter)
Hmm, my best dress.
Why do I get the feeling
that someday
I'll be describing this
to a psychiatrist?
Listen to them laughing.
This is so humiliating.
I'm never gonna
live this down.
Damn Flanders.
You know, Simpson,
I feel kind of silly,
but what the hay, you know?
Kinda reminds me of my
good ol' fraternity days.
D'oh! Oh, my God!
He's enjoying it.
(horn honks)
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.