I don't care what Bart says,
there's nothing crazy about
taking your cat for a walk.
[speaking gibberish]
Huh?
[dog panting]
[goat bleating]
[gasps]
- [dog barking]
- [bird squawking]
Wow. What is this place?
This park is a paradise
for emotional support animals
and their caring human partners.
Oh, that's lovely.
Now get out!
Your mangy cat can't be
in here if she's un-vested.
Oh, but my kitty
is so empathetic.
She's the most caring,
lovable, gentle,
- sweet...
- [chicken squawks]
[gasps] My anxiety chicken!
- [Snowball II yowls]
- [chicken squawks]
Somebody do something!
I can't do things,
I'm an empath.
I'm conflict-averse.
Support me, Apples.
Oh, boy.
Well, it was peck-and-go
for a minute there,
but Gwyneth Poultry
is gonna be all right.
Here's your astronomical bill.
Oh, they'll be covering it.
$16,000?! For a chicken?
I just ate a whole bucket
of them for 20 bucks.
Prosthetic beak?
Cluck-lear implant?
Bawk therapy? We don't
have the money for this.
[squawks weakly]
[squawks sadly]
Hmm...
They say all it takes
to financially ruin a family
is one unexpected medical bill.
Who knew ours would be
for jacking up
some bougie-ass chicken?
[laughs]
I am so sorry. You can sell
my Malibu Stacy Dream House.
It's increased in value.
I just redid the kitchen.
Relax. We're not gonna
sell your toys.
The sax is where
the real money is.
Homer.
What? My upper-lower,
middle-lower,
lower-class income
isn't gonna get us out of this.
Hmm. In order to save
this family,
I'm gonna have to do something
I've never done before,
get a job.
Oh, you've had tons of jobs:
cop, realtor, gym owner,
erotic baker,
weed sommelier.
Those were for my own growth.
This time, it's not personal.
Ooh, this one sounds perfect.
They're hiring cooks.
Ooh, cooking.
That's one of the only things
I don't doubt myself at.
"Exciting work,
competitive salary,
team players wanted
at GimmeChow."
What's GimmeChow?
It's a new food delivery app.
The teachers have been using it
ever since
Lunch Lady Dora was on
Cafeteria Nightmares.
[groans] They're only hiring
for evening shifts.
Evenings? That's when you
and the food make dinner happen.
I don't know how
to make pork chops.
Where do you kill the pigs?
In the sink?
Come on, guys.
We can help Mom out
and cook dinner as a family.
Aw, geez, you know,
I probably would not...
Yeah, I'd love to, but that's...
Homie, we need this.
Honey, of course
we're all happy to help.
Look, I'm already cooking.
This is how nachos are born.
Mr. Largo? But you
already have a job.
I teach music
in a public school, Marge.
Do the math. I sure didn't.
Folks, I'm Finn Bon Idée.
I am CEO and head mind-blower
here at GimmeChow,
and I came up with a way
to disrupt restaurant delivery.
By getting rid
of the restaurants.
- [explosion]
- Introducing
the GimmeChow ghost kitchen.
20 new delivery-only
dining concepts,
operating out of
one central kitchen, ours.
Together, me and you,
and your shift manager...
[automated voice]
Jill Junderson.
...are gonna revolutionize
food delivery
and feed all
our friends here in...
[automated voice]
"Spring-feld."
That's the excitement
I like to...
Oh, we got a question.
Wait, so one kitchen is
pretending to be 20 restaurants
when it's actually
zero restaurants?
It sounds like
you're catfishing the public.
Think of it as
catfish po'boy-ing them,
which is a special
at Mama Juju's Bayou Bistro.
How much does this job pay?
- Minimum wage.
- [overlapping grumbling]
Plus overtime.
Sweet, juicy overtime.
That'll replace
the newspaper in your wallet.
And believe me,
this job's gonna be
"easy peasy
like grilled cheesy."
One Easy Peasy Grilled Cheesy.
That's you, Chef.
Chef? [chuckles] Wow.
No one's ever called me...
Make that 11 grilled cheeses.
Six sushi burritos.
21 loaded churros.
They're not stopping!
Cheeses. I need cheeses.
Cheesus, Allah, Buddha, Hashem.
We need 'em all, Chef.
Hot stuff coming through, Chef.
For the last time,
you're not my type, Chef.
- Corner.
- Behind.
- Under.
- Whoo. Over.
- Betwixt.
- Ceiling.
Baloney banh mi.
Veal lover's pizza.
And fire those
grilled cheeses, Chef.
Heard, Chef. Give me a sec.
I need mayo.
- Ah!
- Please don't press charges.
My parole officer's
trying to three-strike me
instead of breaking up
with me like a man.
It's fine. It's fine.
It's not deep.
Oh. Where the hell's the mayo?
Here's your mayo, Chef.
Ah. This is Wing Hut on Super
Bowl Sunday all over again.
Where the hell are my damn
grilled cheeses, Chef?
Ah. Spill. Sorry, Chef.
I'll get it.
[grunting]
[bleep]
Here's your pho, Chef.
Get your dumplings
off my burner.
[gasps]
Homer, it's afternoon.
Why didn't you wake me up?
I tried, but you hit me
with a spatula.
Oh, this is my only day
with all of you and I missed it.
How are things
at GimmeChow, Mom?
It's been two months of hell.
Last night, Kirk lost
the tip of his finger
in someone's disco fries.
Disco guys like disco fr...
Oh, God!
So, how's dinner
been going without me?
Great. Tonight,
we're all making lasagna.
You know, cooking as a family
has been kind of fun.
Right, kids?
Mm-hmm.
Oh... Knowing you all are making
home-cooked meals together
is the only thing
getting me through this.
Love you so much. Bye.
She's gone. It's GimmeChow time.
I'm getting pizza,
pierogis, and paella.
Fish-and-chips
and cake pops for me.
Guys, we've been ordering
delivery for two months.
I'm getting an ulcer
from all the lying.
Or all the chile rellenos.
We got to tell Mom.
Hey, hey, hey.
Bup-bup-bup-bup-bup.
Let's not do anything rash.
We'll totally cook
for ourselves, tomorrow.
But we still need to eat
tonight, right?
Indian food, maybe?
Well, I am a little hungry.
Tofu tikka masala.
Mmm. Tofu tikka masala.
Tofu tikka masala. Order up.
Hey, hey, good news, gang.
Don't stop working.
You guys have been
such rock stars,
management is gifting you all
smartwatches.
Apple Watches?
Ankle watches. Monitors, really.
They buzz and say stuff
to make sure
you're always hustling
and a-grinding.
[groans softly]
Gil, did you have a chance
to ask payroll
about our overtime?
You know, Marge, I did.
Funny story.
Turns out,
since you work past midnight,
those hours count as a new day,
so you won't be
getting overtime.
That story's not funny at all.
[ankle monitor voice]
Rest detected.
- Activating motivational zaps.
- [buzzes]
Ow! I'm moving, I'm moving.
We work hard for that money,
and you're stealing it.
Look, GimmeChow's
just a start-up,
so money's really tight.
You understand, right?
[groans]
GimmeChow? More like "holy cow"
'cause their stock
just went through the roof.
Ever since the pivot
to ghost kitchens,
- this app is on fire.
- [alarm ringing]
We've got GimmeChow CEO,
Finn Bon Idée,
who, as of today, is the world's
newest billionaire.
[coughs] Billionaire?
Finn, congrats.
What's your secret?
No secret, Cliff.
I just work a lot harder
than anybody else at GimmeChow.
[Marge grunts]
[crying]
Mom, is everything okay?
I'm fine, honey.
Just watching the man
who's been cheating me
out of my overtime pay.
It kind of shakes my faith
in billionaires.
Oh, this is all my fault.
I feel so guilty
you're having to work this hard.
It's okay, sweetie.
We're getting there, slowly.
[sighs] It just
never seems to go up.
[Finn]
Cliff, GimmeChow is a family,
united by one goal:
enriching our shareholders.
I mean that.
[gasps] United. That's it.
You could start a union.
A union? [groans]
That could be good,
but you know how I feel about
fusses, let alone making them.
[Finn]
Gotta run, Cliff.
I'm doing ayahuasca
with Jeff Bezos
in outer space.
Okay, let's bring this jerk
back down to Earth.
Union? I don't know, Marge.
The podcaster who tells me
how to be a free-thinker
says unions are for communists.
Unions are the reason
we have child labor laws
and pensions and the weekend.
He was union's idea?
Sure was.
What do you drivers think?
Marge, I hate-a the GimmeChow.
First, they drive-a me out
of the business,
and then they rip-a me off.
This is a-not okay.
But I can't afford
to make-a the waves.
Please just consider signing
these union cards.
And keep this quiet.
We don't want management
to hear about this yet.
Hey, you're in
for a treat, gang.
For no reason whatsoever,
management has asked me to play
this educational video for you.
So, eyes up, ingrates.
Hey, team,
if you're watching this,
your kitchen has been infested.
But not with mice or roaches,
which are fine,
but with talk of unionizing.
[dramatic music plays]
Unionizing? What's that?
- Sounds scary.
- It is, Chef.
Joining a union would add
another person to your kitchen:
- the Union Ogre.
- Oh!
I create an unnecessary barrier
between you and management.
And I take money
out of your pocket.
[chewing loudly]
Hey, I could have bought
a neck tattoo with that.
Let's kill this monster
before he kills us.
[stabbing sounds over video]
[scoffs]
They'd rather spend their money
on unsubtle cartoons
than paying us fairly?
At least make it live action.
We're grown-ups, people.
- [others] Yeah.
- Where's Betty Boop?
That does it. Marge,
here's my signed union card.
We're with you, honey.
[humming happily]
[Marge]
Homie. Homie, guess what.
We did it.
We started a union.
Oh, that's, uh, great, honey.
[chuckles]
That's great.
[belches]
Whoops. Sorry.
Too much Tuscan osso buco.
Which we made as a family,
of course.
You think management will
retaliate against me?
Oh, I wouldn't worry about it,
honey.
[yawns]
Corporations aren't vengeful,
just people.
Vengeful people.
[snoring]
[Gil]
Good news, Marge,
management's decided
to reimagine your role
in the company.
You're firing me
for starting a union?
I wish.
We can only fire you
for being bad at your job.
So you just got promoted
to delivery driver.
You got 60 minutes
to deliver 40 orders,
or you're out on your keister,
with cause.
[all gasp]
Can't forget about cause,
ah-cha.
[sighs heavily]
♪ ♪
On your mark, get set...
go!
[tires screeching]
♪ ♪
♪ My feet won't take me
that far ♪
♪ So I gotta ride in your car ♪
♪ My feet won't
take me that far ♪
Oh!
- ♪ I gotta ride in your car ♪
- [tires screeching]
♪ To seal the eyes... ♪
[grunting]
♪ To feel the eyes... ♪
Where in the hell
is my banana cream pie?
♪ I say ride the bull,
wild bull today-ay ♪
[Marge grunts]
♪ He-He,
oh, no, oh, no, oh, no ♪
♪ He-He ♪
♪ He-He, oh, no,
oh, no, oh, no, no... ♪
I'm gonna make it.
One last order,
but it's too big to throw.
[tires screech]
- Aah!
- [song ends]
Oh, no. No!
[buzzer blares]
[ankle monitor voice]
Delivery failed.
[door squeaks]
Food's... [shrieks] here!
Homer, you're user "Mm-Food"?
You've been placing giant orders
every night.
We thought it was a hobo camp
with a stolen credit card.
[gasps]
You haven't been cooking at all.
- Sushi time!
- [Bart and Lisa gasp]
Worst of all,
my family lied to me.
[Gil]
No, worst of all is
you're fired with cause!
[Gil laughing maniacally]
[grunts]
If you're hungry,
we've got dinner.
- [grunts]
- [whimpers]
And Mom's eating
all the empanadas
with the wrong sauces.
Not the verde, use the roja.
Roja!
She wouldn't starve her family
over one little act
of betrayal, would she?
Let's go for the pot stickers,
real casual.
- [growls loudly]
- [all cry out]
No wonder this jug
hasn't been going up.
You've been getting
delivery for weeks.
Honey, we tried cooking,
but do you have any idea
how hard it is
to make dinner
every single night?
[Marge growls]
My own family betrayed me.
You know what family
would never do that?
My union family.
And now, I can't even
be a part of that.
- [doorbell rings]
- Hmm?
[gasps]
What are you all doing here?
Aren't you supposed to be
at work?
We were so manchego cheesed
about not getting paid
our overtime that we decided
to go on strike.
And we can't strike
without our leader.
Oh.
And guess what, Tube Dress?
All the other delivery app
workers are striking with us.
Every food delivery app
in Springfield is shut down.
Yes!
[Homer]
No!
Stupid strike.
I didn't realize it,
but I've gotten addicted
to GimmeChow.
I haven't eaten
since this whole thing started.
Why don't you get something
from the cafeteria?
Food only tastes good when
someone brings it to me now.
[alarm blaring]
- [alarm stops]
- [Lenny] Whoa, geez.
- Easy there, Homer.
- You could've fried
every electronic device
in Springfield.
Mmm, fried electronic device.
Aw, that one
didn't even make sense.
I'm losing it. I need to eat.
I'd sign a deal
with the devil himself
- to get my GimmeChow back.
- [phone rings]
Hello?
Yes, this is union rabble-rouser
Marge Simpson's husband.
Tonight on "Dollars:
the GimmeChow Strike."
Sweet for labor,
or bat for business? You decide.
Zooming in from Springfield,
union capo,
Marge Simpson. Marge,
I'm gonna be as impartial
as possible here.
Why are you starving America
with your psychotic demands?
We're not starving anyone.
All we want is our fair share.
Is that too much to ask?
Yes. And here to tell us why
is GimmeChow's
new brand ambassador,
- Homer Simpson.
- What?
Hey, Cliff.
Big fan of your whole deal.
Homer, you're working for them?
I sure am.
I was honored when GimmeChow
offered to pay me
in GimmeChow gift cards
to talk to America
about... "how unions
get in the way of innovation."
You're in a union
at the nuclear plant.
And I haven't innovated
one thing over there.
Look, we're living
in the future.
This little device
can get me anything I want.
Songs, sneakers, anonymous
gay hook-ups, so I hear.
Why shouldn't it
also bring me food?
But at the cost of human misery?
Misery is how
all the best stuff is made.
Pyramids, railroads, the blues,
those great soccer stadiums
in Qatar,
all the things America loves.
Why do you hate America,
Marge? Ow!
- [grunting]
- Hey! Ow! Marge, stop.
I encourage everyone
who respects workers' rights
to join us on the picket line.
When we stand together, we win.
♪ ♪
Marge, your speech on TV worked.
Looks like the whole town's
with us.
[all]
Hey, hey, we get how you feel.
Oh, that's so nice.
[all] Now get in the
kitchen and cook our meals.
- What?
- Attention, union thugs.
The eaters of Springfield
have had enough.
You have awoken a lazy giant.
You're just corporate shills
standing in the way of justice.
Shut up, burger flippers.
Just for that, I'm gonna spit in
your face instead of your food.
[all yelling]
Good news, everyone.
I found a way to end the strike.
[cheering]
You're meeting our demands?
No. I'm firing everyone.
[others]
Aw...
Because GimmeChow Ghost Kitchens
are now fully robotic.
And food deliveries are back
with non-complaining drones.
[cheering]
- [drones whirring]
- Ah.
[sighs] I guess the greed
of the most selfish
will always squash any hope
of a decent life
- for the rest of us.
- Oh, my guy.
Great work, Homer.
Really, I could not
have busted up
this union without you.
And stabbing your wife
in the back? [chuckling] Nice.
Gee, when you say it like that,
it sounds like I stabbed
my wife in the back.
[drone whirring]
Oh... I thought that fried food
delivered by electronic devices
would've been
my dream come true.
[gasps] That's it.
Fried electronic devices,
now it makes sense.
[chuckles]
[alarm blares]
My work is done.
[cheering]
The malfunctioning drones
are dropping everything
from apple pies
to zucchini fries,
but nothing is tanking faster
than GimmeChow stock.
Props, where the hell's my tank?
I can't get disrupted.
I'm the disruptor.
I'm the crusher of unions.
I'm the... Oh! [screams]
That's what I get for using
non-union prop guys.
[Homer]
Marge!
Homer, only you could make
a mess this big.
I did it for you, honey.
All the food in the world
means nothing to me
if you're not there to keep me
from choking on it.
[both moaning]
[Wiseguy] With his
automated robots destroyed,
Finn Bonne Ideé was forced
to hire union workers
at a fair wage,
including overtime.
Homer used his
GimmeChow gift cards
to pay off the chicken's
medical expenses.
And Marge forgave Homer,
but then brought it up
every time they fought
for the rest of their marriage.
Captioning sponsored by
20th CENTURY FOX TELEVISION
and FOX BROADCASTING COMPANY
and TOYOTA.
Captioned by Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Shh!