♪ The Simpsons ♪
(chalk screeches)
(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(tires screeching)
(horn honks)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
(growling)
I am not cleaning that.
Ah, who am I kidding?
Now, Maggie...
when you grow up
you can suck your pacifier
all you want.
(humming)
(loud burp)
Extra mustard for Bart's
sliced diagonally,
not length-wise.
Light mayo for Lisa,
cut off the crust.
Double bologna for Homer--
(overlapping chatter)
Where's my lucky red cap--
Mom, I hate those
pimento things--
Marge,
I split my pants again.
Ooh! Can I have
two sandwiches today?
-Make them bologna--
-Mom, I can't eat those--
One at a time!
-Double bologna!
-No pimentos!
-Don't forget to make it--
-Mom, where's my--
That's enough!
There you go, Lisa--
no pimentos.
Bart, your hat's where you
left it-- behind the toilet.
Homer, I'll sew your pants,
but I'm out of bologna.
-Thanks, Mom.
D'oh!
-(cat yowling)
-Videos to return
grocery list,
flea dip for the cat
Homer's dry cleaning...
I think that's everything.
Marge, can you take
my ball to Nick's today?
A bottle cap got lodged
in the finger hole.
Homer, I'm running late
as it is.
Can't you just use one of
the balls at the alley?
(groaning)
Ohh, alley balls?
All right. Don't whine.
Just put it in my left hand.
Kids, hurry up or you're
going to miss your bus.
-No way.
-Never happen.
Well, I'll be damned.
(groaning)
Mom, bart's making faces at me.
It's a nervous twitch,
and I'm a little
sensitive about it
if you don't mind.
Mom, he's doing it again!
Bart, quit it. Quit it!
Hey, quit it,
quit it, quit it.
Mom!
(monster-like voice)
Get... out!
(car wheels squeal)
Fruit leather...
tree fresh
imitation orange drink...
Krusty brand
duck sausage pizza...
Sorry lady, you've got
the wrong Nick's.
You want Nick's
on the other side of town.
I don't know what
Nicky's telling you.
I haven't flushed a ball
in years.
(jackhammer pounding)
MAN: Oh, this miserable
stress headache.
Feels like there's
a rat in my brain!
DEEJAY 1: It's time for
another Bill and Marty
classic crank call.
DEEJAY 2: Hello, is this
Mr. Justin Sherman?
SHERMAN: Yes.
DEEJAY 2: Sir,
your wife is dead.
SHERMAN: Oh, God, no!
DEEJAY 2: (snickering)
That's right.
She just walked through
a plate glass window.
There's blood everywhere.
SHERMAN:
But I just talked to her.
(deejays laughing)
(screams)
(bus horn honking)
Bart's making faces.
Where's my
lucky red cap?
-Alley balls?
-Your wife is dead.
I haven't flushed a ball
in years.
(jackhammer pounding)
Noooo!
Look, lady, this
better be good.
(lion's roar)
This is Arnie Pie
with Arnie in the Sky.
We've got big problems
on the Springfield
Memorial Bridge, people.
Traffic going waaay back
in both directions.
And look out at the corner
of 14th and Elm
'cause I just
dropped my bagel.
She's locked in the car
and refuses to move.
Did you flash
your lights?
Yes.
Well, I'm fresh out
of ideas.
All right!
A chance to catch some rays.
(honking horn)
Come on! Come on!
I got a body in the trunk.
(honking horn)
Mr. Genie, stop fiddling
with the buttons.
Oh! Now you've gotten
chocolate all over everything!
This is Kent Brockman
reporting live from
Arnie Pie's traffic copter
but I can assure you, this is
no mere morning traffic report.
Hey!
Face the facts Arnie.
An overworked and
under-appreciated housewife
has snapped and parked
her car on the bridge,
refusing to budge.
This reporter is now
going to be lowered down
in the Channel 6 sky harness
for an exclusive interview.
Huh?
Ow! Hey!
Ow!
(Homer laughs)
Hey sweetheart,
what's the matter?
Not getting enough
of the good stuff at home?
D'oh!
(indistinct chatter)
Let me through.
I'm her husband.
That explains a lot.
(chuckling)
(sighing)
Try to talk her
out of there
but don't put your lips
on it or anything.
Hello.
Hello!
Is this thing on?
Hello?!
Homer, is that you?
What should I say?
Well how about,
"Yes, it's me"?
Yes, it's me.
Tell her you love her.
I love you very much.
CROWD: Awww.
And, uh...
later tonight, I think you
and I should, uh...
snuggle?
(laughing)
Ha, ha!
Uh, why don't you
just wrap it up?
Look, Marge, I can tell
something's bothering you
but if you come out
of that car
I promise to do
whatever it takes
to make it better.
Please, honey?
Okay.
Cuff her, boys!
Off the record, ma'am,
all the gals on the force
-knew just how you felt.
-That's nice.
Do you think you could
loosen my cuffs?
No.
Don't you worry,
Mr. Mayor.
This little bird'll be cracking rocks
by the end of the week.
Wiggum, you glorified
night watchman, let her go!
But she broke the law.
Thanks for the civics lesson.
Now listen to me.
If Marge Simpson goes to jail,
I can kiss the chick vote
good-bye
and if I go down,
you're gonna break my fall!
Word to the wise, Quimby.
Don't write checks
your butt can't cash.
Hear me loud and clear Wiggum,
you bite me, I'll bite back.
You talk the talk, Quimby,
but do you walk the walk?
I hereby declare today
to be Marge Simpson Day
in the city of Springfield.
(cheering)
They're like trained seals--
toss 'em a fish
and watch 'em slap
their fins together.
Well, all's well
that ends well.
Good night, Marge.
(snoring)
(groans)
MAN: Many years ago
the Spanish explorers
discovered a little
piece of heaven
nestled in the
Springfield mountains.
They called it Rancho Relaxo
and so do we.
Today, it's Springfield's
only two-star health spa.
Swim, play tennis,
or just sit
and stare at the walls.
At Rancho Relaxo,
you're the boss.
Remember, you can't spell
"Relaxo" without relax.
-Homer?
-(groans)
-Homer!
-What?
I need a vacation.
What?! But, Marge,
we just had a vacation.
Remember Mystic Caverns?
(chuckles)
I need to unwind.
I know you do, Marge,
but come on, you know what
our vacations are like--
those three monsters
in the back seat
"Are we there yet?
Are we there yet?"
And let's face it, I'm no
day at the beach either.
"Marge, can I have
another sandwich?
Marge, can I have
another sandwich?"
No, I mean
a vacation by myself.
What?!
You mean we're getting
a divorce?
Marge, I can change.
No, Homie, no.
I still love you.
A lot of couples
take separate vacations.
Well, okay...
but you have to swear
you're coming back.
I swear.
All right, then.
(snoring)
MARGE: Thanks again for taking
the children while I'm away.
-Don't worry yourself.
-Uh-huh.
We've got six months
of maternity leave
we're never
gonna use anyway.
Homer, can you bring
Maggie out?
Wish I'd thought
of that.
(grunting)
She's starting to give.
Homer! If Maggie
really doesn't want
to leave the house
maybe she should
just stay with you.
Are you sure
that's wise?
Uh-huh.
He'll probably trade her
for a beer
and a nudie magazine.
(chuckling)
For your information,
I can take care of my--
(screams)
See? Got her
on the first bounce.
MAN (on PA): All aboard for
Shelbyville, Badwater,
Kettlestone Testing Grounds,
and Rancho Relaxo.
Good-bye, Homie.
Good-bye? Where's
my clean underwear?
Check the dryer.
How often should I
change Maggie?
Whenever she needs it.
Marge, Marge, how do I
use the pressure cooker?
Don't!
♪♪ (relaxing)
MAN: This is Koma--
W-K-O-M-A.
Restful, easy listening.
Coming up next,
a super set of songs
about clouds.
(chomping)
(metallic clunking)
Hmm?
Hello, Maggie.
Sorry, honey.
Mommy went crazy
and went far, far away.
So it's going to be
just you and me for a while.
Just you and me.
Kids, you haven't touched
your tongue sandwiches.
Do you need
something to drink?
We've got Clamato, Mr. Pibb,
and soy milk.
That's all right.
(yawns)
I think I'll just hit the hay.
It's 12:30 in the afternoon.
I'm aware of the time.
Lisa, you'll sleep in my bed.
Bart, you'll be sleeping
with your Aunt Patty.
-In your bed?
-Uh-huh.
And I should warn you,
I'm told I snore.
(chuckling)
Ooh, Divorce Court is on
in 15 minutes!
I'm scared, Lisa.
You think you know fear?
Well,
I've seen them naked.
(screams)
Oh, hello,
and welcome to Rancho Relaxo.
I'm Troy McClure.
You might remember me
from such films as
"Today We Kill,
Tomorrow We Die,"
and "Gladys,
the Groovy Mule"
but today you'll see me
in my greatest role--
your video tour guide
to Rancho Relaxo.
Our tour starts
in your very own room
where Relaxo-Vision offers you
the latest Hollywood hits
and after midnight
the finest "R" rated movies
Europe has to offer.
Ooh-la-la!
Today's selections are:
(male voice inserted)
Chef Rodrigo,
what are you up to?
Taste for yourself, Troy.
Mm-mm-mmm!
That can't be good for me.
It tastes too good.
That's where you're wrong,
Troy.
This whole pot
is only 14 calories.
(moaning)
Oh, Gregory...
where have you been
all my life?
(laughs)
-Feeling tense?
-Uh-huh.
Then just push nine
on your phone,
then the pound sign,
then 4-8-3.
We'll do the rest.
(moans)
HOMER:
Come on, Maggie.
Nummy-nummy-num.
Mmm-mm!
Mmm. Strained peas.
(to tune of
"Rule Brittania")
♪ Shakespeare's
fried chicken ♪
♪ Come gorge
yourself today... ♪
(grunting)
♪ Nyah-nyah, nyah-nyah,
la, la, la... ♪
(growling)
(yelling)
D'oh! Let go!
Mmmmm...
Ohh... ahh...
Marge,
it's times like this
I'm glad I flunked out of
that Mexican med school.
Hi, Barney.
Thanks for keeping
me company.
No problem.
Well, well...
if it isn't little Bart.
Remember
your Uncle Barney?
Hey, Homer,
let me hold him.
All right,
but just be careful.
Whoa! Someone smells stinky.
(sniffs)
Oh, it's me.
Bart, you really
shouldn't be looking
through other people's things.
Find anything good?
I said it before,
and I'll say it again.
Ay, caramba!
Hey, Lis, bang, bang!
Aw, Bart...
that's a blackhead gun!
Eww!
Best McGyver ever.
Mm-hmm.
Richard Dean Anderson
will be in my dreams tonight.
(loud, obnoxious snoring)
(shuddering groans)
(sighs)
HOMER:
♪ Go to sleep ♪
♪ And good night ♪
♪ La-da-da-da, da-da-da ♪
♪ Dee-dee-dee ♪
♪ May your Christmas
days be nice ♪
Good night, my little pork chop.
(Barney snoring)
(belches)
Oh, Maggie?
Time for your 9:00 a.m. feeding.
Heh, heh, heh.
(screams)
Maggie?
Maggie?!
(snoring)
Oh... hoo...
(grunting)
Maggie!
Oh, man.
You want a bad night?
Try sleeping
on one of these.
Barney,
I've lost the baby.
It's the worst thing
I've ever done.
Don't worry.
You know what
I'm gonna do?
I'm gonna make you
an omelet.
Just help me look.
Are you sure?
I make them
with two kinds of cheese.
-C'mon!
-Whoa!
Hey, Homer, I think
I've got her.
(grunting)
Come on!
Barney, you're gonna
pull her arm off!
The sooner
I get her out,
the sooner
we can have omelets.
(grunts)
Hmm, so, what's
the verdict?
Oh, dear God.
I can't even put a bag
over my head.
Yes, you can.
Hello, I'd like the department
of missing babies.
MAN: Please hold.
♪ Baby, come back ♪
♪ Listen, baby ♪
♪ You can
blame it all on me ♪
♪ I was wrong ♪
♪ And I just can't live
without you ♪
(Marge reading)
Hmm, I guess
I've done everything.
By now you've seen what
Rancho Relaxo has to offer.
Uh-huh.
But remember, we can't tell
you how to have a good time.
-You have to tell us.
-Oh.
As I said to Delores Montenegro
in "Calling All Quakers"...
"Have it your way, baby."
♪♪ (corny theme)
Hello, room service?
This is Marge Simpson.
I'd like a hot fudge sundae
with whipped cream
and some
chocolate chip cheesecake
and a bottle of tequila.
Let's get out of here,
Thelma.
Okay, Louise.
(long, deep sigh)
What do you want?
I came to see the kids.
Wait here...
and don't steal
any light bulbs.
Hmm...
BOTH: Dad!
Hey, kids.
You haven't seen Maggie
around anyplace, have you?
BOTH: Mm-mm.
Oh... well, I got to go.
(door closes)
PATTY: Come on, kids.
It's time to rub
Aunt Patty's feet.
(shuddering groans)
(bad British accent)
Hello, Gov'nor.
Lube job while you wait?
Don't touch me.
(sobbing)
(phone rings)
-Yello.
-Hi, Homie.
I feel much better.
Listen, Marge, uh...
how would you feel
if I told you the dog ran away?
Homer, that's awful.
Oh. Well, I got
good news for you.
The dog didn't run away.
Well, good.
I'm coming home, honey.
You can pick me up at the
train station in an hour,
and bring the kids. Bye.
D'oh!
Please, don't jump.
I know you're going through
some tough times
but you have your whole life
ahead of you.
Well, Marge...
Maggie was very young.
It's not like we got
so attached to her.
No.
Marge, isn't life funny?
One day, they're babies,
the next thing you know,
they're off on their own.
(doorbell rings)
Are you the man
who reported the lost baby?
-Yes.
-Can you describe her?
Uh, she's small...
she's a girl...
-Bingo!
-Oh, Maggie!
Not so fast.
You're wanted on three counts
of criminal neglect.
You found my baby!
Oh, thank you,
thank you, thank you!
(embarrassed chuckling)
Schucks.
Just don't do it again,
you big lug.
(grunting)
You're not going anywhere.
Hi! Did you miss me?
(overlapping dialog)
HOMER: Never leave again!
Never leave again!
Never leave again.
I missed you too.
MARGE: And from now on,
I hope you'll help me out
a little more than
you used to.
You got it, sweetheart.
You have enough blanket, there?
Well, I could use a little more.
And sometimes,
I want a little time to myself
and I expect you to help--
BART: Mom...
I think I speak
for everyone
in this bed
when I say you have
nothing to worry about.
Now, let's just
try and get
a little shut-eye. Okay?
(all sighing)
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.