Ha, ha, I don't know, neighborinos.
I'm all for Halloween fun...
...but a séance sounds a little PG-13.
But this is your chance
to contact your late wife, Maude.
Well, I do miss the missus.
Maude Flanders,
we the living beseech you to appear.
BART [AS MAUDE]:
Ned...
...I'm back.
Give me a kiss.
[ALL SCREAMING]
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
Chill out, dudes. It's me, Bart Simpson.
[ALL SHOUTING]
What are you looking at?
[WAILING]
[ALL SCREAMING]
Maude. You still look as pretty
as the day I buried you.
[MEOWS]
Are you ready for tales that will
shatter your spine and boil your blood?
- Well, duh.
- Then choke on these!
[LAUGHING MANIACALLY]
Treehouse of Horror 13
[HOMER SCREAMING]
Now to spend some quality time
away from my family.
[SIGHS]
I've got a list of things for you to do.
- My favorite is number three.
- Oh, I'd love to.
But someone made me
too many pancakes...
...and now I have to sleep them off.
Oh, those were for
the Church breakfast.
Were they now?
[GRUNTS THEN GROANS]
Hammocks. Get your hammocks.
The hammock man.
I'm glad he's a little early today.
The price is $10.
But I must warn you,
this is no ordinary hammock.
Its webbing is a mesh of comfort
and evil.
You had me at "comfort."
Mm-hm. Hmm, Mr. Hammock,
say hello to Madam Ass. Unh!
[GRUNTING]
What the...? It made another me.
- How cool is that?
- Wa.
Hmm, no bellybutton.
Shuttle's in the hangar.
You wanna be my slave?
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
Outstanding.
Oh, uh... Mm-hm.
Speed it up, ugly.
[HOMER CLONE SCREAMS
THEN THUDS]
[HOMER GRUNTS]
Eh, he had a good run.
[GRUNTING]
I'm gonna need help with this. Hmm.
[LAUGHS]
[SLURPS]
Beer for me?
No, you've got chores to do.
Chores? Me need clone.
Clone? That's ridiculous.
Where am I supposed to find a...?
Wait a minute.
[GRUNTING]
Wow, four of me.
I think
this could be a magic hammock.
And it just might be the answer
to my problems.
Uh...
What do you think, Homer?
Does this make my hips look big?
[IN MONOTONE VOICE]
Outfit good, flatters butt.
Oh, aren't you a dear?
Then after World War II,
it got kind of quiet...
...till Superman challenged FDR
to a race around the world.
FDR beat him by a furlong.
Or so the comic books
would have you believe.
The truth lies somewhere in between...
[SNORING]
[HOMER & LISA GRUNT]
[GRUNTS]
Me good dad.
Hmm. Does Dad seem a little dumber
than usual?
Me not notice.
Homie,
you've been such a sweetheart today.
Let's go upstairs and...
[WHISPERS]
[CHUCKLES]
[GRUNTS]
- I'll take it from here, fake-o.
- Uh-uh.
- Uh-huh. Unh!
- Unh!
[IN UNISON]
Why you little... Aah!
Man, are we evenly matched.
Me concur.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[YELLS AND LAUGHS]
It would take three clones
to beat the original Homer.
ALL:
Hmm.
Huh, I mean four.
ALL: Oh.
- Suckers.
[CHATTERING]
MARGE:
Kids, your father made us breakfast.
BART & LISA:
Yay!
- Go, go, go.
- Okay.
Say, Homer, I was, uh...
I was wondering if I could borrow
that chainsaw you, uh, stole from me.
Yeah, but you have to leave
a credit card.
- No problem. Discover okay?
- Ned.
Okay, here's my Amex.
[GRUNTS]
Mm-hm.
Homie, I must say
you have the energy of 20 men lately.
Twenty-three.
Today, I'm gonna mow the lawn,
do my taxes, shoot hoops with Bart...
...and girl it up with Lisa.
Aw.
[YELPS THEN DOOR SLAMS]
[ALL GROANING]
Oh, I gotta get rid of these guys.
[TIRES SQUEAL]
Now, before I abandon you
in this cornfield...
...does anyone remember
the way home?
HOMER CLONE:
I do.
[THUDS]
Anybody else?
Come on.
Okay, everyone out.
[ALL GRUNTING]
Now to make sure this hammock
never troubles anyone again.
[GRUNTS]
[TIRES SQUEALING]
Ooh. Mm?
[GROANS]
[CHATTERING]
Let's all go out
for some frosty chocolate milk shakes.
[ALL GRUNTING]
Ah, look at that corn.
Old Gil's hard work is finally paying off.
Well, at least I got my health.
Aw.
HOMER CLONES:
Beer, beer, beer.
[CANS RIPPING OPEN
THEN GULPING]
[HOMER CLONES BABBLING]
[HOMER CLONES'
PANTS UNZIPPING]
[HOMER CLONES SIGHING]
Like comedy clubs in the late '80s,
these ravenous clones are everywhere.
They've destroyed every building
in town...
...except Moe's Tavern,
which is reporting record business.
[CHATTERING]
[GULPING]
Now, uh, who's gonna be
picking up the tab?
ALL:
Lenny.
Anything for Homers.
Dad, is there something
you'd like to tell us about this horde?
You'd think so, but no.
They look like you,
they were rude to Patty and Selma...
...and the horde has been described
as very gassy.
Yeah, it's a good group.
Currently the, uh, Vietcong...
I mean, the, uh, Homers
are occupying these areas.
By tomorrow...
[ALL GROANING]
Good God, we're doomed.
No!
We're out of doughnuts.
That's it.
I know exactly what we should do.
Thank God. And you said we shouldn't
let little girls in the war room.
Look, I was wrong, okay?
[ALL GASPING]
ALL:
Mm, doughnuts.
Want doughnut.
- Doughnut.
- Chocolate.
[ALL GRUNTING]
ALL:
D'oh! D'oh! D'oh!
HOMER CLONE:
Son of a...
D'oh!
Thank you, general. That's a big relief.
The horde is almost dead.
There's still some writhing
and twitching.
- But that should stop by morning.
- Good news.
Mm.
One handsome hubby is all I need.
[MARGE GASPS]
No bellybutton? You're a clone.
- Then the real homer...
- First over cliff.
[GASPS]
My Homie's dead?
How will I go on?
You like back rub?
Oh, well.
[CROSBY, STILLS AND NASH'S "LOVE
THE ONE YOU'RE WITH" PLAYING]
And if you can't be
With the one you love
Love the one you're with
[THUNDER CRASHING]
[SQUEAKS]
Goldie,
you were more than just a goldfish.
- You were a member of the family.
- Rest in peace, pal.
"William H. Bonney."
"Gunned down July 14, 1881.
Aged 21."
So young.
"I dream of a world without guns."
Don't we all, William?
[SINGSONG]
Lisa has a dead boyfriend.
He's not my dead boyfriend.
He is a dead boy
who happens to be my friend.
Mr. Bonney,
I'm gonna make your dream come true.
If not for guns, poor William Bonney
might've become a doctor or a senator.
Or a frustrated novelist.
Ha, ha, sure. The point is let's stop
the madness and ban guns now.
CROWD:
Yeah!
Yeehaw! The girl's right.
I'm sorry. I can't live without passion.
Well, well, not so tough
without your gun, are you, Snake?
[GROANS]
Ow. I guess you are.
That's what I like about this job,
you learn stuff.
Twenty-eight, 29. There's one missing.
Not Mr. Blastie.
It's okay, boy.
You'll be shooting angels in heaven.
[SOBBING]
Well, boys, now it's our turn.
Uh, this always made me
feel like a man, you know?
Now all I got is my enormous genitals.
Three cheers
for a gun-free Springfield!
- Hip, hip...
CROWD: Hooray!
BONNEY: Hooray!
[THUNDER CRASHING]
Springfield's weapons of death
have been converted...
...into weapons of climbing
and sliding.
[GIGGLING]
The bumps tickle my bottom.
I proudly declare our town
utterly defenseless.
If only poor William Bonney were here
to see his dream come true.
Oh, but I am.
William Bonney?
Better known as Billy the Kid.
Ha-ha-ha!
[ALL GASPING]
[GUNFIRE]
Looks like the only guns left
are in my cold dead hands.
Now, I'd like you to meet
the Hole in the Ground Gang.
Frank and Jesse James.
[ALL GASPING]
- The Sundance Kid.
ALL: Aah!
- What happened to Butch Cassidy?
- "What happened to Butch Cassidy?"
We're not joined at the hip.
And the most evil German of all time,
Kaiser Wilhelm.
CROWD:
Huh?
He ain't no cowboy.
Sure I am.
Yippy, wippy, wippy.
Okay, he's in.
Now, let's rob the bank,
give the money to the poor...
...then rob the poor
and shoot the money.
[CHEERING]
[SPEAKING IN GERMAN]
[SCREAMING AND GUNFIRE]
[YELLS THEN GRUNTS]
Play us some "pian-ee."
["FUR ELISE" PLAYING ON PIANO]
[GUNSHOT]
That's piano! I said, "pian-ee."
[SALOON MUSIC PLAYING ON PIANO]
You, play the "cell-ee."
You, sing a song about cattle rustling.
And you,
sing one about, uh, robbing banks.
[SINGING] Calf's in the field
So you sneak up slow
Grab him by the tail
And go, man, go
[SINGING] Break into the bank
And snatch that dough
BOTH:
Please don't hurt our family
[CHEERING]
Marge, let me do a solo.
This could be my big break.
I very much doubt that, Homer.
These are horrible ghouls
from the past.
Hey, so are the Grammy judges.
Ha-ha-ha, ugh!
Pardon the grabbing...
...but I've perfected a device
that could save us all.
A time machine.
We can go back to the past
and save our guns.
Give me.
Uh, for flailing out loud,
I hope he doesn't do anything...
...to ruin the space-time continuum.
That's all...
Oh, dear.
Poor William Bonney might have
become a doctor or a senator.
[ALL GASPING]
Hear me, people of the past.
Hey, everyone, that's us.
I come to deliver
a terrifying message of hope.
Grab your guns and follow me.
- Yeah!
- All right!
[CHATTERING]
Dad, what are you doing?
Ooh, how to explain this to a child?
Hmm.
Future Daddy needs
to double kill these corpses...
...so they won't come back as zombies
and... Get him!
[GRUNTING]
[SCREAMING]
[GRUNTS THEN YELPS]
[CROWD CHEERING]
Another tragedy prevented
by gun violence.
I guess guns really are the answer.
Hear me, people of Springfield.
I come from
yet another distant future...
...where gun violence has destroyed
the very Earth itself.
What is this, open mike night?
Hah! Now to get me
some caveman hookers.
Tell me again why we're spending
our vacation on the Island of Lost Souls.
Hey, what could be more fun than
an island shaped like a big smiley face?
Welcome to my island.
Dr. Hibbert?
But we heard you'd gone mad.
Yes, completely mad.
About providing
topnotch vacation values. Ha-ha-ha.
Willie, help them with their bags.
[GROANS]
[GROWLS THEN SIMPSONS GASP]
Now, he may try to slobber
on your crotch.
Ha, ha. I've been around Scotsmen.
[SCREAMS THEN WHIMPERS]
Homer, someone's in trouble.
Hey, I'm on vacation.
Dr. Hibbert, this is a topnotch resort.
Can you recommend some activities?
Well, one activity you might enjoy
is not asking questions.
[LAUGHS]
But man's inquisitive nature
is what separates us from the animals.
Why must we be separated? Think what
Shakespeare might've accomplished...
...if he'd had the eyes of an eagle
or could spray stink on his critics.
Now, who'd like some turkey?
It's a lovely nerd...
[LAUGHS]
I mean "bird."
[SCREAMS]
No! Wait a minute now.
Guess what, I'm dying, ha, ha...
...with the basting
and the butterballing...
...and the chestnut stuffing
in my pupik.
Gobble, gobble, gobble. Death.
Homie, something very creepy
is going on here.
They're gonna try
to sell us timeshares?
I think I'm going to do
a little sleuthing.
Bring back some ice.
[PEOPLE SHOUTING NEARBY]
"House of pain."
This must be where you pay the bill.
[LAUGHS]
Why am I always so funny
when no one's around?
[GRUNTS]
Oh, I'm around.
[MARGE SHOUTS THEN GROWLS]
[PURRS]
Unh. What's up, honey?
Want a little loving?
[PURRS]
Woo-hoo, quite a tiger there. Easy, easy.
Ha, ha, I guess it has been a while.
Okay, that hurts more than it tickles.
[MARGE PURRING]
Quiet, youse.
[THUDS THEN YELPS]
Isn't vacation sex always the best?
[GROWLS]
Marge, you were like a wild beast.
So voracious and prowly.
And I've never seen you
use your tail like that.
[BIRD CHIRPS]
[GROWLS]
What the...? Oh, my God.
She's become a monster.
Which I have to admit,
I sort of suspected during the sex.
[GROANS]
Gotta find a way
to change Marge back.
And replace the M&M'S I took
from the minibar.
NED:
Hey, Homer.
Flanders.
Oh, a perfect vacation ruined.
Hate to be a needy Neddy,
but could you do me a favor?
- Hmm.
- Milk me.
Uh, I really don't wanna do that, Ned.
Oh, come on, Homer. All I'm asking
is for you to yank my teats...
...and harvest my milk.
- Ugh, fine.
Ooh, that's nice. You're actually quite
gentle when you wanna be.
You know, you're not helping.
[SINGING]
In the jungle, the creepy jungle
Homer rides a freak
Shh. Hey.
[CHATTERING]
Huh! What's that?
[GRUNTS]
[SQUEAKS]
I'm a dog.
[BLOWS HORN]
Hear me, accursed brethren.
I understand that some of you
are still wearing tattered pants.
Please, throw them on the bonfire
and embrace your animal essence.
Okay, but I'm keeping the tattered vest.
I still have my dignity.
Hey, slops.
Ooh, a toenail. Ha, ha.
I can't believe it. Hibbert's turned
you all into human guinea pigs.
We prefer "Italian-American pigs."
Hey, Dad, check it out.
"Eat my shorts"? Why, you little...
Maggie.
Lisa. Ugh!
We were just playing.
What game?
Let's Eat Maggie.
[GRUNTS]
Manimals, inverta-broads.
You must fight back
against the one who did this to you.
Yar, the half-man, half-gorilla
speaks the truth.
[ALL GRUNT]
[LAUGHING]
Now, I admit I made a few mistakes,
but all in the name of progress.
Hear, hear.
- It's Mr. Burns.
- With a fox attitude.
Think about it, my hideous children.
Aren't you better off now
than you were as humans?
Me gusto pollen.
Disco Shrew can still boogaloo.
[DISCO MUSIC PLAYING]
[ALL GROAN]
You guys are nuts.
All you can do is eat and sleep...
...and mate,
and roll around in your own filth...
...and mate and eat...
Where do I sign up?
[BIRD CHIRPS]
So how do you like being a walrus,
Dad?
It's great. I haven't been this skinny
since high school.
Homie, someone owes me
a back scratch.
[GROANS]
Look at that island
shaped like our number four.
Makes you think.
[WOMAN SCREAMING]
[English - US -SDH]