♪
Ah, what a long day.
What should we read tonight?
Good Night,
Escaped Gorilla,
The Pookadook,
What Do You People
Do All Day?
The Pookadook,
S'up, Moon?
The Pookadook?
Wait, how many Pookadooks
do we have?
Oh, I guess just one.
When did we get this book?
Whoop...
♪
Should we read this tonight?
"There's a nasty little monster
called the Pookadook.
"Only special people see it.
"People like you.
"Pookadook, Pookadook
feeds on your rage.
What happens next?
Just turn the page."
Hmm. I don't know, maybe
we shouldn't read this book.
Okay.
"How does he get in,
this mean Pookadook?
Why, you let him in
by reading this book."
(gasps)
Oh...
It's okay, sweetie.
It's okay.
Shush, shush, shush,
shush, shush.
Sleepy cheek, sleepy cheek.
Oh, mmm.
Oh, baby cheek.
I love baby cheek.
Oh.
(sighs)
(Homer snoring)
-(Maggie cries out
over baby monitor)
- Maggie!
(screaming, crying)
Huh? I thought I put that
on the shelf.
(grunting) Bad book.
Oh, Maggie,
you aren't still scared of
that silly Pookadook, are you?
- Oh.
-(pounding on door)
Mm. Don't shoot anything.
Those are new crayons.
Hmm. Hmm.
(gasps)
"When Pookie gets a hold of you,
"you'll change for the worse,
"eliminate those nuisances...
(gasps)
...the littlest one first."
(groans)
"Now burn it all up
on Dad's barbecue.
That's exactly what Pookadook
hoped you would do"?
(gasps) Oh, no.
(coughs, gasps)
(chuckles evilly)
Oh.
Time to put the baby down.
(chuckling)
-(door opens)
- Bart and I are
building a dojo.
Ooh, we could use that
to chop up the lawn furniture.
BART:
I want to chop!
The family's getting in the way
of Maggie-Mommy time.
I'll make them sleep
with the fishes.
Sleep overnight
at the aquarium.
Thanks for signing us up, Marge.
LISA:
Too bad Maggie's not
old enough to go.
Maggie and I have
our own fun planned.
(Maggie whimpering)
Aw, you gonna miss Daddy?
(crying)
Cranky pants!
Give her to me.
(Homer humming cheerily)
Now it's just you and me.
(sinister laughter)
Huh?
Hmm. Oh, her thinks her
can get away.
Her is mistaken.
(electricity snaps off)
(lock rattling)
Oh, peekaboo,
I hear you.
(knocking on door)
Maggie, let Mommy in.
I know you're in there.
Young lady, open the door
this instant.
Let me in,
you little poop machine.
(deep, sinister voice):
Let me in!
(panting)
Is that all you got?
Missed me.
- Whoa.
-(thuds)
(Marge panting)
(deep grunting)
(evil laughter)
(sinister voice):
Not gonna work.
Look what else
my loving family got me
for my birthday.
A vacuum that cleans
the outside.
I guess cleaning the inside
wasn't enough.
No fun for Mom.
(sawing sounds)
(grunts)
Baby's gonna fall.
Got you!
(gasps)
(voice lightens):
Baby cheek.
Oh. (coughs)
(coughing)
(normal voice):
Oh, Maggie, I'm so sorry
I got possessed
and almost chopped you up
into little pieces.
Oh, but I'm here now.
Mommy's here.
Stay back,
you overdressed hat demon.
I know you feed on
my repressed resentment
towards my family,
but I can swallow feelings
like a python eating
a baby goat.
(vacuum whirring)
Okay, it was actually
a good present.
HOMER:
Marge, we're home.
The kids got sick
in the touch pool.
I put the barf clothes
on your purse.
-(groans)
-(Shop-Vac growls)
Ah. Oh.
(Maggie laughs)
-(Marge sighs happily)
-(growling)
LISA:
Disgusting.
The human race is
20 cow farts away
from total extinction.
- And we deserve it.
-(gasps)
Huh?
"Any person whose name is
written in this Death Tome
will meet their death
and be dead."
What?
"You must specify how
the victim will die,
and you may not kill
the same way twice."
This is obviously just
a stupid prank.
But I never throw away a book.
-(gasps)
- REPORTER (on TV):
Internet sensation Tofu,
the world's most
clicked-on cat...
BOTH:
Aw.
...is being held hostage
by a gunman.
BOTH:
Aah!
Wait, maybe I could
stop this guy.
No, that's never gonna work.
Well, even if it doesn't,
it'll feel good
to do some journaling.
Ha-ha, I'm totally
gonna get away with murd...
Oh! Oh, my heart!
Heart attack! And...
- ...death.
-(yowls)
- What?
- LISA: What?
Oh, my God,
I killed a man.
A bad man.
Which actually makes me...
(gasps)
...a hero.
DEVILISH VOICE:
It's rare to find
- bloodthirsty vegetarians.
-(gasps)
-(thunder crashes)
-(cries out)
I am a Shinigami.
A god of death.
In my realm, I am called
Steve Johnson.
(evil laughter)
Wait, your name is Steve?
Well, when I was born
eons ago,
Steve was a very exotic name.
I mean, there were, like,
three Necroblivias
in my nursery cave alone.
This must be your Death Tome.
I'm sorry, I-I kind of
killed somebody with it.
(nervous chuckle)
Oh, but now that
you've used it, it's yours.
I think you'll find that murder
is almost as addictive
as plastic surgery.
- Oh. Have you had...
- I haven't.
But I-I don't think there's
anything wrong with it.
- Mm.
-(nervous chuckle)
Don't worry, no one else
can see or hear me.
I was karaoke-ing
with my employer,
as is the salaryman's
obligation.
You're stinking drunk.
I'm so proud.
It's the part of my job
that I... do best.
What an ugly house.
Thank goodness this eyesore
will soon be submerged,
after my side corporation
Globo-Warm
melts the polar icecap.
But millions of people
will drown.
True, but I'll be able
to dock my yacht
outside my kitchen.
Hmph.
I have to kill Mr. Burns.
Wow, I thought
you'd struggle with that,
but you're like,
"Boom. Dead time!"
Well, I'm gonna give him
a very dignified
and humane murder.
The most peaceful way to go.
(snorts)
-(pained cry)
-(flesh sizzles on hibachi)
- Ooh, how is he still asleep?
-(Burns cries out)
Oops. (giggles)
Okay, that was much
crueler than planned,
but I saved the world.
Did you? Globo-Warm has
many dedicated employees
willing to carry out
Burns' dream
of drowning the Earth.
LISA:
(sighs) Fine.
Wow, that is a big board.
I gotta come up with
a lot of ways to die.
Well, just have to be creative.
(chorale chanting
in foreign tongue)
(screams)
(screaming, grunts)
♪
(yelps)
Really? A toilet gator?
I was running out of ideas.
(yawns)
I'm going to bed now.
Oh, what about
the second page?
Wha...?!
♪
(grunting)
(yells)
Oh, no. Ah!
(yawns)
And the last guy, oh,
I don't know.
Liquefied in a giant blender.
Already did that.
That was puréed.
It's a totally different
setting. (groans)
Hmm.
Police have determined
that the unexplained deaths
of Globo-Warm executives
were murders
committed by one bloodthirsty
super-killer.
What?
Um, how could they know that?
They know that thanks to
an anonymous detective
known only as L.
I'm not worried.
They'll never in a million years
figure out how I...
The super-killer murders
by writing names
on some kind of
supernatural book,
or perhaps tome.
What the wh... How?
Well, I know I'll sleep easier
once they catch
this super-killer.
Wait, I know. I'll kill L.
Oh, but I thought
you only killed
to save the planet.
Killing L will only
save yourself from jail.
I don't have time to explain why
what I do is good and pure.
L, punched to death
by kangaroo.
(scoffs)
It's not gonna work
unless you have his whole name.
(groans)
How can I find out L's name?
Wait a minute,
I recognize that L.
I know who you are.
It's not L, it's EL,
as in El Barto.
BART:
Took you long enough.
How did you figure out
how I killed all those people?
I found out about
your stupid book
by reading an even stupider
book; your diary.
Your little murder spree
was a welcome break from,
"Janey is so mean to me."
I'm not a murderer.
I'm justice
It was a justice spree.
I'm saving the world.
And I can't let you
stop me. I can't.
Lisa, you're actually
gonna kill me?
(gasps)
Oh, my God.
I almost killed
my own brother.
The Death Tome corrupted me.
The stain on my soul
will never be...
Oh, so now you're trying
to bore me to death?
(Lisa grunts)
- Crushed by...
- No. I'm sorry.
- ...space junk.
-(Shinigami laughing)
- Don't!
(demonic laughter)
(pained groan)
No!
At last, I'm free.
- I... (crying out)
-(bones cracking)
Damn it,
I'm a freaking Shinigami.
(Lisa grunts)
Well, you are a god of death.
You could kill Janey.
Would that make you
feel better?
LISA:
No.
Maybe.
This is the snack holder,
where I can put my beverage,
or, if you will, cupcake.
Wow, Dad, you really know
your monorails.
(possums chittering)
(hissing)
Homer, there's a family
of possums in here.
- I call the big one Bitey.
- Ha!
- Yes!
(chuckles)
We all call him Bitey.
Dude, dude, what if
Homer was drunk during Monorail?
Yeah. Come here, dude.
- Mm, beer.
-(gagging)
Whoo-hoo! Boring.
Stupid sexy Flanders.
Why you little...
(grunting)
ANNOUNCER:
"Marge vs. the Monorail"
is experiencing
technical difficulties.
But there are plenty
of other classic
Simpsonsworld moments
playing out right now.
- Oh, let's get high
and shoot Mr. Burns.
-(laughs) Yeah!
- I am so smart...
- This Homer unit is stuck
in a catchphrase loop.
He won't go into sleep mode.
Where's my burrito?!
- Where's my burrito?!
- Ugh, I'll do a hard reset.
I'm king of the wor...
(powers down)
Damn cloud!
(elephant trumpets)
So how was your date
with the guy in Props?
Oh, he's so arrogant.
Just 'cause he's in charge
of Sideshow Bob's rakes.
Okay, we get it.
There's a lot of rakes.
(gasps)
What the frosty chocolate
milkshakes is this place?
Ooh, slideys.
(gasps)
Wh-Where am I?
What am I?
Aah! Where's my junk?
Whoa, whoa, he's awake.
(stammers)
Where's Marge?
Where's my family?
Uh, calm down, Mr. Simpson.
I know it feels like
you're a man,
but you are actually something
much, much more expensive:
intellectual property.
Look, we've got a bus full
of Australian superfans coming.
Let's just wipe his brain, okay?
Put that thing down, or else!
Look, Monorail Homer,
your programming
won't allow you to intentionally
hurt a human, okay?
So just be a good robot
and let us saw your skull open.
Oh. Okay. Here you go.
Ow! Ah, my bad!
Ooh, sorry, sorry.
Ugh.
(Homer gasps)
-(mechanical whir)
- Lisa,
we're not people, we're I. P.
(laughs) I pee.
You got to help me find
a way out of here.
I'd like to help, Dad,
but my diorama
on The Tell-Tale Heart
is due tomorrow.
(grunts) How can I
make you understand?
Oh, yeah, the thingy.
Oh, God, oh, God, oh, God.
We're replicants
in a ridiculous theme park
for an ancient TV show
that stopped being good
after season 45.
(gasps) Do I even exist?
What is consciousness?
Okay, I can handle
being a machine.
I don't love it, but I can deal.
Look, honey,
it's never easy to find out
you're not actually alive,
but that's just part of life.
I know the love we feel is real.
So, we've got to wake up
the rest of the family
and get the hell out of here.
Now, help me pick out
the hottest Marge.
We can get out
through the main entrance,
but we'll have to make it
across the park
without being detected.
Should we wake up
a Grampa robot?
No time.
(all sputtering)
Okay, act like robots.
Catchphrases, everyone.
- Mmm... beer.
- Don't have a cow, man.
Um... dinner's ready?
Oi, Homer!
There's your hedge, mate.
Get your fat bum in that hedge.
SUPERFANS:
Meme! Meme!
Meme!
(whimpers)
(Bart grunts)
I'm so sick
of that stupid hedge.
BOTH:
Oi! Oi! Oi! Oi! Oi! Oi! Oi!
Oi...!
-(alarm blares)
- SECURITY: Danger.
- I'm gonna make it.
I'm gonna make it.
- Human safety breach.
- Aah!
- Proceed to exits.
Security droids deployed.
We got to go. They're onto us.
(all gasp)
(chuckles) My cat's breath
smells like cat food.
That's nice, Ralph,
but we're sort of in a hurry.
(all gasp)
(all gasp, groan)
RALPHS:
I choo-choo-choose you...
to die.
If we want to escape with
our delusions of being alive,
we have to fight.
(echoing): Testing.
Eat T-shirts,
you lovable kill-bots.
(screams)
(gasps) There's too many.
There aren't enough T-shirts
in the world to save us.
Get in.
RALPHS:
Whee! Whee! Whee!
Dying tickles.
♪ Canyonero ♪
LISA:
Look out! Those people are real!
So are we.
(screaming, shouting)
(grunts)
♪ Canyonero ♪
♪ Hyah, Canyonero! ♪
Well, we've driven for hours,
and no one followed us.
I think we're free.
Well, what do we do now?
Play out the scariest
scenario of all,
real life.
WAITRESS:
What can I get you, hon?
Whoa! Turn off the headlights.
You got big eyes.
Oh, the cheese got left out,
so it's a little sweaty,
but you'd never know.
Forget I said anything.
Take your time, take your time.
♪ Sweaty cheese, sweaty cheese ♪
♪ At the end of the day ♪
♪ You're still cheese ♪
♪ To me. ♪
All right.
♪
Captioning sponsored by
20th CENTURY FOX TELEVISION
and FOX BROADCASTING COMPANY
and TOYOTA.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org
KODOS: Another "Treehouse
of Horror" in the books.
Get it?
KANG:
I got what little there was.
(Kang and Kodos shudder)
KODOS:
What the hell? It's us.
That's too freaky.
-(Kang and Kodos screaming)
-(tentacle steps running away)
(spooky theme music playing)
♪
-(screaming)
-(organ music playing)