(SlNGlNG) The Simpsons
(TlRES SCREECHlNG)
D'oh !
(SCREAMlNG)
(TlRES SCREECHlNG)
(DlNGS)
l have to research a paper.
Where did all the books go?
Books? Books are
for squares.
We're now a multimedia
learning center
for children of all ages. . .
But mostly bums.
(SNORlNG)
BART: Ay, caramba!
Huh? What?
(LlSA READlNG)
There are hardly
any books at all.
No books?
But Krabappel wants
a paper on Henry Vlll.
And l have to score
at least a pumpkin sticker
or better on it.
Aw. There, there.
l can help you kids.
(ALL GASPlNG)
l know a little
something about history.
Gather round.
Henry Vlll had
everything he could want,
except a son to follow
in his footsteps.
(FANFARE PLAYlNG)
(SlNGlNG)
I'm Henry the Eighth, I am
Henry the Eighth,
l am, l am
I've been eating
since 6:00 a.m.
For dessert
I'II have dinner again
My name's
synonymous with gIuttony
I'II aIways eat
a turkey or a ham
Stop singing that song !
We all know who you are!
Her Majesty,
Margarine of Aragon !
What are you
doing out of bed?
l just planted my seed
in your womanly dirt.
Your Majesty,
l know you want a son.
But must we discuss my womb
in front of the entire court?
(ALL LAUGHlNG)
As royal physician,
it is my learned opinion
that her womb is
filled with sea serpents.
(GROANS)
(MUTTERlNG)
Must sire a dude.
Father dearest,
l am the son you crave.
l'm smart, athletic
and ever so masculine.
Could a girl belch
like this? (BELCHES)
Oh !
My beautiful boy!
Why can't l have you?
l don't know.
Too much jerkin'
your merkin?
Why you little. . .
Get out of my dreams
and into my wife!
l could've married
the King of France.
He wasn't so preoccupied
with procreation.
Ting-a-ling-a-ling.
Know what l mean?
Oh, look at me.
l eat and eat and eat,
and l never get any thinner.
Well, there's more
of you to worship, O Sire.
Who would dare
to flatter a king?
Anne Boleyn,
loyal subject, big fan.
Modern Wench
magazine dubbed me
"Anne of
the child-bearing hips."
Yes. Wide hips indeed.
My son could cartwheel out.
Yoink!
Hey! Where are
you taking me?
Marriage counseling.
(MOANS)
Mmm.
We came here to talk
about our problems.
Fine! l want to
marry Anne Boleyn.
But l can't chop
my wife's head off
because her father
is the King of Spain !
Your Majesty,
your feelings are valid,
but l'm afraid marriage
takes a lot of hard work.
And who needs that?
l say trade in that
lemon and get busy!
Woo-hoo!
Divorce? Sire,
there's no such thing in the
Cath-diddly-atholic Church.
But it's the only
church we've got,
so what are you gonna do?
l'll start my own church.
What?
Yes, my own church.
Where divorce will be
so easy,
more than half of marriages
will end in it.
Your Majesty,
l work for the Pope,
and l think
a celibate ltalian weirdo
knows a lot more
about marriage than you.
Mmm, l understand.
And because you
stuck to your principles,
l'm going to canonize you.
l can see my house!
Sweetie, sometimes
a daddy and a mommy
decide to live apart.
lt's not your fault.
lt's just that
you came out the wrong sex
and ruined everything.
So grow a penis or get lost.
(STRAlNlNG)
l can't.
Buh-bye.
Well, why can't
your heir be female?
Or why can't
we elect our leaders?
l wonder if l could
canonize a child?
Leaving !
Hey, l invented divorce!
How did you get
half of everything?
You should've
invented the pre-nup.
And now half of
your kingdom, please.
l get lreland?
(LAUGHS)
And by the power vested in me
by you just now,
l pronounce you
king and trophy queen.
ln the name
of the Henry, the Hank,
and the holy Harry. . .
Amen. Henry.
Okay. Now let's put
a son in the oven.
Oh, Henry!
Henry, sorry l bore you
a daughter.
(CHUCKLES) Stop.
Anne, l love her
as much as l love you.
(DRUM ROLL)
Your head lives for
five seconds afterwards
so l left a magazine
in the basket.
Oh, my horoscope!
"Today will bring
welcome new changes
into your life." Wrong !
Sir Scratchy,
l accuse you of conducting
a Catholic mass!
Lord ltchy,
l accuse you of not signing
the Act of Succession.
(GRUNTlNG)
(MOANS)
lf only l had a son
to enjoy this with.
Hey, baby.
How would you like
to be queen for a day?
(LAUGHS) lt's funny,
'cause you're king.
Do you, Jane Seymour,
take this king to be
your lawfully wedded husband
till your first
little spat?
l do! l double do!
Henry is the ginchiest!
The Lord is my. . .
l told you l was a dude!
You didn't dump me.
l dumped you. . .
(SCOFFS) Why on earth
did l marry you?
My track record !
l've had 1 0 sons.
Now take a ride
on the kingmaker!
(SHUDDERS)
Swing and a miss!
Come on ! l'm 95.
You could use
a butter knife,
for God's sake.
Don't just stand there.
Bury me.
Sire, l know
what you usually do
to the bearer of bad news,
but, well,
we're running out of pikes
to stick your
wives' heads onto.
l'll show you
running out of pikes!
Hey, what do you know?
You were right.
That means a lot.
My whole life,
l was looking
for that one woman
whose execution
could bring me happiness.
Now l realize l was
just beheading myself
for divorcing you.
And locking me
in a dungeon.
(LAUGHS)
(COUGHS)
Listen to us.
We still finish
each other's sentences.
Margarine, won't you
take back an old
head-chopping fool?
Of course, Your Majesty.
Let me just fluff
your pillow for you.
(GASPlNG)
See ya in hell, fat man !
Finally,
Henry's daughter Elizabeth
became queen.
England's power
was never greater.
And British actresses
always had a role to play
when they got
to a certain age.
That was awesome, Mrs. S.
Check plus-plus, here l come!
(GlGGLlNG EXClTEDLY)
(GRUNTS)
Wow. The library
really is a great resource!
And l just came
in here to trip nerds
for nothin'. Ha-ha!
Mom, l can't find
anything on Sacagawea.
Just a couple of
books on Ron Santo.
No problem.
ln elementary school,
we girls learned
about Sacagawea
while the boys
were learning math.
Okay.
All right! Toilet paper!
ln 1 804, President Jefferson
sent Lewis and Clark
and some
embedded journaIists to
find the Northwest Passage.
They paddIed up
the Mississippi
from St. Louis.
When winter came,
Lewis and Clark
tried to set up camp,
but encountered
much hardship.
(STRAlNlNG)
Come spring, they sought help
from Native Americans.
Long have we awaited
the coming of
the white man. . .
And Carl.
Thanks. And welcome to
the United States of America.
Have a flag.
And while you're at it,
cover your nakedness
and worship our Lord.
Yeah, yeah.
l'll get right on it.
Now, in order
to aid your journey
across the land
l offer you the guidance
of my daughter, Sacagawea.
ln our language,
her name means
"little know-it-all
"who won't shut
her maize hole."
l will be happy to
help the Americans.
Of course, l will be sad
to leave my husband,
the French fur trader,
Charbonneau.
l will come with you.
Because by myself,
the darkness,
she scares me.
l don't know why
l ever sold you to him.
Okay, those berries
are poison.
Those leaves are poison oak.
And your belt is a snake,
also poisonous.
l'll tell you
what's poisonous,
your attitude.
You know these. . .
(GROANlNG) l'm dying !
But at least people
will always remember
the expedition
of Lewis and Clark
and Tweedleburger. . .
Also, if you're confronted
by a mountain lion,
try to make yourself look
as big as possible.
And when you get a chance,
bury your friend.
Hey, we're still mourning.
Let's get a drink.
All right, customers!
And they said
you couldn't open
a bar in Kansas.
Hey. . . Hey!
Well, nothing can
crush the frontier spirit.
That'll do it. (GROANS)
LEWlS:
At last the Pacific Ocean.
SACAGAWEA:
That's a mud puddle.
Some of us find solutions
instead of just
pointing out problems.
How did you two ever
get to be explorers?
We got the job
because we own a compass.
Turns out the needle
was just painted on.
lt's been two years,
so our brave explorers
should be right about here.
You morons!
(ALL GASP)
(GUNS COCKlNG)
(BOWS COCKlNG)
Wait! That's my brother!
Don't kill them !
They're my friends!
Oh, come on.
Can't we at least
have one pity scalp?
Ah ! My brother-in-law.
l haven't seen you
since l killed
all your buffalo.
Water under
the bridge, eh? Eh?
Don't forget the eyebrows.
CLARK:
Wow, the Columbia River!
Now we just ride this baby
down to the Pacific
and get us some
sweet mermaid sex.
For the last time,
those are salmon !
How do you like that?
Sacagawea has an opinion.
Big surprise.
You know,
you could be a little more
grateful to us
for civilizing you.
(BLOWS NOSE)
l am the only
reason you guys made it
this far alive!
From now on,
you're on your own !
Stupid things
with their compasses
painted on.
She'll be back.
She forgot her husband.
lngrates,
after all l did for them.
Oh, warm, wooly rock,
you're my only friend.
(ROARS)
(EXCLAlMS)
(ROARlNG)
We're big ! We're big !
Which you mountain
lions find terrifying !
(MEOWS lN FRlGHT)
(GASPS) They remembered
what l taught them !
Of course we did.
We'll never
forget you, Pocahontas.
Sacagawea.
Gesundheit.
(GASPS) Look!
The Pacific Ocean !
We made it! We discovered
the magnificent
Pacific Northwest.
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
l say we give this
lovely land a name
worthy of its beauty.
Eugene, Oregon !
And we owe it all to you.
You're gonna get
the greatest honor
this country can bestow.
And today, Lewis' promise
has been fulfilled.
What is that? A quarter?
A Chuck E. Cheese token?
No! lt's a Sacagawea dollar.
You can trade
it in at the bank
for a real dollar! Huh?
Bart, what famous
historical figure do you
want to write about?
l don't know. The boogeyman?
Come on, Bart.
We can make this fun.
History's like
an amusement park,
except instead of rides,
you have dates to memorize.
Mom, everyone who
ever lived is boring.
Boring?
ls there anything boring
about a bad-ass rocker
who lived fast
and died young?
l know there's a catch,
but tell me more.
As a young prodigy,
this popular musician
wowed audiences
across 1 8th century Europe.
And now
the star of our show,
my son, Mozart!
He makes Bach turn back.
Haydn go into hidin',
and, well,
those are the only ones
there have been so far.
(CHEERlNG)
Hello, Vienna!
Are there any aficionados
in the house?
Yeah !
Sonata in A,
K331 , Third Movement!
l can't hear you !
Sonata in A,
K331 , Third Movement!
(PLAYING TURKISH RONDO)
(SQUEALlNG)
Great show, Son,
but you forgot to push
the merchandize.
Huh? Huh?
Papa, let me be
the headliner.
l always show up on time
and l close the piano lid
ever so softly.
Oh, little Salieri,
why don't you go play
with the other three
untalented members
of our family?
Tito, Randy, and Jermaine.
(SOUL MUSlC PLAYlNG)
Sally, no one
practices as hard as you.
But it's your
brother who keeps us
in lead-based face powder.
(SWOONlNG)
(MOANS lN DELlGHT)
(HARPSlCHORD PLAYlNG)
Ew! A plague rat!
(LAUGHlNG)
Don't you have
music to write?
l'm doing it right now.
l call this
my "Symphony in Gee,
My Sister Sucks."
(GROWLS)
(CHUCKLES)
O Lord, why did you give such
transcendent talent
to such an undeserving fool?
Because you are ugly!
What is it about
music that enchants us?
The notes.
Our next award is sponsored
by Heinrich's Bratwurst.
"Papa, can we have
a Heinrich's Bratwurst?"
For outstanding composer
age 1 0 and under,
the winner is. . .
Please let me win.
. . .Mozart.
(CHEERlNG)
(SCOFFS) l can't stand it.
Thank you. Thank you.
l want to see
you all next week
at my concert in Krakow!
(ALL LAUGHlNG)
Wow, it's sold out.
Mincing room only.
(GlGGLlNG)
l hope they like the opera.
Oh, they're like sheep.
As the emperor goes,
so do they.
(CHUCKLES SMUGLY)
Wine here! Get your wine!
Claret, Port, Riesling !
Emperors drink free.
l'm an emperor!
(BUBBLES AND SlZZLES)
Nachti-Nacht.
(CACKLES)
(SlNGlNG) Beans, oh, beans,
deIicious in your mouth
But watch out
When beans come out
down south
Tooting,
some caII it pooting
It's air-poIIuting
The gas comes
shooting right from your
butt, butt, butt,
butt, butt, butt, butt,
butt, butt, butt
Ooh ! This makes me
want to fop till l drop.
(MOANlNG)
l say. . .
(YAWNlNG)
(SNORlNG)
The emperor finds it boring.
Then so do we.
(TlTTERlNG)
(SNORlNG)
(GASPS)
People bored with opera?
That's impossible!
(CACKLES)
To failure, dear brother.
Oops.
(SNORlNG)
(REQUIEM PLAYING)
(COUGHlNG)
(MUSlC STOPS)
Oh, Mozart,
l know you are gravely ill.
So l brought you
the very finest doctor
in all of Austria.
Guten Tag, everybody.
Guten Tag, Dr. Nick.
l can tell from here
you have too much blood.
Let's get you
covered in leeches.
Don't be shy.
Eat the little boy.
Now, in the morning,
you'll be good as new
or dead !
But the important thing
is we'll know.
(REQUIEM PLAYING)
(SOBBlNG)
Mozart, you can't die.
(MUSlC STOPS)
l don't want to
live in a world
without the income
you produce.
(SOBBlNG)
(SNlFFLlNG)
l'll never forget when
you were a little baby
and l sang you
the lullabies you wrote.
Where is my sister?
Where is darling Salieri?
(SOBBlNG)
l never wanted you to die.
l just wanted to
destroy your talent
and your joy.
Dear sister,
l have a confession.
ln the eyes of history,
l always thought
your music would
be judged the best.
Really?
But now that
l'm dying young. . .
l'll be cool forever.
(SlGHS)
Eat my pantaloons!
(REQUIEM PLAYING)
Mozart is dead !
(ALL GASP)
Get you genuine death masks!
Fresh off the corpse!
Be the first on your block
to give me money!
(CHUCKLES SMUGLY)
l must show the emperor
my Requiem Mass.
With Mozart dead,
l am, at last, the greatest
composer alive!
(CACKLES)
You'll have to
wait your turn.
The emperor
is with yet another
musical prodigy.
(PLAYlNG PlANO)
Splendid, young Beethoven.
l hereby declare all
other music obsolete.
(CACKLES TO THE TUNE OF
BEETHOVEN'S FIFTH SYMPHONY)
(BEETHOVEN'S
FIFTH SYMPHONY PLAYING)
(WHlSTLES)
(MUTTERlNG lNCOHERENTLY)
(LAUGHS lNSANELY)
And that's
the life of Mozart.
Thank God he died young.
l've gotta get dinner
on the stove.
Mom, that sounds a lot like
the movie Amadeus
which was
historically inaccurate.
Mozart worked hard
on his music.
Salieri was
a respected composer.
All l know is
the guy who played Mozart
was also in AnimaI House.
Now there's
a movie with good music.
(SlNGlNG)
Animal house, house, house
Nobody ever went to cIass
Then we saw
Donald Sutherland's ass
Animal house, house, house
Then they did the end
like American Graffiti
Where you found out
what happened to everyone
English - US - PSDH