CHORUS [SINGS]:
The Simpsons
How I Spent My Strummer Vacation
D'oh! Ah!
[ALL SHOUT THEN GRUNT]
[SHARKS GROWLING]
- Hi, Moe. Got any beer?
- Sure. Check in the fridge.
Wait a minute, I'm at work.
You gotta pay for it.
What the...? Where's my money?
MARGE: Dear Homie, had to buy diapers
for Maggie. Love, Marge.
- Wha...?
MARGE: Simpson.
Oh.
LISA: Dear Dad, took money
for the book fair.
BART: Homer, I need cash
or they're gonna break my legs.
Sorry, Homer.
- So you're gonna let me walk out sober?
- I'm afraid so.
- And you can live with that?
- Ya-huh.
Fine. There are plenty other ways
for me to alter my consciousness.
Oh, yeah.
Are you gonna buy those toads
or just lick them?
Lick them. Go away.
Ah.
Thanks for the donation, Mr. Simpson.
Do you feel okay?
Jewish? Oh, no, I'm not Jewish.
[LAUGHING]
Wait till Moe sees
how wasted I got without him.
He's gonna plotz.
You wouldn't serve Homer
because he didn't have money?
What happened to you, Moe?
You used to be about the booze.
Oh, yeah. I guess I got caught up
in all the glitz and glamour.
[SQUEAKS]
[HUMS]
- Well, Moe.
- Homer, I'm so sorry. Have a free beer.
Oh.
Uh, I don't care about the color of your
skin, Lenny.
You're my friend.
[CHUCKLES]
Man, I've never seen anybody
get loaded so fast.
Can you say the alphabet backwards?
Oh, you'd like that, wouldn't you?
You...
- Hey, I'm worried.
- I've had just about enough of you.
- Oh, yeah?
- Uh-huh.
- Oh, rats.
- I'm out of here.
We can't let our friend drive like this.
I'm liable here.
- Uh...?
- Get his keys.
[GRUNTING]
Hey, you want my keys?
Get them now, jerks.
[LAUGHS]
So long, jerks.
[LAUGHING]
[MIMICS ENGINE RUMBLING]
Running after the car, huh?
Let's see if you can follow this.
[SCREAMING]
Oh, that's it.
[WHISTLES]
[HOMER HUMMING]
MAN: Where to, pal?
HOMER: Moe's Tavern.
Good morning, everybody.
What's for breakfast, cutie?
Homie, it's 5 p.m. We're having dinner.
What? Wait a... That can't be right.
Wait. Was last night the night
we set the clocks ahead eight hours?
You got loaded at Moe's
and the car had to be towed home.
If I was that drunk,
I would remember it.
It's true. I couldn't even wake you up
for work this morning.
I had to tell Mr. Burns
you had violent diarrhea.
Oh, couldn't you come up
with a less embarrassing lie?
But you did have violent diarrhea.
Nobody open the hallway closet
until I say it's okay.
[BOTH SHUDDERING]
Remember how you got home
last night, Dad?
Of course.
It was, uh, some kind of a light rail.
There's no light rail in Springfield.
Oh, won't anyone pretend
to believe me?
- I will, Dad.
- That's why you're my favorite.
All right, time for my favorite show.
MAN [ON TV]:
MTC: Monkey Trauma Center...
...will not be seen tonight...
Oh.
MAN: ...so we may present
this cheaper show.
WOMAN [ON TV]:
Taxicab Conversations.
Hey, I read about this show
in Teen Modern Maturity.
They film passengers with cameras and
catch them at their most uninhibited.
That explains that.
[DISCO MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS]
[HUMMING]
Looks like somebody
got down tonight.
Disco Stu always gets down, baby.
Because when the beat is hot, the...
[SIGHS]
- Hey, can you keep a secret?
- What is it, hon?
I hate disco.
It's all I've talked about for so long,
people think I'm a one-note guy.
[SIGHS]
It's just getting harder, you know.
I had no idea Disco Stu
was so complex.
- How you doing?
- Talky thing, ain't you?
Another proud moment
for the Simpsons.
I don't remember anybody telling me
I was gonna be on TV.
- So, what do you do for a living?
- Oh, you know, I'm a guy at a place.
How'd you get such a crappy job?
You a convict or a junkie?
- Little of both. You got a family?
- Oh, yeah.
Wife and two or three kids.
Can't imagine my life without them.
Oh, you big fooler.
Pretending not to remember
so you could surprise us.
[CHUCKLES]
Yeah, I'm pretty great.
At the end of a hard day...
...there's no better feeling than coming
home to the people that you love.
- Oh, Homie.
- That is so sweet.
I had no idea, Dad.
I just assumed with all the stranglings,
you know...
That my family isn't the center
of my universe?
Are you nuts?
Then there's those other days...
...where you just wish
you never got married or had kids.
[GROANS]
One minute,
you're a carefree teenager...
...with dreams of being a rock star,
or a photographer for Playboy...
...then, bam,
some babe gets her claws in you...
Huh?
...and, boom, you got a bunch of kids
that always needs love.
[BOTH GASPING]
So whammo, you get stuck
in some boring job...
...where they don't let you play guitar
or take pictures of naked women.
And all you can do
is watch yourself get bald and fat...
...and kiss your dreams goodbye.
[SNORING]
Oh, I can't believe they took
Monkey Trauma Center off for this.
[SNORING]
Lousy family.
So I'm just some babe
who sank her claws into you.
- A hot babe.
- Oh!
Have you always resented us, Dad?
Oh, I don't resent you, sweetheart.
What I was trying to say,
and maybe I didn't use the right words...
...was that marriage is like a coffin
and each kid is another nail.
- But as coffins go...
- Please don't say anymore.
Sorry we ruined your life, Homer.
Hmph!
Oh, what have I done?
[ALARM WHISTLES]
- Get in.
- What?
Get in.
Hey, what's this suitcase for?
- Are we going on a trip?
- You are.
[LAUGHING]
[WHIMPERS]
Where are you taking me?
A place where you'll never be bothered
by your family again.
[GASPS]
Oh.
[WHIMPERS]
[SCREAMS]
Get out of the car, Homer.
You can't just leave me out here.
There's not another woman for miles.
Sorry, Dad.
Maybe now you'll appreciate us.
While you're spending the week at...
Rock 'n' Roll Fantasy Camp.
[HOMER GASPS]
The Rolling Stones' Rock 'n' Roll
Fantasy Camp.
But I thought
you guys were mad at me.
For once in my life, I'm confused.
We had a family meeting
and decided...
...that even though what you said
about us was incredibly thoughtless...
...and hurtful, you had a point.
- Damn straight.
- You work a job you don't like...
...so I'm able to be home with the kids.
And you take me places you hate like
museums, plays and the Olive Garden.
And even though you knew
I ratted you out to the IRS...
- ...you never busted me.
- You what?
So to say thank you
for all your sacrifices...
...we spent our family vacation fund
on something that's just for you.
- Do you like it?
- You guys are the best.
I love you. I love you. I love you...
Ugh, oh.
I'm okay.
I love you. I love you. I love you.
[OWL HOOTING]
Hey, what gives?
Where are all the rock stars?
I don't know,
but it's starting to get dark.
[GUITAR PLAYS NEARBY]
Huh, what was that?
Oh, it's getting closer.
- Hello, campers.
- How you doing?
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
It's Mick Jagger and Keith Richards.
[GROANS]
Welcome
to Rock 'n' Roll Fantasy Camp...
...where you'll experience
the complete rock 'n' roll lifestyle...
...without the lawsuits and STDs.
- Whoa! STDs!
- Now, you're all here for one reason...
- To rock!
- Who said that?
That's right, Otto. We're here to rock!
[ALL CHEERING]
So get a good night's sleep.
And remember rule number one,
there are no rules.
[ALL CHEERING]
Rule number two, no outside food.
Oh, what a gyp.
Hey, Mick, you gonna teach us
your cocksure strut?
Not today,
I got a ton of paperwork to catch up on.
Ah, tell me about it. At my job, we...
Oh, you're gone.
RICHARDS [ON PA]:
Hey! Wake up!
[ALL GROANING]
Are you ready to receive
professional training in rock?
- Have you been awake all night?
- I am so excited, I couldn't fall asleep.
I even took some pills
I found on the floor.
You took pills you found on the floor?
Uh-huh, now I'm afraid that if I stop
talking, I'll die. Isn't Mick cool?
I thought he'd be all like,
"I'm a rock star. Aren't I great?"
But he's just like you or me
or Jesus over there.
- Can I have a guitar?
[WHISTLES]
People, if everyone's gonna pick guitar,
I'm not gonna have enough.
- Oh, come on.
- There's lots of other fun instruments...
...like bass.
Come on,
who'd like to be a bass player?
Out of my way, nerdlinger.
- My image.
OTTO: Get me the Strat.
Hand me the Strat.
I'm telling Mr. Jagger.
Ooh, "I'm telling Mr. Jagger."
[LENNY KRAVITZ'S "ARE YOU
GONNA GO MY WAY?" PLAYING]
The clothes you wear on stage should
be a defiant statement of individuality.
HOMER:
Like this, Mr. Kravitz?
God, no.
May we talk about, uh, accentuating
the masculine area?
Did you hear that, people?
Apu asked about crotch stuffing.
Now, I don't do it.
Kenny Loggins does.
I trusted you!
[SOBBING]
[GUITAR PLAYING]
Now, a guitar has many,
many nicknames.
An ax, a gitbox...
Well, I guess that's it.
Anyway, we're gonna start
with the fundamentals.
Playing a burning guitar
with your teeth.
All right, fire.
- Mr. Seltzer?
- Setzer.
No, I think it's Seltzer.
[GRUNTS]
- What is it, Homer?
- I came up with a stage move...
...I feel is very cool.
[GRUNTING]
[SINGING]
Baby, baby, baby, baby
We've gotta start using
a cheaper oatmeal.
HOMER:
Sorry, Mick!
Simpson!
["SHE'S SO COLD"
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
Okay, strut, strut, strut...
...strut, strut, spin, and rooster.
Look, everyone, Homer's got it.
[SINGING] I'm so hot for me
I'm so hot for me
I'm so cold
Okay, now schoolmarm.
I'm the burning fire
I'm the bleeding volcano
Everybody's naughty...
...and freeze finish.
WIGGUM:
Ow.
No matter where you are...
...always say it's the wildest town
in the whole damn world.
When you said it in Springfield last year,
you didn't mean it?
Yeah, sure I did. But only because
Springfield really is the wildest town...
...in the whole damn world.
- Yes, I knew it. I knew it.
- Springfield!
[GUITAR PLAYING]
Lyrics are the hardest part
of songwriting.
When you come up with something
meaningful and heartfelt...
- Boring.
- Will you stop saying that?
Rock stars are supposed
to be about drinking...
...and getting drunk and boozing it up.
Girls that have legs
and know how to use them.
And why I can't drive 55.
You just want mindless generic rock?
Precisely.
[GROANS]
[SINGING] See that drunk girl
Speeding down the street?
ALL:
Yeah!
She's worried about the state
Of public schools
[ALL BOOING]
She likes to party,
she likes to rock
ALL:
Yeah!
She prays that our schools
Don't run out of chalk
[ALL BOOING]
Getting away from the gig
can be a matter of life and death.
So you gotta be in
great physical shape.
Okay, follow me.
[AUDIENCE CHEERING
OVER SPEAKERS]
- Paparazzi to the left.
- I got them.
[GRUNTING]
I'm entitled to a private life.
I'm not a role model and so forth.
Good, Homer. Now, just past
the groupies and we're home.
WOMAN [ON RECORDING]:
I love you. Please sleep with us.
They're bloody cardboard.
We know.
[SINGING]
You ain't never caught a rabbit
And you ain't no friend of mine
- Yeah!
ALL: Aah!
Well, what do you think?
Uh, you rock, Homer.
Really?
You really think I'm better than you?
That was great, Homie.
- What the hell are you doing here?
- Camp is over, Homer.
- It's been a week already?
- I'm glad you had fun.
- But it's time to come home.
- Your mother's right, Homer.
- Gotta get back to the real world.
- We've all gotta get home.
My lawn's not gonna mow itself.
And I've gotta put up
the storm windows. Winter's coming.
HOMER:
Wait. Don't go.
I wanna keep on rocking.
Come on, guys. A-one, a-two...
I'll take that.
No!
[SOBBING]
It came with a pick.
[GROANS]
Come on, Dad.
No! No! I won't go. You can't make me!
- You knew this day was coming.
- I knew nothing.
Ugh, stop kicking me, Dad.
Never.
[SOBS]
My dream has been shattered
into shards of a broken dream.
I was so close to being a rock star...
...but now,
there's a chance it might not happen.
I'll just have to settle
for being a fat, bald, fat nothing.
Finally. Can we go now?
Now, before I lock the door,
do you have to go to the bathroom?
No, I'm fine.
Ugh, I'm so despondent.
Cheer up, Homer.
It's only rock 'n' roll camp.
But I like it.
[SOBBING]
Tell you what, we're doing a benefit gig
before we leave.
How would you like to join us
on-stage?
- For serious?
- For serious, Homer.
Can I have 40 guest passes?
Woo-hoo!
Wow, all access.
All access.
Ooh, good thing it's laminated.
Ha-ha-ha.
[GRUNTS]
- Sir, you can't...
- All access.
Oh, sorry.
[HUMMING]
[WOMEN SCREAMING]
HOMER: All access.
WOMAN 1: Ooh.
- Nice.
WOMAN 2: You rock.
[CHATTERING]
Wow, Homer. I ain't had front row
seats since my Moonie wedding.
After the show, you can come backstage
for pizza and pop.
- Yes!
- All right!
Now, that's a winning combination.
Here you go. Front and center.
I'm so proud of you, Homie.
It's like you're Kid Rock
and I'm Pamela Anderson Lee Rock.
[CROWD CHEERING]
Ooh, gotta run. Enjoy the show.
Okay, let's see the eyes.
Now the fire.
Thanks, mate.
- Couldn't you find a fuel-efficient Satan?
- Don't you have a crotch to stuff?
Evening, fellow rockers.
There you are. Thought we were
going to go on without you.
I'm ready. Just give me a guitar.
How many solos should I do? Four.
I'll do four.
Uh, Homer, you didn't think
you were gonna be playing with...?
[GASPS]
My official tour jacket. Lookit...
Wait. You misspelled "guitar hero."
Look, sorry if there's been
a misunderstanding, Homer.
We really just need you
to tap the mikes and say:
- "Test, test."
- Can't you do it?
Oh.
Okay. So I'll, uh...
Okay.
[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
- Look, there's Dad!
- Woo-hoo! Yay, Homer!
I'm his groupie, ha, ha.
Am I saying that right? Groupie?
- Yeah!
WOMAN: Yeah, Homer!
CARL: You're the man, Homer!
You're the man!
LENNY:
You rock the house! Let's go, Homer!
MOE:
It's go time! It's go time!
Test. Test.
Why is he performing
the duties of a roadie?
Am I saying that right? Roadie?
Test, test. Check, check.
- Hey, he's not rocking out at all.
- Test.
Test. Test.
[SINGING]
You're testing my love for you
Check, check
You're checking to see if I'm true
[CROWD CHEERING]
Test one, test two
Test three, test four
You test me like the water
In El Salvador
- Whoa, El Salvador!
- What's all this then?
He's stealing the show from us.
JAGGER:
Not on my shift.
Let's rock 'n' roll.
[ALL CHEERING]
[SINGING]
Baby, baby, baby, baby, baby
Uh-oh.
[SCREAMS]
No!
[CROWD CHEERING]
Oh, yeah. It's good to see the spectacle
back in rock.
[ALL SCREAMING]
Did you know
it was gonna turn into a riot, Dad?
Oh, yeah.
When you've been in as many as I have,
you can sense them coming.
- Did they ever find Tom Petty's toe?
- What am I, the lost and found?
There's no excuse
for our horrible behavior tonight, Homer.
We acted like a bunch
of angry young men.
Rock 'n' roll is supposed to be
about peace and love.
I hope you won't judge the entire
Brian Setzer Orchestra by my actions.
What we're trying to say,
Homer, is we're sorry.
By the way, I don't suppose
any of you have seen my, um...?
- No. Sorry.
- Oh.
There's no need for apologies, guys.
You're rock stars.
You're supposed to be reckless
and destructive...
...and be celebrated for behavior
that would land normal people in jail.
That's what I told them, Homer.
Just the same,
we'd like to make it up to you.
We're doing a gig tomorrow
to benefit the victims of tonight's gig.
We'd consider it an honor
if you join us.
Well, you're very sweet, Mick.
But the only rocking I wanna do
is in my living-room chair...
...surrounded by the world's
greatest backup group, my family.
[OVER RADIO]
There goes the last DJ
Are you sure you don't miss hanging out
with your rock-star friends, Dad?
No, I got something
to remember them by.
[LAUGHS]
- Have fun at school, kids.
- Later, Homer.
Mr. Simpson,
this zone is for school buses only.
[SCREAMS]
[ALL LAUGHING]
Rock 'n' roll! Woo-hoo.
[KIDS CHEERING]
["RIP THIS JOINT"
PLAYING OVER SPEAKER]
Papa says no
Make up you mind 'cause I gotta go
I'm gonna raise hell
at the Union Hall
Drive myself right over the wall
Rip this joint
Gonna save your soul
Round and round and round we go
Roll this joint
Gonna get down low
Start my starter
Gonna stop the show
And I've gotta put up
the storm windows. Winter's coming.
Everybody's naughty and freeze finish.
[SINGING] She likes to
party, she likes to rock
HOMER:
Yeah!
But there's lots of other fun instruments,
like bass.
I hope you won't judge the entire
Brian Setzer Orchestra by my actions.
Rock 'n' roll is supposed to be
about peace and love.
- Who said that?
- Will you stop saying that?
[ALL LAUGHING]
JAGGER:
Simpson!
[English - US -SDH]