♪ The Simpsons ♪
(chalk screeches)
(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(tires screeching)
(horn honks)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
(elephants trumpeting)
Mmm, delicious.
Now, Krusty,
I hear it's your birthday.
So, I got your mother's recipe
for matzo balls.
Hey, I don't do the Jewish
stuff on the air.
But, Herschel, bubelah--
Ix-nay on the Ew-jay.
Roll the cartoon!
It's so sad that Krusty
is ashamed of his roots.
Marge,
it happened again.
Ohh--
What are you gonna
change your name to
when you grow up?
Lois Sanborn.
Steve Bennett.
♪ They fight, and fight ♪
♪ They fight and fight
and fight ♪
♪ Fight, fight, fight,
fight, fight, fight ♪
♪ The Itchy & Scratch show ♪
Ow!
Hee-hee-hee!
-Ow!
-Hee-hee-hee!
This is a rather
lifeless outing.
Don't worry, they're building
to something.
Ow!
Hee-hee-hee!
BOTH:
Kids, say "no" to drugs.
I could pull a
better cartoon out of my a--
(nervous chuckle)
Hey, whoa,
wasn't that great, kids?
That's as bad as the tasteless
Itchy and Sambo cartoons
of the late '30s.
The writers should be
ashamed of themselves.
Cartoons have writers?
Yeah, sort of.
Oh yeah, well, you and I
could write
a better cartoon
than that.
Write a cartoon ourselves?
Bart, are you thinking
what I'm thinking?
Probably not.
Lie in the snow
and count to 60.
Hi-yah!
(evil laugh)
Merry Christmas, suckers.
MARGE: "Third notice?"
"Final notice?"
"Some guys are coming?"
What's this?
An invitation
to our high school reunion!
Gee, that's odd.
They didn't send one
to you.
This is it, Homer.
It's time to tell her
the terrible secret
from your past.
Marge, I ate those fancy soaps
you bought for the bathroom.
Oh, my God.
No, the other secret.
Marge, I never graduated
from high school.
That still doesn't explain
why you ate my soap.
Wait, maybe it does.
I never passed
Remedial Science 1A.
And you're a nuclear technician?
Marge, ix-nay on the
uclear-nay echnician-tay.
What did you say?
I don't know.
I flunked Latin too.
According to this book
the first thing we need
is a setting.
Okay, settings--
settings-- settings--
setting--
(groans)
How about a barber shop?
Great!
Scratchy's getting a haircut.
Then Itchy, the barber,
chops Scratchy's head off
with the razor.
(Bart laughs)
Ah, too predictable.
The way I see it,
instead of shampoo,
Itchy covers Scratchy's hair
with Bar-B-Q sauce.
Opens a box
of flesh-eating ants
and the rest writes itself.
(screams)
Hey, this show ain't
no good.
Hyah!
Finished.
Now, all we have to do
is put our names on it.
Fine--
put my name first.
No way.
All right,
then to decide it
I propose a race
around the world.
Meet me at Leicester Square
at noon tomorrow.
The queen herself shall
drop the checkered flag.
Look, there's only
one reasonable way
to settle this.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Poor predictable Bart.
Always takes rock.
Good old rock.
Nothing beats that.
-Rock.
-Paper.
D'oh!
MAN: You call this writing?
If I puked
in a fountain pen
and mailed it to the monkey
house I'd get better scripts.
But, sir, at Harvard--
Oh, at Harvard they taught you--
Hit the streets, egghead.
You should have majored
in not getting fired.
Sir, a Lisa and
Bart Simpson
sent you a script.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
"Dear Mr. Meyers:
"My brother and I
watch your show.
"You should be proud
that children everywhere--"
Blah-blah-blah,
bling-bling-bling, blah.
Hey, egghead!
Sing "Fair Harvard."
♪ Fair, Harvard ♪
♪ I-- ♪
You, sir, have
the boorish manners
of a Yalie.
Here's a witty
rejoinder for ya!
(groans)
Bart, they rejected
our script.
I guess we're just not
cut out to be writers.
Maybe he just doesn't
take us seriously
'cause we're kids.
Let's put a grown-up's
name on it.
How about Grandpa?
He's pretty out of it.
He let those guys use his
checkbook for a whole year.
ABE:
When I read your magazine,
I don't see one wrinkled face
or a single toothless grin.
For shame!
To the sickos
at Modern Bride magazine.
Hey, Grandpa.
We need to know
your first name.
You're making my tombstone!
No, we're just curious.
All right, let's see--.
First name, first name.
Well, whenever I'm confused,
I just check my underwear.
It holds the answer to all
of the important questions.
Call me Abraham Simpson.
Grandpa, how did you
take off your underwear
without taking off your pants?
I don't know.
(groans)
Hmm!
(chuckles)
(knocking)
What?
Sir, you locked my office,
and I wanted to get
my Harvard mug.
Shut up!
(groans)
(chuckles)
(laughing)
Roxie, get me Abraham Simpson.
(phone ringing)
Phone call, Simpson.
Yeah?
Is this the Abraham Simpson
who wrote the Itchy and
Scratchy episode?
Itchy and what?
You must be some kind
of crazy person.
I'm sorry, but we have
a substantial check here
for a Mr. Abraham Simpson.
That's right.
I did the Iggy.
Ah, my high school yearbook.
You handsome devil.
"I can't believe
I ate the whole thing."
(chuckles)
"Activities: None.
"Sports: None.
Honors: None."
So many memories.
Time to go to the reunion.
It will be great to see
the old gang again.
Potsie, Ralph Malph, the Fonz.
That was "Happy Days."
No, they weren't all happy days.
Like the time Pinky Tuscadero
crashed her motorcycle
or the night I lost all
my money to those cardsharps
and my dad, Tom Bosley,
had to get it back.
(groans)
Hello,
Principal Dondalinger.
Oh, Marge Bouvier,
it's so good to see you.
Sorry, sir.
We're not letting vagrants
sleep in the gym tonight
but we will be putting some
scraps by the back door.
-D'oh!
-Oh, it's you, Simpson.
Eech.
Look. There's Bobby Mindich,
the class clown.
I am not a crook.
(laughs)
Richard Nixon.
I know.
♪ Do the hustle ♪
(laughs)
Oh, my God.
It's my old boyfriend
Artie Ziff.
(humming)
Hello, Marge.
Have you heard?
I'm stinking rich.
Jealous?
I'll bet you'd trade it all
for one night with my wife.
I would.
Hmm!
Homer!
(imitating Cheech and Chong)
Hey, man, it's Dave.
Open up, man.
Dave's not here, man.
(laughs loudly)
Okay, now let's move on.
(laughing)
The guy's so high
he doesn't even
know that's Dave.
Homer. Homer?
Homer's not here, man.
Okay. Very good.
Now let's get on with our
(imitating Ed Sullivan)
really big show.
-Ed Sullivan.
-Shh.
First, the award for the alumnus
who's gained the most weight.
-Homer Simpson.
-Oh, my God!
How did you do it, Homer?
I discovered a meal
between breakfast and brunch.
And now, the award
for most improved odor.
Homer Simpson.
Yes!
And the person who traveled
the least distance to be here--
(southern accent)
Well, kiss my grits.
Homer Simpson.
What can I say?
It hasn't been easy
staying in my rut.
Class of '74
I was just leafing through
your permanent records
when I discovered
something shocking.
Homer Simpson never passed
Remedial Science 1A
and thus never graduated
from high school.
(gasping)
I'm sorry, Simpson, I'm gonna
have to take back those awards.
(laughter)
This is Howard Cosmell.
Homer Simpson is a boob.
What do you think, J.J.?
Dyno-mite!
Didn't graduate?
How low can you get?
Barney, where's
your cummerbund?
It fell in the toilet.
Marge, I have my pride.
I'm going to go
to night school,
earn my high school diploma
and get back my
"most improved odor" trophy.
Mmm.
You're a comedy writer?
My God, you're so old.
I want my check!
(laughs)
You're a writer, all right.
All right,
here you go, Simpson.
I want another one!
You're a funny guy.
How would you like a staff job,
I'll start you at $800 a week?
My chest hurts.
All right, leeches.
I want you to see what
a good writer looks like.
His name is Abraham Simpson,
and he's got something
you couldn't get
at your fancy schools--
Life experience.
Actually, I wrote my thesis
on life experience and--
Quiet!
Abe, tell them about
your amazing life.
I spent 40 years
as a night watchman
at a cranberry silo.
Wow!
So, this patch steadily
releases nicotine into my body
eliminating my need
for cigarettes.
(goofy laugh)
(grunting)
Roll the cartoon.
♪ The Itchy & Scratchy Show ♪
Bart, our cartoon's on TV!
All right!
Turn up the volume.
MAN: Erosion is a slow
but steady process.
(screaming)
Ah, this show ain't no good.
Hyah!
(piano plays)
♪ They fought and bit ♪
♪ They fought and fought
and bit ♪
♪ Fought, fought, fought
bit, bit, bit ♪
♪ It was the Itchy
& Scratchy show ♪
(playing end theme from
Stephen J. Cannell productions)
(sighing)
Bart, Lisa, I have
something to tell you
and I'm not proud of it.
Dad, whatever you say,
you know you'll always
have my love and respect.
I never graduated
from high school.
(laughing)
(growls)
(gagging)
(doorbell rings)
Hello, son.
I was on my way home
from work
and thought I'd drop by.
Oh... you have a job?
They pay me $800 a week
to tell a cat and mouse
what to do.
I see.
♪ La, la-la, la-la, la-la ♪
♪ La-la, la-la, la-la, la-la,
la-la, la-la, la-la, la-la--♪
Dad, can we talk to
Grandpa alone for a minute?
All right, but if he
starts to wig out
try to lure him
into the cellar.
Then we put your name
on the script and sent it in.
Didn't you wonder why
you were getting checks
for doing absolutely
nothing?
I figured 'cause the Democrats
were in power again.
Grandpa, we could write
the scripts for you
and split the money
three ways.
I don't know.
I'd better sleep on it.
(snoring)
Grandpa?
-Grandpa!
-Ah! Duh!
Oh, why did you wake me?
I was having the nicest dream.
I dreamt I was the queen
of the old west.
I kept a six-shooter
in my garter, I did.
-Do we have a deal?
-Sure, sure.
(snoring)
Boys, stop!
You can both marry me.
Whoo!
Whoo! Yee-hee!
Hey, how would you kids like
a tour of the studio?
BOTH: Yay!
Abe, you coming?
-Any stairs?
-Just one.
Nuts to you.
(snoring)
Wow, it must be expensive
to produce all these cartoons.
Well,
we cut corners.
Sometimes,
to save money
our animators will reuse
the same backgrounds
over and over
and over again.
Welcome to Remedial Science 1A.
My wife recently passed away.
I thought teaching
might ease my loneliness.
Will this be on the test?
-No.
-Oh.
Hey, Mel, bring
me another nicotine patch.
I think there's some space
on my butt.
And now here's another fine
Itchy & Scratchy cartoon
by Abraham Simpson.
ALL: Yay!
(screaming)
Now I'm going to burn
this doughnut to show you
how many calories
it has.
No!
The bright blue flame
indicates this was
a particularly
sweet doughnut.
(sobbing)
This is not happening.
ABE: Dear Mr. President:
There are too many
states nowadays.
Please eliminate three.
I am not a crackpot.
Good news, Abe.
Who are you?
No, no, you've been
nominated for an award.
You're so good,
I fired the other writers.
From now on, the fate
of the entire company
rests on that delightful
coconut of yours.
Oh, no,
we're all doomed.
I'm a complete fraud.
Sorry, I didn't catch
any of that.
And now I got to go.
All right,
here are your exams.
50 questions,
true or false.
True.
Homer, I was just
describing the test.
-True.
-Look, Homer,
just take the test
and you'll do fine.
False.
All right, brain,
you don't like me,
and I don't like you
but let's just do this
and I can get back
to killing you with beer.
It's a deal.
Thank you for this award.
It is a tribute
to this great country
that a man who once took
a shot at Teddy Roosevelt
could win back your trust.
Yo, Grandpa,
time for the awards.
Did you call the girl
from the escort service?
They said their insurance
won't cover you.
That's an onion
in the ointment.
ANNOUNCER:
And now to present the award
for outstanding writing
in a cartoon series,
Krusty the Clown
and Brooke Shields.
Well, here we are--.
The star of "The Blue Lagoon"
and me, the blue-haired goon.
What the--
That's terrible.
Cartoons have the power to make
us laugh and to make us cry.
Wouldn't you agree,
Krusty?
First of all,
my hair is green, not blue.
I got nothing to work
with here. Nothing.
Uh--
Well, at least I can
take off this girdle.
(grunting)
Oh, yeah.
The nominees for best writing
in a cartoon series are:
Strongdar, Master of Acom.
"The Wedding" episode.
Action Figure Man.
The "How to Buy
Action Figure Man" episode.
Please, Mommy,
I want it.
Hmm--
Ren and Stimpy.
Season premiere.
And finally,
Itchy & Scratchy.
The "Little Barber Shop
of Horrors" episode.
Cross my fingers for me.
(cracking)
That's gonna hurt
come winter.
(screaming)
(giggling)
And the winner is--
"Itchy & Scratchy.
Abraham Simpson,
writer."
BART:
All right, Grandpa, whoo!
That was the first time
I ever saw Itchy & Scratchy
and I didn't like it one bit.
It was disgusting and violent.
I think all you people
are despicable.
For shame!
(grumbling)
He's right. We've been
wasting our lives.
The hell with cartoons.
I'm gonna do
what I've always dreamed of.
I want to write that sitcom
about the sassy robot.
Here, kids, I guess
you deserve this.
Let's go.
LISA: I guess nobody likes
the truth, huh, Grandpa?
Nope.
BART: I'll never watch
an awards show again
unless that delightful
Billy Crystal is involved.
Marge, I passed!
That's wonderful, Homie.
At our next high school reunion
I'll have nothing
to be ashamed of.
Hello, Dondalinger.
Simpson, is that a plunger
stuck on your head?
D'oh!
(groans)
♪ Hens love roosters ♪
♪ Geese love ganders ♪
♪ Everyone else
loves Ned Flanders ♪
Not me.
♪ Everyone who counts
loves Ned Flanders ♪
Knock that off, you two.
It's time for church.
We're not going to church today.
(gasps)
What?
You give me one good reason.
It's Saturday.
Okely-dokely-doo.
♪ Hens love roosters ♪
♪ Geese love ganders ♪
♪ Everyone else loves
Ned Flanders ♪
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.