♪ The Simpsons ♪
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
(video games beeping)
Thirsting for a way to name the unnamable,
to express the inexpressible.
Tell me more.
Keep cool, Simpson.
Be in the game
but not of the game.
(roars)
No es bueno.
-(machine gun fire)
-(screaming)
-(grunts)
-Winners don't use drugs.
Ehh! Ehh! Ehh! Ehh!
-Aw! I'm outta money.
-Don't say that out loud.
Two Caucasian males
out of money in Sector 4.
Go to Code Red.
-(alarms blaring)
-(everyone gasps)
(pounding footsteps)
I'm sorry.
You'll have to leave.
Oh, man.
How are we supposed to kill
the rest of the afternoon?
You mustn't kill time, boys.
You must cherish it.
Seize the day!
Can I have some change
to go get loaded?
Ah. Finally,
a little quiet time
to read some
of my old favorites.
"Honey roasted peanuts.
"Ingredients: salt,
"artificial
honey-roasting agents,
pressed peanut sweepings."
Mmm!
Homer, I have to go out to
pick up something for dinner.
-Steak?
-Money's too tight for steak.
-Eh, sure. Steak.
Ah. The last peanut--
Overflowing with the oil
and salt of its departed brothers.
Uh-oh.
Something's wrong.
Hmm. Ow! Pointy.
Eww! Slimy.
Uh-oh! Moving.
Aha! Aw. Twenty dollars.
I wanted a peanut.
(thinking) Twenty dollars
can buy many peanuts.
Explain how.
Money can be exchanged
for goods and services.
Whoo-hoo! Whoa!
(grunts)
(whimpers, shrieks)
♪♪ ("The Flight
of the Bumblebee")
-Ow!
-Ow! Ow!
You know,
this is wearin' a bit thin.
You think so?
-Bart! Look!
-Maybe a plane exploded.
Our prayers
have been answered.
Hello, gents.
What will it be?
Apu, give us a Super Squishee.
One that's made
entirely out of syrup.
-Entirely ou-- (gasps)
-(all gasping)
An all-syrup Super Squishee?
Oh, s-such a thing
has never been done.
Just make it happen.
Oh. Oh, dear.
(clanking, rumbling)
-(syrup glugging)
-(yelps)
Oh! She won't hold!
She's breaking up!
-(bell dings)
-All done.
If you survive,
please come again.
(both yelling, whooping)
-(squeaking)
-(gasps) It's so thick!
(sucking)
(coughing)
(gasping)
Your turn, Bart.
(sucking)
(coughs)
Whoa! That's good Squishee.
(groaning)
What's it like,
Bart? Bart? Bart?
-(babbling gibberish)
-Give me that!
(slurps, moans, yelps)
Okay. We're young, rich,
and full of sugar. What'll we do?
Let's go crazy Broadway-style!
-(hands slap)
-(both) Yeah!
♪ Springfield, Springfield
It's a helluva town ♪
♪ The schoolyard's up
and the shopping mall's down ♪
♪ The stray dogs go
to the animal pound ♪
-♪ Springfield, Springfield ♪
♪ New York, New York ♪
-New York is thataway, man.
-Thanks, kid.
♪ It's a helluva town ♪
-♪♪ (show music continues)
-Whoa. Wow.
-(blows)
-(caterwauling)
Huh? Huh? Huh?
Mmm! Free goo.
MILHOUSE:
Hey! Don't bogart that Squishee!
(gulping) I don't know where
you magic pixies came from,
but I like your pixie drink.
-♪♪ (continues)
-(laughing)
(groaning)
-My head.
-(tsking)
The remorse
of the sugar junkie.
(groans)
I don't remember anything.
Really? Not even this?
(screams)
Oh, no!
I must have joined
the Junior Campers.
-(whimpers)
-The few, the proud, the geeky.
(chortles)
Boy! A man on a Squishee bender
can sure do some crazy things.
(horn blows)
(groaning)
Uh-oh.
Not again?
(belches)
Okay, look.
I made a terrible mistake.
I wandered into a Junior Camper
recruitment center,
but what's done is done.
I've made my bed, and now
I've gotta weasel out of it.
I know you think the Junior Campers
are square and "uncool,"
but they also do
a lot of neat things,
like sing-alongs
and flag ceremonies.
Marge, don't discourage the boy.
Weaseling out of things
is important to learn.
It's what separates us from the animals...
except the weasel.
All I've gotta do is take
this uniform back after school.
You're lucky. You only joined
the Junior Campers.
I got a dirty word shaved
into the back of my head.
(gasps) What is it with
you kids and that word?
I'm going to shave you bald,
young man,
until you learn that hair is not a right--
It's a privilege.
What's in the bag, wuss?
Huh? Oh, look.
Camper's pampers. Ha-ha!
-Keep away!
-Keep away! Nyah-nyah-nya-nya-nyah!
Yeah, whatever.
You better pretend you want
your uniform back, twerp.
(gulp)
-Keep away!
(spiritless)
Oh, no. Woe is me.
My precious uniform.
Oh.
Guess what, class.
-Time for a surprise quiz?
-(all gasp)
Well, that's not what I was gonna say,
but it's a good idea.
Ha! Take out a sheet of paper.
Books under your desks.
-(groans)
-But I'm supposed to--
I've gotta-- I'm supposed to--
Oh, Warren, I nearly forgot.
All Junior Campers are excused
to attend their patrol meeting.
Um, Mrs. Krabappel,
I'd love to stay,
but this uniform carries
certain responsibilities.
Hey, look! Sergeant Dork!
-Ha-ha!
-Enjoy your test.
Ha-ha-- Aw.
Hello, alternative to testing.
-(moans)
-Well, it's Bart Simpson. Come on in.
You're just in time for
Sponge-Bath the Old Folks Day.
Help yourself,
but stay above the equator.
-(shrieks, yelps)
-(thuds on floor)
Now, just breathe into him
every three seconds.
Make sure you form a tight seal
around his mouth.
BART: No!
(coughing, gagging)
-Should I keep doing it?
-Well, sir, just apply
a smidgen of peanut butter
to an ordinary pine cone,
and you've got yourself
a makeshift bird feeder, sir.
I'm outta here, man.
Okay. Everybody take out your
Junior Campers pocketknives.
Hmm? You guys get to
play with knives?
-Oh, cool. A "spork."
-Don't hurt me!
Ooh. Sorry, Bart.
That's a Neddy no-no.
You're not allowed
to handle a pocketknife
till you read this booklet
on knife safety and pass a test.
Aw, who needs
a cruddy knife anyway?
-Knives are boring.
-Whoa!
When I say put your beer
on a coaster, I mean it!
You call that a knife?
This is a knife.
(whimpering)
Down I go.
-(grunts)
-(sighing) Oh.
(exhales)
Oh, hi, Bart.
I'd gladly share these
sweet cookies with you,
if only you would help me
remove this ribbon.
-Here's a knife.
-Oh, thank you.
Now let's all share
the goodness.
-Share this.
-(groans)
(bullies laughing)
(groaning)
This man's appendix
is about to burst.
Luckily, I have
my trusty pocketknife.
-(whimpers)
-(flesh slicing open)
-(crowd gasps)
-Stand back! (grunts)
-(explosion)
-(cheering)
-Thank you, Dr. Hibbert.
-Don't thank me.
-Thank the knife.
-(crowd cheering)
Oh. Seems like
everywhere I look,
people are enjoying knives.
"Don't do what
Donny Don't does."
(sighs) They could've
made this clearer.
Oh! They won't let you
have any fun.
Well! If it isn't the leader
of the wiener patrol,
boning up on his nerd lessons.
Homer, you should be
more supportive.
-You're right, Marge. Good work, boy.
-Hmm.
♪ Egghead likes
his booky-wook ♪
-Homer!
-Just tucking him in.
Here you go--
Your rubber training knife.
You've attained the rank
of Pussy Willow.
Rubber knife?
This place is for wimps.
Okay, kids. Now I'm gonna
teach ya how to trap wild animals.
But this should only be used
-in a life-or-death situation.
-Hmm.
Ooh! Floor pie.
I-- Whoa!
(rope stretching)
Jeez!
Oh!
Ah!
(whimpering)
Aw. Oh.
-(yelps)
-(thuds)
Bart!
Mmm! Apple.
♪ The Itchy and Scratchy Show ♪
♪♪ (strumming)
(yowling)
-(thunder)
-(snoring)
-(thundering)
-(laughing)
The guys who wrote this show
don't know squat.
Itchy should've
tied Scratchy's tongue
with a taut-line hitch,
not a sheet bend.
Oh, Bart. Cartoons don't have
to be 100% realistic.
(Homer humming)
Howdilly-hey, Camper Bart!
Ready for today's meeting?
-You know-dilly know it, Neddy.
-Okilly-dokilly.
Now, our annual father-son
rafting trip is next weekend.
(thinking) Oh, no.
Me bring Homer on a rafting trip?
Duh, I'm the captain.
My son is Bart.
-What an oaf.
-How embarrassing.
I'm glad he's not my father.
(shudders)
(sniffling)
Oh, Warren, I know your dad
is in prison, but don't you fret.
A special celebrity dad
has been arranged for ya.
But my older brother
would like--
Sorry, but I'm afraid Ernest Borgnine
has already been confirmed.
(laughing)
Hiya!
I'm sure you kids
know me best...
as Sergeant Fatso Judson
in From Here to Eternity.
(cheering)
How was jerk practice, boy?
Did they teach you
how to sing to trees...
and build crappy furniture
out of useless wooden logs?
Huh? D'oh!
(growls)
Stupid poetic justice!
Actually, we were just planning
the father-son river-rafting trip.
Heh-heh!
You don't have a son.
Look. Homer won't wanna go.
So just ask him,
and he'll say no.
Then it'll be his fault.
I don't wanna go. So if he asks
me to go, I'll just say yes.
(thinking) Wait! Are you sure
that's how this sort of thing works?
Shut up, brain,
or I'll stab you with a Q-tip.
Dad, I really want you to
come on this trip with me.
Bart, I'd be delighted to
go on your trip with you.
BOTH:
D'oh!
-(crying)
-Aw, come on, kid. Quit cryin'.
It'll be fun.
I promise.
(laughing)
Arr! Here be a fine vessel,
the yarest river-goin'
boat there be.
I'll take it.
Arr. I don't know
what I'm doin'.
Okeydokey.
Everybody find a partner.
Two dads to a raft.
(all chattering)
Please not Flanders. Please not Flanders.
Please not Flanders.
Well, Homer, looks like
we're boat buddies, huh?
Want me to zinc your sniffer?
(campers chattering, yelling)
(gasps)
I guess now we know why...
they call 'em rapids
and not "slowpids, huh?"
-(laughing)
-You are not my son.
Eh. Now, what happened to that
gosh-darn map I brought?
-(wind gusts)
-(yelps) Um, I don't know.
But lucky for you,
somebody here is responsible.
Hey! There's a new Mexico.
Whoa, Nelly!
Oh! Quick, Homer!
Which way do we turn?
So many Krusty Burger
locations.
(drooling)
Uh-oh! No time.
Matthew, Mark, Luke and John!
-(grunting)
-(all screaming)
Hey, where are the sissy
and the bald guy goin', huh?
(all yelling)
-(horn blows)
-Paddle harder, Homer.
-We gotta fight the current.
-Wrong again, Flanders.
In a situation like this,
you just relax
and let the current
take you back to land.
(whimpering)
D'oh.
-♪♪ (Archies: "Sugar, Sugar")
-♪ Sugar, do-do-do-do do-do ♪
♪ Aw, honey, honey
do-do-do-do do-do ♪
-♪♪ (tempo decreases)
-♪ You are my candy girl ♪
-♪♪ (stops)
-♪♪ (slurring, stops)
(yells)
Lousy piece of junk!
Hey! I got that
for my birthday.
Now I have to face
stupid reality again.
Flanders!
My socks feel dirty.
-Give me some water to wash 'em.
-Again?
Homer, we have to ration
the water carefully. It's our only hope.
Oh, pardon me,
Mr. Let's Ration Everything.
What do you think
we're floatin' on?
Don't you know the poem?
"Water, water everywhere,
so let's all have a drink."
-ALL: Homer! No!
-What does it matter?
We're doomed.
-(calling)
-NED: Wrong.
We're saved!
Seagulls always stay near land.
They only go out to sea
to die.
(squawks)
Whoo-hoo!
See that, boy?
Your old man was right,
not Flanders.
We are doomed.
In your face, Flanders!
Well, at least Ned is trying.
What are you doing to help?
Well, since you're all such
a big bunch of big ration babies,
I'll just be in charge
of the rationing.
Look here, boy.
The secret is to take
tiny bites, like so.
Mmm! Mmm! Mmm!
-Stop it!
-(all shouting, indistinct)
-HOMER: Let go of my hand!
D'oh!
(grunts)
(bawling)
Why couldn't I be
on one of the smart rafts?
I bet they're having
the time of their lives.
♪♪ ("Dueling Banjos" playing)
(chortling)
Shh! Shh, shh! Shh!
I keep telling you, lady.
Your husband and son have
to be missing for a week...
before we can start searching.
I'd like to help sooner.
I would,
but we're very,
very busy down here.
Heesh!
King me.
(growls)
Still no help.
You know,
it is cougar season,
and those things
don't mess around.
(worried murmur)
A rescue plane!
Get the flare gun!
(grunts) This ain't
one of your church picnic
flare gun firings, Flanders.
This is the real thing.
D'oh! All right.
Well, that's okay.
When they come to rescue him,
they'll rescue us.
D'oh!
Here's our chance.
Dolphins always help
humans lost at sea.
(dolphins vocalizing)
Come back!
(gasps)
Oh, we're done for.
We're done for.
We're done-didilly done for!
We're done-didilly-dodilly
done-didilly-dodilly
done-didilly-dodilly done--
Flanders!
Snap out of it!
Thank you, Homer.
I don't know what got--
-(Ned grunting)
-Dad! I think he's okay.
-(grunting)
-It's better...
-to be safe than sorry.
-Dodilly--
-Sorry.
-Didilly--
-You see anything yet?
-Nothin', Captain.
Somebody took all the beer
and cold cuts.
That's it. I'm not even castin' off
until we go to the store.
You know, Homer,
this cheese doodle
is our last morsel of food.
You'll thank me when we're
fryin' up a big, juicy fish.
-(strained grunt)
-Godspeed, little doodle.
He'll be back.
Here, fishy, fishy, fishy.
We're waiting.
Son, there's something I was gonna
give you at the end of this trip,
but, since we
may not survive,
I want you to have it now.
(gasps)
A real Swiss Army knife. Cool!
I stole it
from that Borgnine guy.
(roaring)
Don't worry, kids. I'll take care
of him with my trusty--
Uh, uh--
Um, uh-- Hmm.
Dad, I know I've been
a little hard on you
the last couple of days.
If I had the strength to lift my arms,
I'd give you a hug.
Thanks, boy.
Now, be careful
when you-- Oops.
(all gasping)
(relieved sighs)
(sizzling)
Dad, don't take this wrong,
but your expression doesn't
fill me with confidence.
The foul stench of death
is upon us!
(sniffing)
Mmm! Hamburger.
(sniffs) Hey, wait!
I smell hamburgers, too.
(sniffing)
According to this map,
there's a Krusty Burger
on an off-shore oil rig.
That's what you're
smelling, Homer.
Oh, if it weren't for this
blasted fog, we'd be saved.
Never mind the fog!
(sniffing) That way!
Steer.
There isn't much time!
(sniffing)
(sign buzzing)
Oh! We're takin' a bath
on this.
We tried to tell ya
these are unmanned oil rigs.
Aw, close the damn thing down.
No one's ever gonna come.
-Huh?
-Give me 700 Krusty Burgers!
You want fries with that?
-(gulping)
-You did it, Dad! You saved us!
I'm proud you're my father.
Go away. Eating.
BORGNINE:
Well, it sure is lucky...
we stumbled upon this old,
abandoned summer camp.
CAMPERS:
Yeah.
-Hey, how about a song?
-CAMPERS: Okay. Yeah.
♪ There was a farmer
had a dog ♪
♪ And Bingo
was his name-o ♪
-♪ B-I-N-G-O ♪
-(heavy breathing)
-(heavy breathing continues)
♪ B-I-N-G-O ♪
♪ And Bingo was his name-o ♪
(all screaming)
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.