Another Springfield day
A truly perfect place to see
your dreams just fade away
Working at the plant's fried
everything inside my pants
Good-bye to all romance
All I've got to show
for 20 years or so is you
- Carl!
- Prescription pain pills!
I have a law degree
For years I've smelled
just like cat pee
This town
just drags you down
She's completely
lost her head
And we will eat her
when she's dead
It really shouldn't be
too long
- Cats! Cats! Cats!
- She'll be our dinner
This truly is an awful town
The water's green,
the sky is brown
Pope Francis came,
he turned around
Our strongest bridge
just holds ten pounds
We're poisoned
by a greedy clown
Kang-a-roo meat!
Traffic suffers
from paralysis
Please.
I'm late for my dialysis.
It's another
Springfield day
I'm too sad to say olé
We've lost our coolest gays
Duffman thinks
this town's okay!
It's another
Springfield day!
Lenny's a survivor!
This will be a perfect day
No way
to go outside and play
And so we're on our way
To a very nerdy
science conference
Take it Bart!
If you're givin' it,
I don't want it.
Bring it home, boy.
My sister sucks!
It's another perfect day!
I brought my stems.
Sir, this is a conference
of Science, Technology,
Engineering and Math.
What about this one?
Dialogue on Pediatric Education.
I find this claim highly doyvik.
It's all true according
to the highly-prestigious
Institute for Purchased Science.
Here's our top scientist now.
Sir, I don't think
this is fooling anyone.
Quiet! And put on the monocle,
Professor Noodle-Strudel.
- So where's your booth?
- I don't have one.
- I just came here for fun.
- Fun?!
One child, please.
I was here first.
If disco's dead,
I don't want to live.
It's Stuicide!
Self-unrolling yoga mats.
Artificial intelligence
that writes TV recaps.
Stranger Things suffers
from season two fatigue.
And look! IMAX Al Gore!
If every family could just
reduce their carbon footprint
by ten percent...
Oh, it's hopeless.
The floods are comin', people!
This is my Woodstock!
You okay, honey?
It's fine. It's fine.
I'm just intellectually drunk.
I guess that's okay.
Marge, Marge, Marge,
you lighten up.
It's science.
Maybe you should sit down.
I ain't sittin'.
I'm ready to fly!
Hey, kid,
I want to show you something.
Are you a pervert?
No. A chemical engineer.
No!
I used to be like you.
You mean incredibly bored?
Oh, let's see
if you think this is boring.
I drop a little water
on powdered sodium...
Listen, I don't know
what you're teaching,
but you and I have
great chemistry.
Except for the lab coat.
It makes you look
kind of heavy.
I actually am kind of heavy,
and it makes me look thinner!
I don't know what could make
this day more perfect.
You didn't applaud.
Nothing.
Here, I'll show ya how it goes.
Thank you.
No selfies.
In a lesser musician,
that boy's attitude
would be needy
masquerading as arrogance.
I'm leaving if he can't sing.
I've had my share
of crazy flings
But they all end up leavin'
And leavin',
well, it really stings...
Oh, God.
He's one small step away
from destroying
all my logic and reason.
Hey, Lisa.
I brought you three waters,
cold, lukewarm and warm.
- That's nice. Any sparkling?
- Damn it!
Hi. I'm Lisa Simpson,
and I'm nervous
about saying anything that will
ruin this perfect moment.
My name's Brendan.
Oh, good, good.
No last names.
Don't want things
moving too fast.
I hope our children
get his hair.
Now to subtly find out
how old he is.
How old are you?
Well, I'm 11, but I'm insouciant
at a 12th grade level,
and I'm talented too.
So unfair, right?
That's amazing, because
the boys I know are re...
I've got sparkling!
Sorry, I'm not thirsty anymore.
Damn it!
So where do you go
to school?
I just moved here.
I'm starting next week
at a school called
Springfield Elementary.
I see it got a few
dreadful reviews on Yelp.
This guy called Gary Chalmers
gave it half a star.
Bloody hell!
Of all the K through sixes
in this world,
you had to walk into mine.
A beautiful hotel bar!
Just like in The Shining!
Oh, hi, lee... tle girl.
If you see your ma...
ma wife,
tell her Homer, not your dad,
wants the credit card.
I will, sir.
- Sir? I'm your dad.
- D'oh!
Today, we are performing
an experiment that
we humorously call
making elephant toothpaste.
Boy, the Germans
sure know their humor.
Let's just hope they know
something about chemistry.
First, add a tablespoon of
dish soap to hydrogen peroxide,
then add the warm water
and the yeast!
German chemistry!
Sounds great, Lisa.
Really great.
You're just a little
behind the beat.
Maybe you're a little
ahead?
You're so cute
when you're wrong.
- Channel that rage!
- No!
Make that reed pay
for my sins!
Yeah!
Knock off that racket!
It's not a racket!
It's the truest
American art form!
Banging on the walls is
the truest American art form,
and I'm a Picasso!
Oh, no! They're playing in time
to the beat of my banging!
Well, then stop banging.
I can't.
The rhythm is infectious.
Here's the school trophy case.
If you look closely, it's empty.
They're actually decals
on the glass.
Oh, hello, Lisa.
I see you have a new friend.
Brendan, this is Nelson.
Lisa, you sure know
a lot of weird guys.
Hello, Brenda.
Excuse me.
Why is being a girl an insult?
So evolved!
Lisa, are you squishy
for this ding-dong?
Lisa, does that fat kid
like you?
Whatever we had,
it's in the past.
I think there's something
in the water in this town.
Oh, man.
On a playground I tripped
Then I saw you and flipped
He used flipped
with a double meaning!
Bastard!
Now I'm skippin'
And trippin' for you
He turned his suffering
into entertainment,
just like the Jewish people!
Nothing can ruin this moment.
Make way.
Dead gophers.
Nothing!
How can you be sleeping?!
Oh, thank God.
Meanwhile, Bart's teacher says
he has a flair for chemistry.
Why that little...
Wait. Flair?
Isn't that a good thing?
Yes. It's too good.
Why don't you ask him
what he's up to?
Because if he lies to me,
it's like a dagger in my heart.
What happens when,
I mean, if I ever lie to you?
Can you find out
what he's really up to?
- I will.
- See? That's a lie right there.
D'oh! Okay, I really will.
- That's also a lie.
- D'oh!
Fine.
I really, really, really will.
Finally, the truth.
Keeping promise.
Stupid tree house.
So far off the ground.
Dad, you haven't even
started to climb yet.
I have to visualize it first.
Thanks, guys.
No problem.
Why did we do that, Chief?
Fat man courtesy, Lou.
Fat man courtesy.
Son, how do I put this?
Are you breaking bad up here?
No, I'm not.
And if you're looking for meth,
go see Cletus.
What?!
Meth Life, proud sponsor
of the 2020 Opioid Olympics!
Ooh, that's street ready!
Dad, I'm just trying
to follow in your footsteps.
You work in science,
and I think that's really cool.
Wow, you've never
said that to me before.
Do you want to go to work
with me today?
You can help me
research my theory
that the chairs can go flat.
I'd like to, but I've got to do
some colloidal titration.
Marge, it's worse
than we thought.
He's speaking in tongues.
He's a religious weirdo.
The worst thing there is.
Cover your eyes, boys.
I'm about to flip Mr. Simpson
the Flanders finger.
You mean...
Yup, a thumbs-up
without a friendly wink.
You have a credit card?
Yeah, but no money.
Oh, a true jazz musician.
Just give the ice cream back.
No way. It was
really hard to scoop.
Prepare to have
your ears belted.
My funny valentine
Sweet, comic valentine
Nelson?
You make me smile
With my heart
Stop! Why are you doing this?
I don't know. There's no
good word for what I feel.
Scared and excited
at the same time.
There is a word, vulnerable.
Vulnerable?
Yup.
I always liked you,
but now I'm seeing you
in a new light.
Your looks are laughable
Unphotographable
But you're my favorite
Work of art
Art
Nailed it.
And so now
there's a jazz war over me.
It's pretty bad.
But it's pretty great.
Scotland once had two queens
fightin' over her.
Loser got Scotland.
Of course, Brendan
is the superior artist.
But that kind of intimidates me.
And Nelson's rough,
but he's sweet.
Plus he thinks I have dimples.
Dimples?
It's that serious?
- Aye.
- Let me give ye advice on love.
The Scottish national flower
is the thistle.
A humble weed.
Legend has it
that the Norse King Haakon
staged a surprise invasion.
But his barefooted army
stepped on thistles,
and their screams
awakened the sleepy Scots.
Many a Norwegian lass
lamented their dead lover
- on that glorious day.
- Willie,
someone spiked the teachers'
vodka with sulfuric acid.
Superintendent Chalmers
lost the tip of his tongue.
Kinner!
Lisa, this is a song about you.
A kid who's almost there.
And when you get there,
you'll blow the roof off.
Yeah, well,
I brought my washboard.
Nelson.
You took our washboard.
I got thongs to scrub.
I really can't believe
that this is a choice.
I mean, look at me.
And look at him.
And then look back at me.
Hmm, they're quiet.
Too quiet.
Now they're loud.
Too loud.
Now they're just right.
Too just right.
Are you sure
Bart's not planning anything?
A boy takes his cues
from his mother.
If I trust him,
then he'll be good.
Hey, don't knock
my mother's method...
complete abandonment
from age five.
The school talent show.
And on the back,
chemical equations.
Still think he's innocent?
We'll just have to go there
and see.
You wanted rock candy,
you got rock candy.
Brendan and Nelson are fighting.
I'm getting Daddy's gun
to under-arrest them.
Oh, no.
I'm gonna call you decrescendo,
'cause you're goin' down.
Nelson, that's clever.
Thanks. For you, I read a book.
All right, Ralphie,
easy, easy.
Give Daddy back his hat.
Oh, you missed everything,
just like Daddy.
So many clams.
Well, you're gonna look
very nice for the show tonight.
It doesn't matter how I look,
I'm not ready.
I've been so distracted
by those boys.
How did you choose Dad?
And never regret it?
Marge, I might've swallowed
a couple of your earrings.
Gotta go.
I do not want to know
how you got these back.
So, we're really doing it.
We're going to a talent show
where Bart is putting on
a chemistry demonstration.
Have I got that right?
If our faces
get melted off today,
I want the last thing Bart sees
to be us believing in him.
Fine, fine.
Let me just finish my will.
And...
Oh, it's good
to have that taken care of.
Nelson? A word?
Take five, Martin.
I'm not even in your act.
I said take five.
Nelson, I cherish
our unhealthy relationship.
Especially the fact
that I can tell you the truth.
Kiddo, you're not a singer.
Okay, fine, I won't sing.
But I'll still perform.
That's how much I want
to hold your stupid hand.
You're up, Nelson.
Hello.
I'm the school bully.
Don't be a dingus.
I'm the next Charlie Mingus.
Could I really choose him?
My choice is clear. Brendan.
Ooh, yeah,
I feel the groove.
Next contestant,
Brendan Beiderbecke.
And Brendan wins!
Not so fast.
We have a disqualification.
This young man does not
live in the district.
Right, his home is 50 feet
into West Springfield,
which means he will be
transferred to a school
three buses and a long bike ride
away from here.
- Brendan...
- No, Lisa.
I can't put you through that.
I guess this
relationship is over
until this town
invests in mass transit.
I'll never see him again.
Lisa, I'm glad
you didn't choose me.
No woman is worth
learning music.
All this time
I've been choosing jazz
over doing my reps.
Well, my reps never let me down.
Lift weights, get dates.
Well, I guess I'm alone
for the moment.
And I like it.
- Good for Lisa.
- She's better off alone.
She doesn't need a man.
Wait a minute, everybody.
Even though
the most interesting and
emotionally compelling part
is over, we still
have one performer
who says he will
blow you away.
So please welcome the original
Dennis the Chemist,
Bart Simpson.
Drop the beaker, Screwy Pasteur.
No.
I wasn't doing anything bad.
Pour the beaker and you'll see.
We are not gonna let you
mix those chemicals.
We got a tip
from an anonymous source
named Seymour Skinner.
Do you even know
what anonymous means?
Helpful?
Mom, I'm innocent.
You believe me, don't you?
Oh, if he's lying,
I'll never forgive him.
If he's telling the truth,
he'll never forgive me.
Glad I'm not you.
Bart, sweetie,
I'll pour the beaker for you.
He's innocent. But then
who put the sulfuric acid
in Superintendent Chalmers'
drink?
I did.
- Willie! Why?
- Why?
Because, Seymour,
I was trying to kill you.
Well, that's okay. Good man.
- But...
- Quiet, Seymour.
The man's got a dream.
I never doubted you.
Well, you should have.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
This episode was supposed
to have been a parody
of Moonlight,
not La La Land.
Moonlight?
But none of us have seen it.
We have the DVD.
We could watch it tonight.
Either that
or X-Men Apocalypse.
X-Men!
I'd like to see Moonlight.