(SINGING) The Simpsons
(SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
(HORN BELLOWING)
(BEEPS)
(PLAYING DIFFERENT TUNE)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(HONKING)
D'oh!
(EXCLAIMING)
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
(ALL GASP)
(ALL SCREAM)
ANNOUNCER: You're listening to
Nationwide Public Radio.
It's now 2:00.
Time for Verbal Tea,
with Amy Levine-Gonzalez.
Oh, boy! This is what
sunny Sunday
afternoons are for.
WOMAN: Today,
we'll discuss a dying form
of Peruvian banjo music,
with Dartmouth banjologist,
Stefan Whitmore.
(PLAYING)
It's just...
It's not that good.
In our second hour,
humorist David Sedaris
takes a wry look
at overcrowding
in America's prisons.
Prison overcrowding?
I've got
a solution for that.
(MIMICKING MACHINE GUN)
(SCREAMS)
Oh, my God!
(MIMICS AMBULANCE SIREN)
U-S-A! U-S-A!
But, first, we're giving
away tickets
to the latest film
by acclaimed
director Mladzieul Klernt.
(GASPS) Her films
are so lyrical.
The phone lines
are gonna be jammed.
Winner of the Romanian
Film Festival's prestigious
Golden Bucket...
Holy crap!
Someone's actually calling!
(MEOWING)
(HUMMING)
Hmm.
Hey! I won four
free movie tickets and
it starts in half an hour!
Free movie tickets?
I feel like Roger Ebert
or his kiss-ass new partner.
But we don't have
a sitter for Maggie.
She'll be fine here
under the watchful eye
of Grandma Shark Week.
(ROARS)
A TV shark
is not a babysitter.
HOMER: How about this guy?
Ha!
Homer!
(NED HUMMING)
Howdy, Homer.
You here for a viewing
of my shampooing?
Shut up, Flanders.
I need a favor.
Would you mind watching
Maggie for a while?
It would only be until later.
Sorry, but I promised
to rewind videotapes
for the poor.
Come on, Flanders.
Doesn't that Bible
of yours
say to love
thy neighbor?
Why won't you love me?
All right, neighbor.
l'll babysit.
Thanks, Ned.
You wear a bathing
suit in the bathtub?
Yeah, so I can't see
my own shrinky-dink.
Makes sense.
(AIR WHOOSHING)
Instead of video games,
they have weird,
free newspapers.
Hmm.
Mom, am I "butch" or a "fem"?
Honey, you can be
anything you wanna be.
Ha!
This theater sucks.
My seat's uncomfortable.
The screen's only
half a screen,
And that guy's
eating an apple.
Would you care
for a segment?
Yes.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(SPEAKING ALBANIAN)
What language is this?
Gibby-Gabby?
It's Albanian,
but the producers
added subtitles
to make it commercial.
Mom, I don't wanna read.
It's the weekend. (GROANS)
I've had enough.
I'm leaving. (GRUNTS)
(SQUEAKING)
Oh, I'm stuck!
Why did I eat
that apple segment?
Oh, oh, oh.
Sorry, Maggie.
That's something
to collect, not enjoy.
It's one of my
Humble Figurines.
He scampered out
of Parade Magazine
and into my knickknack nook,
and, well, his little
buddies soon followed.
You like them, huh?
Come on, I'll show
you the other 300.
(GASPS)
How could this have...
Oh. (SIGHS)
I feel so much empathy
for those villagers.
They had to drink
their own tears.
I was so bored,
I cut the ponytail
Off the guy
sitting in front of us.
"Look at me.
I'm a grad student.
I'm 30 years old,
"and I made
$600 last year."
Bart, don't make fun
of grad students.
They just made
a terrible life choice.
Judas-bear,
you're not touching
your Last Supper.
I can't eat because
my conscience is heavy.
Boys, enough of
your shenanigans.
It's bedtime.
BOTH: Mmm!
Ned, let me
give you
a little something
for babysitting.
I can't take money
from a neighbor.
Although business
at the Leftorium's
been pretty slow
since that big chain
store came to town.
(SIGHS)
You've got
a big house, Ned.
If you need
extra money,
why don't you
rent out a room?
Well, it might be
fun to be a landlord...
Land fella.
There's only one Lord.
I need a place
to crash
while my mom's
drying out.
Well, I'd love
to help you out,
but you do have
to be over 18.
I am. Check out my ID.
Wait, this is my license.
No, it's not,
you hump.
(RAVING)
Well, I do appreciate
that you've got
a cashier's check.
Now, do you
have any pets?
(RAVING)
(GASPS)
I am Katja and
this is Vicki.
We make much study
at community college.
We're, like, here
about the room.
We moved out
of our dorm
Because it was,
like, co-ed.
Sometimes we saw (GASPS)
the boys in their robes.
You poor thing.
Now, I've heard
about those robes.
Flapping everywhere.
Girls, welcome
to your very own
Ned and Breakfast.
Silly talk means "yes"?
(BOTH GIGGLE)
Here's your room, ladies.
You can catch
some z's while
you earn those degrees.
You rhyme like
Snoopy-Dogg.
Well, thank you.
I know what
we can ask Jeeves.
Why does he suck?
Hey! A banner ad!
Sexyslumberparty.com?
It's flashing.
We better click it.
(BOTH GIGGLING)
Katja, do you think
anyone's watching?
If they are,
they will see us
explore our sexhood
without restraint.
Hey, this is one of
those dirty websites.
Two girls?
Who would want that?
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
(BOTH GASP)
You may
inside come.
I got phi beta cappuccinos
for Ned's pre-meds.
BOTH: Flanders?
That's odd.
I could've sworn
I just heard someone
shriek my name.
BART: You heard nothing!
That's better.
(GIRLS GIGGLING)
(LAUGHS)
Spank me again with
little boy's picture.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
What are you kids
laughing at?
And if you say
Jimmy Fallon,
I'll know you're lying.
(GASPS) Scantily clad co-eds?
Why, you little... (GRUNTS)
(GAGS)
To have
a libido...
Dad, look
who's in there.
(GASPS) Flanders?
(GURGLING)
He doesn't
even know
what's going on!
Wait'll I tell
everyone about this.
I'll feel important
without drinking.
That'll be weird.
HOMER: What a combination.
Hot chicks and
stupid Flanders.
(BOTH GIGGLING)
And you say
Mr. Flanders remains
completely ignorant
of their
dot-Kama-sutra?
Yup, and nobody's
telling him.
Not even
his good buddy, God!
Boy, nothing is sexier
than still photos
in a girlie magazine.
Whoa!
Sensual, isn't it?
And the best part is,
Stupid Flanders
doesn't even know
it's happening
in his stupid house.
Hence my nickname,
Stupid Flanders.
(HOMER LAUGHS)
(CHURCH MUSIC PLAYING)
Hey, Moses.
Are you a loser?
"Yes, l am, Homer."
(DOOR OPENS)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATION)
How are those
two comely boarders
of yours, Ned?
Well, Mel,
they're swell.
Oh, yeah.
They're just what
my laptop needed.
(GIRLS GIGGLING)
Son, I need to pee,
but I can't
stop watching.
Fetch me a bottle.
Come on, Dad.
I've seen you hit
the toilet from here.
What are you
two doing?
(GASPS) Uh...
We're watching
the latest photos
from Mars.
Ho-ho! Great stuff.
Worth every billion.
(GASPS)
Bart, turn away
from that screen and
look out the window!
No problemo.
(BOTH GIGGLING)
(GASPS)
It's happening
in Ned's house!
Why would
he allow that?
Well, that's obvious.
He doesn't even know.
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
Come on.
You tell him
right now.
Ned, Homer
has something
to tell you.
(GROANS) Uh...
I'm thinking about
getting a yogurt franchise.
It's called Plops.
It's... (SCREAMS)
You know
what I mean.
(MOANS)
Okay. Flanders, you see...
You soft-core
sophomores took advantage
of my trustful nature
and sullied the Internet
by putting pornography on it!
NED: Get out!
(BOTH GASP)
(ALL CHEERING)
The whole town
is laughing at me
behind my back.
(SIGHS) I guess
you're the only
real friend I have.
Are you kidding?
Homer's the one
what wised us up
to the sexy goings-on.
Homer,
is this true?
Ned, I had no choice.
It was just so funny.
The Bible says,
"Cast your bread
upon the waters."
But all I got
was a bunch
of soggy bread.
Mmm. Soggy...
Don't say it, Homer!
This is not the time!
...bread.
Mmm.
What's wrong,
Daddy?
Well, Toddy,
you know how I said
our friends are
like the Canaanites?
Today I realized
they're more like
the Midianites.
(BOTH GASP)
(SIGHS) I wish
we lived in a place more
like the America of yesteryear
that only exists
in the brains
of us Republicans.
"Made in Humbleton, PA."
I don't usually make
big life decisions
based on things
stamped on things
that I bought
at a garage sale,
But corn dog it, boys,
it's time for a change!
(BOTH EXCLAIM)
Dad, I don't think
you realize what
you've done.
You've totally
humiliated the best friend
the Simpsons ever had.
You're right. But you know
who the real victim
is here? Ned.
That's what
we've been trying
to tell you!
Oh, yeah.
What's this?
"Goodbye, Springfield"?
NED: "The Flanders family has
pulled up stakes.
"You have laughed at us
for the last-diddly-ast time."
"Last-diddly-ast"?
(WAILING)
He's gone!
And it's all
someone's fault!
Well, Homer,
you've driven away
the best neighbor
a family could ever want.
But at least
we have a chance
to start fresh.
So let's be
on our best
behavior, okay?
Don't worry, Marge.
I've taken every precaution.
This is so humiliating.
Well, at least
your name's
on the bowl.
Hmm.
(GROWLING)
(BOTH GROWLING)
I submit! I submit!
Hmm.
(DOOR BELL RINGS)
Hi, I'm Homer Simpson.
I live next door.
So, is that
your whistle?
Damn straight.
Clay Roberts.
I coach wrestling,
so everybody
calls me Coach.
Listen, neighboreeno,
I want to start
our relationship
off on the right foot,
so if you need anything,
anything at all...
What jag-off left this here?
(GASPS)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(TUBA PLAYING)
(BARKING)
Boys, we're home.
(MARGE HUMMING)
(SINGING) Kick it
(LOUD MUSIC PLAYING)
(WAILING)
That's coming
from next door!
Don't worry, I'll
straighten things out
with Coach Clay.
We're good buddies.
We play this game
called "Who can
punch the softest?"
And he always lets me win.
Hey, Coach,
do you mind turning
down the music?
My baby's trying
to take a nap.
That's too bad
because my twins
are just waking up, dude.
Encourage me.
Looking good.
Feel the burn.
Louder!
You're a god!
I can't think of anymore.
Just say, "Go, 90, 90!"
Go, go, go!
Say it like
you mean it,
you wuss!
Howdy, Humbletonian.
Picnics and
Pixy Stix!
I'll see your smile
and raise you a wink
and a giggle.
This town is sweeter
than a cake made of pie.
Even the dogs
curb themselves.
Everyone new begins here,
in the dimple department.
NED: (GASPS)
Can I start yesterday?
There is one personal matter.
I'm afraid
you'll have to lose
the hippie lip.
(GASPS) Get rid
of Dr. Fuzzenstein?
Why, I couldn't dream
of thinking about considering.
(SIGHS) I'll see
what I can do.
Very good.
Until then,
you can wear this.
(GRUNTS)
(MOANS)
Daddy, why do you
have to shave
your nose-neighbor?
You know what?
I'm not gonna.
My moustache
has the right to life.
It's my body and my choice!
(SINGING) Bad Company
I can't deny
(ALL GASP)
Bad, bad company
Until the day I die
Oh, yeah
Ooh
This is for you.
(MUSIC PLAYING ON TV)
ANNOUNCER: Tonight on
"Celebrity Chop Shop,"
we sell the parts
off Jason Bateman's Bentley.
What did you do
to my car?
Dude, you've been
chop shopped!
Why would you do that?
How am I gonna get home?
Chop shop!
(ZAPPING)
Huh?
(GASPS)
Hey! You knocked
out my power.
How am I supposed
to eat without
watching TV?
Yeah. Something
tells me you won't
starve, huh?
(GROANS)
Huh, chief?
When are you gonna
stop poking me?
Will it be soon?
Relax, dumbass.
By the way.
I borrowed some gas
from your car, you dumb-ass!
But I siphoned that
gas from Flanders.
Flanders.
What are you doing,
reminiscing?
Like a woman?
Like a woman
who's made the biggest
mistake of her life!
(WAILS)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
(GRUNTS)
(GASPS) Homer?
What are you
doing here?
I was just driving around
the Mid-Atlantic states,
ringing doorbells
at random.
And I just...
(WAILING)
Who am I fooling
with my awesome lies?
I want you to come
back to Springfield!
Why? So you can make me
a laughingstock again?
No. I want
to make you
a respecting-stock.
I don't know
if you've noticed.
But I borrowed
a lot of your stuff
over the years.
Well, that is true.
In fact...
Shut up, Flanders.
But some things
I could never
take from you.
Your kindness,
your gentle spirit,
and your infinite patience
with a big, dumb jerk like me.
Ned, I don't deserve you
as a neighbor,
but will you forgive
a young, handsome fool
and come home?
Homer, that's really touching.
But my boys and I
are trying to make
a new start,
and people here
are a little bit
more my cup of...
(INDISTINCT TALKING)
Are there letters
to pick up or no letters
to pick up?
I can't tell and I'm
looking right at it.
Ooh, that tears it!
Boys, put on
your goody two-shoes.
We're moving
back to Springfield!
But l have
a girlfriend.
Now you've got
a pen-pal.
Yay!
So you see,
Mr. Roberts,
I really would
like my house back.
Really? Well,
that's too bad
because I'm not leaving.
See, I like this place,
and I've already
got fatso, here,
broken in.
Ain't that right,
fatso? Huh?
(GRUNTS)
Yeah. lam a little pudgy.
You got me. Yeah.
Now, Coach,
I've tried to be
Christian and respectful.
But l guess
I'm just gonna
have to point out
your $200,000
check bounced.
Legally, I still
own this house.
Yeah? Tell it
to the Marines!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
Okay! Okay, I give. Ow!
(GRUNTS)
Ow!
Why did you do that?
I was begging for mercy!
I saw my advantage
and I took it.
That's what heroes do.
Okay, Ned. Get ready
for your welcome
home surprise!
(GASPS)
Homer, did you steal
the organ from
the church?
Maybe. We don't know
that for sure.
Well, you gotta
take it back.
After the party.
(PLAYING)
It sure is great
to look down my nose
at everybody again.
Mind if I waggle
my finger a little bit?
Go nuts.
Flanders? Okay, that's it.
It's really irritating!
(GRUNTS)