♪ The Simpsons ♪
-(chalk screeches)
-(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(tires screeching)
(horn honks)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
MAN: Ladies and gentlemen,
it's Up Late with McBain.
I'm your announcer
Makrokuffen Fuerer Wolfkassel.
And here's McBain.
(applause)
Ja, and thank you, ja.
That's nice.
Let's say hello
to my music guy, Scoey.
(applause)
That is some outfit, Scoey.
It makes you look
like a homosexual.
(booing)
Whoa, maybe you all
are homosexuals too.
(booing)
This is horrible.
The Fox network
has sunk to a new low.
Lisa, you got a letter.
It's from my pen pal, Anya.
"Dear Lisa, as I write this,
I am very sad.
Our president
has been overthrown, and--"
MAN: "Replaced by
the benevolent General Krull.
"All hail Krull
and his glorious new regime.
Sincerely, little girl."
Oh.
You got a letter, too, Bart.
(gasps)
♪ The Itchy and Scratchy Show ♪
(screams)
(laughing)
Bart, what's wrong
with you?
Oh, my God!
Someone's trying to kill me!
Oh, wait. It's for Bart.
MARGE: This one's done
in different handwriting.
Oh, I wrote that one
after Bart somehow
put this tattoo on my butt.
(laughter)
Ha-ha.
But who'd want to hurt me?
I'm this century's
Dennis the Menace.
It's probably the person
you least suspect.
That's good, Dad.
I say we call Matlock.
He'll find the culprit.
It's probably
that evil Gavin Macleod
or George "Goober" Lindsey.
Grandpa, Matlock's not real.
Neither are my teeth,
but I can still eat
corn on the cob
if someone cuts it off
and smushes it
into a fine paste.
Now that's good eatin'!
I checked around.
The girls are calling you
"Fatty fat-fat-fat,"
and Nelson's planning
to pull down your pants,
but nobody's trying to kill you.
Oh, that's good.
(girls chanting)
Fatty fat fat-fat.
Fatty fatty fat-fat.
All right. This is dedicated
to Bart Simpson
with the message,
"I am coming to kill you
slowly and painfully."
(maniacal laughter)
♪ Wipeout ♪
♪♪ ("Wipeout" plays)
-Bart, I'm going to get you--
-(gasps)
...some ice cream at the store,
since I'm saving so much money
on diet cola.
-(Bart gasps)
-Say your prayers, Simpson.
Because the schools can't
force you like they should.
Maude, these new finger razors
make hedge trimming
as much fun
as sitting through church.
You're going to be
my murder victim, Bart,
in our school production
of Lizzy Borden
starring Martin Prince
as Lizzy.
40 whacks
with a wet noodle, Bart.
I'd like to help you, ma'am,
but I'm afraid there's no law
against mailing
threatening letters.
I'm pretty sure there is.
Hah! The day I take cop lessons
from Ma Kettle--
Hey, she's right, Chief.
Well, shut my mouth.
It's also illegal
to put squirrels down your pants
for the purposes of gambling.
(laughter)
Boys, knock it off.
(squirrels chittering)
Bart, I figured it out.
Who's someone you've been making
irritating phone calls to
for years?
-Linda Lavin?
-No, someone who didn't deserve it.
Hello. Moe?
We know you're
the one behind this,
so knock it off
or we're going to the cops.
No, no.
I'll take care of it.
Okay, it's over.
Get them out of here.
All right, andale, andale!
You're out there somewhere.
But where? Where?
(thunderclap)
(laughing)
"Dear 'Life
in these United States,'
a funny thing
happened to me..."
Use a pen, Sideshow Bob.
Parole granted.
Next up for parole,
Bob Terwilliger,
A.K.A. Sideshow Bob.
Take care, Snake.
May the next time we meet
be under more felicitous
circumstances.
-Gah?
-Take care.
Bah.
Sideshow Bob has no decency.
He called me Chief "Pig-ham."
(audience laughing)
Now I get it. Good.
Sideshow Bob tried to kill me
on our honeymoon.
(audience murmurs)
How many people in this court
are thinking of killing her
right now?
Be honest.
(gasps)
Ah, she's always leaving
the toilet seat up.
Robert, if released,
would you pose any threat
to one Bart Simpson?
Bart Simpson?
Ha! The spirited little scamp
who twice foiled my evil schemes
and sent me to this dank,
urine-soaked hellhole?
We object to the term
urine-soaked hellhole
when you could have said
pee-pee soaked heckhole.
Cheerfully withdrawn.
What about that tattoo
on your chest?
Doesn't it say,
"Die, Bart, Die"?
No. That's German
for vie, Bart, vie.
(laughing)
No one who speaks German
can be an evil man.
Parole granted.
ERNEST:
Wow! Public library.
Let's stay here
for a while, Vern.
(loud laughter)
(coughing)
That man is so rude.
Yeah.
(laughing)
If you don't mind,
we're trying
to watch the mov--
ERNEST:
Hey, Vern.
Help me get my head
out of this toilet.
(toilet flushes)
(loud laughing)
Oh, really, now.
That's too much.
Ah! Sideshow Bob!
-You wrote me those letters.
-You awful man.
Stay away from my son.
Oh, I'll stay away
from your son, all right.
-Stay away forever.
-Oh, no.
Wait a minute.
That's no good.
Oh!
Wait.
I've got a good one now.
Marge, say,
"Stay away from my son" again.
-No!
-(groaning)
And turn and flex
and shake and bounce.
Now Sideshow Bob can't get in
without me knowing.
And once a man is
in your home,
anything you do to him
is nice and legal.
Is that so?
Oh, Flanders?
Won't you join me in my kitchen?
(sinister laughing)
(door opens)
Uh, doesn't work
if you invite 'em.
Hi-dily hey!
-Go home.
-Toodle-ly doo.
Now, don't you fret.
When I'm through,
he won't set foot
in this town again.
I can be very,
very persuasive.
(gun cocks)
(siren wails in distance)
-Come on. Leave town.
-No.
I'll be your friend.
-Oh, you're mean.
The following
neighborhood residents
will not be killed by me--
Ned Flanders,
Maude Flanders.
Oh, isn't that nice?
Homer Simpson,
Marge Simpson,
Lisa Simpson,
that little baby Simpson.
That is all.
Woo-hoo!
Did you hear, Bart?
Oh.
Don't worry, Mrs. Simpson.
We've helped hundreds
of people in danger.
We'll give you
a new name,
a new job,
new identities.
Whoo! I want to be John Elway.
(crowd cheers)
ANNOUNCER:
Elway takes the snap
and runs it in for a touchdown!
Thanks to Elway's patented
last-second magic,
the final score
of Super Bowl XXX:
Denver 7, San Francisco, 56.
-Woo-hoo!
-I don't think this is such a good idea.
This isn't just
because of Sideshow Bob.
It's a chance to turn around
all our stinking lives.
I'll be Gus,
the loveable chimney sweep.
Clean as a whistle, sharp as a thistle.
Best in all Westminster. Yeah!
-Shut up, boy.
-We have places
your family can hide
in peace and security.
Cape Fear, Terror Lake,
New Horror Field, Screamville.
Ooh! Ice Creamville.
-No. Screamville.
-(shrieks)
Tell you what, sir.
From now on, you'll be
Homer Thompson at Terror Lake.
Let's just practice
a bit, hmm?
When I say,
"Hello, Mr. Thompson,"
-you'll say, "Hi."
-Check.
Hello, Mr. Thompson.
Remember now,
your name is Homer Thompson.
-I got ya.
-Hello, Mr. Thompson.
(groaning)
Now, when I say,
"Hello, Mr. Thompson"
and press down on your foot,
you smile and nod.
-No problem.
-Hello, Mr. Thompson.
I think he's talking to you.
-Here you go.
-Oh, what a cute convertible.
You guys at the Bureau
thought of everything.
Hey, look,
the F.B.I. Light Opera Society
sings The Complete
Gilbert and Sullivan.
♪ Three little maids
from school are we ♪
♪ Pert as a schoolgirl
well can be ♪
♪ Filled to the brim
with girlish glee ♪
♪ Three little girls
from school ♪
♪ Everything
is a source of fun ♪
♪ Ha-ha-ha-ha,
ha-ha, ha-ha ♪
(laughing)
(thud)
Lousy speed bumps.
Ooh!
Oh!
(slurping)
Uh, this coffee's too hot.
SIDESHOW BOB: Ow!
Hey, kids, want to drive
through that cactus patch?
-Yeah!
SIDESHOW BOB: No.
Well, two against one.
SIDESHOW BOB:
Oh! Ow! Oh! Ow!
Ow! Ow! Ow!
♪ The Thompsons ♪
Wow, a houseboat.
You know,
the great thing is,
if you don't like
your neighbors,
you can just pull up the anchor
and sail someplace else.
(laughter)
(groans)
-(blow landing)
-(faint groaning)
Homer, where's the dog?
Uh, I tied him up
out back.
(panting)
(sighs)
We've left it all behind.
How can you make
a clean break
with your life?
Relax, Marge.
I tied up all the loose ends
before we left.
Hello!
You have my pills!
I'm cold,
and there are wolves after me.
(howling in distance)
SIDESHOW BOB:
Hello, Bart.
(screaming)
Down here, Bart.
Ow!
What do you want?
Surely there's no harm
in laying in the middle
of a public street.
(loud groaning)
-(trumpeting)
-Not the elephants! No!
-(crunching)
-(groaning)
-(splatting)
(crunching and splatting)
-(groaning)
-(splatting and crunching)
(groaning)
(bird chirping)
(glugging)
Ah!
Mom, Dad, I saw Sideshow Bob,
and he threatened to kill me!
Bart, don't interrupt.
Homer, this is serious.
Oh, it is not.
Roman numeral III:
surprise boy in bed--
(slurping)
...and, uh, disembowel him.
No, I don't like
that "bowel" in there.
Gut him.
Ah! Le mot juste!
(moaning)
(creaking)
Bart, you want some brownie
before you go to bed?
(screaming)
Come on, let me cut you
a brownie while they're still hot.
Dad, I'm kind of edgy
right now.
I'd appreciate you
not coming in my room
screaming and brandishing
a butcher knife.
Why?
Oh, right.
This Sideshow Bob thing.
I'm sorry, boy.
Bart, you want to see my new
chainsaw and hockey mask?
-(screaming)
-(saw whirring)
Oh, sorry.
What am I thinking?
(water gurgling)
(groans)
(door creaking)
Hello, Bart.
Mom! Dad!
Your family can't help you now.
(grunting)
-(snoring)
-Oh, no! Dad's been drugged.
No, he hasn't.
Uh-oh.
(crackling)
Ohh!
-Oh, yeah.
-Well, Bart.
Any last requests?
Well, there is one, but...
-Nah.
-No, go on.
Well, you have such
a beautiful voice.
Guilty as charged.
Uh-huh. Anyway, I was wondering
if you could sing
the entire score
of the H.M.S. Pinafore.
Very well, Bart.
I shall send you to heaven
before I send you to hell.
And a-two and a-three and...
♪ We sail the ocean blue ♪
♪ And our saucy ship's
a beauty ♪
♪ We are sober men,
and true ♪
♪ And attentive
to our duty ♪
♪ I'm poor little buttercup ♪
♪ Poor little buttercup ♪
♪ Though I could
never tell why ♪
♪ What, never?
No, never ♪
♪ What, never? ♪
♪ Hardly ever ♪
♪ He's hardly ever
sick at sea ♪
♪ For he himself
has said it ♪
♪ And it's clearly
to his credit ♪
♪ That he is an Englishman ♪
♪ He remains ♪
♪ An Englishman ♪
And now, the final curtain.
(guns cocking)
Hold it right there,
Sideshow Bob.
You're under arrest.
By Lucifer's beard!
Uh, yeah. It's a good thing
you drifted by this brothel.
I knew I had to buy some time.
So I asked him
to sing the score
from the H.M.S. Pinafore.
Ooh, a plan fiendishly clever
in its in-tric-acies.
Take him away, boys.
Hey, I'm the chief here.
Bake him away, toys.
What did you say, Chief?
Do what the kid says.
Hmm. It's so good
to be home again.
Look what happened
without my pills!
(gasping)
Bart, run upstairs,
get Grampa's medicine.
Not so fast. I want to court
this fair young maiden.
GRAMPA: There's something
you should know about me.
JASPER: I've got Steve
and Eydie tickets.
I'm all yours!
(kissing sound)
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.