Am I the only one who remembered
daylight savings time?
Been here 17 years.
Been on the HBO, the Netflix
and one House Hunters
International.
But now I got two new hotshot
lawyers working my case.
No sign of a struggle,
no DNA evidence in the cabin
and no attractive young woman
declared missing.
I think there's a very real
chance no one was murdered.
I was on the jury
that convicted him.
Had we known
there was no victim,
we might not have voted guilty.
I repeat, might not.
Fantastic news.
We got picked up
for a second season.
And my appeal?
Mostly to women 25 to 54.
You mean appeal appeal.
Oh, well, that's not happenin.
What is it, sweetie?
Are you gassy?
When is she not gassy?
Baby burn.
If only you could talk.
It's the people who can't speak
that have so much to share.
Or maybe not.
Wait a minute.
I think there's a show
about teaching a baby
sign language.
I could finally talk to my baby.
Maggie, we have a fun week
of repetitive drills ahead.
I wonder what the kid
was so upset about.
Don't worry, little baby.
I'll be okay till morning.
Now I'm screwed.
Congratulations, babies, we've
learned some great signs today.
I hope you don't want more,
because we're all done,
because our government funding
ran out.
Okay, Maggie.
Do you want more
or are you all done?
More or all done?
Oh, great,
now I'm out of Cheerios.
Oh, I thought
they were doughnuts
that were really far away.
More?
More? Aw, that's 22.
You busted.
Always say all done
on a hard 17.
Can you say that? Hard 17?
Don't teach her gambling.
Let's go, dealer. One more hand.
Aw, sir, I don't want
to take your money.
Remember to make sure
that the warriors you kill
are actually dead.
I recommend stabbing,
dissolving in acid,
dynamite in the butt...
Jason. You're late for dinner!
Ma, I'm talking
to 30 million people!
Boil them, let pigs eat them,
Kentucky-fry them...
Don't play that in front of Maggie.
She'll have nightmares.
Suit yourself.
This is more like it.
Hansel shoved the blood-covered
witch into the oven.
I'm burning alive,
screamed the witch.
More? More?
You want more book?
My baby's communicating with me.
Let me test it out.
Do you like peas?
Do you like applesauce?
Do you like Star Wars movies?
What about Baby Yoda?
This is so exciting.
Look, look what Maggie can do.
Maggie, do you want more?
That's my girl.
Look, everyone. She's doing it.
Yeah, that's great.
Dad, check this out.
He only sings
when we're not looking.
Classic aggravation humor.
A dancing frog.
Bet that would cook up nice.
You're missing a crucial moment
in Maggie's development
because of these.
From now on,
we're gonna limit the time
we spend looking
at our stupid phones.
Yeah, that's great.
And then we'll have
a conversation.
Steve Jobs wouldn't let
his children use his iPads,
and he was a great parent,
I assume.
From now on, everyone gets a
half hour of screen time a week.
- And that's it.
- Really, Marge?
You think you can give up
your Pinterest?
My cake fails are important.
If people fail at cake,
they need to be told.
Okay. Half an hour a week
for everyone, including me.
I believe there's something
you're forgetting.
And? And?
No more screens. You too.
Here at Messages, we treat
your addiction humanely,
with hiking and biking and
human equivalents of things
that work with rats.
And all we ask for
is your brain when you die.
Well, let's pray this place
won't be necessary.
All right, let's round 'em up.
Okay. It's been one week.
Let me check your screen times.
They're really low.
I'm so proud of you.
I forgot how great it was
to crack the spine of a book.
I'm calmer, I'm happier,
I'm seeing things
I never saw before.
Did you know our second dog
is a cat?
Sorry, last time I was here,
I left my screen time
reversal wrench.
I could just get that back.
You guys have been having this
man dial back your screen time?
Oops. Looks like
I just lost a contract.
Well, anybody want to buy a van?
It only has two miles on it.
What the...?
Okay, close your eyes.
I'm putting these someplace
you'll never find them.
No cell phone. Stuck at work
all day with nothing to do.
Lookin' at my feet.
Hey, big guy.
What, are you bored?
Why don't you do
the Daily Jumble in the paper?
Unscramble the words
to solve a funny riddle.
Oh, that's what it is.
I thought the proofreader
had a stroke.
Let's see.
D-D-A.
Dad.
Dad. I got something!
For the first time ever,
I solved a puzzle.
Dad ate all the pie.
Call the newspaper.
Tell them someone has solved it.
And get me some pie.
I love not using a phone.
It's made me much more
in tune with the world.
It's like my senses
are heightened.
Okay, Maggie, time to go.
Say goodbye to your aunts.
So cute.
What's she saying?
She always sleeps so good
when she's here.
Careful. If we enter
the Martian atmosphere
at too steep an angle,
we'll burn up.
Tell my family I love them.
They know that, Steve.
They know.
Bart has to use
his imagination.
This is Jupiter One.
Do you copy?
I copy.
What are you doing?
I'm talking to Jupiter One.
Oh, I'll show you Jupiter One.
Jupiter One to mission control.
Firing photon torpedoes.
I'm doing a very important
two-page paper.
Do you have any way to find a
book without using a computer?
Well, the old card catalogue
is in the basement.
Bang on this pot to scare
the possums away.
Okay.
Old card stock.
So tactile.
Look, this one
has an old handwritten note.
Dear Reader...
Ooh, that's me.
See also, Lost Wax Technique.
I will see also.
N-J-X-I.
Jinx.
P-I-U-Q. Quip.
I'm solving words
I don't even know.
Jumble boogie,
doo-doo-doo, doo-doo-doo
Get down, get down
With the goobie,
doo-doo-doo, doo-doo-doo
Unjumbled that is boogie
Doo-doo-doo, doo-doo-doo,
solve a jumble
In your face, world,
I'm so humble
Now, watch me twirl
Okay, okay.
I need the recipe
for puttanesca sauce.
Can't go online.
No problem.
I've got cookbooks.
Padma Lakshmi's Hot and Zesty.
Tiffany Haddish's
Fun with Radishes.
I made 14 of those,
they weren't that fun.
I know who to call.
Hello?
What's the recipe
for puttanesca sauce?
Oh, you want-a the recipe?
Sure, sure, get a pencil.
Step-a one, you come here.
Step-a two,
you pay for it.
Step-a three,
I put it on-a some pasta.
And that's-a the recipe!
Oh, what a great day.
Oh, you said it.
I spent five minutes today
just looking at the sun.
Hey, where's Mom?
And why do I hear clicking
from this closet?
Hold on a beat.
Just hold on.
Who was the one who said
no screen time?
Who?
It was you.
I know.
I have a problem.
So, I'm signing us
all up for a month
at that screen addiction
rehab center.
But we're not addicted, you are!
That's exactly
what an addict would say.
Or a normal person.
That's also what
an addict would say.
Well, what
wouldn't an addict say?!
Not that, that's for sure.
We'll all go there
starting tomorrow.
And I'll watch the pets.
I brought a bunch
of them inside.
I'm the beta.
Are we there yet?
- Are we there yet?
- Knock off that racket!
I said knock it off!
Mom's got the problem.
How come we're stuck in...
paradise?
Oh, Zen gardens, infinity pool?
Dr. Drew on call?
I'm just here because
I can't stop Fruit Ninja.
Die, mangoes, die!
If this is an addiction center,
I'm hooked.
Welcome to Messages.
I am Dr. Lund.
Doc, this prison is great.
Nothing but the best
for my family.
I just have one question.
How much does this place cost?
Your stay is entirely
funded by donations
from tech billionaires,
who feel guilty
that their sleek, disruptive
technology put you here.
It's free?
Kids, we've found
our summer home.
The adults will
reconnect with healthier,
time-tested alternatives
like eating,
drinking, fornicating,
relentless hide-and-seek,
the braiding of hair,
listening
to Dana Gould's podcast.
Four people suffocated in the
Creature from the Black Lagoon's
suit until they got it right.
At least,
I'm guessing that's true.
And you, young man, instead of
playing first-person shooters,
we are going to put
a real rifle in your hands.
Take that, Second Amendment!
It's time to start
healing, Marge.
I love your accent.
I didn't know I had one.
This is our one computer,
on which you can say
auf wiedersehen forever
to your old online life.
Farewell, Instagram,
Facebook and NextDoor.
You all entertained me
and scared me.
Yes, Marge, yes.
Cut forever the puppet strings
that have made you
dance like
a psychotic Pinocchio.
Facebook accounts
cannot be deleted.
Do not try. Do not try.
What is wrong, Homer?
Why the pickle puss?
I don't know if I can live in a
world without online solitaire.
I have an answer for you.
It's sealed.
I will open the plastic.
The box is shut.
I will open the box.
Could you...?
I will deal the cards.
- And also...?
- I will play the solitaire!
I need a jack, I need a jack.
I used my phone for everything.
Except to call the parents
who gave it to me.
You can call them now.
Hello, Dad?
You don't say.
What did he say?
He hates me.
Okay, okay. Let's just talk.
Any subject...
except video games.
A tear rolled down my face,
as my avatar did the electric
shuffle on her corpse.
Yes!
That game is awesome!
I'm losing control,
but that's all right.
Today's therapist has
many effective options.
The gas is never a good sign.
I have to say,
all this talk about no devices
has really made me
want my phone.
I know, I was talking with
some guys about the weather,
and I realized I have no idea
what the temperature is
in Cupertino.
- I need my phone.
- Me too.
What if Krusty posted a tweet?!
I must retweet!
- I must retweet! I must retweet!
- I need my phone!
- Must retweet, must retweet!
- Must retweet!
- I need my phone!
We can't leave!
Studies show tech is more
addictive than heroin.
Google and TikTok
say that's a lie.
We have to be cured.
You couldn't be
more wrong, Marge.
You couldn't be more wrong.
Since this nation was founded,
families have faced the problem
of staying together without
driving each other crazy.
For the first 200 years,
they played fiddle music
until they had a war.
It was a good system.
Then, they came up
with sitting around a radio.
But without a screen, they still
had time to look at each other.
So World War II.
With peace came TV, which bought
Silicon Valley the time
to invent the devices
that isolate us completely.
Finally, the American family
was safe...
from itself.
Is any of that true?
Once I post it on Reddit,
it will be.
Okay, we'll just say goodbye
and then we'll get our things.
What's going on here?
I thought this was
a screen-free environment.
It is, for the patients.
But the rest of us have
side hustles to perpetrate.
I'm making $400
a day from home.
Want to know how?
You're sending that spam
through my e-mail account?
You stole her password
when she checked in!
Unlike every other rehab,
this one is a scam!
And we're gonna
expose you to the world!
I'm afraid not.
You signed a contract.
And every exit is guarded
by a laser-detection system.
You have lasers
at a rehab center?
Let me remind you,
this is an evil rehab center.
Anyone order a ride
from Jupiter One?
I'm riding in a spaceship.
Stick that spammer
in the darkest,
dankest cell we've got, Lou.
The one furthest from the Wi-Fi.
One bar, scumbag.
One bar is all I need
to scramble
your Spotify suggestions.
Hope you like Little River Band.
No, no!
Please, turn the siren on.
Much better.
Only 12 doughnuts for three cops,
well, there's no way
to divide them evenly,
so I'll just eat them all.
Captain Wiggum,
I could help you
with your food addiction.
What do you mean?
Psychologically,
you are a baby with a gun,
sticking food in his mouth.
Eat, eat, eat, all the day,
like a schwein.
Wow, you are such
a great profiler.
With you, we wouldn't
even need DNA evidence.
Boy, so sick
of getting criminals
to give semen samples.
Chief, you don't need semen.
A lock of hair will do.
It what?!