(exclaiming)
♪ The Simpsons 25x14 ♪
The Winter of His Content
Original Air Date on March 16, 2014
(school bell ringing)
(Barney belches)
(whistle blows)
(yells)
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
(grunts)
(game buzzes)
D'oh!
(Bart laughs)
(Homer screaming)
(both giggling)
- MARGE: Whoa!
- HOMER: What the...?
(Homer laughs)
- Mmm, mail.
- Oh, "urgent notice." Hmm.
If it's not
final, who cares?
(toy squeaks, siren whoops)
DOLL:
Donkey!
HOMER (muffled):
There you go.
(both moaning)
(frustrated grunt)
(glass shatters)
(phone rings)
(both giggling)
Ugh, if it's important,
they'll call back.
(phone continues ringing)
LISA: Mom! Dad! The retirement
home lost its license
and Grampa has
nowhere to live!
BOTH:
D'oh!
Oh! That man can't remember
anything except our number!
(sighs)
Get in the car, Dad.
Look who's here,
the big dummy!
You do know I'm
a doctor now.
Yeah! M.D.!
Major Dummy!
Grampa, what happened?
This place is unlivable.
My contract clearly
promised "barely livable."
Yeah, well, we're closing down
Codger Stadium here
until they fix up their violations.
And there are a lot of 'em.
Mannequin nurses.
Like I said,
lot of violations.
Oh! I guess Grampa's
coming home with us.
Unless... what about that
nice dog boarding place?
The really good one, where they
each have their own dog partner.
- No kennels!
- You're right.
Bad idea, bad idea.
Should we just, you know, drive by
and take a look at the place...?
(groans)
Bad idea. Bad.
When are your relatives
going to be here?
Can I be honest with you?
They're not.
We're all alone
in this world.
All I have left is a phone
message from my late wife.
OLD WOMAN: Pick up the phone, big shot!
I know you're there!
You're both coming home with us.
- You mean it?
- Mm-hmm.
Ah, just let me say
good-bye to my girlfriend.
Don't get fat.
Honey, Grampa is the closest
thing I have to a father,
and I love him, but
three octogenorous?
Homie, Homie,
we'll be old someday.
(laughs) Speak
for yourself.
Glug-glug-glug.
Chomp-chomp-chomp.
(gasps)
Beep...
(laughs)
My lifestyle is my
retirement plan.
Oh!
- And don't forget my ripple.
- You're not taking your ripple.
Without ripple, I never
would have had you.
Ripple's your real daddy.
(chuckles)
This is gonna be a swell
flophouse, sister.
So, where should
we park our pills?
What pills?
- Aah!
- (laughs)
Don't worry, Marge.
It's childproof.
Oh, oh...
Homer, how are we doing
with those cots?
(grunts)
Uh... come on, boy.
Your job is to guide me.
Well, I really think you
should watch your temper.
I mean down the stairs,
you stupid kid!
Stupid kid? Do you really think
that's the way we should communicate?
You just want to see your
old man trip and fall.
Well, sorry to disappoint
you, lad, but...
What the...?
D'oh! D'oh! Ooh!
Not what I was hoping
for, but it'll do.
(cackles)
Okay, boys, shower up.
And I better hear
some towels snapping.
Muntz, what is wrong
with you?
Now, you get undressed in front of
everyone that's staring at you.
(all gasp)
(gasps) Is that
women's underwear?
My mom can't afford to buy me
clothes, so I wear her hand-me-downs.
(sobs)
(children laughing)
Muntz, there's a kind of poverty
that toughens you up, but this...
is sad.
(children laughing)
Hey, leave him alone. I, too, know
the pain of hand-me-down underwear.
My dad buys the underpants
gorillas wear during monkey shows.
So if you're gonna laugh at
Nelson, laugh at me, too.
Simpson, I won't
forget this.
From now on, you and I
are as tight as whiteys.
♪
(all passing gas)
(gasping and groaning)
(electrical buzz)
(groans)
♪
(gasps)
(electrical buzz)
(laughs)
- (yells)
- (screams)
(groaning)
(whimpers)
(screams)
(bell rings)
(laughing)
I've had it up to here with
those freeloading wrinkle bags.
They pee all night,
they cry all day,
and every time they use the
computer, the font is huge.
Aah!
Dad, did it ever occur to
you that we're learning
how to take care of
you when you're older
by watching the way
you treat Grampa?
Have you seen how he
treats my grampa?
Never visits him.
Never even acknowledges
his existence.
Your grampa's alive?
- Oh, yeah.
- Okay...
Well, can you please be
nicer to our grampa?
For me? I love Grampa.
You may not realize it,
but he's a treasure.
GRAMPA: Keep it down in
there, you jabbermouths!
I'm trying to
watch C-SPAN2.
- Please?
- Okay. (laughs)
You know, I love him, too.
In a manly way.
That never shows itself.
Now, we're going to need
three hearing aid batteries,
all different and
hard to get.
And this has to be in the
fridge, next to the butter.
And the butter
has to be open.
Oh, I'll see what I can do.
I can handle them
from now on, Marge.
Gentlemen, I've
been thinking.
My glorious youth and
beauty won't last forever.
Someday, when the
leaves have turned
and the moon has broken apart
into chunks of floating cheese,
I will be old.
What's your point,
pound cake?
I'm hoping we can find
a way to coexist.
- What did he say?
- He wants to see if ghosts exist.
Ooh, they do. My Uncle
Bill is here right now.
Oh, Bill, Bill, I'm so sorry I
wasn't a very good ladder holder.
That's all right.
Enough about that.
Did the clock
ever get wound?
This can only be good.
This family's had a lot of
hoods put over their heads.
Uh, Chief, something
about that looks fishy.
Aw, Lou, you got a
suspicious mind, you know?
You remind me of that Elvis song.
Uh, uh, "Clambake."
You know, 'cause you open your yap
when things get hot. "Clambake."
JIMBO:
All right, take off his hood.
- Where am I?
- Our secret place.
The empty swimming pool
from the country club
that closed down rather
than let women in.
(coyote howls)
Now, enter the stolen
bicycle graveyard.
We've decided to make
you an honorary bully.
Bestow upon him the necklace
of unknown retainers.
Um... thanks,
but I'm not sure I
want to be a bully.
It's too late. You've
seen our faces.
(long grunt)
Wow, never had breakfast at
6:00 in the morning before.
I love yakking at the manager while
he's trying to unlock the door.
Now we'll talk about dead
people you never met
while we get a
little exercise.
(Homer sighs)
When does
the exercise start?
- This is it.
- Yeah, we're mall-walking.
Oh, my God. This
counts as exercise?
I'm barely moving and
I'm smelling Cinnebun.
Sometimes you have to wait till you're
38 to discover who you really are.
I'm a 79-year-old man.
Son, welcome to the club.
Now, say something
pathetic.
Uh, okay, um...
Oh, I can't.
That's my boy.
I-25.
- What letter?
- "I."
- What number?
- 25.
- What game?
- Bingo!
Damn it!
Who's the icebox pie, Abe?
Your younger brother?
My son... but he's taken.
Well, I'm not surprised...
the way he tears into
corn on the cob.
Now, Mildred, he's
a married man.
You can't see the ring because
his finger's too fat.
Join the party, Abe... there's
plenty of room in my bed...
once they take the
railings down.
I said beat it! For
the time being.
Now, Homer, you stay away
from those red-door hoochies.
They're just trying to get a
chicken dinner out of you.
Hmm.
Well, thanks for
the chicken dinner.
How did you know
I wanted one?
(chuckles)
All you gals like
chicken dinners, Marge.
Don't call me a gal.
Makes me feel like
I'm your mother.
(shivers)
- I better turn up the heat.
- It's 82 degrees.
Huh?
Are you wearing sock garters?
- Young lady, in my day...
- Your day is my day!
We're the same age!
(gasps)
You're turning
into your father.
(Grampa-like sputtering)
You won't feel so bollixed once my
Social Security checks start coming!
They're not coming for
another 29 years.
(gasps)
Did your ear lobes
get longer?
Falsies.
(owl hooting)
(cell phone chimes)
Whoa. A tweet
from Chester!
- Who's Chester?
- "Who's Chester"?
Just the most legendary
bully of all.
They say he once
wedgied a kid in half.
Whoa.
He's calling a bully summit
for next Saturday night.
Hey, isn't that the same night the U.S.
figure skating finals are on?
They've been promoting
it like hell!
Excuse us, we're
looking for owls.
- Screech or hoot?
- Either one's fine.
That was an order!
- (hooting)
- Screech! Screech!
Where's the Lord
of the Fries?
Actually, Homer got up early
to count and sort pills.
Then he called the police when
a Frisbee landed on our lawn.
Then he went to the
drugstore for an egg cream,
but he only
brought a nickel.
I didn't mind that
he grew bald.
I didn't mind that he got fat. I
didn't mind that he got fatter.
But no one told me he'd
get older than me.
Oh... (sniffles)
Say it, honey... you're no
longer attracted to him.
Maybe.
It's on tonight, and everyone who ever
took anyone's lunch money is there.
♪
DEEJAY (over speakers): All you boppers
going to the park tonight,
make sure you're not packin'.
We don't want any...
"accidents."
BART:
Ay, caramba.
How'd you babies get here?
Did your mommy bring you?
Yes.
WOMAN:
Nelson!
I might have to move the trailer
house while you're gone.
Look for me downhill.
I ain't got much gas.
Smell you later.
Hey, my old weasels! How's
Shelbyville Elementary?
Not bad, not bad.
We've ruined picture day
three years in a row.
(both grunt)
CROWD (chanting):
Chester! Chester!
They say the day
of the bully is over.
Popular music condemns us.
Documentary filmmakers
expose our craft.
And cyber-bullying has taken away
the warmth of human punching.
But I say to you, the day of
the bully has just begun!
Can you dig it?!
Hey, why are you
doing this?
Because I don't
want to sit around
like Prince Charles waiting
for the queen to die!
Can... you... dig... it?!
- (crowd cheering, shouting)
- Ooh, I can totally dig it.
(grunts)
Chester's been shot!
(high-pitched scream)
(panicked yelling)
This kid did it! His
sling is still warm!
Get that boy! And his friend, the
kid with the lady's underpants!
How does everyone know?
DEEJAY: To all you boppers
out there, be on the lookout
for a sling-daddy who took
down our main man Chester.
This is KBLY, your source for
bully news, weather and sports.
100% supported by money
taken from nerds.
I can't believe you
did that, Bart.
I don't even want to sit on the
same side of this car with you.
I'm just doing it
for balance.
I didn't shoot him!
Oh, yeah? Well, why'd you
bring your slingshot?
I don't know. I feel
naked without it.
DOLPH:
Yeah, I get that.
That's how I feel about
my eyebrow ring.
The only way out is on the subway,
past everyone else's territory.
We'll just have to wait
it out here until we...
(all yelling)
We're gonna have
to jump for it!
(grunts)
No! I lost my flip-flop!
Just keep moving!
(flip-flop
flapping)
Oh. Well, well, well.
Looks like youse and me may
be up here for a while, huh?
(fake yawn)
(sighs):
There.
Yippee!
Aw, damn it! I just had to get her
parkour lessons for her birthday.
You'll have to get past
the S.A.T. Preppers!
790 assault, 780 battery.
I didn't say to begin.
(roaring gibberish)
DEEJAY: Word on the street is that
the S.A.T. Preppers failed the test.
The Springfield bullies
are still at large.
That's right, yeah, so,
uh, give yourselves up.
Um, if I put on the
radio, can I hear myself?
(click, electronic feedback)
(echoing over speakers):
Wow. That's crazy.
Whoo, whoo.
Hello, Lou.
♪
I only have a-pennies.
Uno... due...
(groans)
(all gasp)
For Springfield!
(honking repeatedly)
Save yourselves...!
Today we are all
Nelson Muntz.
ALL (sadly):
Haw, haw.
Springfield. We're safe.
I'm gonna kiss the ground.
Loser! You're gay
for the ground.
Well, you're gay
for homophobia.
Wow. You just made me
gay for tolerance.
(bottles clinking)
(singsongy):
Bul-lies...
come out to play-ay...
Oh, no! He's got
three bottles!
(singsongy):
Clinky, clinky...
I know a place that serves an
early early bird breakfast.
Steak and eggs for 50 cents,
and it was 40 years ago.
- Oh, boy.
- Yeah. - Ah...
Oh, my God! I know that kid!
We got to help him.
Oh, I'd love to,
but, uh, I'm sure
that it's some sort
of a holiday for me.
Fine! Your generation did its
part when it won World War II
and created The Rockford Files.
I t th one.
(groaning)
It's so hard
running in sand.
No! No!
I can't be old yet. I won't let the ravages
of time catch up with me till I'm 52!
- (grunts)
- Ow! Ow!
No! (panting)
Um, I've never really
been in a fight.
(sobbing)
Now, let's go home, son.
♪
How did I get here?
(passionate kissing, moaning)
Ooh, what's your hurry?
We got ten minutes between the kids falling
asleep and the old guys waking up.
(gasps)
Go, go, go!
GRAMPA:
I hear smooching!
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
♪ Somewhere out
on that horizon ♪
♪ Out beyond the
neon lights ♪
♪ I know there must
be something better ♪
♪ But there's nowhere
else in sight ♪
♪ In the city ♪
♪ Oh, oh. ♪
Shh!