CHORUS: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
(whistle blows)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(chimes)
(honking horn)
(tires screeching)
D'oh.
(screams)
(Homer screams)
Now, remember,
we have to leave nature
just the way we found it.
Everything we pack in, we pack out.
What if I have to do my business?
Use this plastic bag.
Oh, how come bears
can crap in the woods
and I can't?
(grunts)
Ah, we're so lucky to have
this untouched piece of paradise
so close to Springfield.
-(buzzing)
-(gasps) Bees!
They sound angry and Africanized.
OK, nobody panic.
There's plenty of spray for me.
-(tires squealing)
-That doesn't sound like bees.
Oh, my god!
It's a racetrack.
(gasps)
The bird sanctuary.
They ruined it.
HOMER: No, they didn't.
They just surrounded it
with something wonderful.
Like a raisin covered in chocolate.
Or a monkey in a cowboy suit.
-HOMER: Hmm.
-LISA: Whoa!
See?
Animals can get used to anything.
(grunting)
(squawks)
Start your engines!
Show us your boobs.
Oh, you better do
what he says, Marge.
BART: Cool!
Way to adapt, little guy.
Why do jerks think everyone wants
to see their stupid name?
(screams)
(grunts)
Sorry to break up your picnic, folks.
I'm two-time
fast car champ Clay Babcock.
You're on fire!
Yeah, I have won a lot of races,
but it's all thanks to my crew, really.
Eh! Ah! Hoo! There it is.
Mr. Babcock, can I take a ride
in you car?
Well, my "A" car was just incinerated,
but, uh, you could ride in my "B" car.
I don't see why not.
Bart, these are the time trials
that determine the pole position.
Shouldn't you be keeping
your hands on the wheel?
Oh, sure, if you want to drive
the traditional way.
-Whoa!
-Sorry.
Boy, these cars are surprisingly roomy.
Yeah, we like to bring
our families along
on the longer races.
If I get tired, I let my wife drive.
She's good.
Get your feet off the upholstery.
(tires screeching)
Folks, I got some spare tickets
if you'd like
to stick around for the race.
That's very sweet,
but we have a full day
of hiking planned.
We can hike anytime.
This is our chance to see cars driving.
-LISA: Oh.
-HOMER: Hmm.
Hi-diddly-ho,
pedal-to-the-metal-o-philes.
Flanders? Since when do you like
anything cool?
Well, I don't care for the speed,
but I can't get enough
of that safety gear.
Helmets, roll bars, caution flags.
I like the fresh air
and looking at
the poor people in the infield.
(cheering)
Dang, Cletus!
Why did you have to park
by my parents?
Now, honey, they's my parents, too.
ANNOUNCER: Gentlemen,
start your engines!
(engines start)
Daddy, can we move closer?
Abso-not-ly, hot-roddy.
We're up here out of range
of the crashes
and the drivers cussing.
-Move your damn butt!
-Bite me!
(all gasping)
(disappointed groaning)
Come on! Somebody crash!
Be patient, son.
A watched car never crashes.
-(crash)
-Oh, I missed one!
MAN: Let's go! Let's go!
The dice! The dice! The dice!
Eight seconds. Great job, boys.
Let's go! New tires! Come on! Come on!
We're going as fast as we can.
Hey, who are you?
Oh, how rude of me.
My name is...
My bad.
ANNOUNCER: And now,
here's something for the guys.
Finally.
ANNOUNCER: Let's hear it
for Fan-demonium!
Hey, racing fans,
who wants a free t-shirt?
-(all yelling)
-Me, me.
(speaking in Spanish)
I do, I do.
Wait. No, I don't.
Hmm. A Ford
urinating on a Chevrolet.
Don't you usually laugh at everything?
Yes. Yes, I do.
Come on! Right here!
-Ow!
-(all gasping)
I'm OK, folks.
(disappointed groaning)
I need a shirt!
Give me a shirt!
Mommy has bosoms like that.
Yeah, I wish.
Neddy, I've had about all I can take
of Homer Simpson's torso.
I'll get some hot dogs.
No foot-longs.
I know.
-They make you uncomfortable.
-(Homer humming)
Well, I guess no one else
wants a t-shirt.
That's a damn lie and you know it!
Give me a shirt!
You heard him, girls.
Hey, t-shirt, t-shirt, t-shirt!
Fire!
Ooh! A bobby pin.
(screaming)
(gasping) Maude?
(speaking indistinctly)
Oh, my lord! She's dead.
(gasps) Ah...
It's hard to believe
we're never going
to see Maude again.
And poor Ned didn't get a chance
to say good-bye.
Well, from now on, I'm never going
to let you leave the room
without telling you
how much I love you
and how truly special--
This is really eating up a lot time.
Maybe just a pat on the butt.
Yeah, that works.
Now, Homie, you know
Ned and the boys need us
and you know what that means.
I know.
No more being a jerk.
That's right.
(sniffs)
In many ways, Maude Flanders
was a supporting player
in our lives.
She didn't grab our attention
with memorable catch phrases,
or comical accents.
-Aye.
-Arrgh.
(speaking gibberish)
But whether
you noticed her or not,
Maude was always there.
And we thought she always would be.
My friends, life is about change.
Just yesterday,
Apu was a lonely bachelor.
(babies crying)
Yes, thank God, those days are over.
And the Van Houtens were enjoying
a storybook marriage.
Yeah. Lots of storybooks
have witches.
-Shut up, Kirk.
-Sorry.
And now the good people
at Fan-demonium,
as part of a generous settlement
will fire a 21 t-shirt salute.
(trigger cocking and gunshot)
(piper piping)
Finally!
Ned, my friend, please know
that the Kwik-E-Mart
is there for you 24 hours a day.
Oh, thank you, Apu.
And I'm going to give you
all of Maude's
frequent-squishee points.
The boys at headquarters
will not like it,
but I'm getting pretty sick
of them and their Bombay attitude.
Yeah, that's enough there, 'pu.
Look, Ned, I know
we ain't hung out much,
uh, what with your insane fear
of drinking,
and me being banned
from the church and all,
but, uh, but that Maude,
she was really something.
Oh, wasn't she? Thank you, Moe.
I appreciate that.
No, I really mean it, though.
I mean, if it was you that died,
I would have been on her so fast.
What are you saying?
What? Nothing. She was hot!
What, you can't take a compliment?
You said "hot." You monster!
(grunts)
That's good. Now, let it out.
That's it. Let it out.
Send me to Maude.
That's it! Ah.
Oh, here I come, baby! Oh, yeah!
(Bart chuckles) Mmm.
Bart? Honey, I think you should go play
with Rod and Todd.
Aw, man, why does everything bad
have to happen to me?
When I'm feeling low,
you know what always cheers me up?
Is it love?
Kindness?
Ooh, tough room.
Video games! What do you got?
"Billy Graham's Bible Blaster"?
Keep firing! Convert the heathens!
(video game music plays)
-Got him.
-No, you just winged him
and made him a Unitarian.
Look out, Bart! The gentle Baha'i!
-(fanfare music plays)
-All right! Full conversion.
Thanks, guys.
This really cheered me up.
(male computerized voice)
Second coming. Reload, reload.
Can we play now?
You are playing. We're a team.
-Yay!
Now, if there's anything,
anything at all
I can do to help out.
Quit hogging Flanders.
I want to comfort him.
(laughs)
That's nice of you, Homer,
but... (sniffling) I think
I'll just go to bed.
Then I insist on walking you home.
Homer, this really isn't necessary.
Those feelings are normal, Ned.
They're part of the process.
Watch the sprinkler.
Hey, that's my sprinkler.
It's natural to feel that way,
but the sprinkler is gone.
It's time to let go.
I just bought that.
I know, I know.
It's never easy.
Do you want anything else?
Water? Chili fries?
How about some white noise?
-(imitating white noise)
-Oh, Homer...
(yawning)
...you don't have to...
(snoring)
Sleep tight, Neddie.
(groans)
(door closes)
(rock clanging)
-Ah... What the...
-(rock clanging)
Oh, you want a rock fight, eh?
(chuckles)
No, Homer! I just need to talk.
OK, be right down.
(laughs)
I just keep replaying
the whole thing in my head.
I can't believe
my last words to Maude
were "no foot-longs."
Yep, it would have been a lot better
if you'd said "I love you"
or "you're special".
You know, something sweet
instead of that hot dog crap.
If I'd only been a gentleman
and got the hot dogs myself,
she'd still be here.
Now, now, now,
don't beat yourself up.
I'm the one
who drove her out of her seat.
I'm the one who provoked
the lethal barrage of t-shirts.
I'm the one who parked
in the ambulance zone
preventing any possible resuscitation.
Ah, but, uh, there's no point
in playing the blame game.
Eh, you're right.
I just got to work
through the grief. (sighs)
There's not going to be
an easy answer.
Easy answer, eh?
Oh, yeah, that's it, baby.
That's the money shot.
Yeah, the camera loves you.
Oh-ho-ho, you tease, you.
(chuckles)
Why are you taping Flanders, Dad?
You'll see.
Do you even have a job anymore?
I think it's pretty obvious that I don't.
OK, I finished
the gardening sequence.
OK, from here, we star-wipe
to a glamor shot of Flanders
-paying his bills...
-(speaking indistinctly)
...then we star-wipe to Flanders
brushing his...
Dad, there are other wipes
beside star-wipes.
Why eat hamburger
when you can have steak?
I'm taking my name off this thing.
So, how you doing, Ned?
Oh, it's been
a hard couple of months,
but I feel like I've turned a corner.
Well, that's all going to change,
-thanks to this tape.
-Tape?
Now, the audio needs
some tweaking
and there's some footage
of Maggie being born
that I couldn't get rid of...
Anyway, enjoy.
HOMER: Single women of Springfield,
your prayers
have been flan-swered...
Ned Flan-swered, that is.
-Is this a dating video?
-Shush.
HOMER: What would you say
about a man
who owns his own house
and his own car?
That's Ned Flanders...
a man who's not afraid to cry.
-Hey, Ned!
-(sobbing)
So that's why you maced me.
(chuckles)
Yeah.
Ned does everything with class.
Whether he's punching in
his ATM code...
or keeping clean in the shower.
Homer!
HOMER: But don't take
my word for it.
Listen to this testimonial.
Oh, I would date Ned in a second
if I was a woman, or gay.
He looks like a cuddler, that Ned.
I--I like that.
I like to be held,
I like to be pampered...
-(bell ringing)
-(gunshot)
(tires screeching)
HOMER: So if you're tired
of dating the same old losers...
What are you doing, Homer?
HOMER: Step up to the best.
Ned Flanders,
the man with the chest.
(instrumental music plays)
(panting ferociously)
(grunting loudly)
Eww...
Now, we'll just send this
to the dating service,
the chicks'll fall for you, and bam!
The healing begins.
Homer, you obviously went
to a lot of trouble, but dating?
It just feels way too soon.
Oh-ho-ho, that's great!
Chicks really dig sensitivity.
Did you get that, Bart?
-Got it.
-Beautiful. And star-wipe
and we're out.
Hmm...
Well, with triple word score, that's 90.
(laughs) I guess my luck
is starting to even out.
Ah, I'm just a Q without a U.
Mm.
(chuckling)
(chuckling continues)
Hello?
Mailman?
These are the women
who saw your videotape
and are interested.
And feel free to root around
In the one-nighter bin.
The bin is spoken for.
Are you going to call all those women?
No, the tapes will do just fine,
thank you.
Homer, I'm having second thoughts.
This feels so disloyal to Maude.
Oh, wake up, Ned.
You think Maude
isn't dating in heaven?
You think she would?
How could she not.
The place is full of eligible bachelors.
John Wayne, Tupac Shakur,
Sherlock Holmes...
(chuckles) Sherlock Holmes
was just a character.
He sure is.
(sexy growl)
FLANDERS: OK, here goes nothing.
(inserts videotape)
WOMAN: If you select me,
you'll get a lot more
than a Wharton MBA
pulling in 200K.
You'll get a woman
who's poised, articulate,
sophisticated, confident,
and highly sexual.
Hang on, I'm getting a fax.
Damn, I've just been indicted.
Looks like we're going to have
to reschedule.
-How's your July?
-Well, I--
Mine's terrible. Let's talk in August.
(sighs)
Mmm...
Dinner was delicious, Edna.
But I can't shake the feeling
that you're just using me
to get Principal Skinner jealous.
Oh, please.
I don't care what
Mr. Engaged-to-be-engaged thinks.
Hear that, Seymour?
SKINNER (over phone):
Edna, this is childish.
Fine, then hang up.
SKINNER (over phone):
I will hang up when he leaves.
(sighs)
Well, Diane,
I've sure enjoyed chatting with you
about your problems
with your mother.
Did you hear that, Foofie?
Sounds like somebody loves us.
-(chuckles)
-DIANE: Yes, he does.
Yeah, well, maybe
I'll call you again sometime.
Ooh, Foofie doesn't like
the sound of that "maybe"
'cause him's a commitment dog.
Isn't him?
(panicks)
So how'd you do tonight, Romeo?
Well, I just can't relate
to the women of today, Homer.
Ah, it's probably me.
I'm about as exciting
as a baked potato.
You're darn right you are.
And you've got lots
of other great qualities, too.
That's right, Ned.
Those floozies we married
in Vegas were crazy about you.
What floozies?
What are you talking...
Marge, we're trying to help Ned.
Lord, I never question you,
but I've been wondering
if your decision to take Maude was...
well, wrong.
Unless this is part of your divine plan.
Oh... could you just give me
some kind of sign?
Anything?
Oh, and after all that
church chocolate I bought,
which by the way, was gritty
and had that white stuff on it.
(sniffles)
Well, I've had it.
Daddy, get up.
You'll be late for church.
Well, you boys can go
with the Simpsons.
I'm not going to church today.
-(both gasping)
-That's right.
And I may not go
to church tomorrow.
(both screaming)
No, I'm not kidding.
I am going to sit right here
and miss church.
You just watch.
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry...
While our organist
is on a much-needed vacation,
we thought we'd try something new.
So get down
and put your knees together
for the Christian Rock Stylings
of... Kovenant.
Hey, isn't that
the bass player from Satanica?
I think it is.
(tires screech)
(gasps)
Electric guitars in church?
Oh, my gosh.
Some dropouts must have
overpowered the reverend.
This is a love song about a dude
I met in a sleazy motel.
-(gasps)
-A dude named God.
Ohh...
♪ In a motel room in Delacroix ♪
♪ I was drinkin'
like a Dartmouth boy ♪
♪ And thinkin' 'bout
the wrong turns ♪
♪ That I took ♪
(snoring)
♪ Well, I woke up
on the puke-green floor ♪
♪ And opened up
a dresser drawer ♪
♪ A-lookin' for a bottle,
but instead I found a book ♪
She's talking about the Bible.
So? She's good-looking.
-Shut up.
-You shut up.
♪ A book about a man ♪
♪ A book about the dude
who lives above ♪
♪ A book about a man ♪
♪ Who drives a pickup
full of sweet, sweet love ♪
(humming)
♪ Now if you think
he doesn't care ♪
♪ Or maybe that he isn't there ♪
♪ It's not too late to see
how wrong you are ♪
♪ So when your soul
has gone astray ♪
♪ Just let God be your triple-a ♪
♪ He'll tow you to salvation ♪
♪ And he'll overhaul your heart ♪
Glad you made it, Ned.
I knew he would.
(grunting)
I'll be right back, boys.
I'm going to go help that lady.
Homer, you help, too.
I toileth not on ye sabbath, woman.
-A pox on thee.
-Hmm.
(grunting)
Ah, that was a lovely song.
(chuckles)
It really got to me.
Been through
some rough times yourself?
I... I recently lost my wife.
(gasps)
I'm real sorry to hear that.
We just lost our drummer.
To a Pentecostal ska band.
Uh, I mean I know
it's not the same but...
No, I hear what you're saying.
It's always hard to replace someone.
Yeah.
My name's Rachel Jordan.
If you feel like talking,
maybe we could grab a coffee.
Well, that... that sounds
real nice, Rachel, but, uh...
I'm (clears throat)
I'm not quite...
I understand.
Listen, we're heading out on tour
with the Monsters of Christian Rock.
Maybe when we get back,
you and I could get together.
(chuckles) Maybe we can.
My name is Ned Flanders
And I'm here every week.
Rain or shine.
♪ it's a show about Ned ♪
♪ About him losin' his sweet wife ♪
♪ She landed on her head ♪
♪ But now it's time to get on ♪
♪ With his life ♪
(theme music playing)
Shh!
Captioned by Visual Data Media Services