CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(school bell rings)
(whistle blows)
(saxophone solo)
(tires skidding)
(clinking)
(tires screeching)
D’oh!
(screams)
♪♪
♪ Laugh it up
with Christ and Krusty ♪
♪ Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha,
ha, ha, ha, ha ♪
♪ We got hired
’cause we are busty ♪
♪ Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha,
ha, ha, ha, ha. ♪
Hey! Hey!
Oh... whoa... whoa!
(thuds)
(laughing)
Real nice--
laughing at an old man’s pain.
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
(loud groaning)
(laughing)
We’ve got a great show tonight,
with all your favorite
second-tier costume characters.
Like Ribwich Rib-it!
Matrix Poochie!
And right off the plane
from his dad’s funeral,
Sideshow Mel!
And now for the highlight
of our show,
a special appearance
-by Elvis...
-(excited gasping)
...Stojko!
(disappointed groaning)
ANNOUNCER (over P.A.)
Olympic Medalist Elvis Stojko
performs
a graceful triple axel.
Elvis Stojko
is so handsome.
He can lace up
my skates any time.
Don’t you hags know
that all male figure skaters
are "twinkly in the lutz"?
That’s a common
misconception.
I have a girlfriend
in Vancouver.
Made-up girlfriend,
made-up city.
("Dance of the Reeds" plays)
(audience "awws")
Just think, Lisa,
if I had paid for those
skating lessons,
that could’ve been you.
(grumbles angrily)
Say, Mel,
those figure skaters,
sure are having
a swell time out there.
Indeed!
Why don’t we join them?
(both groaning)
Oh, my back.
("Dance of the Sugar
Plum Fairy" plays)
Wow, Krusty and Mel
sure can skate.
Nothin’ slows down
the baby boomers.
(cheering and applause)
(both screaming)
(audience gasping)
Aw, don’t look
so shocked.
You knew the deal.
(pulley squeaking)
SNOWMAN:
Children, we need your help.
The Grumple has stolen
all of our holiday cheer.
That can’t
be good.
Grumply, grumply groo,
I’ll throw my net over you.
Look out!
It’s the Grumple!
(Homer whimpering)
SNOWMAN, CANDY CANE, REINDEER:
Oh!
Whoa, watch where you’re
going there, pally.
We’ve got a basketball
game in an hour.
But we’re trying to get
to Mistletoe Mountain.
Tell it to the Utah Jazz,
snowflake.
Elvis, Grumple,
Candy Kevin!
Let’s teach
these guys
the real meaning
of Christmas.
(punches landing, grunting)
(groaning)
Come on, Homer.
Let’s get the kids
out of here.
Homer?
Give back
that holiday cheer,
-you bastard!
-Never!
This sweater
is gorgeous.
I’ll take one
in "wife" size
and three in
"mistress" size.
Now Smithers,
I need your advice
picking out a gift
for a very dear friend of mine.
A single fellow,
a bit quiet,
but one with a warm,
loyal heart.
Well, sir,
a fellow like that
might have had his eye
on this silver frame.
It would go great with his
collection of Art Deco...
Shut up, shut up!
There he is.
Hello, Phillip.
What are you
doing here?
(gasping)
Oh-ho. Never you
mind, Mr. Nosey.
(both laughing)
Are you going
to that string quartet thing?
-’Cause I’m not.
-(both laughing)
(sotto voce)
Are you still here?
Go pay for that.
Well, uh...
what can ol’ Santa bring you
for Christmas, son?
I want a dirt bike,
one of those video game
chairs that vibrate...
Dad, he’s not
the real Santa.
We can’t afford
that stuff.
Shut up.
Shut up. Shut up!
(sobbing)
I better go
after him.
What can I do for you,
young lady?
What I want
can’t be bought at any store.
Oh, what is it, sweetie?
Peace on earth?
What? No!
I-I mean,
that’s a given.
But also, the Malibu Stacy
Pony Beach Party Set
with Sparkle Sand.
It’s sold out
everywhere.
You know,
Santa thinks he saw an
extra Beach Party Set
sitting back
in the stockroom there.
(gasping)
Really?
Y-You just wait here.
Let me go check,
Sugarplum.
(cash register dinging)
Oh, thank you,
thank you, thank you!
You really made my
daughter’s Christmas.
Well, her smile
made mine.
Gil!
March your fake boot
fronts over here!
Mr. Costington!
Sir, I’m glad I have
this chance to talk to you.
I’ve been on the payroll
here since May,
and I’d really like
to start working
in Ladies Shoes.
Not literally,
of course.
I... I couldn’t walk
very fast,
though I’d learn
if that’s what it takes.
Never mind that now!
Did you sell
the Malibu Stacy set
I put aside?
That was for you?
It was
for my daughter!
You nitwit!
I want my dolly!
(jowly)
You nitwit!
Now get back
that toy.
Gee, I’m sorry, sir.
Taking back that
doll would break
a little girl’s heart
on Christmas Eve.
I made a lot
of mistakes in my life,
but I would never do that.
Well, then, you’re...
fired!
But I...
(Gil stammering)
Aw.
Oh, you poor man.
Fired on Christmas Eve.
(grunts)
Why don’t you have dinner
with us tonight?
Please, Santa?
Well, let me check
the bus schedule here.
If I get it...
make a transfer there.
Well, I could be there
by 2:00 a.m.
We’ll give you a ride.
That’s swell.
Could you swing
by my ex-wife’s place?
I want her to see me
riding in a car.
SIMPSONS:
♪ And a partridge in a... ♪
(Gil scat singing)
♪ ...pear tree ♪
(all laughing)
(laughing)
He did that.
Oh, yeah.
Well, I guess ol’ Gil
should skedaddle.
You can’t go
home tonight.
It’s cold.
It’s late.
Yeah, maybe I should
spend the night here, too.
You’re getting
a cab, old man.
In fact, I believe
I see it now.
But I haven’t given you
a present.
Your present
is leaving.
Oh, I don’t see
a cab.
Well, since I’m staying,
how about another song?
♪ Jazzin’ around
the Christmas tree ♪
♪ It’s a skit skat holiday. ♪
LISA & BART:
It’s Christmas!
-It’s Christmas!
I didn’t think it would
ever come, but it did!
(both laughing)
What is all this?
Well, I figured since
you invited me to stay,
I might as well go down
to the bus locker
and get my stuff.
Oh.
Marge, we have
a problem here.
You have a bigger
problem out there.
Grumply, grumply groo,
your blood will make my stew.
(whispering loudly)
Do you think that’s
the same Grumple
from the ice show?
Because I do.
(grunts)
Hey, who wants some eggs
a la Harold Stassen?
Huh?
They’re always running!
(Gil laughs)
(Lisa laughs)
(whispering)
Do you really understand
what that means?
(chuckles)
Kinda.
Why did you let that loser
into our home?
I’ll tell you why:
Christian Charity.
Christian Charity?
What does a porn star have
to do with this?
He’s gotta go.
I promise you
he’ll leave after today.
Really?
Who’s gonna make him?
I will.
He sure has a lot of markers
that don’t work.
Well, I got something.
Gah! A spider bite,
or as I like to call it,
a "Christmas kiss."
Listen, uh, Gil...
I sort of
thought that...
you know, you’d be
on your way by now.
Really?
You’re gonna put me out
on Christmas Day, huh?
(chuckles)
Well, that’s all right.
I can go down
to the men’s shelter.
I just hope that weird priest
with the runny eye
ain’t serving soup,
’cause they...
Wait, you don’t have
a place to live?
(whispering loudly)
Lower the boom.
(sighs)
I guess you don’t
have to leave
till the holiday’s over.
(grunts worriedly)
(whispering loudly)
Has the boom
been lowered?
No!
(whispering loudly)
D’oh...
TV ANNOUNCER:
Appearing in their
first Rose Parade,
the marching band
from Altoona, Pennsylvania
playing "Rachel’s Theme"
from Batman Begins.
Hey-ya, Marge,
Happy New Year.
You make
any resolutions?
Yes. One...
involving you.
What a coincidence!
I made one, too.
I’m gonna move
my fanny off this sofa.
(gasps)
Oh.
And move it over to that
recliner by the phone
’cause I’m expecting
a call any minute now
from my old boss
at Jackpot Realty,
asking me to take over
the Scottsdale office.
Really?
Oh, yeah. That desert air’s
gonna give the ol’ one-two
to my bronchitis.
(chuckles)
(coughing)
Oh... boy.
(sighs)
I guess you can stay
a little longer.
Ah, thank you, Marge.
You know, those floats
should really slow down
and savor it, ’cause your life
can go to Hell pretty quick.
(grunts)
We’re not keeping
that moocher
in this house
another minute.
(coughs)
He’s still in need.
We have to let him stay.
It’s what Dr. King
would want us to do.
Oh, that’s it.
We’re changing doctors.
Please,
just a few more days.
Marge, admit it.
You just can’t say
"no" to anyone.
That’s why you have three kids.
It’s true.
I do have trouble saying "no."
It all started when I was seven.
Marjorie,
we need you to hide our
cigarettes in your dollhouse.
No!
(both growling)
Mom?
Gramma?
Aunt Larina?
Anybody?
Whoa-whoa-whoa-wha--
Ugh.
And that’s why I have trouble
saying "no" to people.
Even Gil.
Marge,
I have no idea
what you were just
thinking about.
Why would you
think I did?
Uh... hmm.
(dog barks)
(grumbling)
What’sa matter,
Homer?
You still miss
the UPN?
Yeah, but there’s
something else.
There’s this loser staying
in our house.
Marge says she’s gonna
kick him out,
but then she never does.
Well, you can’t kick him out,
’cause then Marge will never
learn to assert herself.
Well, I guess I’ll have
to wait for Marge
to show
some backbone and--
You again?!
(growling)
(grunts)
Aah!
What the hell
is this thing?
♪ Happy holidays ♪
♪ May the calendar keep bringin
happy holidays ♪
MARGE:
Homie.
Wake up.
I rented that negligee you like.
(purrs amorously)
Those legs
go on forever.
Oh, wait, they
stop right there.
(both chuckling)
(both giggling)
Oh... Mmm!
Homer, don’t forget
it’s Valentine’s Day!
What you gettin’ the missus?
A heart-shaped box
of chocolates.
(grunting)
Gil, listen.
We’ve been
very patient,
-but I want you to...
-(phone rings)
Is that for me?
GIL:
Is it the Scottsdale job?
It’s your foot doctor, Gil!
Yes.
Oh, dear.
I can’t tell him that!
Aw, geez!
Boy, I was...
Well, I’m still a winner!
As long as I got
a cup of coffee
and a tomorrow on the calendar,
ol’ Gil’s comin’ back.
Oh. Say, Homer, how about
closin’ up that robe?
I’m seeing the whole
butcher shop.
For your information,
since I bought it,
I put on a ton of weight.
♪ Happy holidays ♪
♪ May the calendar keep bringin
happy holidays... ♪
♪ McCarthy pumps
the old bassoon ♪
♪ While I the pipes do play ♪
♪ And Hennessy Tennessee
tootles the flute ♪
♪ And the music is
awfully grand... ♪
Oh, their drunken singing
is ruining St. Patrick’s Day!
Well, just let ’em
finish this one song.
♪ There’s O’Brians, O’Ryans,
O’Sheehans and Meehans ♪
♪ They come from Ireland... ♪
(muttering angrily)
(whimpers)
(lively Irish music plays)
♪ Happy Holidays ♪
♪ Happy Holidays... ♪
♪ While the merry bells
are ringing ♪
♪ May your every wish
come true ♪
♪ Happy Holidays ♪
♪ May the calendar keep bringin
happy holidays to you ♪
LISA:
Oh, man.
Now he even mooches
our lunches.
(Bart grunts)
All he left me with are
these used nicotine patches.
Give me your lunch,
dingus.
Oh, mini quesadillas!
Zesty!
(groans)
♪ Happy Holidays ♪
♪ May the calendar keep bringin
happy holidays... to you ♪
I’m so sick of Gil.
He ruins Thanksgiving,
uses my leg razor
to peel his carrots...
Marge, I hate to
interrupt the ol’
solilo-diddly-iloquy,
but I just want to
thank you for your
early Christmas card.
Christmas card?
I haven’t even taken
the photo yet.
Isn’t this your posse
on this glossy?
(gasps)
That Photoshopping freak!
Oh, I don’t mean to cause
Gil ill will, but still...
Don’t you defend him!
I want that mooch out
of my house right now!
Marge, I’ve never seen
you like this before.
That’s right!
I just found my gumption,
and I like it!
Marge Simpson is gonna say no!
Gil! Gil?
Gil!
Gil’s gone.
Back to Scottsdale.
-Problem solved.
-End of story.
Can we have pancakes
for dinner?
Gil’s gone?
But I have a "no" inside me
that has to come out.
Hey, Marge,
you want a thousand dollars?
No!
I mean, yes!
Too late.
(groaning)
Don’t worry. I make
six of those a year.
Even though Gil left,
I still have
to kick him out.
I need this, or I’ll never
be able to say "no."
Mom, I understand
your psychological need,
but I’m not sure
what you can do.
I’ll tell you what.
We’re going
to Scottsdale!
Scottsdale?
Will we stay
at a Tripletree Resort?
-Sure.
-Then forget it!
I’ll ask these active
seniors if they know Gil.
I’ll have you
know I’m 32.
Oh!
(gasping)
There he is!
Gunderson?!
Whoa, Gil’s a big shot!
And to think he and I once
shared a shower.
I don’t care
how successful Gil is.
He’s still a mooch,
and I need to tell him off!
(screeching)
117 degrees?
Ooh, that reminds me.
(heavy panting)
There’s water
under the seat!
(whimpering)
Now remember, Marge,
we’re not buying anything
for more than 1.2,
but if I scratch my nose,
that means
we can go to 1.5.
People, remember,
you’re selling dreams!
When a family owns a home,
it means they own
a piece of America.
And what matters most
isn’t the commission you make,
it’s the smiles on their faces
when they know they own
that land free and clear.
He’s the best
I’ve ever seen.
He’s talking
at a Century 22 level.
(groans)
Gil, remember me?
Marge Simpson?
What are you doing here?
Lookin’ for a home
on a quiet cul-de-sac,
where your neighbor
could be Tanya Tucker?
Listen, bub.
I have something
to say to you,
and it can’t wait.
Oh, well, looks
like we got
a Backout Betty
on our hands.
But watch ol’ Gil take her
from furious to curious.
Now, ma’am, you say
you can’t wait,
and you’re right.
With interest rates climbing
and choice properties
in the Kingsbridge School
District drying up...
The only house I’m
interested in is my own,
which you defiled
for 11 hellish months.
But now I’ve
learned to say "no!"
No to your mooching!
No to your manipulation!
And a big fat no to the
Kingsbridge School District!
Aw, come on, you can’t
say no to ol’ Gil.
No!
Why, he’s as pathetic
as we are.
(laughing)
Gunderson!
I put you in charge
of this office
because I thought
you could tame this town.
You’re fired!
Here’s a box
for your stuff.
I can’t live
in this!
♪ May the calendar
keep bringing ♪
♪ Happy holiday to... ♪
♪ Ba-ba-bop-de-ba-you! ♪
(doorbell rings)
(collective gasp)
Grumply, grumply groo,
we’re here to share
Christmas with you!
ALL:
Awww...
♪ Have a grumply grumply
Christmas ♪
♪ Free of grumply groo ♪
♪ Oh, by grumple, have a grumpl
grumply Christmas, won’t you? ♪
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Shh!
Enhanced by Fotokem