(theme music playing)
CHORUS: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
(whistle blows)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
(honking horn)
D'oh! (screams)
(tires screeching)
(all grunting)
Whoo!
ANNOUNCER: Are you sick of
ordinary-shaped amusement parks?
Am I ever.
Then be the first family
on your block to visit Blockoland,
the amusement park made
entirely of Blocko brand
assembly fun blocks.
So, how much did you love Blockoland?
It was all right, I guess.
Kids... how would you like
to go to... Blockoland?
BOTH: Meh.
But the TV gave me the impression that...
We said, "meh."
M-E-H. Meh. (loud slurp)
Well, I'd like to go.
How about you, Maggie?
(exclaims)
(effort grunt)
-Oh.
-Aw.
(chuckling)
(engine starting)
-(Santa's Little Helper barking)
-Maggie, no!
-(vehicle rattling)
-ALL: Ow! Ow! Ow!
HOMER: We're here.
(Block character squeaking)
Howdy, partner. (chuckles)
Four score and seven blocks ago, my-- Aah!
-(both grunting)
-(sighs)
Ow, ow, ow.
Whee!
OK, we have our choice of Rectangle Land
Cube Country, or Squaresville.
Squaresville sounds pretty cool.
(chuckling)
(monotone voice) I am a robot.
Do what I say. (chuckling)
I am a washing machine.
Do what I say.
(chuckling)
(both grunting)
Take that! In the face!
You knocked his block off.
Come with me.
Check it out.
I built myself a healthy apple.
But you made it out of ham cubes.
Yep, a shiny new apple.
I get it.
Everything's made of blocks.
Even the water.
Hey. Ow.
Hey, Boat 28, stop splashing.
What are you going to do about it?
Uh-oh.
(sputtering)
(coughing)
Ah! Leeches.
(screaming)
Ow! Why did I get this Lego shirt?
Don't you mean Blocko shirt?
Right, right-- Blocko shirt.
Lisa, how's your Eiffel Tower kit?
It's OK, but it's missing a piece.
Welcome to real life, Lisa.
You can't fight City Hall,
a.k.a. Blockoland,
so don't even try.
What kind of a thing is that
to tell your children?
It's what I always tell them.
I told them that twice yesterday.
And then again as
they were going to sleep.
[scoffs] I'm sure the gift shop
will replace the missing piece.
You're right, honey.
Hear that, kids?
The Simpsons are going to Blockoland.
(all cheering)
HOMER: Excuse me.
You sold my little girl
a shoddy Eiffel Tower.
Hey, tough luck, pal.
You can't fight the souvenir industry.
We're too powerful.
Yeah, you're right.
But before I go
I'm going to give you
a little souvenir of my own.
(grunting)
Aw, what the hey.
Here you go.
Thank you, Dad.
Hey, any friend of Marge
is a friend of mine.
So, how's that new block I got you?
Great.
Ah.
You know, standing up
for the little guy felt good.
I'm going to do it more often.
(gasp)
(impact grunts)
(grunting)
-(tires screeching, engine revving)
-(Marge grunting)
-WIGGUM: Scram!
-LOU: (screams)
Those bullies are gone now.
You idiot.
They were beating out
my shirt fire. (grunts)
My heart was in the right place, jerk.
Hyah!
Thanks again, Dad.
Well, you're welcome, honey.
Now I'm going to spend the whole day
helping shmoes with their problems.
You got a problem, Bart?
A girl at school won't go
to the dance with me.
♪ Bart's got a girlfriend ♪
No I don't, that's the problem.
♪ Bart's got a problem. ♪
Don't worry, son.
I'll handle this.
Come on.
Why won't you go out with Bart?
He's a smelly, ugly dork.
Please. Ugly is such a smelly word.
Who would you rather go out with?
Tommy.
Well, duh.
He's breathtaking
but Bart has inner beauty
like you'd find in a rodent.
And face it, you're no prize, either.
You wear braces, you dress like a kid
and you're not getting any younger.
Take what you can get.
He's right. Grab something,
and don't let go.
Well, Bart's not so bad.
Uh, they wouldn't honor
my coupon for two free streaks.
They wouldn't?
Well, I'll go to bat for you, honey.
Yes, may I help you?
Nice place you got here.
Oh, look, a hair net.
Be a shame if it was hurled to the ground.
(grunts)
Oh, how clumsy of me.
And...
Oops.
Why are you doing these things?
Either you honor my wife's coupon
or a lot more lids will be unscrewed.
But I cannot streak that much hair.
Think of the cost.
I'd be ruined.
Oh, really.
Boy, you weren't kidding.
Your profit margins are razor-thin.
You see? This is what I'm...
Wait a minute.
$400 a month for loafer lightener?
But we must have it.
It is the lifeblood of the industry.
You get the same results
with a mincing gel.
But of course!
I will save thousands. Thank you.
Oh, Homie, I love them.
I can't thank you enough.
The satisfaction of helping
another human being
is all the thanks I et cetera.
And I gave that man directions
even though I didn't know the way
'cause that's the kind of guy
I am this week.
Ah, lousy Isotopes.
They're a disgrace to baseball.
They lost again?
Mm-hmm.
The team's been terrible
since they got bought
by that cheap, heartless Duff Corporation.
Hey, Moe, give me a Duff.
Oh, yeah, sweet Duff.
What a minute. Duff owns
the Springfield Isotopes?
Since when?
They bought them a year ago
from the Mafia.
It was the last of the family-owned teams.
I tried to return my season ticket
but they wouldn't give me my money back.
They said they wanted it.
Say no more.
I'll help you, Lenny.
You want to help me?
Oh, haven't you heard?
He's the new Homer.
He's wonderful.
I'm trying to get a refund
for this ticket.
Is this the executive office
of the ball club?
Nope. This is the equipment shed.
Oh. Well, is that it?
That's where we keep the water heater.
-Is...
-That's a tractor.
I see.
MAN: Sir, we can't give your friend
a refund just because the team is losing.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Spin that back to where it was.
Yes, sir.
This meeting is over.
OK.
So, uh, you want to go
get something to eat?
No, I don't.
Get out of here.
No, no, not that door.
(gasps)
"Albuquerque Isotopes?"
What is all this stuff?
It's not anything.
It has no purpose.
What a crazy room.
There's no Albuquerque Isotopes.
It's the Springfield... Oh.
No, no, there's no "oh."
You're moving the team
to Albuquerque, aren't you?
No, no, we would never abandon
our loyal Springfield fans.
By the way, all this barging
into rooms marked "Private"
must have made you thirsty.
-Would you like a beer?
-Well, OK.
But you can't silence Homer Simpson.
I'm the friend of the downtrodden
and I'm not going to forget
what I saw here today.
Of course not.
-(buzzing)
-Duffman, could you bring in two bottles
of smooth, untainted Duff?
DUFFMAN: Oh, yeah!
(Baritone voice) ♪ Oh, yeah! ♪
Now, Homer, we've developed this additive
that makes beer super, super malty.
Care to try it?
Wait a minute.
Will this erase my memory?
No, not at all.
Man, that is malty.
But he'll never know.
(evil laughter)
-Good grief.
-(whining) Ow, my head!
How long have I been out here?
All night. You were yelling at the swing.
I was?
But I love the swing.
Dad, you were nuts.
You know me, occasionally I'll be quirky.
I'll-be-quirky...
Albuquerque!
I'll be right back.
Members of the media
thank you for coming.
The proof that the Isotopes
are moving to Albuquerque
is right behind this door.
MAN: Excuse me.
Joel Duffman, the Newsly Times.
What's with the smear campaign
against this beloved brewer?
And weren't you once in a loony bin?
Oh, yeah!
He's right, folks.
The only story here is the rich,
smooth taste of Duff.
Yes, that is an important story.
But so is this!
(trumpet playing)
Well, I think I know tomorrow's headline,
"Local Man Is Liar."
That is a good headline.
BROCKMAN: So let me get this
straight, Mr. Duff,
the Isotopes are not
moving to Albuquerque?
Absolutely not.
So, are you calling Homer Simpson a liar?
Well, we have obtained this footage of him
with his pants on fire.
(screaming) Oh, no!
Well, Homie, I believe
you're telling the truth
about the Isotopes.
I don't mind being called a liar
when I'm lying, or about to lie
or just finished lying.
But not when I'm telling the truth!
Yeah, but what can you do?
There's all kinds of ways
to get the public on your side.
Bob Dylan wrote songs.
Cesar Chavez staged hunger strikes.
That's it.
I'll go on a hunger strike.
Oh, Homie, you couldn't
keep up a hunger strike.
You eat while you brush your teeth.
You're eating a huge sausage right now.
So?
I can stop.
And I will stop.
I am on a hunger strike
starting right... now.
(whimpering)
Mmm! Mmm!
(sucking noises)
Let's see those double-A
baseball honchos ignore this.
You're really not going to eat anything?
My hunger strike will not end
until Duff admits they're moving the team.
Bart, my chains.
Mm-mmm.
Mm. Mm.
Now it begins.
Dad, I'm so proud of you.
If you need some inspiration
here's a book of
Mike Farrell's core beliefs.
(mumbling)
Man, he really hates Wayne Rogers.
Goodbye, Homie.
Here's Dr. Hibbert's number
if you feel weak.
Don't worry, Duff's not going to
let me waste away to nothing.
Uh, Dad...
D'oh...
What a great ball game.
Thanks, Weekend Dad.
Stop calling me that.
Hey, kid and man!
Don't support a team run by liars!
Liars?
They're secretly planning
to move to Albuquerque.
That's crazy!
It would've been on a talk radio show
like Sports Chat or Sportszilla
and the Jabber Jocks.
-Yeah!
-Why you little... (yells)
Oh, so hungry...
Can't give up...
must continue fighting evil corporation...
Oh, Seymour, you shouldn't have!
It's going to go straight to my thighs.
Well, Edna, it just
might have some company.
Oh... Seymour!
(startled grunt)
Nice try, God.
But Homer Simpson doesn't give in
to temptation that easily... hey!
(slurping)
Stop that!
(all eating)
(sighs)
There's still more meatloaf.
Oh, that's impossible.
Come on, come on, we all have to pitch in
and eat your father's share.
Uh, why don't you just cook less?
I don't do things that way, Lisa.
♪ Dancing away my hunger pangs ♪
♪ Moving my feet
so my stomach won't hurt ♪
♪ I'm kind of like Jesus ♪
♪ But not in a sacrilegious way ♪
Geez, Homer's losing it already.
Yeah, but his weary shuffling
makes my heart smile.
(moans)
I'm so hungry.
(rumbling)
His tummy sounds angry, Daddy.
Yeah, that's his stomach eating itself.
It's such a beautiful day.
Where are the crowds?
Duffman is thrusting
in the direction of the problem.
Hmm, people seem to be drawn to that kook.
Maybe we can exploit him.
It's too dangerous, sir.
He knows about Albuquerque.
Duffman is a cautious cat.
No, listen, fans love wackos.
Remember that busty woman
who ran out on the field
and farted at the ballplayers?
I think we've found our newest attraction.
Duffman has a bad feeling about this.
Can it, Sid.
(normal voice)
Why don't you can it, Howard?
(snoring)
Uh? Wha...? What's going on?
What am I doing here?
Order of Mr. Duff.
And word to the wise,
If someone hits a home run
the fireworks come out here and here.
(bat cracks)
(crowd cheering)
Got to go!
(organ fanfare plays)
ANNOUNCER (over PA):
Folks, it's time to meet
a real super-fan
Hungry Hungry Homer.
He's on a hunger strike
till the 'Topes win the pennant!
(cheering)
What? That's not why I'm here!
(distant) They're moving the team
to Albuquerque!
Hear that, folks?
He said, "Go, 'Topes!"
(cheering)
Oh, all this hunger for nothing.
Get your hot dogs!
Fat, juicy hot dogs!
Pork chops and apple sauce!
Peking duck!
Get your crispy Peking duck!
Yeah, Duck Man, over here!
(sizzles)
Mmm!
(smacking)
(smacking and slurping)
Do they have to chew so loud?
Oh... I'm wasting away...
Oh, I'm down to a B-cup.
It's been a whole week!
Why are you letting my husband die?
What does that have to do with baseball?
Death is a part of baseball.
Oh, yeah, the main part.
Guys...
Uh, we won't let any harm come
to your husband, Mrs. Simpson.
He'll be fine.
He's not moving.
(flies buzzing)
He's probably resting
from all the moving he did
before you got here.
He'll start moving in
a second, I'm sure of it.
Turn on the sprinklers.
(slow groaning)
You see there? He's fine.
Oh, look at him go!
(growls)
Oh, I'm so hungry.
Oh, why keep starving myself?
No one cares.
Mm? (moan)
-Who are you?
-The spirit of Cesar Chavez.
Why do you look like Cesar Romero?
Because you don't know
what Cesar Chavez looks like.
Why are you here?
To tell you not to give up.
Oh, but I want to...
He's talking to himself, sir.
And his smell is distracting
the center fielder.
Yeah, this is getting sad.
Let's bring him in.
(snoring)
OK, Skinny, on your feet.
What's happening?
Did I crush your corporation?
No, you're being replaced.
-(moans)
-(crowd booing)
And now, taking over
for Hungry Hungry Homer...
let's welcome Paint-Drinking Pete!
(gulping)
(crowd cheering)
(Homer groaning)
Well, Homer, your hunger strike lasted
12 amazing days.
(weakly) Oh, me so hungee.
Of course you are, Hungry Hungry Homer.
So why not break your fast
with our brand-new
Isotope Dog Supreme?
(sniffs) (shuddering)
Oh, so hard to resist...
mesquite-grilled onions...
jalapeno relish...
Wait a minute, those are
Southwestern ingredients!
(puzzled murmurs)
Mango-lime salsa?
That's the kind of bold flavor
they enjoy in...
Albuquerque!
(all gasping)
He's right!
Yeah, and the wrapper says
"Albuquerque Isotopes"!
Homer was right!
They're planning to move the team!
(angry clamoring)
Now, now, now, now, see here, people
let's not be too hasty.
Tell the truth! Come on, everybody...
(chanting) Tell the truth! Tell the truth!
Get him out of here.
Don't listen to him, Duffman.
For once in your life,
stand up for the little guy!
New feelings brewing in Duffman.
What... would Jesus do?
(surprised grunt)
(yelling)
(all cheering)
Oh, yeah!
(cheering)
(chanting) Eat! Eat! Eat!
(gulps) (sighs)
The truth never tasted so good.
(cheering)
Way to go, Slim!
(gulping)
Damn, that town's got too much spirit.
Looks like we'll have to steal
some other baseball team.
See what Dallas wants for the Cowboys.
Uh, that's a football team, sir.
They'll play what I tell them to play...
for I am the Mayor of Albuquerque.
(closing theme music)
Shh!
Captioned by
Visual Data Media Services