Hmm.
(yelling)
Ahh.
(thudding)
Did you hear that, Bart?
Maybe it was
just the cat.
No. She's sleeping with me.
(meowing)
(thudding)
(groaning)
Did you guys hear
something moving around
in the attic last night?
Attic? Oh, that's silly.
(laughing)
Seriously, though,
don't ever go up there.
Homer, isn't it
about time for the--
You know.
Yeah, yeah.
I'll go feed it.
♪ Fish heads, fish heads ♪
♪ Do, do, do, do,
do, do, do ♪
(whistling tune)
(grunting, chewing)
(Homer shuddering)
(rattling and clanging)
(metal clanging)
(growling)
(whimpering)
-What's up there?
-Yeah, is it a monster?
-We have to know.
-Come on, what's the secret?
No more questions.
I work my butt off
to feed you four kids,
and all you do is--
What?
Three.
We have three kids, Homer.
Yeah.
Three nosy kids.
And you know
what happens to nosy kids
who ask too many questions?
-No, what?
-What does happen?
-Does something happen?
-What happens?
(thunder rumbling)
LISA: Hurry up.
Mom and Dad
will be home soon.
-Wah!
-Oof.
The unsold copies
of Dad's autobiography.
Oh, my God,
Bart, look.
-(chains rattling)
-(gasping)
-(thunder rumbling)
-(whimpering)
(ghoulish laughter)
(screaming)
LISA: Bart, do you think
it's safe?
BART: I don't care.
I can't breathe in here.
(Maggie sucking)
(gasping and coughing)
See, Marge,
who needs a car wash
when you can just
drive around in the rain?
BOTH: Mom, Dad, we saw something in
the attic! We saw something in the attic!
You went into the attic?
(gasping)
I'm very disappointed
and terrified.
Oh, my God, Marge.
It's escaped.
(footsteps)
(door opening)
(touch tones)
Yes, doctor.
It's what we've
always feared.
It's loose.
Hugo is loose.
See you soon.
Who or what is Hugo?
(sighing)
I'm afraid we haven't been
entirely honest with you, Bart.
You see...
you have a brother.
So, I have two brothers?
Lisa, please.
Yes, Bart, you have
a twin brother.
You see, when you
were born, there was...
an irregularity.
HIBBERT:
A monstrous irregularity.
(screaming)
Yes, I remember
Bart's birth well.
You don't forget a thing
like... Siamese twins.
I believe they prefer to be
called "conjoined twins."
And hillbillies prefer to be
called "sons of the soil,"
but it ain't
gonna happen.
Now, normally the birth
of Siamese twins
is a joyous occasion,
but unfortunately
one of them was pure evil.
I think I'll
bottle feed that one.
HIBBERT:
A routine soul smear
confirmed the presence
of pure evil.
It was then I knew
the only option
was to separate you two
immediately.
You'll both need
to sign these.
(chuckles)
But what to do
with poor Hugo?
Too crazy for boys town,
too much of a boy
for crazy town--
the child was an outcast.
So we did the only
humane thing.
We chained Hugo up
in the attic like an animal
and fed him a bucket
of fish heads once a week.
It saved our marriage.
You expect me
to believe all this?
If any of it was true,
wouldn't I have
a big, hideous scar-- Wha!
We've got to find Hugo.
We'll search out
every place
a sick, twisted, solitary
misfit might run to.
I'll start with
Radio Shack.
Right.
Bart, you stay home
and tape the hockey game.
(rustling)
You're here...
aren't you?
Yes, Bart.
I never left you.
What do you want
from me?
You'll see...
after the surgery.
(screaming)
(thunder crashes)
-You're crazy.
-Am I?
Well, perhaps we're all
a little crazy.
I know I am.
I went mad
after they tore us apart,
but I'll be sane
once I sew us back together.
But you'll kill both of us.
No. It's easy.
Look, I've been practicing.
I made a pigeon-rat.
Well, let's get started.
You want to be
on the right or the left?
-(screams)
-Hugo, stop!
Huh?
(laughing)
There, there, Hugo,
I understand.
All those years
caged up in here--
why, you've probably
never even seen
your own face
in the mirror, have you?
Here.
Hmm?
(grunting)
We think we saw Hugo
at the airport.
He was boarding
a plane to Switzerland--
Oh.
You know,
isn't it interesting
how the left,
or sinister twin
is invariably
the evil one.
I had this theory that--
Wait a minute.
Hugo's scar is
on the wrong side.
He couldn't have been
the evil left twin.
That means the evil twin
is and always has been... Bart.
Oh, don't look so shocked.
Well... chalk this one up
to carelessness on my part.
But I think there's a way
to set everything right.
(laughing)
Care for a drumstick, Hugo?
(noisily chomping)
Mom, Hugo 's
eating his napkin.
(laughing)
MARGE: He's so cute.
Hey, can I have
some turkey?
No. You finish
your fish heads.
Then we'll talk.
This tooth will be perfect
for my science project.
Science has already
proven the dangers
of smoking, alcohol
and Chinese food
but I can still ruin
soft drinks for everyone.
Hey, Lis, check out
my science project.
Ow! What's that
supposed to prove?
That nerds
conduct electricity.
Ow!
(sizzling)
Stupid, Bart.
(electrical crackling)
Oh, boy, mold.
That's science fair pay dirt.
Hmm.
Looks about the same.
Ah.
Oh.
(gasping)
Tiny little people?
My God!
I've created life.
MARGE: Lisa! Breakfast!
We're having waffles!
Ooh, waffles.
Hey, these aren't waffles.
These are just
square pancakes.
I'm sorry, honey.
The waffle iron's
in the shop.
That waffle iron's been
in the shop forever.
So, how are my little
stone age tub dwellers?
Oh, my gosh.
They're evolving so quickly.
They've already reached
the Renaissance.
Wait. One of them
is nailing something
to the door
of the cathedral.
(gasping)
I've created Lutherans.
Wow. It's almost like
seeing into the future.
Hey, what is this goo?
You trying to grow a friend?
Hey, you built a model city.
Is that the school?
Whoops, my finger slipped.
Oops, my finger slipped.
Bart, stop it!
(laughs)
-(sirens wailing)
-(screaming)
Oh, my poor little guys.
That Bart is so rude.
(snoring)
(small explosion)
What the heck?
Ah!
Ow!
(grunts and groans)
(machine gun fire)
(groans)
(groaning)
Your micro-jerks
attacked me.
Well, you practically
destroyed their whole world.
You can't protect
them every second.
Sooner or later you'll let your guard down
and then flush.
It's toilet time
for tiny town.
(sighs loudly)
(whirring hum)
Aah!
(grunts)
It worked!
The debigulator worked!
(trumpet sounds)
ALL: Hail, Lisa.
Welcome to our world,
most gracious Lisa.
Your world is incredible,
and you speak English.
We have listened to you speak
since the dawn of time,
o, creator
and we have learned
to imatoot you exarktly.
LISA:
You think I'm God?
But of course.
You look down on us
from heaven.
You gave us life
and only your
divine intervention
can save us
from the devil.
The devil?
What devil?
The one you call "Bart."
(all gasping and hissing)
Oh, no, no, no, no,
you don't understand.
Bart's just my brother.
The devil is
your brother?
(gasping, murmuring)
I must say we find
that quite perplexing.
Uh, God, hi.
Bill Watson.
I, uh, live
in the Clark building.
I have a question.
If you're so good,
why do you allow
bad things to happen?
Why am I so fat?
MAN: Why do bad things
happen to good people?
(overlapping dialog)
Listen, I can take care
of everything.
All you have to do
is unshrink me.
Unshrink you?
Well, that would require
some sort of a rebigulator
which is a concept
so ridiculous
it makes me want to laugh
out loud and chortle,
uh, but not at you,
o holiest of gods
with the wrathfulness
and the vengeance
and the blood-rain
and the hey, hey, hey,
it hurts me.
Look, the destroyer!
He returns!
(screaming)
Help!
WOMAN: Save us, Lisa!
Bart, no!
First rate work, Bart.
This universe
you've created
is even more impressive than
Martin's milk carton ukulele.
Willie, you can throw out
the other projects.
We have a winner.
Principal Skinner, wait!
I created the universe!
Give me the gift certificate!
Ah, great.
I'm stuck in this lousy tub
for the rest of my life.
Shouldn't you people
be groveling?
(crowd murmurs in agreement)
And bring me some shoes.
Nice ones.
MAN: She'll want socks too.
I'll get socks.
Ah, the old fishin' hole.
So peaceful and relaxing.
Doesn't even matter
if I catch a single fish.
(sighs)
Come on, you stupid fish!
Take the bait!
Don't make me come down there.
What the--
Son of a--
Oh, my God!
Space aliens!
Don't eat me!
I have a wife and kids!
-Eat them!
-Silence!
We are travelers
from a certain
nearby ringed planet
whose name we'd prefer
not to mention.
My name is Kang.
And this is
my sister Kodos.
MALE VOICE:
Hello.
(gulps) I suppose
you want to probe me.
Well, might as well
get it over with.
Stop. We have reached
the limits
of what rectal probing
can teach us.
This is a mission of conquest.
Take us to your leader.
I guess you mean
President Clinton.
-(zipping)
-He usually hangs around Washington, D.C.
President Clin-ton.
Excellent.
Except... um, there's
this election next week
so after that,
it might not be him anymore.
It might be what's-his-name,
uh, mumbly-Joe...
I saw him on TV the other--
Uh... Bob Dole.
Hmm... an election.
That complicates matters.
Set grid coordinates
for Bob Dole.
Well, night everybody.
-Good night, senator.
-Good luck next week.
What?
Bob Dole doesn't need this.
Wha-wha-what's happening?
Is it noon already?
What the hell is this,
some kind of tube?
Hey--
Well, thanks for taking care
of Dole for me.
Hey!
(gurgling)
(whimpering)
Commence
bio-duplication.
(electronic humming)
Oh, no.
Aliens...
bio-duplication,
nude conspiracies.
Oh, my God!
Lyndon Larouche was right!
KODOS' VOICE: What?
Are you still here?
I'm afraid we'll have
to dispose of you.
No! No! What are you
spraying me with?
KANG'S VOICE: Rum. So no one
will believe your story.
Aah!
And don't come back.
(screaming)
Kent Brockman here
with "Campaign '96."
America flips a coin.
At an appearance this morning
President Clinton made
some rather cryptic remarks
which aides attributed to
an overly tight necktie.
KODOS:
I am Clin-ton.
As overlord, all will kneel
trembling before me
and obey my brutal commands.
End communication.
That's slick Willie for you.
Always with the smooth talk.
Marge! Marge!
There I was,
I had just caught
the largest fish
you'd ever seen,
when I was abducted
by a flying saucer.
Sure you were, rummy.
(gasps)
That's one of the creatures!
Senator Dole, why should
people vote for you
instead of
President Clinton?
KANG: It makes no difference
which one of us you vote for.
Either way,
your planet is doomed.
Doomed!
Well, a refreshingly
frank response there
from Senator Bob Dole.
These candidates make me want
to vomit in terror.
I've got to stop them.
Ladies and gentlemen,
73-year-old candidate Bob Dole.
(cheering)
Abortions for all.
(crowd booing)
Very well.
No abortions for anyone.
(crowd booing)
Hmm.
Abortions for some,
miniature American flags
for others.
(crowd cheering)
Fooling these earth voters
is easier than expected.
Yes. All they
want to hear
are bland pleasantries
embellished by
an occasional
saxophone solo
or infant kiss.
Uh, Mr. President, sir,
people are becoming
a bit confused
by the way you
and your opponent are,
well, constantly
holding hands.
We are merely exchanging
long protein strings.
If you can think
of a simpler way,
I'd like to hear it.
My fellow Americans,
as a young boy I dreamed
of being a baseball.
But tonight, I say we must
move forward, not backward,
upward, not forward,
and always twirling,
twirling, twirling
towards freedom.
(cheering)
Stop! Those candidates
are phonies!
(crowd gasping)
(groans)
You heard me.
They're alien replicons
from beyond the moon.
(derisive snorting)
(grunting)
Don't forget
your stinking flag.
Oh, why won't anyone
believe my crazy story?
-(clanking)
-Ow!
(gasps)
Hold on, guys.
I'll help you.
Oh, no, am I still here?
I don't want to serve out
my term naked in a tube.
I am so mad at the secret
service right now.
Hey, who the hell
are you?
I'm Homer Simpson, sir.
And I'm going to get you
back to Washington
before it's too late.
You know, senator, being in
suspended animation
gave me time to think.
Partisan politics
are tearing our country apart.
You got a point
there, Bill.
If you and I are going to whip these
one-eyed space fellas,
we're gonna have to
set aside our differences.
Together we can lead America
into a new golden age.
Friend, you got a deal.
Homer, let us out.
It's time to tear those
aliens a third corn chute.
Hmm, hmm, hmm.
Num, num, num, num... there.
D'oh!
Oh, no.
What have I done?
What am I doing?
What will I do?
(engine revs)
KANG: The politics
of failure have failed.
We need to make them
work again.
Tomorrow when you are sealed
in the voting cubicle,
vote for me, Senator Ka--
Bob Dole.
(applause)
I am looking forward to
an orderly election tomorrow
which will eliminate
the need
for a violent bloodbath.
(applause)
(Homer yelling)
(footsteps)
America, take a good look
at your beloved candidates.
They're nothing
but hideous space reptiles.
(crowd gasping
and screaming)
It's true.
We are aliens.
But what are you going
to do about it?
It's a two-party system.
You have to vote
for one of us.
He's right.
This is a two-party system.
Well, I believe I'll vote
for a third party candidate.
Go ahead--
throw your vote away.
(both laughing)
All hail President Kang.
Ow!
I don't understand
why we have to build a ray gun
to aim at a planet
I never even heard of.
Don't blame me.
I voted for Kodos.
-(whip cracking)
-Oh!
♪♪
(high-pitched scream)
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.