CHOIR: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screech)
(theme music playing)
D'oh!
-(tires screech)
-(grunts)
(Homer grunts)
(snoring)
(groans)
(humming)
Well, if ain't my next-door neighbor,
-King Toot.
-Moe.
How many times I got to tell you not to
throw your trash in my dumpster?
Oh, come on, Szyslak.
I got to make space in the store
for my new side business--
a tanning salon that secretly
has cameras in the beds,
which feeds into my website,
www.tancams.com.
-That is registered.
-Yeah, sounds great.
Maybe then you could afford
to rent your own dumpster.
I like my current deal--
free... of... charge.
(clanging)
(grunting)
I'll eat your hair!
-You call that a testicle kick?
-(tires screech)
All right, you two, break it up.
Drive on, asphalt cowboy,
or I'll squeeze his brain out
like an edamame.
Eh, uh, a what?
Those beans you eat
before your sushi comes.
Oh, salt peas.
I call them salt peas.
Look, Officer,
after 20 years of being neighbors,
tempers sometimes flare up.
Moe's a good guy.
No, no, now, it's my fault.
I'm a hothead.
I ain't got no beef with you, Toot.
(whispering)
You better stay out of my dumpster.
I've also been stealing the catalogs
out of your mailbox.
-(punching thudding)
-(instruments clattering)
(grunting)
(screaming)
It's my dumpster!
(screaming continues)
(both growl)
And that's the terrifying tale
of how the Quebec Nordiques became...
the Colorado Avalanche.
Oh, no! King Toot's is closed!
Dad, you're going to have
to take me to...
the big box music store.
Look at all these monstrosities.
HOMER:
Lisa, how many times have I told you
to bow down to our corporate overlords?
(Lisa groans)
(doorbell dings)
BOTH: Hmm.
HOMER:
It's like some kind of guitar central.
Hmm. (groans)
Hmm. Hmm.
Midlife crisis at 12 o'clock.
Mm-hmm.
Okay, let me guess, dude.
You're an axman--
you're looking to score a new blade.
"Stig." (chuckles)
You've got a name that's not a name.
So what's your poison, bro?
Les Paul? Straight up Gibson?
No, no, no, classic Strat, am I right?
Oh, I don't have what it takes
to play guitar.
I mean, I'm no Joe Walsh
in the brains department.
(chuckles) Who is?
Look, you don't have the weak,
womanly fingers of a guitar princess.
You, my friend,
have the muscular stumps of a bass man.
Try this on.
(note plays loudly)
What the rock?
Now that was a lick.
I did a lick?
Keep them coming.
(notes repeating)
Yes, now bob your head.
Bob it, bob it, bob it.
Dude, usually it takes years
to learn such neck confidence.
Now check this out.
♪ ♪
Oh, my God.
I'm amazing.
Dude, you're already one of
the greatest bass players of all time.
Okay. Now...
Oh, how are you set for stage lights?
I'm not set at all.
Ooh, what about gels?
This is embarrassing to admit, Stig,
but I haven't even thought about gels.
(Marge humming)
-(bass playing loudly)
-(gasps)
(screams)
What is that racket?!
Music!
Beautiful music!
What?!
Beautiful music, baby.
The bass guitar?
This doesn't really seem like you.
Sure it is.
You know I've always loved
laying things down.
-Grooves are just the latest.
-(groans)
I feel a powerful connection
to the history of famous bass players.
Like what's-his-name from The Who.
Or that guy from Led Zeppelin
who wasn't Page, Plant, or Bonham.
Those are the only two I know for sure.
It's so cool to have
another musician in the family!
Oh, yeah, and you know
what the great thing is about music?
It's so easy.
Uh, well, to truly master an instrument
-you'll need years of...
-So easy.
-(bass playing)
-(gasping)
-(siren wailing)
-(gasps)
(groans)
(gasps) Oh!
Ooh!
(groaning)
MARGE: I can't take it.
All Homer does is play that stupid bass.
Doink, doink, doink, doink,
doink, doink, doink.
You're not alone, Marge.
A man gets older,
has a career, a few kids,
and suddenly there's a hole in his life
that can only be filled by jamming.
For my Julius, it was the drums.
Timothy has that awful guitar.
Kirk just loves his keyboards.
I never knew so many women
suffered from extramarital jamming.
Oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God.
What if all the dads jammed together
in a dad band?!
That way they would play
their horrible music
in one garage at a time.
Marge, you're a genius!
This menu was right--
good things do happen at 'Zerz.
♪ 'Zerz! ♪
(cymbals clattering)
I don't know, guys.
I'm not sure I'm feeling this.
The bass is kind of known
for being a solo instrument.
What were our wives thinking?
We probably don't even like
the same tunes.
On the count of three, everyone say
their favorite kind of music.
One, two, three...
ALL: Hard-driving rock!
-(gasping)
-Dads, let's jam!
(rock song playing)
Garage bands rule!
(gasps)
I almost forgot the most important thing.
(rock song playing)
(song ends)
Great practice, guys.
What do you say we give it
another six hours,
then call it a day?
Excuse me, but my wife told me
about your get-out-of-the-house band.
And, uh, perhaps you need a singer?
Oh, yeah, Apu,
I'm sure you're a great singer.
But the balance of the band
is really delicate right now,
and we're not really looking
for a world music vibe.
No disrespect to world music.
I love world music.
No, no, I will sing the classic
power ballad "Hopin' for a Dream"
by my favorite band
from the 1980s, Sungazer.
(clears throat)
Okay, here we go.
♪ When I close my eyes ♪
♪ I wish that I could fantasize ♪
♪ Pull a dream right out of the air ♪
♪ Take a chance, turn it into a prayer ♪
That sounds nothing like terrible,
terrible world music.
Why is your voice different
when you sing?
It is because of all the years
I spent at the Kwik-E-Mart...
(rock song playing)
...where classic rock anthems
were piped in
on a never-ending loop.
The endless repetition
drove many clerks to madness.
The only way to maintain my sanity
was to sing along until
it seemed like our voices were one.
♪ Hopin' for a dream ♪
-♪ Hopin' ♪
-♪ Focus like a laser beam ♪
♪ I'll keep fighting
till I want something great ♪
♪ Hopin' for a dream ♪
(song ends)
Guys, are you feeling this?
Are you feeling this?
-I'm feeling it.
-I'm definitely feeling it.
I felt something earlier,
but I was afraid to bring it up.
I think we all felt something.
We are more than just a garage band
desperate to do anything other
than hang out with our families.
We are now a cover band.
And we shall be called... Covercraft.
Because we play covers
and this is our craft.
-And it sounds like Hovercraft.
-That was not my intent.
Okay, Covercraft, hands in.
-Cover...
-ALL: Craft!
R-O-K-C.
(carnival music playing)
(instruments tuning)
Okay, this crowd is about to experience
the special magic of the cover band,
the thrill of live music
without the fear
of hearing anything new.
-Hmm?
-(sighs)
Apu, what's wrong?
What if-- What if I am no good?
This is the Cabbage Festival, man.
I-I don't know if I can face that crowd!
(groans)
Buddy, buddy.
Think of it this way--
you're not singing
in front of all those people,
you're alone at the Kwik-E-Mart
in the middle of the night.
You just wear this onstage,
and everything will be fine.
(gasps) My uniform!
All alone at the Kwik-E-Mart.
♪ ♪
♪ When I close my eyes ♪
♪ I wish that I could fantasize ♪
♪ Pull a dream right out of the air ♪
♪ Take a chance, turn it into a prayer ♪
♪ Girl, you know I want to be the guy ♪
♪ With a hunger burning deep inside ♪
♪ Tonight I wish upon a falling star ♪
♪ To discover what my yearnings are... ♪
Everyone loves you, Dad.
You could become a famous rock star!
Well, son, I do have the talent.
My mind is full of ideas
for great songs I could write...
down the names of and then cover.
But then I remember--
I'm just a regular guy,
jamming with my buds.
Oh, sweetie.
This band has brought out
the best in you.
Yeah, you really get that
it's all about the music.
Yep. t's all about the music.
And it would take a pretty unforeseen
development to change that.
Pretty unforeseen...
Gentlemen, I think we've found
what we're looking for.
HOMER:
Guys, I really need your honesty here.
At the Squidport Senior Jamboree...
was I too in the pocket?
(Covercraft members gasp)
KIRK:
Freddy Freeman, Shredder Stevens,
Nick Delacourt, and Peter D'Abbruzio--
you're four of the five guys
from Sungazer!
But where's your lead singer,
Grant LeDavid?
Uh, he passed away.
-How?
-(whispers)
What kind of erotic asphyxiation?
-Oh...
Apu, you're the only man
on the entire Internet
who's got the pure Sungazer sound.
Will you be our new lead singer
and join us on our stadium tour?
ALL: Ooh!
I think I can answer for Apu.
He's flattered,
but the small-time success of Covercraft
is all that any of us have ever wanted.
Uh, actually, I...
Apu has a rich life here in Springfield--
a store full of great products,
a lovely him-type wife,
and eight super kids--
Anoop, Sandeep, Nabendu, Gheet,
Pria, Uma, Poonam, Sashi...
Shut your mouth.
I want to do it! I want to do it!
I want to be a singer
for a real rock band!
-SHREDDER STEVENS: Sun...
-ALL: ...gazer!
Gotta say, I'm kind of jealous of Apu
getting a break like that.
Not me.
I'm nothing but happy
that our friend is headed
for fame and fortune.
APU: Tonight we play Las Vegas--
and the theme of the casino is circus!
Circus! Ha!
(whimpers)
I want his fame and fortune so much!
Why must the Lords of Rock
be so cruel?!
(laughing)
Sammy Hagar? You're not dead.
Damn it! I told you those
jalapeño poppers had too much breading!
Sorry, Señor Hagar.
Nah, nah, nah, it's cool, man.
I went to rock star heaven.
And there was this great back patio
with this sweet fire pit.
If you had the right wristband--
which I did.
(laughs)
News story in aisle three?
Local clerk,
Apu Nahasapeemapetilon,
is a dead ringer for a dead singer.
He's living the rock star dream
as front man for
'80s chart-toppers Sungazer
on their Last Final Hell Re-Freezes Over
Ultimate Good-bye For Serious This Time
Never Again
Part Two of Question Mark Tour.
Apu and the band appeared
on Saturday Night Live
as the punch line
in a game show sketch.
-What's a game show?
-Something you make sketches about.
KENT BROCKMAN:
It looks like Apu won't be playing
the Cabbage Festival ever again.
Dad, you shouldn't be jealous of Apu.
Remember, it's all about the music.
I'm not jealous. I'm envious.
Jealousy is when you worry
someone will take what you have.
Envy is wanting
what someone else has.
What I feel is envy.
Hmm.
-Wow, he's right.
-You know what?
Apu leaving is the best thing
that ever happened to this band.
We're gonna be like Genesis
after Peter Gabriel left.
You mean more popular
but not as good?
Phil Collins-era Genesis
is not as good, huh?
"No Reply at All,"
"Land of Confusion,"
"Throwing it All Away,"
"Illegal Alien,"
"I Can't Dance,"
and I'm sure I don't need to mention...
"Invisible Touch"!
Hmph!
(Covercraft playing)
(grunts)
You know, we really could use
a new lead singer.
You know,
I've been known to sing a little.
What? So you can also
get famous and bail on us?
You're out of the band!
Well, you can't just kick him out.
Oh, so you're sticking up
for Yoko here?
Looks like I've got another Yoko
on my hands.
How can there be two Yokos?
Yoko! Yoko! Yoko! Yoko! Yoko!
All you Yokos are out of the band!
(grumbling)
-Are you okay?
-Do I sound okay?
You sound great!
Your licks are really... juicy.
They're not juicy. My licks are dry.
Dry and scratchy like a cat's tongue.
You didn't join a band to
become famous like in Almost Famous.
You loved playing music
with your friends.
That was enough to make you happy.
Well, it's not enough anymore.
When something great happens
to one person,
everyone else's life gets a little worse.
Look it up, it's called physics.
Apu is a good man.
He sent over front row tickets
and backstage passes
to his show at the Costington Center.
Oh, you mean he generously invited us
to come watch him be a rock star?
Stop feeling sorry for yourself.
Your friend had a wonderful thing
happen to him,
and you are coming with us
to share in his talent.
I'll never have a per diem.
You don't know what a per diem is.
Still want one.
Hmph.
Apu wouldn't be able to sing a note
if I didn't help him
get over his stage fright
with his Kwik-E-Mart shirt.
(gasps) Backstage pass,
you just became a payback rage pass.
Look at all this rock star
dressing room stuff.
What a sellout.
Cheese plate...
Oh, sorry, cubed cheese plate.
Lemon tea, probably for his throat.
Mm-hmm!
Let's see how he performs
in front of all those people
without his magic-people-
performing-in-front-of shirt.
-(door opens)
-(gasps)
But, Mr. Shredder, you promised me
after we played my hometown
I could have a day off.
I also promised I'd kick heroin.
Hmm?
But the tour is so hard on my family.
My octuplets are being raised
by roadies and bodyguards.
This is not proper.
Look, Apu,
for 25 years we wasted money
on women, drugs,
and guitars with live fish inside.
And now we want to keep it going.
You signed a contract for a three-year,
57-country tour at union scale--
no per diem.
-(gasps softly)
-You're in the band.
Oh, well, I guess it's show time.
-(gasps) Homer?
-I'm sorry, Apu.
I thought you were living
your dream life,
so naturally I wanted to ruin it.
But now I know things stink,
so I'm okay with it.
Oh, what is the point?
I am trapped like a Kwik-E-Mart
hot dog on a roller.
Kwik-E-Mart hot dog, eh?
You want every hot dog in the store?
Every one? Okay...
ALL: Yeah!
FORUM ANNOUNCER:
Ladies and gentlemen,
Tucks Medicated Pads presents...
Sungazer!
(cheering)
Uh, people, I am sorry to report
that all the original members of the band
have been struck down
by a mysterious case
of hot dog poisoning.
-(groaning)
-Rather than refund your money
or reschedule the show,
we have a surprise for you.
Get ready to rock with a group
that is truly all about the music--
Covercraft!
♪ ♪
♪ Hopin' for a dream ♪
♪ Hopin' ♪
♪ Focus like a laser beam ♪
♪ I'll keep fighting ♪
♪ Till I want something great ♪
♪ Hopin' for a dream ♪
-♪ Hopin' for a dream ♪
-(audience cheering)
♪ Hopin' ♪
♪ To someday, somehow have a goal ♪
♪ I'll keep fighting
till I want something great ♪
♪ I'm hopin' for a dream ♪
♪ Hopin', hopin', hopin' ♪
♪ Hopin' for a dream ♪
♪ Hopin' ♪
♪ Dreams are great or so it seems ♪
♪ If I never find one
I guess that's okay ♪
-♪ I'm hopin' for a dream... ♪
-♪ Hopin', hopin', hopin' ♪
♪ Hopin' for a dream ♪
-♪ Oh... ♪
-♪ Hopin', hopin', hopin' ♪
So there I am, on Easter Island,
and the heads ask me
to play them a song.
I say, "Why me, heads?
You've heard the music
of the universe itself."
And they say, "Sammy,
your stuff rocks just a little harder."
That's when I wake up.
I'm in the Springfield Elementary
parking lot,
doing a buck fifty-five
in my Ferrari 512 Boxer.
I was cornering so hard,
I blacked out from the Gs, man.
They say I ran over the groundskeeper.
Probably get life in prison.
But I got a plan to escape,
using only this harmonica
and some guitar picks
with my face on 'em.
Who's with me on this?
(theme music playing)
(Hagar laughing)
Subtitled by Jimmy Boots