Can't let you do it.
Can't let you break my record.
27... 28...
Okay, Homer, this is
the last pickled egg.
Keep it down
and you win 50 bucks.
Okay. If I win,
we're going out for omelets.
Yeah! I am the champion
of this very bad idea!
He's gonna blow!
Hey, Moe, you're not gonna serve
those eggs, are you?
No, no. I... I find
another use for 'em.
I was 50 bucks up until I blew
every egg out of my belly.
Whoa! Hey there, pal.
I'm afraid that was
the mayor's favorite light pole.
You give me the car,
I give you 500 bucks
and I make all of this go away.
This is awkward.
You don't have to thank me.
Marge.
When you start a sentence
with Marge,
it's really bad.
Marge, Marge, Marge.
I sold our car!
- What are you gonna drive?
- Your car.
Well, then I guess
I'll be riding the bus.
That's right. Like rock stars
and Rosa Parks.
Now just wait till you see
what's become of our car.
Feast your eyes on this!
Four-legged angel
Who will speak for you?
Raised in the rain
With no bone to chew
Well, maybe
Someone will love you
Why are you showing me this?
I don't get it.
And I'm crying.
Lousy wrong channel.
The Legends of Demolition
Derby-Derby-Derby
are coming to Springfield
Springfield-Springfield!
So shut up!
And get your ass-ass-ass
over-over-over here-here-here!
Proceeds go
to stuttering
stuttering-stuttering.
Wait for it. Wait for it.
We've got all
the Demolition Derby greats!
Vince Dead Tooth McGee!
James Psychiatric Disorder
Porter.
Meth MacFarland.
Mysterious Fandango
and a very drunk Billy Joel.
I'm sorry, but most of
these names mean nothing to me.
Here it comes!
And making
his triumphant return
to the Crash Zone
after a full skull transplant,
Gene No Helmet Dupree!
Eh? My car
in a demolition derby!
And we got primo tickets
for Saturday night.
Look at 'em fan.
Wait, wait, wait.
This is the point
where Lisa always ruins it.
No, I'm good with it.
People get out their aggression
and destroy carbon-burning cars.
See? Ruined it.
And then I noticed
there wasn't any more cinnamon
on top of my rice pudding.
And I said,
where's the cinnamon?
And they said, there never
was any cinnamon, Abe.
Fine, Dad, we'll get you
some cinnamon!
I can't tolerate cinnamon!
So, I started asking everyone
in the TV room
if they remembered the cinnamon,
and the answer
will surprise you.
The results were incon...
When did you get that put in?
Worth every penny.
But how many pennies is that?
Homer Simpson, you can't just...
All right, young'uns.
You know that movie Cars
that you likes?
Well,
all your favorite characters
is gonna commit suicide
here today.
What?
Ladies and gentlemen,
please silence all cell phones
and holster all truck nuts.
And now, in conformance with the
latest paleontological theories
about dinosaurs, please welcome
the all-new Truckasaurus Two.
I love you,
Steven Spielberg.
Now, a brief moment in memory
of those we lost
in the past week.
And now...
let the bash-'em-ups begin!
If I get hit by a brain,
can I keep it?
Be sure to get it signed
afterwards.
There's our car!
Without Dad's weight in it,
it really moves.
Oh, my God, this is it.
Only one car stands in our way.
It's down to Homer's Boner
and Car-rak Obama,
the Affordable Health Care
Mobile,
which you can't kill
no matter how hard you try.
My whole life has been leading
to this one moment.
My chest hurts!
That's called pride.
My arm is numb!
Numb with pride.
Son, I need to go
to the hospital.
Sure, Dad.
I missed it.
Can you see the pain
you're causing him?
Go on, git!
I'm sorry to say
it doesn't look good.
Homer, your father would like
to see you one last time.
I hope you've got a return
receipt on that balloon.
I always do.
Homer, there's something
I need to tell you.
I'll give you two a moment
in this semiprivate room.
Where is the nurse with my...
Son, I did a terrible thing
many years ago,
and I need you to forgive me
before...
before it's too late.
Anything, Dad.
You already said that part.
Remember, you can't tell anyone.
It's awful!
I swear. Now get to the point.
You didn't!
Okay.
I forgive you.
Your conscience is the one
clean thing in this room.
Well, we tried everything
we could...
and the last thing worked.
How did you save him?
When a body is
in too much pain,
the brain releases a hormone
to bring a merciful death.
But an expensive new drug
blocks that and keeps him alive.
What a glorious day!
I'm gonna live!
And my son has forgiven me
for the worst thing I ever did.
Yes. Forgiven.
Sir, you just destroyed
a box of hospital cotton balls.
- That's $75,000.
- D'oh!
Now I want to watch
my favorite new show,
currently in its 17th season.
It looks like another murder
at Jackson Island Naval Base.
That's what makes America great.
Prompt investigation
of in-house naval crimes.
Homie, look who's here.
Yeah, I see.
Oh, Homer,
are you a Sunday puzzle?
'Cause you sure seem down
and a'cross.
My dad did something to me
I can never forgive.
No worse than what
God did to his son,
and they wrote a book together.
Bye.
He tricked me with his code blue
and his flatlining.
And I fell for it like a sap.
What did he do?
I promised him
not to say what he told me,
but I will never look at him
the same way again.
Yeah, but you forgave me, so
that means you have to love me.
Marjorie, I'm sorry,
but I do not want to be in
the same room with this man.
I'm going to Moe's.
Then I'm going to Moe's!
Then I'm staying here!
A gun and a sailor hat.
Nothing screams naval crime
more than that.
I'm going to Moe's.
I hate seeing a father and a son
sit at opposite ends of the bar.
'Cause it means
I got to walk more.
Now come on, youse guys.
Bury the old hatchet.
Hey, life is short.
You could be killed
by a drunk driver,
die of cirrhosis,
stabbed in a bar fight.
All kinds of random bad things
happen to my customers.
All right, look,
here's 50 cents, huh?
Play the jukebox
and the love tester.
Hit the road, Jack
And don't you come back
No more, no more,
no more, no more
Hit the road...
You heard Ray Charles.
Actually, in my jukebox,
we can't afford no Ray Charles.
It's a white guy named,
Charles Ray.
Excellent vision,
excellent vision.
Dad, Grampa, the place
we're going is the perfect way
to make you guys friends again.
I went there
for Janey's last birthday party.
You think
you can solve our problems
at a kids' birthday party place?
It's cheaper than therapy,
and it comes with cake.
If cake solved problems, Homer
would have a Nobel Peace Prize.
That's a bullcrap prize.
They gave it to Kissinger.
Welcome to the Escape Zone,
the latest attempt to get people
to save a dying mall.
Now, would you like
to be buried alive?
Done it for real.
How about Medieval Dungeon?
Got to be less torture
than listening to him. Hey.
Thank you.
Okay, you two are trapped
in a dungeon.
The only way out is to solve
ten puzzles by working together.
Yeah, whatever.
Super!
They're just sitting there.
I bet they'd hurry
if they knew we had balloons.
They're moving.
Son, if you take this sword and
stick it in that magic portal,
I think it might open
a bookcase somewhere.
Yes, that makes
perfect sense. I'll just...
Homer? You're not getting out
to say good-bye to your dad?
He's probably afraid
we'll see how much
the car lifts when he gets out.
No, I'm not.
There's only one way
to make you guys understand.
I'll tell you
what Grampa told me.
That was in confidence.
And in this family, we keep
our promises. Starting now.
I am telling!
Oh, God. Oh, God.
I hate conflict.
- Then just leave your body.
- Okay.
Hey!
When I was growing up,
my dad loved to make
model World War II airplanes.
Watch it, son.
You're gonna break the wing.
Oh, now you got glue
up your nose.
Don't eat the decal.
How many have you had?
Just leave me be.
I work hard all week
at the model plane factory,
and this hobby is my one escape.
Can you please watch
this little monster?
When he gave me to her,
it was the best thing
he could've done.
- This is the dough.
- Dough.
Yes, dough. Now, I need someone
very strong to roll this out.
Recipes
For the oven in my mind
3x5 cards with the recipes
Of my mother's pies
Apple cobbler
Peach pie, key lime,
and meringue
Pies made for me
by my mother
While my father
would harangue
Can it be that
It was all so tasty then?
Was her rhubarb
So sublime?
If we had the chance
To bake it all again
Tell me, would we?
Could we?
Love you.
She loved me.
And for each pie she made,
she wrote down the recipe
and put a special note to me
on the back.
We don't know
what life will bring,
so on your birthday
or any day you need it,
you'll know
that your mother loved you
and have reasons
to love yourself.
You just taught me food is love.
I like myself.
That lunch box
was the most valuable
possession I ever had.
When she left,
those recipes
were all I had left of her.
And that's the end.
What a sweet story.
And there's some things
that shouldn't be gone into
until a man is dead
and can't be kicked.
After she ran away,
my father was furious
and did something terrible.
He threw my recipes
off a cliff.
Everything
that reminded him of her.
He lied to me.
He told me she took the recipes
with her when she left.
Are you sure, Daddy?
Yes. And don't ask me again
till I'm on my deathbed.
Wait.
Why are you looking like that?
If this man had had those notes,
his life
would've been different.
He would've had confidence.
He would've had
his mother with him!
I would've had hair!
Homie, that's not
very realistic.
And I would've been
more realistic.
Grampa, so thoughtless.
- Mean old man.
- His slippers don't even have bottoms anymore.
I never thought I'd say this
word, but here it comes, coot.
Homer, why are you smiling?
We're finally hating together
as a family.
What do you say we all go
to that home and yell at Grampa?
Oh, that would be lovely.
Now enjoy
this sweet song of hate.
If I could save hate
in a bottle
The first thing
that I'd like to do
Is to hate every day
Till eternity passes away
Then end
with a giant screw you
But there never seems
to be enough time
To hate the things
you want to hate
Once you hate them
- Lousy Grampa.
- So heartless.
Always calls me
buddy or fella.
Don't forget
he's hard of hearing.
Lousy Grampa!
So heartless!
What you did was crap, Grampa!
- I want to yell at him first.
Hey, has anyone considered
the silent treatment?
The silent treatment
doesn't work.
It doesn't work.
It does not work.
Okay, fine, it works.
It works so well.
Please say something.
How long has it been?
Three months?
I don't even remember
a time before this.
Where's Grampa?
- He hasn't touched his lunch.
- Or his lunch meds.
My beloved family...
Oh, boy.
I've learned
an important lesson,
never get things
off your chest.
Which reminds me of a gal
named Chesty Lazar.
She ran a speakeasy on Hawaii
right before Pearl Harbor.
Pearl Harbor
was the name of the lady
who bought the joint...
Digression, digression...
Crazy talk...
Ah, here's the end.
The point is,
confessing don't really
make you feel better,
'cause it don't redo
the bad thing you did.
So I'm gonna undo what I done
if it's the last thing I do.
Oh, no. He's heading for that
cliff to look for those recipes.
I'm gonna find him, save him,
and tell him I can't wait
till he dies.
Leave me alone!
I'm gonna find it!
Don't do it, Dad!
Most is forgiven!
Wait, what's your rope tied to?
Oh, my God.
Please be okay. Please be okay.
Don't worry, son.
This will give you
all the rope you need.
Dad, no! I love you!
Mom left, but you were there.
Cranky, a little drunk,
sometimes not there,
but you were always there.
Oh, you love me.
That's all I need to hear.
Good thing I also threw out
your mother's bed when she left.
I can still smell her perfume.
And I've got the recipes back.
They're gone, just like Mom.
- I'm sorry, son.
- It's okay, Dad.
Life doesn't always give you
neat endings
that tie everything up in a bow.
This pie is fantastic.
It's what I imagine eating
great jazz would be like.
Always with the jazz.
It tastes exactly like
my mom used to make.
Exactly!
Excuse me, how the hell
did you get this recipe?
It was a miracle, actually.
33 years ago,
this place wasn't doing well,
possibly due to our location
under a cliff.
I went out to contemplate
my fate...
when, suddenly, like a gift
from God, the recipes came.
I'd never seen such recipes,
such brilliant
fruit combinations
and such beautiful messages
on the back.
Those messages were for me.
Well, then you should have them.
Everything tied up in a bow.
What's it say?
It says...
Your father is an okay guy.
- Thanks for telling me.
- Thanks for buying it.
Mr. Simpson,
based on your budget,
I am afraid there's only one car
on this lot you can afford.
You know this car?
Do I!
I thought
that's where you were.
Geez, what's wrong with her?