♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
♪♪
Tonight on Eye on Springfield,
just miles from your doorstep,
hundreds of men are given
weapons and trained to kill.
The government
calls it the Army.
But a more alarmist name
would be:
The Kill-bot Factory--
But first, Springfield
has come down with a fever,
football fever,
brought on by the biggest game
of the year.
The pigskin classic between
the Shelbyville Sharks
and our own
Springfield Atoms.
If you have the fever,
there's only one cure:
Take two tickets and see
the game Sunday morning.
ANNOUNCER: Warning:
Tickets should not be taken internally.
See? Because of me,
now they have a warning.
Hey, Dad, sell you these
for 50 bucks.
-Whoo-hoo! Sold!
-(door slams)
Those aren't tickets
to the game, Homer.
What do you mean?
It says right here:
"Free wig with every purchase
of large wig. Downtown Wig Center."
Why, you little--
Hmm. Free wig.
(humming)
(imitating Marge)
I love you, Homie. Mmm.
(chuckling)
I don't need her at all anymore.
(chattering)
(snoring)
(yawns)
(chuckling)
I did it. Second in line.
And all I had to do
was miss eight days of work.
With the money you
would have made working,
you could've bought tickets
from a scalper.
In theory, yes.
Jerk.
-(yelps)
-Give me, uh, 30,000 tickets.
That'll be $950,000 please.
Look, the thing about that is
I only got $10 on me.
-Can I pay you the rest later?
-Sure.
Ohh.
MAN:
♪ Whoo-hoo-hoo ♪
(fingers snapping)
RADIO DJ: That was Bobby
McFerrin's new one,
"I'm Worried, Need Money."
Okay, if you want two tickets
to the big pigskin classic--
-(pig snorting)
-(DJ laughing)
Just get to a phone
and be our 13th caller.
Get tickets! Must get tickets!
Find phone! Yes!
Ho-ho.
Stupid sheep.
-(Homer shouting)
-(tires deflating)
DJ: Still waiting
for that caller.
(whimpering)
Oh, we have a winner!
What's your name, sir?
NED: Ned Flanders.
Oh, not Flanders.
Anybody but Flanders.
NED: Oh, golly. If that doesn't
put the "Shaz" In "Shazam."
Oh, listen.
What's the cash value of those tickets
so I can report it
on my income tax?
(groans, shrieks)
♪ I've got two tickets
to paradise ♪
♪ Won't you pack your bags
we'll leave tonight ♪
♪ I've got two tickets
to paradise ♪
(imitating guitar riff)
Excellent guitar riff.
Why am I such a loser? Why?
Well, your father was a loser,
and his father, and his father.
It's genetic, man.
D'oh!
What's so special
about this game anyway?
It's just another chapter
in the pointless rivalry
between Springfield
and Shelbyville.
They built a mini-mall,
so we built a bigger mini-mall.
They made the world's
largest pizza,
so we burnt down
their city hall.
(chuckles)
Yeah, they swore they'd get us back
by spiking our water supply.
But they didn't
have the guts.
Ohh, the walls
are melting again.
(chuckling)
Personally I think
I'm overdone.
God, if you really are God,
you'll get me tickets
to that game.
(doorbell rings)
Hidilly-ho, neighbor.
Wanna go to the game with me?
I got two tickets.
(grunts)
Why do you mock me, O Lord?
Homer, that's not God.
That's just a waffle
that Bart tossed up there.
Mmm. I know
I shouldn't eat thee, but--
(growling)
Mmm. "Sacrilicious."
(doorbell chimes)
-MARGE: Homer!
-Huh?
Are you planning to hit
Ned Flanders with that pipe
and take his tickets?
Ye-- No.
-Hmm?
-Oh.
Flanders, I decided I'd like to go
to the game with you.
(chuckles) Well, get out the Crayolas
and color me tickled pink.
Ooh, what's with the lead pipe?
Were you gonna give
my noggin a floggin'?
Well, yeah.
(chuckles)
(laughs)
(chattering)
(gasps)
Duck!
I can't let the boys
see me with you!
-What? (grunts)
-Hi.
Hey! Look, Homer's got
one of those robot cars.
(crashes)
One of those
American robot cars.
Men, there's
a little crippled boy
sitting in the hospital
who wants you to win this game.
I know because I crippled him myself
to inspire you.
Well, I hope they win,
or Mr. Burns
said he's coming back.
Wow! These are amazing seats,
huh, Homer?
Yeah.
Hey, everybody!
Here comes fun!
(chuckles)
Ow!
I'll take two dogs,
two sodas,
and, uh,
two ice cream bars.
What the hell happened
to my dogs?
I want answers.
Well, I guess
I should pay my share.
(chuckling)
Relax, Homer.
I keep telling you.
You're my guest.
Ooh, you brought me
a nacho hat!
Thanks, ned.
♪ Nacho, nacho man ♪
♪ I want to be a nacho man ♪
(crowd cheering)
Blue 27 on three.
If anyone can pull it off,
it's Stan "The Boy" Taylor!
(muttering)
Stan, Stan, he's our boy.
If he can't do it, no one...
will.
Hut!
(grunting)
(blowing whistle)
We won!
We won, Flanders!
Whoo!
(kissing)
(murmuring)
(chuckling)
Yeah.
Losers! Losers!
Kiss my big Springfield behind,
Shelbyville!
Whoo! Ha-ha!
I am invincible!
Invincible! You're--
Ow! Oh!
(chattering)
Hey, somebody sign
an autograph.
Please, somebody.
Sign an autograph?
Hey, would you sign--
You fat, stupid jerks!
-Hmm?
-It was him!
Ned? Is that--
Ned Flanders?
Hidilly-ho, Stanster.
You know Stan Taylor?
Know me?
Ned Flanders saved me.
I used to party all night
and sleep with lingerie models
until Ned
and his bible group
showed me
that I could have more.
Professional athletes--
Always wantin' more.
Ned, they gave me the game ball.
I want you to have it.
-(gasps)
-Stan, tell you what.
Homer Simpson here is just about
the biggest Atom fan
that's ever
graced God's green earth.
I bet he'd enjoy it
even more than me.
Sure. Anything for Neddy.
Here you go.
Wow, thanks.
Now I have four children.
You will be called
"Stitchface."
Wow, Flanders. This is about the nicest
thing anyone's ever done for me.
Ooh, I guess it's time
for me to duck again.
No! I want everyone
to know that
this is Ned Flanders,
my friend!
-What did he say?
-I don't know.
Something about being gay.
Homer,
that's our wedding photo.
Marge, quit living
in the past.
(groans)
Heydilly-ho, window buddy.
Just wondering if you'd like
to come over and give
the new pool table a whirl.
I'll be there.
And this time
you can be the nacho man.
Dad and Ned Flanders friends?
Heh. What's next?
A's on Bart's report card?
Hey!
Uh, be careful there, Homer.
That is sort of a new table.
(chuckles)
Watch this, Ned.
They don't call me
Springfield Fats
just because
I'm morbidly obese.
(gasps)
Now you got a lawsuit
on your hands.
Just kidding.
-What's wrong, Jeremiah?
-It's not fair.
My brother Joseph
has a sin to confess.
I wish I had one too.
Oh, don't you see?
You do have a sin to confess.
The sin of envy.
(bleating)
That's all well and
good for sheep,
but what are
we to do?
Boring!
Let's watch something else.
Aww!
Now, boys.
Mr. Simpson is the guest.
He gets to decide what to watch.
-Yeah.
-(clicking remote control)
Hey, what gives?
I thought you had a satellite dish.
Sure didilly do.
Over 230 channels locked out.
Okay, boys, time for bed.
Say good night.
Good night, Daddy!
Good night, Uncle Homer!
Oh, Uncle Homer.
Ned, since you've let me
spend time with your family,
I want you
to get to know my family.
-Hey, everyone!
-Hey.
I'd like to introduce
Ned Flanders, my best friend.
Hey, I don't want no people in here
with their "Evils of alcohol" Rap.
Wait a second. You're the man at
the hospital who reads to sick children.
"And truly, she was my friend Flicka."
(sniffs)
-(gasps)
-If this gets out, the next words you say
will be muffled
by your own butt!
(tires screech)
Honey, I'm so glad
you're home.
Can't talk. See Flanders.
-Later sex.
-(groaning)
Bless the grocer
for this wonderful meat,
the middleman
who jacked up the price.
And let's not forget
the humane but determined boys
over at the slaughterhouse.
Hiya, Flanders.
Ooh, dinner.
May I join you?
(grunts)
-(gasps)
-Mmm.
(gasps)
(chuckling) Homer,
I'd love to chitty-chat,
but tonight's the night
I do my charity work.
Uh, yeah.
A judge made me do that once too.
Stupid lack
of public urinals.
Hey, just so you don't
have to suffer alone,
I'm coming with you!
Oh-- Heh, well--
(chuckles)
That sounds super duper.
Oh, you poor,
unfortunate man.
Let's get you out of
those clothes immediately.
And we'll do whatever we can
about the smell.
But I-- All right.
Oh, come on!
We've been here for 15 minutes.
Can't you see they're
sucking the life out of us?
Homer, maybe you'd have
more fun at Moe's tonight.
Ah, for some reason, Moe's always
closed on Wednesdays.
"And then they realized
they were no longer little girls.
They were little women."
(sniffs)
Come on. Come on!
Just give 'em the slop
and let's get out of here.
Oh, I can do it
faster than that!
Mmm, mmm. Mmm, mmm.
Mmm, mmm.
Wow!
Look at that enthusiasm!
This is front-page material.
Homie, I'm very proud
of you.
But don't you think you're spending
too much time with Ned?
Your family
needs you too.
Oh, of course you'd say
something like that, Marge.
You've hated Ned for years.
In fact, you wanted to
bash his head in with a pipe.
That was you!
Love, Marge.
Don't hate. Love.
The Flanders are
a bunch of geeks, man.
The "Flandereses"
are not geeks!
Okay. Rod and Todd are.
And the wife has a thing for me.
But she hides it behind a mask
of low-key hostility.
But we've got to
give this thing a chance.
I want the two families to take
a trip together this weekend.
-No way, Jose.
-Yes way.
Don't worry, Bart.
It seems like every week
something odd happens
to the Simpsons.
My advice is to ride it out,
make an occasional
smart-aleck quip,
and by next week, we'll be back
to where we started from,
ready for another
wacky adventure.
-Ay, caramba!
-That's the spirit.
Don't worry.
I brought my
"Rappin' Ronnie Reagan" tape.
It always makes
the trip go faster.
♪ Well, well, well ♪
♪ W-w-w-w-w-w-well, well, well♪
(chuckling)
You know something?
He did say "well" A lot.
♪ Well, well, well
w-w-well, w-w-well ♪
♪ Well, well, w-w-w-well
well, well, well, well ♪
More. No, no,
keep going.
More. More.
Right there. Let her go.
Okay, let's go boating!
-How are my boys doin', Homer?
-They're fine.
There. I hope the children
enjoy my special fruit punch.
We got the recipe from
the fruit punch advisory board.
Oh, gosh. I'm sorry.
Our boys don't eat sugar.
But why would the advisory board
give us bad advice?
-No sugar!
-(both groaning)
Thank you,
but we're not allowed.
Ah, it's okay.
There's no sugar in pixie sticks.
-Trust me.
-Okay. Hmm.
-Don't hog it all, smelly head!
-Go to hell, zit face!
-Give me that sugar cane!
-(both groaning)
(cackling)
I'd like to propose a toast
to the coming together
of the Simpsons
and the Flanders.
If this were
a more perfect world,
we'd all be known
as the Flimpsons.
So here's to
my best friend, Ned.
(sighs)
Well, sir,
my entire family
is very touched and--
-Food fight!
-BART: Yeah!
HOMER: ♪ Da-na-na
na-na-na-na, na-na ♪
Mmm.
(all shouting)
(grunting)
-Whatcha doin'?
-We're headin' back.
Todd's got Zesty Italian
in his eye.
Okay. But at least let me take
the boat out for one last spin.
-Oh, I don't know.
-Too late!
(groans) Oh, Lord,
please give me the strength
to endure
Homer Simpson's friendship.
-(boat engine revving)
-(Homer shouting)
(crashes)
Hmm, your car.
Boy, what are the odds, huh?
(chuckling)
Cheers to Homer Simpson
for all his recent charity work!
ALL: Yea!
(grunting)
Jeers to this rusty tailgate.
(whistling hymn)
There's Homer.
There's Homer too.
(screaming)
That's also Homer.
That's Homer!
Huh?
(groans)
-(shouts)
-What's the matter, Ned?
I-- I think I hate
Homer Simpson.
(gasps)
(yells)
Marge, I think I
hate Ted Koppel.
No, wait. I find him
informative and witty.
Night.
(snoring)
-Off the rim!
-Oh! Almost.
Boy, that was close.
Hey, what's up
for today, Neddy?
Uh-- (sighs)
Ah, Homer, we're gonna visit
the boys' grandmother.
Family only, you know?
-Right. No reporters.
-(Ned sighs)
No. I-- I-- I mean
just the Flanders family.
Oh, okay.
Oh, boy! Grandma!
-We're not going anywhere.
-But you said--
Uh, sometimes to keep from
hurting someone's feelings,
we have to say things
that aren't exactly--
Lies make
baby Jesus cry.
(sighs)
Neddy! Neddy!
Let's get in a quick nine
down at the Pitch 'n' Putt.
(engine revving,
tires screeching)
Neddy! Neddy!
-(groaning)
-He's gaining on us!
-I'm scared!
-(crying)
Come on, Ned!
Move this thing!
I can't! It's a Geo!
(grunting)
(screaming)
-(groaning)
(groaning)
Hmm. I guess
he didn't see me.
We did it!
We got rid of--
(siren blaring)
(chuckling)
I told you, officer.
I'm not hepped up
on goofballs.
Yeah, right.
Ned Flanders.
I never would have imagined.
(gasping)
Oh-- Oh-- Ah--
Oh-- Oof!
High as a kite, everybody!
Goofballs!
Yeah, where's your messiah
now, Flanders? Ah.
(bells tolling)
Oh, I can't do it, Maude.
I can't face
their accusing eyes.
Oh, don't worry, Ned.
This is a house
of love and forgiveness.
-There he is, Ned Flanders.
-The fallen one.
The evil one.
I bet he's the one that wrote
"Homer" all over the bathroom.
Oh, I think
we should leave.
Hey, Flanders, over here!
I got us some kick-ass seats!
(moans)
(clearing throat)
Before I get started
on today's sermon, entitled
"What Ned did,"
I'd like to publicly congratulate
Homer Simpson on his recent charity work.
-(applauding)
-(kissing)
I live to give.
(moans)
That's beautiful.
We appreciate the kisses.
Now, let us bow our heads
in a silent prayer of thanksgiving.
(nose whistling)
(whistling continues)
Stop it! Breathe through
your damn mouth!
-Oh!
-(gasping)
Oh, can't you see
this man isn't a hero?
He's annoying.
He's very, very annoying!
Well, Ned Flanders
is just jealous.
Ah, the guy's hepped up
on goofballs.
Let's sacrifice him
to our god!
Come on. We did it all
the time in the '30s.
(chattering)
Stop it! Stop it!
Stop it!
(gasps)
How dare you talk about
Ned Flanders like that.
He's a wonderful,
kind, caring man.
Maybe even more so than me.
There have been times
when I lost patience with him,
even lashed out at him,
but this man has turned
every cheek on his body.
If everyone here
were like Ned Flanders,
there'd be no need
for heaven.
We'd already be there.
(group sighs)
(clears throat)
Um--
Well, I think we all owe
Ned a heartfelt apology.
We were wrong
to doubt him.
-Hey, that guy's right!
-Yeah.
(chattering)
That was a very nice thing
you did, Homie.
(sniffs)
Thank you.
Thank you so much,
Homer.
You really are a--
(sniffs)
-You're a true friend.
-Right back at ya, buddy.
(moans) Now, how about
that game at the Pitch 'N' Putt?
Just try and stop me.
I don't get it, Lise. You said everything
would be back to normal.
But Homer and Flanders
are still friends.
Yeah. Maybe this means the
end of our wacky adventures.
Guess what, everyone!
My great-uncle Boris died
and left us
his old country house!
There's only one catch.
They say it's haunted.
But I'm sure
we can prove 'em wrong
by spending the weekend there.
-Hididilly-ho, neighbor!
-Get lost, Flanders.
Okilly-dokilly.
(both sigh)
-(wolf howling)
-(bat screeching)
HOMER: See, I told ya.
There's nothin' to worry about.
-This place isn't--
-(Simpsons scream)
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.