D'oh!
Dad, we're four episodes early.
Here it is, Myra...
the key to the trophy case.
If we'd ever won a trophy,
I would've turned
the heck out of it.
I can't believe
you're retiring, sir.
Martin, I must ask you to keep
secret what you just heard...
the shocking news
that I'm retiring.
Sir, you are addressing
a student safety monitor.
With diagonal belt comes
great responsibility.
I've got a secret! Firsties!
What?!
Skinner's quitting!
I won the pool!
Guess who's renting two
songs from iTunes!
Skinner's retiring!
Bombardment!
He will be missed!
He stood up for me when they
tried to ban bombardment!
Bombardment!
My fellow Americans,
and Uter...
the rumors are true.
I'm resigning the principality
effective Taco Tuesday.
Seymour, you will be missed.
And now, the flyover by
the Permission Slip Angels.
My distance-vision eye.
Skinner leaving. One last
chance to honor him...
with a shot to the head.
Move it.
Come on, Bart! Take the shot!
I don't have the damn shot!
Now, in honor of our
principal's retirement,
we'll have a performance
from a super talent
who's gonna wrap up
our feelings.
I can't believe
this is good-bye
You were like a mommy
who wears a tie
You once called men
who put me in a net
You always told me
when I was wet
They said I had to wait
two years to do karate
Even though my friend who is
the same age is in the class
Karate!
There's a certain
lack of elegance
in rhyming karate
with karate.
Karate!
Now, I'll share a fond farewell
with one student chosen at
random to represent you all.
Bart Simpson.
There is a God, and his
name is the Devil.
Bart, come forward.
In the words of the late
David Bowie, né Jones.
Ch-Ch-Ch-Changes.
All rights reserved, Ziggy
Stardust Publishing.
Gotcha!
No. Got you!
Now, Willie! The honey!
Simpson, I'm not retiring.
This was all
just a prank on you.
Leave him alone!
Where do I go?
How do I live this down?
Mom, my humiliation
bath is getting cold.
Hold still. You've got
honey in your pits.
Sticky.
Bombardment!
Oh, Nelsoned by Largo.
I'll get them back.
I'll get them all back.
And that'll be
the end of it forever.
Not good enough!
What are you gonna do, Bart?
Wait, wait, wait. Don't tell me.
I'll have nightmares,
like the one where I'm wearing
my pajamas during the daytime.
You are wearing your pajamas.
Some day I want to be
a racecar driver.
Do you know
how many get killed?
They don't show
that on the pajamas!
Pranking Bart was
my Sergeant Peppers,
after a lifetime of
Back Off Boogaloos.
What the...? Simpson!
My skin!
Hey, Brandine.
These woods is filled
with scary white people.
What else is new?
Bait the traps.
Mama needs
a new people coat.
Thanks to one vengeful
prankster, clowns...
once a source of delight...
have now become more twisted
than the balloon animals they
wrap their creepy hands around.
We only hope
that by showing it on TV,
no one goes out
and copies it.
Now, let's tell you
how it's done.
Send your copycat videos
to Kent's Krazy Klown
Karnival of Kartoon Karnage.
Upside down and inside out,
and you can feel it...
Oh, no. No. Now people have
to judge us by our music.
We're doomed.
20 seconds to air.
How many times have
I told you not to wake me
till it's two seconds to air?
Krusty, I have to warn you.
People's attitudes
have changed about...
Hey-hey, kids!
Calm down, children.
I'm here.
The shirtless man with
the bone through his skull
and a grass skirt with
nothing down under.
I tried to warn you.
People hate clowns now.
And the advertisers
want to meet with you.
What is it with Bart
and these pranks?
- I don't get it.
- I don't know.
Boys will be boys.
That's another thing I don't get.
What does that mean?
Spoons will be spoons.
But they don't make you
go to juvenile court
at 8:00 in the morning.
Yo. If we hurry, we can get
those breakfast burritos
- they serve at the courthouse.
- Those are good, Marge.
Children's Court of Springfield
is now in session.
Apologies.
Divorced dad, no sitter.
That must be really tough, Judge.
I raised a turtle by myself.
Pure hell.
Milhouse said he'd help,
and he just walked away.
Let me look at your file, son.
Your Honor,
I can save you some time.
I've done it all, juvie,
state juvie, groovy juvie,
the Montessori prison,
Outward and Inward Bound.
So you're down to
fry me or free me.
What can I say?
I'm a widdle dickens.
Well, Bart, based on the
ancient judicial principle
boys will be boys...
- I'm going to hand down a suspended...
- No!
Marge, for once, let us
get rich people justice.
No. Judge, I love my son, but
he's got a real problem.
He needs to learn the
meaning of consequences.
Bart, I sentence you to 28 days
at the Tomorrow's New Horizons
Addiction Rehab Center
and General Rotten Time Ranch.
Mom, how could you
do that to me?
- Yeah, Mom.
- Because I love you, Bart.
And a mother's
toughest job is saying...
help me,
my kid has a problem.
I do not! All I ask is,
Dad, while I'm gone,
will you hold onto my
can of peanut brittle?
Anything for you, son.
Snakes!
Gotcha!
Why you little...!
The snakes ate
all the peanut brittle.
I don't know.
I don't know
if I did the right thing.
Comfort me.
Oh, Marge, part of being
a parent is doing things
that'll make your child
never speak to you again.
Oh, no, honey,
I didn't mean never.
Definitely on his deathbed.
When he's dying.
I had to do it.
He was out of control.
Look what he did to Krusty.
I feel terrible for his writers.
I beat you
if you don't flip sign.
Flip, flip, flip, flip, flip!
What are you here for?
To laugh at me?
- No.
- Please laugh at me!
I don't exist
unless you laugh at me!
Look what you've done to me!
He looks just like me!
And Maggie looks just like Lisa.
And Milhouse's mother looks
just like Milhouse's father.
Why is this universe so lazy?
Never mind that.
Krusty, our son's prank
caused this.
We're gonna help you.
Forget it. I'm finished.
- Wait, wait.
- What?
You can still work.
What if you gave up comedy,
and transitioned
to serious acting?
Impossible.
I've never shown genuine
emotion in my life.
I'm even reading this
off a card.
Okay, next card.
But seriously,
I gotta speak from the...
next card... heart.
I can't be a dramatic actor.
I have all the depth
of a foot bath.
Next card. Skip that one.
Next card.
A lot of funny actors have
transitioned to drama.
Tom Hanks, Albert Brooks.
I'm not convinced.
- Michael Keaton.
- I'm in.
- Zach Braff.
- Now I'm not so sure.
- Bryan Cranston.
- I'm in. And hopeful.
Greetings! I am your director,
Llewellyn Sinclair,
and you are
the Barbies and Kens
whom I shall pose
in my Malibu beach house
of thespic triumph.
My choice for our play
is Arthur Miller's
Death of a Salesman.
However,
the rights cost too much,
so we'll be doing this knockoff
version, The Salesman's Bad Day.
Don't worry,
the text is just Play-Doh
to be extruded through
the Fun Factory
of my Tony Award
watching genius.
To play Willie Salesman, please
welcome the man who's taking
a bold leap into
intentional unfunniness,
and giving me a ride
home tonight,
and maybe more, hmm?
Mr. Herschel Krustofsky.
Hey-hey.
Let me see the script.
My line. My line. Garbage.
Garbage. My line.
I don't know.
Should I really be doing this?
I'm an out-of-work has-been
whose next logical step
is to take his own life.
And that's exactly what
Death of a Salesman is about.
I thought this was
The Salesman's Bad Day.
And that's exactly
what I said.
Anyone hear different?
I thought not!
But Krusty,
the part of Willie Loman,
I mean Salesman,
is perfect for you.
You'll just be playing yourself.
- Can I play someone I like?
- No.
I know he can't see me, but
can he still feel my love?
I'm afraid the glass
blocks that too.
Marge, I promise I will
make your boy whole.
I want to believe that
so much.
I'll never forget
how peaceful he was
in those moments before he
took his very first breath.
Bart, you act like you
don't have a problem,
but deep down,
you know you need help.
No way. I am awesome.
Sit down and I'll elaborate.
I think I'll need some help.
Marge, could you come in here?
Please, take my seat.
We need to get to
the bottom of this.
Right to the point.
No, no, no!
Oh, well, maybe I should try
a different tack.
Mom, don't sit down!
I don't want to hurt you.
Okay, you just completed
step one, learning empathy.
Pop, look.
I am losing the weight.
Come on, Krusty!
There's raw emotion just
beneath your surface.
Frack it!
Oh, I don't know, I'm scared.
The theater is not for cowards.
All I ask for is integrity
and honesty
in The Salesman's Bad Day.
Title may change.
Now, Herschel, summon
that talent you've hidden
from the entire world
for 60 years.
I can't!
Hershel, my son, listen
to me and listen good.
You are a once-in-a-generation
performer.
You think so?
No! I was faking it.
And if I can do it, so can you.
And now, become a great actor.
And now, sense memory.
And now, be present.
And articulate!
- And we breathe.
- Oh, okay.
And great actor.
I'm sorry, my sons.
Clench butt.
I'm finished as a salesman.
Clenchier.
The only thing I have left
worth anything is...
Transport me
to another plane.
My life insurance.
But, Pop, that only
pays off if you're...
Big pause.
Dead.
Your pop is gonna go out
on his route, boys.
One last time.
No, Pop. No.
Tell your mother I'm sorry
about the woman in Boston!
Also, my death is a metaphor
for American industry!
I'm doing it. I'm doing it!
And I'll be fine, unless I get
those voices in my head.
You can't act.
You're a clown, and that's
all you'll ever be.
And when you die,
they'll be playing this.
No.
No. Stop it.
No! No! No!
Anything wrong, Krusty?
Only what's tormented me
my entire life.
Very good.
See you tomorrow.
Reverend, I'm here
for my last step.
To make amends for the
rotten things I've done.
Oh, fine.
Let me get into uniform.
I'm sorry I cut all the
Bible ribbons short
so no one could mark
their place.
Why you son of a...
Willie, I'm sorry
I shaved your beard.
I've had to wear
a merkin on me face.
I also had the blades removed
from your lawnmower.
You've just been
riding around.
No one interferes
with me mowing!
And I'm sorry I used
your baseball chalker
to write Skinner Sucks.
I'll show you who su...
Wait, you can do that?
Please don't encourage me.
Thank you for encouraging me.
We're out of chalk.
You know, I had
just completed rehab.
Well, me too.
America loves a lot of things,
but I never dreamed a
comeback was one of them.
- Tell me, Krusty.
- No, no.
No more of the K word.
I'm a serious actor now.
If only my father could see me.
Oh, I see you. Son, you
used to be a putz.
Now you're a putz trying
to be a schmendrick,
which makes you
a schmeckle.
Get out of my head!
Yet another puff piece
that ends in madness.
I know you lost the love
of Linda Ellerbee
while we were launching
the luge
at the Olympics
in Lillehammer.
B-B-B-Brokaw.
Bart Simpson
cured of pranking?
I never thought
I'd see it.
And you haven't.
Look up there.
Water balloons,
ready to drop.
It's times like this
I'm glad I have eyebrows.
Sweetie, I've never been
prouder of you.
I knew my little bad seed
could bloom into a flower.
You're proud of me?
That's right.
Now go give that speech
and know that sitting in that
audience will be your mother,
who's always believed in you.
Nothing can rain
on my parade today.
I... I... I... Run!
Simpson!
Motherhood sucks.
Boys will be boys.
You can't come in here.
This is the boys
will be boys room.
Tonight, you will make
theatrical history.
You'll take a play
that has been seen
all over the world more
times than man can count,
and you will do
the best version ever.
How do I know? Because
I just took six Valiums.
See you outside.
You'll never get rid of me.
You'll always be
a self-hating clown.
When I was 17,
I walked into the Amazon.
The company, not the river.
And when I was 21,
I walked out.
And, man, was I loaded.
Thank you, Jeff Bezos.
Listen to your uncle, boys.
He's a great man.
The audience is quiet.
That means you're bombing.
Quick, you got to get a laugh.
Drop your pants,
show your fanny.
You know,
your A material.
Get out of my head.
I... am...
a serious actor!
Laughs? I'm getting laughs.
- And not from a machine.
- Go with it.
I'm a salesman
A dying salesman
I'm Willie Loman
Just watch me go, man
I'm gonna suck
That old gas pipe
Pipe, pipe
Whatever doesn't kill me
makes the play longer.
This play will run forever.
Okay, but now
that I'm big again,
I can't work Tuesdays,
Thursdays,
the month of July, or Toronto
Raptors' home games.
I'm the Spike Lee of that team.
Standard exemptions.
I love it.
He fails at everything he can
His sons can't stand their old man
It's sell, sell, sell
Till he dies, dies, dies
In a car crash
All's well that ends well.
How did it end well?
He's ruining my play.
Well, don't worry. You've got
plenty of other good plays.
Oh, wait. You don't.
Hey, I'm America's
greatest playwright.
Exactly.