♪ The Simpsons ♪
(chalk screeches)
(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(tires screeching)
(horn honks)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
(growling)
Hey, Homer, let's book!
I want to get there in time
to whip eggs at the warm-up act.
Wow, my concert-going jacket
still fits.
And this is where
I used to hide my beer.
(gasps)
Billy beer!
(gulping)
My little guy's
first rock concert.
I hope The Spinal Taps
don't play too loud.
Oh Marge, I went to thousands
of heavy metal concerts
and it never hurt me.
(loud, high-pitched ringing
drowning out Marge's voice)
I hear you.
Come on, boy.
There goes
Davy Crockett
in his bald-skin cap.
(laughing)
(growling)
D.J.:
In other Spinal Tap news
Mayor Quimby honored
the aging super group
in a ceremony
at City Hall.
D.J. #2: I guess you could
say he was trying to "Tap" into the
"spines" of the
young voters, huh?
D.J.:
Uh, yeah. Let's play the tape.
(honking horn)
Hey, Milhouse, cool jacket.
It cost me 50,000
Bazooka Joe comics.
Now just meet me back here
after the show.
Thanks, Dad.
Sure you're not
gonna be bored?
Boy, some of the best times
I've ever had
were in the back seat
of a car.
(chuckling)
(shocks squeaking)
HOMER:
Ohhh...
Oh, baby.
(grunting with pleasure)
Ahh.
Official tour '92
T-shirts, $31.
Check it out--
Spinal Tap kicking
Moammar Gadhafy
in the butt.
The timeless classic,
now 2 for $1.
Hey, hey, hey,
Bill and Marty here.
And we're backstage rapping
with the Tap.
Fellas, I'm gonna hit you with
a phrase that has dogged you
throughout your career--
"Washed up."
Yet here you are, among the top
105 concert acts today.
What's your secret, guys?
Well, after
the Berlin Wall fell,
our records started selling
on the dismal side
of the Iron Curtain,
and naturally that gave
us a boost.
We're very big in Bulgaria,
and what's-his-name?
The other Garia.
-Hungaria?
-Yeah, whatever.
I can't think of anyone
who's benefitted
more from the death
of Communism than us.
Maybe the people who actually
live in the communist countries.
Oh yeah, I hadn't thought of that.
I bet you're right.
On the other hand, each of us just
bought our own soccer team.
How many Hungarios
can say that, eh?
Test... test...
Gee, I'm sorry, man.
Huh?
About the Frisbee.
Frisbee?
Say, guys,
I wonder if you'd mind
recording a couple
of promos for us?
Like what?
Maybe you could say
"Nobody rocks like
Bill and Marty on KBBL."
We don't know that,
do we?
What if somebody rocks
as good as you?
Or better. I mean...
We don't want to look stupid.
Okay, we can respect that.
How about,
"Rock-a-doodle-doo!
You're listening
to Bill and Marty"?
-Yeah, sure.
-That's good, yeah.
(chanting)
Tap! Tap! Tap!
I just looked out there,
and there's puddles of water
all over
the freakin' stage.
Well, I don't want
to lie to you boys.
Six days a week the place
is a hockey rink.
Well, this is
a rock concert
not the bleedin'...
splish-splash show.
Ladies and gentlemen,
boys and girls...
Duff beer, in association
with Laramie cigarettes,
is proud to welcome Spinal Tap!
♪ We are the children
who grew too fast ♪
♪ We are the dust
of a future past ♪
♪ We raise our voices
in the night ♪
♪ Crying to heaven ♪
♪ And will our voices
be heard ♪
♪ Or will they break
like the wind? ♪
Medium setting.
(jazz music playing)
(humming to radio tune)
(playing instrumental break)
Thank you!
(squealing)
(grunting)
All right!
This morning
we were driving down...
Route 401...
(loud cheering)
That's only four miles
from my house!
And we thought they knew
how to rock in Shelbyville.
(jeering)
But nobody rocks like...
Springfield!
(wild cheering)
(playing hard rock intro)
Well, it seems
some silly twit
did not get a
big enough oxygen pump,
but that's supposed
to be a devil.
Filled up with air,
it's very evil and impressive.
We salute you,
our half-inflated dark lord!
-Oy!
CROWD:
Oy!
(playing solo)
(cheering)
You know, people think there are
only five members of Spinal Tap,
but they are wrong.
(coughing)
Could we turn up
the house lights, please?
That was the cue to turn up
the house lights
so we can tell
the audience
they're the sixth member
of the freakin' group!
We are trying
to put a tiny thrill
into their gray little lives.
Oh, forget it.
Turn on the lasers.
Aah! My vision.
That's it.
Show's over.
Good night, Springden.
There will be no encores.
(confused, angry chattering)
They were only on
for 20 minutes.
What a gyp.
Gnarly show, man.
Want to trash
the stage?
Okay.
Aah!
♪ There was
a little Spanish flea ♪
♪ A record star
he thought he'd be ♪
♪ He heard of singers
like Beatles ♪
♪ the Chipmunks
he'd seen on TV... ♪
♪ Why not
a little Spanish flea? ♪
♪ And so he... ♪
KENT BROCKMAN:
Tonight, a city weeps.
As for the first time ever,
a hockey arena becomes
a scene of violence,
following a concert
by Spinal Tap.
Mmm, I hope my poor
little baby's okay.
See for yourself.
(Bart yelling)
Unh!
(gasps)
Of course it would be
wrong to suggest
that this sort of mayhem
began with rock and roll.
After all, there were riots
at the premiere of Mozart's
The Magic Flute.
So, what's the answer--
ban all music?
In this reporter's opinion,
the answer, sadly is yes.
BART:
Hi, Mom.
Oh...
Oh, thank God.
Mom, I want to be a rock star.
Mm... we'll discuss it later.
Is Milhouse okay?
Uh... I'll be right back.
(door slams)
(tires screeching)
Help! Help!
(humming)
Homer, I've been thinking
about what Bart said.
If he's really interested
in being a musician
maybe we should
buy him a guitar.
That's a waste of money.
We already have a guitar.
(playing
"Pop Goes the Weasel")
I meant a real guitar.
This is real.
(hollow plastic knocking)
Wow!
And it came with
a free instruction book.
Now boy, we spent
a lot of money
so you'd better get real good,
real fast, or pow!
Homer!
Hey, I thought I was
supposed to encourage him?
(heavy metal guitar playing)
(Cockney accent)
I'd like to play me latest chart topper.
It's called
"Me Fans Are Stupid Pigs."
(groaning)
Bart, you've
got to go on.
Slag off.
You've changed, man.
You used to be about the music.
I said slag off!
Cool!
(playing sour notes)
(skillfully playing
the blues)
-Knock it off.
-I'm sorry.
(playing sour notes)
(skillfully playing
the blues)
Knock it off!
I's just jammin'
with ya.
(playing sour notes)
Hey, Simpson what are
you trying to play?
"Polly-Wolly Doodle."
Oh, yeah? Well, it sounds
Polly-Wolly crappy.
Ha-ha!
Burn.
Hey, cherry ax,
Bart dude.
I think it's broken.
Oh, really? Give it here.
(playing heavy metal licks
like a pro)
(cheering)
I didn't know you played
the guitar, Otto man.
Hey, that's all I did
in high school.
My old man said
I was wasting my time
and I'd never amount
to anything.
(laughing)
I, uh... hmm.
Now I'd like to slow
things down a little bit.
♪ If I leave here tomorrow ♪
♪ Would you still
remember me? ♪
(horns honking)
♪ ...and this bird
cannot change ♪
♪ Whoa, whoa, whoa... ♪
Although I'm sure
I will receive a severe wedgie
from my bus mates,
I must remind you
we should have been at school
ten minutes ago... Ah!!
Uh-oh. Better fasten
your seat belts, little dudes.
We don't have seat belts.
Uh... well, then
just try to go limp.
(tires squealing)
Better take a shortcut.
(kids screaming)
Good show last night.
Yeah, quite good.
(kids screaming)
(screaming)
Good Lord! Did anyone
get the license number?
-Gee, I forgot.
-I don't think so.
(screaming)
-Yay!
-Whee!
It's a miracle
no one was hurt.
I stand on my record--
15 crashes and not
a single fatality.
Let's see
your license, pal.
No can do.
Never got one.
But, if you need proof
of my identity,
I wrote my name
on my underwear.
Oh, wait--
these aren't mine.
Well that tears it.
Until you get a license
and wear your own underwear,
mister, you are
suspended without pay.
Who's gonna drive the bus?
I drove an all-terrain
vehicle in Da Nang.
I think I can handle it.
Where's Otto?
Otto?
That's one palindrome you
won't be hearing for a while.
(gasps)
Off we go.
♪ Hail to the bus driver,
bus driver, bus driver ♪
bus driver man ♪
♪ He drinks and he cusses ♪
♪ He stinks up the buses ♪
♪ Hail to the bus driver,
bus driver man ♪
(laughing)
Oh, there's an opening.
Oh, too late.
Nope, nope...
Uh... that would be
cutting it a little close.
I think you have to be
more aggressive, sir.
Nonsense.
One of our good citizens
will slow down and wave me in.
(humming "Bus Driver Man")
Nope...
(humming)
(gruff laughter)
What's so funny?
I was just thinking
about the time
Homer caught his nose
in the toaster.
We'll watch
the tape tonight.
Oh look, you got someone
at your window.
My name's Patty.
I'll be testing you.
When you do good,
I use the green pen.
When you do bad,
I use the red pen.
Any questions?
Yeah, one: have you
always been a chick?
I don't want to offend you,
but you were born a man,
weren't you?
You can tell me.
I'm open-minded.
I won't be needing this.
All right! Yeah!
So, how did I do?
Well, you failed every segment
and misspelled "bus"
on your application.
Drag.
Let me in.
Let me in!
-(horn honks)
-♪ He steps on the clutch ♪
♪ And the toilet goes flush.
Hail to the...♪
Shut up!
(groaning)
Hey, landlord,
some clown changed my locks
padlocked the door,
and put up an eviction notice.
Yeah. That was me.
You?
Well, uh... why?
Because you haven't paid
your rent.
Can I at least
get my stuff?
All I found in there
was a jar of mustard
and a couple
of old Cycle magazines.
Wow! I had mustard?
Rough day, Apu.
Pump me a Squishee
and don't spare the syrup.
Perhaps you'd like to try an experimental
flavor of my own concoction--
a delicious
chutney Squishee.
Uh... okay.
You can really taste
the chutney.
(spitting)
Ow!
Otto man?
You're living
in a dumpster?
Oh, man, I wish.
Dumpster brand trash bins
are top-of-the-line.
This is just a Trash-co
waste disposal unit.
Otto, why don't you
come home with me?
You can stay in our garage.
A garage!
Somebody up there likes me.
(Otto groaning)
(snoring)
(loud guitar music playing)
♪ I feel like rockin',
so I think I will ♪
♪ I'll rock it, rock it, rock it
till I get my fill, yeah ♪
Whoo!
Hey.
Bart, what's going on?
Mom, I thought
you might forget
our little conversation
this afternoon,
so I took the precaution
of recording it.
What conversation?
BART: Mom, can Otto live in our
garage for as long as he wants?
(Bart imitating Marge)
He sure can.
Marge, what
were you thinking?
That's not my voice.
Oh, everybody says that
when they hear
themselves on tape.
I don't understand this.
Why can't you stay
with your parents?
The admiral and I
don't get along.
Please, let me stay here.
I've got nowhere else to go.
Forget it-- that line
didn't work for my Dad
and it's not gonna
work for you.
Dad, Otto's going through
a real tough time.
Can't he stay with us
for a while?
I know we didn't ask
for this, Homer,
but doesn't the Bible say
"whatsoever you do
to the least of my brothers
that you do unto me"?
Yes, but doesn't
the Bible also say
"Thou shalt not take...
moochers into thy... hut"?
Please, Dad?
If you let Otto stay,
he'll help around the house
and chip in a few bucks
whenever he can.
All right, he can stay.
But I get to treat him
like garbage.
Wow, what's the catch?
The can of corn costs... 57¢!
(bell rings)
I could sure go
for a can of corn.
Otto you can't just sit
there watching TV all day.
You know,
you're right.
I should do
a little reading.
Uh, you got any of those
"Where's Waldo" books?
-No.
-How about anything written
-from the vampire's point of view?
-No.
How about anything
where guys
send in naked pictures
of their chicks?
Otto, I think you
should get a job.
Look, the only thing
I was ever good at
was driving a bus
and now "the man" says
I need a piece of paper to do that.
So get that piece of paper.
I tried!
Oh, Lord, how I did try.
(sighs)
(playing riffs)
Will you knock it off!
I can't hear myself think.
(Otto stops playing)
I want some peanuts.
That's better.
Hey, how come you never play
your guitar anymore?
I'll tell you
the truth. Dad.
I wasn't good at it
right away, so I quit.
I hope you're not mad.
Son, come here.
(laughs)
Of course I'm not mad.
If something's hard to do,
then it's not worth doing.
You just stick that guitar
in the closet
next to your shortwave radio
your karate outfit,
and your unicycle
and we'll go inside
and watch TV.
-What's on?
-It doesn't matter.
-(pounding)
-Open up! Open up!
I got to go,
and no fooling.
Hey, pop-n-fresh!
You're supposed
to giggle.
(growls)
(cries out)
That guy has got to go.
I know how you feel.
But he is good
with the kids.
So the lady drove faster,
but the strange car
kept banging into her
from behind.
(gasps)
So, finally,
she swerved off the road
into the woods
and lost the other car
and that's when she realized
the man in the other car
wasn't trying to hurt her.
No-- he was trying
to warn her...
about the ax-wielding maniac
hiding in her back seat!
Did the maniac kill her?
Natch. You know how I know?
How?
Because...
I was that maniac.
(Lisa screaming)
Hey, I was just kidding.
That's it.
He's out of here.
But Homer, we're the only
family he's got.
I don't care.
This is not Happy Days,
and he is not The Fonz.
Hey-y-y, Mr. S.
Listen, you drain-clogging,
last-cookie-eating,
collect-call-getting sponge.
I want you out of my house.
-Heavy.
-What are you gonna do, Otto?
Oh, don't worry.
There's plenty
of money out there
for a guy who knows
how to fake his own death.
Well, before you do that,
maybe you should take
the driving test again.
I can't pass that thing.
I got a zero last time.
This time I'm hungover.
You can do it, Otto.
You're the coolest adult
I ever met.
Wow. I've never been called
an adult before.
I've been tried as one, but...
I'll do it.
"Alcohol increases
your ability to drive."
False?!
Oh, man!
I don't know about this,
Bart dude.
Your Dad is right.
I am a bum.
He didn't call you a bum.
He called you a sponge.
Sponge?
(grunting)
Does this look like something
a sponge would do?!
I'll show him who's a sponge.
Well, if it isn't
Wee Willy Washout.
I want to take
the test again.
Why?
So I can staple
my license
to Homer Simpson's
big bald head!
Really? Well, here's
your written test.
I'll get you started.
"B," "C," "D,"
"A," "B..."
Homer had a piece of food
on his face for three days.
(laughing)
It wasn't little either.
It was a chicken wing.
(hysterically)
Wing!
Ooh, what was that?
It doesn't matter.
Let's get some margaritas.
I'm buying.
Otto!
That's what
my driver's license says.
KIDS: ♪ Hail to the bus driver,
bus driver, bus driver... ♪
Yes, hail to the bus driver,
bus driver man.
(guitar riff)
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.