♪ The Simpsons ♪
D'oh!
-Ahh!
-(tires screech)
♪♪ (fife and drum)
NARRATOR: 1796.
A fiercely determined band
of pioneers leaves Maryland
after misinterpreting
a passage in the Bible.
Their destination:
New Sodom.
This is their story.
This is going
to be great.
I hope they show the time
where they traded guns
to the Indians for corn.
And then the Indians shot
them and took the corn.
Egad, a monster!
It's a horrible fiend!
It's some sort of land cow!
Stand back,
fellow settlers.
(grunting)
(cheering)
Ye've saved our
fledgling community.
Mr. Springfield
how can I hope
to achieve
such greatness?
A noble spirit embiggens
the smallest man.
(cheering)
Springfield rules!
Way to go, Springfield.
"Embiggens?"
Hm, I never heard that word
before I moved to Springfield.
I don't know why.
It's a perfectly
cromulent word.
Now, you all know
Springfield's 200th birthday
is only a week away.
Every class will do its part
to make our local Bicentennial
just as memorable
as our national Bicentennial.
Of course, you children
are too young to remember that
with the possible exception
of Kearney.
Those tall ships really lifted
the nation's spirits
after Watergate.
To celebrate our Bicentennial
all 20 of you
will write an essay
about Jebediah Springfield.
And the best 18
will be put on file
in the school library
available to anyone
who requests them.
Can we do illustrations?
No.
Hey...
they need volunteers
to play old-timey people
in the parade.
Look, I can be a butter churner,
a typhoid carrier...
an apprentice.
I think I'll be
an apprentice, Marge.
What kind
of apprentice?
That's for my master
to decide.
How about town crier?
You'd be great at that.
Do you think so?
Well, yeah, Dad, you're
a big fat loudmouth.
And you can walk
when you have to.
Well, if you kids
believe in me that much,
I'll give it my best shot.
(door creaking)
Dangerous river crossings
threatened life and limb
but helped our founding fathers
save on bridge tolls.
(coughing)
Excuse me.
I didn't mean
to startle you
but I do love
to talk Jebediah.
Even when I'm
drinking my chicory.
I'm the curator,
Hollis Hurlbut.
Hi. I'm Lisa Simpson.
I'm here to research
a report on Jebediah.
Oh, you're in for a treat.
You know, some historians
consider Jebediah Springfield
a minor patriot.
But I think you'll find
he's easily the equal
of William Dawes
or even Samuel Otis.
Congratulations, Ned.
-You are our new town crier.
-D'oh!
May your shrill nasal voice
ring throughout our streets
and brains.
Thankily-dank, Mayor.
I shan't disappoint.
Har ye, har ye.
I declare myself
pickled tink
about Springfield's
bicen-ciddily
ti-ten-toodily-
rin-tin-tennial...
day.
You su-diddily-uck, Flanders.
Give me that.
Hear ye, hear ye.
Ye olde town crier
proclaimed crappy by all.
Chooseth Homer Simpson
and he shalt rock thy world.
Good God, he is fabulous.
He's embiggened that role
with his cromulent performance.
Top notch criering, I admit.
But the hat and bell
belong to Flanders,
so no dice.
Oh-ho-ho, they're just
family heirlooms.
That shouldn't stand in the way
of Homer taking my job.
Less chat, more hat.
-(fabric ripping)
-Woo-hoo!
Hear ye, hear ye.
The Homer Broadcasting System
is on the air.
All hollering, all the time.
I'm going to make...
You're to restrict
your criering to the parade
and selected pre-approved
publicity events.
Okay.
This case holds
our most treasured exhibit.
Objects owned and
used by Jebediah.
Here's his fife
upon which he sounded
the sweet note of freedom.
His hatchet,
which he hacked
at the chains of oppression,
and his...
chamber pot.
Wow!
(bell dings)
Excuse me, my microwave
Johnnycakes are ready.
(sputtering)
(plays shrill note)
(gasps)
"The secret confessions
of Jebediah Springfield"?
"Know ye who read this
there is more to my life
than history records..."
Firstly, I did not tame
the legendary buffalo.
It was already tame.
I merely shot it.
Secondly, I have not always
been known
as Jebediah Springfield.
Until 1796,
I was Hans Sprungfeld,
murderous pirate.
And the half-wits of this town
will never learn the truth.
(evil cackling)
"Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha."
Oh, my God!
Our town hero is a fraud.
"I write this confession
so that my infamy will live on
long after my body has succumbed
to my infectious diphtheria."
Ew.
(yells)
Ugh. Agh. Ugh. Agh.
HOLLIS: Here's Johnnycakes.
Is everything okay?
You look a bit flushed.
Oh, it's just
the excitement
of studying Jebediah.
Sounds like
you've come down
with a serious case
of "Jebeditis."
Just when I was getting over
my "Chester A. Arthritis."
(both chuckling)
You had arthritis?
Um... no.
(bell ringing)
Hear ye, hear ye!
What's for breakfast?
Toast.
I don't understand thee, Marge.
Hmm. Ye olde toast.
Ooh!
What would you say
if I told you
that Jebediah Springfield
wasn't as great
as he's cracked
up to be? Look.
Jebediah was really
a vicious pirate
named Hans Sprungfeld.
His tongue was bitten off
by a Turk
in a grog house fight.
No tongue, eh?
How did he talk
and eat and laugh and love?
He had a prosthetic tongue
made out of silver.
Yes. That'd do.
He was one of the
evilest men of the 1780s.
He even tried to kill
George Washington.
The dastard!
Give me all your money.
Never!
(laughing)
(both grunting)
Ooh! Ow!
I got the white
stars you wanted
but I couldn't find
any red hearts
yellow moons or
green clovers.
Well, I'll use it,
but I'm not paying for it.
The next time Hans
Sprungfeld was seen
he had changed his name
to Jebediah Springfield.
Lisa, honey,
when my family first
came to this state,
they had a choice of living
in Springfield or Stenchburg.
You know why they
chose Springfield?
Because everyone knows
Jebediah Springfield
was a true American hero,
end of story!
I believe you, honey.
You do?
Of course I do.
You're always right
about this type of thing
and for once, I want in
on the ground floor.
Oh, thanks, Dad.
Ralph, "A," Janey, "A,"
and Lisa, for your--
(clearing throat)
essay,
"Jebediah Springfield:
Super Fraud," "F."
But it's all true.
Ah! This is nothing
but dead-white-male bashing
from a P.C. thug.
It's women like you
who keep the rest of us
from landing a husband.
Well, nice talking to you.
(sobbing)
(door slams)
Lisa?
Miss Hoover thought
I made the whole thing up.
She called me a P.C. thug.
I've been called
a greasy thug, too,
and it never stops
hurting,
so here's what
we're going to do:
grease ourselves
up real good
and trash that place
with a baseball bat.
(sniffles)
That won't help, Dad.
No one's ever gonna
believe me.
But you have proof.
We could go get
that confession
out of Jebediah's fife.
-We could?
-Come on.
We can use the baseball bat
to smash open the case.
-No baseball bat.
-Oh!
Hi, Mr. Hurlbut.
Oh, you're back.
And you've brought a friend.
Town Crier. I'd like
to ask you a few questions.
One: where's the fife,
and two: give me the fife.
Hey! Stop!
I've got nothing
but respect
for the office
of town crier
but this is well outside
your jurisdiction.
Oh, yeah? Well, put this
in your fife and smoke it.
What the--
That's Jebediah's
secret confession.
It proves he was a fraud.
"The secret confession
"of Jebediah Springfield.
Know ye who reads..."
Oh. I think, Lisa, that
you've been taken in
by an obvious forgery.
Unfortunately, historical
research is plagued
by this sort of hoax--
the so-called
confession.
It's just as phony as
the Howard Hughes will,
the Hitler diaries or
the Emancipation Retraction.
But it explains why there's no
record of Jebediah before 1795.
He was Hans Sprungfeld
until then.
That's preposterous.
Now, get out!
You're banned from
this historical society--
you and your children and
your children's children.
For three months.
I'm not gonna give up.
I refuse to believe
that everyone refuses
to believe the truth.
I'd like 25 copies
on goldenrod, um,
25 on canary, 25 on saffron,
and 25 on paella.
Okay. 100 yellow.
You don't have to
help me with this, Dad.
Oh, sure I do.
I always believe in
helping the little guy
and you're the
littlest guy I know.
Question:
Is your name Ridley Scott
or James Cameron?
No, it's Homer.
Then I would thank you
to stop peering
at my screenplay, Homer.
If I see a movie
where computers
threaten our personal liberties,
I will know
that you stole my idea.
I'm just waiting for my kid.
HOMER'S BRAIN:
Mental note: steal his idea.
Hi, Apu.
Can I put this poster
in your window?
Well, of course you can,
you little pixie.
Ooh! You are just as sweet as
the stix which bear your name.
(gasping)
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
Take that down.
As a semi-legal immigrant,
your poster could land me
in a predicament
as red hot as the candies
which bear that name.
He wouldn't let
me put it up.
Okay. Well, that's
not gonna stop us.
I know a much better way
to get attention.
Hear ye, hear ye!
My daughter
has something to tell you
about Jebediah Springfield.
Aw! That little cutie
wants to do something cute.
Shut up, you bums, shut up!
Go ahead, angel.
(clearing throat)
Jebediah Springfield
was nothing more
than an evil,
bloodthirsty pirate
who hated this town.
Good God!
Homer,
you know I support
uh, most any prejudice
you can name
but your hero-phobia
sickens me.
You and your daughter
ain't welcome here no more.
Barney, show
them the exit.
There's an exit?
Evil bloodthirsty pirate...
Hello,
Town Jubilation Committee?
I got something that's going
to make you a lot less jubilant.
Can't you understand,
little girl?
Jebediah was no criminal.
That's right.
The reason they say
he had a silver tongue
is because he was
such a fine speaker.
That's a myth that got
mixed up with the truth.
You are tampering with
forces you can't understand.
We have major corporations
sponsoring this event.
I hope you know
you're sponsoring a celebration
for a murderous pirate.
A pirate?
Well, that's hardly
the image we want
for Long John Silver's.
Well, I see no way
of settling this.
I say we imprison them
for the duration
of our Bicentennial.
There is one way.
Get the silver tongue.
If Jebediah's
who I say he is
then it should
still be in his grave.
(murmuring)
I guess, but human
decency prevents--
Dig him up!
Dig up that corpse!
If you really love
Jebediah Springfield
you'll haul his bones
out of the ground
to prove my daughter wrong.
(chanting) Dig up his grave.
Pull out his tongue.
Can't we have one meeting
that doesn't end
with us digging up a corpse?
Now, Lisa,
when you see
there's no silver tongue
in there,
will you stop trying
to ruin Jebediah's reputation?
Yes.
What do we win
if the tongue is there?
Credibility.
Ah, what a gyp.
(gasping)
Jebediah Springfield
has been replaced
with a skeleton.
No, that's the skeleton
of Jebediah.
Gotcha. Gotcha.
Okay, uh...
well, let's start
looking for that silver tongue.
Don't forget to
look in his shoes.
When I lose something
sometimes it turns up
in my shoes.
Actually, if it's anywhere
it would be lodged
in the sinus.
(chuckles)
All right, here goes.
Forgive us, Jebediah.
We mean no disrespect.
(all gasping)
Well, that
settles that.
There is no silver tongue,
is there, Bonesy?
Oh, I wish, Chief.
With that kind of dough,
I could buy me some eyeballs.
(laughing)
That's the spirit, Bonesy.
Why don't you
sing a song
for the nice people?
All right.
(clears throat)
♪ Camptown ladies
sing this song ♪
♪ Doo-dah, doo-dah... ♪
I was so sure.
Hear ye, hear ye.
Everybody
makes mistakes.
Let's go home.
Not so fast, Simpson.
This foul business
was all your fault.
By the power
vested in me
I hereby strip you
of your ceremonial bell...
No! No!
and tricorner hat.
You will have the hat cleaned
and then return it.
Oh...
Oh, Dad, I'm
really sorry.
I know how much you wanted
to be in the parade.
Oh, it's not
your fault, honey.
I'm supposed to be
the responsible one.
I shouldn't have let you
let me get carried away.
(knocking)
Why did you dig up
the bones of the past?
Why did you disturb
the ghosts of history?
I-I-I...
(grunts)
General Washington?
You did some good work
exposing Jebediah, Lisa.
Don't stop now.
There's just one piece left
in the puzzle.
But I've caused so much trouble already,
General Washington,
I can't go on.
We had quitters
in the revolution too.
We called them Kentuckians.
Well, I'll just have to find
another little girl
to be President.
What's your friend
Janey's number?
No! Not Janey!
She'll pack the Supreme Court
with boys.
Oh, let me help you,
George Washington.
I still want to help you.
"I want to help you,
George Washington"?
Even your dreams
are square.
Can you open my milk, Mommy?
I'm not Mommy, Ralph.
I'm Miss Hoover.
(laughing)
The missing piece of the puzzle.
I've got it!
You? What are you
doing here?
I was right
about Jebediah
and now I can prove it.
Oh, please,
not that claptrap again.
Haven't you hurt Jebediah enough
with your childish tales
of pirate ships and fisticuffs
and a silver tongue
that can't be found?
That's because you stole it.
That's a lie!
I'm an antiquarian, damn it!
It's my job
to seek out the truth.
But when you found the truth,
you couldn't take it.
You couldn't stand that you'd
devoted your life to a fraud
so you covered it up,
didn't you?
-Didn't you?
-No!
No! That's
preposterous.
I mean, I couldn't.
You-You can't.
Stop it!
Where's the silver tongue?
I thought no one
would ever find it.
When I pried open
the coffin, it was there.
That shiny tongue
sticking out of his mouth
razzing my entire career.
My-My life.
Before the dust could settle,
I pocketed it.
But I thought I had
you fooled.
You did, until I realized
that Jebediah's confession
was saying more
than he meant it to.
How else could he
have gotten this?
(gasps)
Sprungfeld must have
taken it with him
when he ran off
after the fight.
Exactly.
This celebration is a sham.
And it's all my fault.
We've got to get the word out
to every man, woman
and child in town.
♪♪ (march)
Stop!
Stop everything!
Stop the parade!
What?
What's going on here?
This is highly unorthodox.
This is Lisa Simpson.
She's discovered something
very important
about Jebediah Springfield
that you need to hear.
(microphone feedback)
(clears throat)
People of Springfield,
I, um...
I don't know
quite how to say this.
Don't be shy,
little girl.
Think of Jebediah
and the words will come.
I did a lot of research
on Jebediah Springfield and--
I think I can pick her off.
Wait. Let's see what
she has to say.
Jebediah Springfield was...
Jebediah was...
great.
I, um, just wanted to say
that I've done some research
and uh... he was great.
Yeah.
Well said.
Great speech.
Jebediah would be proud of you.
♪♪ (march resumes)
Why didn't
you tell them?
Because the myth of Jebediah
has value too.
It's brought out the best
in everyone in this town.
Regardless of who said it,
"A noble spirit
embiggens the smallest man."
(gunshot)
(bell ringing)
Well, hey, it's Homer.
Good to see you, neigh--
Get lost.
Hear ye, hear ye!
Hear ye!
He is not the official
town crier!
Police! Do something!
Well, I'd like to, ma'am,
but he's too damn good.
Let him march, boys.
Let the man march.
♪♪ (old-time western)
♪ Hitch that team up,
Jebediah Springfield ♪
♪ Whip them horses,
let them wagons roll ♪
♪ That a people
might embiggen America ♪
♪ That a man
might embiggen ♪
♪ His soul ♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.