CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
♪♪
(school bell rings)
(whistle blows)
(beeping)
♪♪
(tires skidding)
(clinking)
(horn honking)
(tires screeching)
D’oh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
♪♪
D’oh!
D’oh! D’oh! D’oh! D’oh!
(pensive music playing)
(screams)
♪♪
(buzzing)
(gulps)
(roaring)
(shrieks)
♪♪
(chittering)
(assorted animals calling
in distance)
(wind howling)
Hey.
♪♪
What took you
so long?
(sighs)
MARGE/BART/LISA:
♪ Happy Birthday, dear Homer ♪
♪ Happy birthday to you! ♪
I don’t have
to make a wish,
because I already have
this wonderful family.
I wish for infinity hamburgers.
(inhales deeply)
Huh?
(blowing and spitting)
(chuckling):
Oh, I get it.
These are those trick candles
you can’t blow out.
No, Dad,
they’re the
opposite.
"E-Z BLO."
(gasps)
This ends now.
(inhaling deeply)
(wheezes)
(wheezing)
It’s okay, Homie.
You’re probably
just tired
from not doing
anything all day.
(panting):
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
Dad, you’re out of shape
even for an American.
I’ll just focus
on one area.
(loud blowing)
(breath running out)
How many did I get?
None? That’s cool.
(wheezing)
(moaning)
(beeping)
You know how many
fires are started
by birthday candles?
If you do, tell me.
It would settle a bet down
at the station house.
I say five, Gus
says a million.
(sighs)
This disasterette was
a real wake-up call.
We need to find a way to protect
our irreplaceables.
You could buy
a fireproof safe.
Or we could
just resolve
to be more careful
with our open flames.
Sir, we’ve been here
six times this month.
Yeah, but, um, one of those,
I dialed 9-1-1 by mistake,
but I was too embarrassed
to admit it,
so I set the house
on fire.
Feels good
to tell the truth.
No, I’m lying again,
it feels bad.
(sighs)
MARGE: Okay.
Everyone gets to put
one precious item
in our fireproof safe.
For me, it’s the family
photo album.
HOMER: Aw.
Our kids used
to be so cute.
Used to?!
Oh, deal with it.
It’s so hard
to choose
just one item worthy
of the safe.
So I made this elaborate
decision tree,
which in itself is worthy
of preservation.
(chuckles)
Tick tock, sweetie.
I picked my Malibu Stacy
hybrid convertible.
It runs on her old makeup
and out-of-style shoes.
I’m going with
the cologne
I wore on our
first date.
(chuckling)
Ooh.
I’m putting in my "Catch
A Rising Krusty" doll!
(mechanical whirring)
Where do the kids today get
these band names?
"The Kinks?"
"The Stones?"
Sounds like my last physical!
(laughing)
References.
(doll groaning)
No. Wait. Don’t...
Now we have nothing
to worry about
in the event of a fire
except our lives.
You see all those crazy
new electronics?
iPod... iTunes...
I give up!
(laughing)
(effervescing)
What’s that coming
out of the safe?
I don’t know-- maybe the Krusty
doll accidentally turned on
the car’s headlight, which
focused on the cologne bottle,
causing it to boil,
and soon explode.
Dad, that’s ridiculous.
(explosion)
(all scream)
What’s the deal
with this "California pizza"?
If I wanted...
(distorted): cheese and
fruit, I’d have to...
(groaning)
(sighing)
No!
It’s gone.
That family album was a record
of my accomplishments.
It’s like what a résumé is
for a man.
I agree, Mom,
it’s very sad.
But we’ll have
to move on.
It’s not like we can restage
all our family photos.
Restage the photos?
Lisa, you fool.
You’ve doomed us all.
(camera shutter clicks)
(crying): No!
(J Geils Band’s
"Freeze Frame" playing)
(music playing over TV)
Okay, we’re recreating
our series finale party
for Star Trek: Voyager.
(weepy): Oh, man, I thought
I was strong enough
to get through this again,
but I’m not.
(sobbing)
(sobbing):
Oh, Captain Janeway!
Your mission
ended too soon.
Too soon.
Our new photos are back!
(grunts):
Ooh!
(all screaming)
That’s why
I got duplicates.
(happy music playing)
Aw! There’s my first
saxophone recital.
Bart looks so cute as a mighty
oak in the school play.
Here I am on the space shuttle,
orbiting Earth.
It sure was nice of NASA
to send you up again.
Oh, my God!
Check out what’s happening
behind your restaged
anniversary dinner.
LISA: Duffman’s on a date
with Booberella.
(gasps)
He’s supposed to be
in a stable, long-term
gay relationship.
Hmm.
This is a celebrity scandal.
We could sell that photo
to a tabloid.
And they pay big money
for photos.
Marge, this
isn’t like you.
Well, it’s just about what we
need to pay for our fire damage.
HOMER: Spooky.
This is good, real good.
Like Lindsay Lohan
looking drunk, high and bony.
Click, click, career over,
see ya in the gutter, freckles!
Homer, I’ll pay you
200 bucks.
Bring me more
snaps like this,
and I’ll make you
a moderately wealthy man.
Moderately wealthy?
(gasps)
Whee! I’m sort of rich!
I can rent anything I want!
That’s quite
an offer.
Can I discuss it
with my wife?
Sure, why not?
Then I’ll do it!
Oh, boy!
I can’t wait
to see Krusty.
Look, there’s his
chauffeur-driven Town Car.
(tires screeching)
(screams)
Your head dinged
my door panel!
Jerks like you
ought to be shot!
Krusty!
How about a nice shot of you
with the boy you injured?
Paparazzi?!
Get lost,
ya parasite.
How about you, Gabbo?
Ay-yi-yi-yi-yi-yi-yi!
Okay, how about
an autograph for my kids?
Well, when you
put it that way...
Ay-yi-yi-yi-yi
yi-yi-yi-yi!
Okay, boy, this is
that snooty supermarket
all the celebrities
shop at.
You’re gonna help
me ambush them.
Look at this place.
Imported beer?
Seedless grapes?
Chewing gum?
(gasps)
The clown on this cereal box
is just a person.
(gasps)
There’s the Rich Texan
and his daughter,
Paris Texan.
Come on, baby,
barf for mama.
Okay, boy,
do something annoying,
but leave yourself
room to build.
Hey, Paris,
I saw a disgusting
part of your body
on the Internet--
your face!
I’m still breaking
in this nose!
(grunting, shutter clicking)
(shutter clicking)
Look at those
celebrities.
I’ve met them all,
and yet they don’t even
acknowledge my existence.
Hello, Homer.
Have you
lost weight?
Oh, like you care,
Betty White.
Tell me,
how’s Maggie?
Her name is Marge!
I was talking
about your baby.
Oh. Uh, she’s
looking very... snappy!
Thanks for taking my picture.
If you want me
to sign it,
here’s a stamped,
self-addressed envelope.
And give Santa’s Little
Helper a big hug for me.
Yeah, that’s right,
just walk away.
(lisping): Beautiful day,
isn’t it, Freddie?
God bless you
and yours.
Dad, it’s
Drederick Tatum.
Try to get him
to punch you.
No problem.
Hey, Drederick!
Yes, how can I help you,
my handsome friend?
Your hip-hop CD was
boastful and unnecessary.
Okay, here we go.
-(camera shutter)
-(grunting)
(grunting)
(screams)
That’s what I think
of the fourth estate!
What are
the first three?
Nobility, clergy
and commoners.
Learn your
French history.
Okay.
Terrific! Outstanding!
This has page one
written all over it.
What the hell
did you do that for?
I wanted to remember my place
in the book I was reading.
(sneaky music)
Boy, I never thought
I’d have my own darkroom.
LISA: Yes,
but why does it
have to be
in my bedroom?
Lis, you can’t stay here
if you’re gonna keep talking.
It’s 11:00 at night,
and I can’t get to sleep!
Well, then you could
come over here
and help Daddy
pour chemicals.
(sighs)
Okay.
(sizzling)
(groaning)
Kids-- they always say
they’re not tired
when they’re the most
tired of all.
(chuckles)
That photo’s mine.
Well, I do like
the extra money.
But I think maybe
you should stop
exploiting human beings’
private misfortunes.
See, Marge-- everyone says
they hate these magazines,
but it’s impossible
to set them down.
Oh, it is not.
Watch me.
(groaning, grunting)
Ooh...
(stammers)
(screaming)
Sideshow Mel is
in a custody battle?!
(gasps)
And it’s turning bitter?
If you read one more thing,
it is a purchase.
Experts disagree on
location of Heaven?
Purchase!
(register beeps)
(triumphant brass music)
Okay, this is the place.
(wind rushing)
Did I attach
the harness?!
No!
Should attach it
for you?!
If you don’t
mind...!
Thank you!
Now to make a young woman’s
wedding day all about me.
Do you, Rainier
Luftwaffe
Wolfcastle,
take Maria Shriver-
Kennedy-Quimby
to be your
lawful wedded...
HOMER: Up, up,
and annoy!
Yes!
(crowd gasping)
I also wreck bar mitzvahs!
Is that horrible man
gone yet?
Yes, Mother, barring some sort
of pendulum effect.
(groaning)
First Amendment rules,
privacy drools!
(camera shutter clicking)
(groaning)
(German accent):
Time to squash that shutterbug.
You promised me
one day
where you wouldn’t
swear revenge on someone.
Promise revoked.
RAINIER WOLFCASTLE:
Greetings, famous faces
and sizzling stars.
(murmuring in agreement)
Thank you for responding
to my e-vite.
Krusty, your response
was the least funny.
I’m a visual comedian.
Did you get the j-peg?
Wouldn’t open.
Oh!
I wish to discuss
our mutual enemy,
Homer Simpson.
(overlapping chatter)
Now, do not worry.
In my film A Future Droid
in King Arthur’s Court,
I learned
that it takes a Robo Knight
to defeat a Robo Knight.
(murmuring in agreement )
And to defeat a paparazzo,
it takes this man!
(foreboding music)
Let me introduce the world’s
greatest celebrity shutterbug--
Enrico Irritazio.
Buono giorno!
How are you gonna
help us, Beefaroni?
Allow me
to explain.
I take embarrassing
pictures of Homer,
harass him day and night.
Justice will be served,
and I will be a god
in your eyes!
(agreeable murmurs)
See? It is good.
I declare this meeting
achourned.
Now please,
take some sushi,
’cause if I give it to the dogs,
they will think,
"Oh, now I get sushi
all the time."
And I am not made of sushi.
Now, Maggie, I had
to use your car seat
to hold the
new TV Guide...
so I’m gonna hang
you from the mirror.
(giggling)
(engine revving,
tires squealing)
Smile!
(camera shutter clicking)
He’s trying to make me
look like a bad father.
Maggie, take the wheel!
(grunting)
Ten and two,
Einstein!
(camera shutter clicking)
Can’t I even have
privacy here?!
(camera shutter clicking)
(suspenseful music)
Scandalous!
Repugnant!
Ausgezeichnet!
I shall make this photo
into my screensaver!
Somehow.
How could you
publish this?
I thought we
were friends!
I have no friends.
Friends take time.
And time is money,
and money pays for things,
like a manicure
and a boiled egg.
Get me one of each,
but not boiled, poached.
Ah, what the hell--
it’s Friday-- scrambled!
Sometimes I wish
I had a twin.
Not that much, though.
We’d just fight.
HOMER: And then he said
he didn’t want a twin
because they’d
just fight.
Sweetie, maybe it’s time
you retired from paparazzying.
It’s never fun to get a taste
of your own medicine.
You’re right.
I’m giving up photography...
and my own medicine!
So long, anti-clotting agent!
Clot, clot, clot, clot
clot, clot, clot, clot!
(Kylie Minogue’s "Can’t Get You
Out of My Head" playing)
(chuckles)
With Homer Simpson
out of the way,
we can go back to our lives
of sybaritic excess.
Stem cell fajita?
Leave the tray.
(loud laughter)
(thunder rumbling)
Listen to ’em.
They’re on top of the world
while I’m sittin’ here
pretending I have a stool.
All because of a bunch
of stuff that happened.
Ah, Homer, don’t
be so quick
to abandon this
paparazzo thing.
Yeah, it’s an American tradition
to cut people down to size
because they’ve brought
so much joy into our lives.
You know who
I can’t stand?
That Robin Williams.
You know, one time I saw him
eating dinner with his children.
He wouldn’t take
the time out
to do all the funny bits
from his movies.
And my sister once saw
Burt Reynolds at an airport,
and he wouldn’t even
cosign her mortgage.
You guys are right--
I should get back in the game.
Oh! But I threw away my camera.
Oh, here,
use this one.
I was gonna use it
to take secret photos
in the ladies’
toilet, but, uh,
no dames ever come
in this joint.
Thanks, Moe!
Sure.
Excuse me, do you have
a ladies’ room?
We need to trade bras
and panties.
Oh, you got
to be kidding me!
(glass shatters)
(song continues)
(thunder rumbling)
Oh!
You call this
a drink?
No, I never called it
a drink.
(thunder rumbling,
music stops abruptly)
How do you want
your comeuppance--
eight by ten
or wallet size?
Celebrities,
hide your shame!
(loud shotgun-like pops
of shutter clicking)
(all groaning and whimpering)
What are you going to
do with those photos?
-Nothing.
-ALL: Huh?
Providing you celebrities
do something for me.
I want you all
to show some respect
for the people
who made you what you are.
Sign an autograph or two.
Support a charity
for something
that hasn’t happened
to a member of your family.
Let one of us regular guys write
a terrible children’s book!
We will take
the deal.
As a sign of good faith,
I invite you and your family
to a barbecue on
my offshore party platform.
(sighs)
It is good doing real things
with real people.
Say, Rainier,
you’re in show business.
Would you mind taking a look
at this screenplay I wrote?
Oh, sorry.
I do not read
unsolicited manuscripts.
(lights buzzing)
(grunts)
Well, at least
it got made.
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Shh!
Enhanced by Fotokem