♪ The Simpsons ♪
-(chalk screeches)
-(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(horn honks)
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
So, kids, caught anything?
Not yet, sir.
What are you using
for bait?
My brother's
using worms
but I, who feel
the tranquility
far outweighs the actual
catching of fish,
am using nothing.
I see.
And what's your name, son?
I'm Bart Simpson.
Who the hell are you?
(chuckles)
I'm Dave Shutton.
I'm an investigative reporter
who's on the road a lot,
and I must say,
that in my day,
we didn't talk that way
to our elders.
Well this is my day,
and we do, sir. (grunts)
All right, we eat tonight!
Hmph!
Wait a minute.
One, two...
three?
Well, leave it to
good 'ol Mary Bailey
to finally step in
and do something
about that hideous
genetic mutation.
(scoffs) Mary Bailey!
Well, if I was governor
I'd sure find better things
to do with my time.
-Like what?
-Like getting Washington's birthday
and Lincoln's birthday
back as separate paid holidays.
President's Day...
Pfft! What a rip-off.
I bust my butt day in
and day out--
MARGE: You're late for work, Homer.
So? Someone will punch in for me.
Try not to spill anything, Dad.
-BART: Keep those mutants coming, Homer.
-HOMER: I'll mutant you.
Oh, man!
Plain cake doughnuts.
Thanks for taking
all the fancies, guys!
Why can't I
ever get here on time?
BURNS (over P.A.):
Hi-ho, faceless employees.
In a few moments
the government inspection team
will be touring our plant.
So look busy
and keep your mouths shut!
That is all.
Very stirring, sir.
Uh-oh.
Here they come.
Hold me, Smithers.
Okay men, Geiger counters on.
(rapid clicking)
ALL: Huh?
I suppose that's normal
background radiation--
the kind you'd find in
any well-maintained nuclear facility,
or for that matter,
playgrounds and hospitals.
Sorry.
(whistles)
Gum used to seal crack
in cooling tower.
I'm as shocked
as you are.
Plutonium rod
used as paperweight.
D'oh. Now that
shouldn't be.
Yeah, well, that's
always been like that.
(snoring)
(shrieks)
Uh... just resting my eyes.
Ah, well done.
A rested employee is
a vigilant employee.
(sighs)
Monitoring station unmanned.
(Geiger counter clicking)
Look here, inspector
could I speak to you
privately in my office?
Mr. Burns, in 20 years
I have never seen
such a shoddy, deplorable--
Oh, look.
Some careless person
has left thousands
and thousands of dollars
just lying here
on my coffee table.
Smithers, why don't
we leave the room
and hopefully,
when we return,
the pile of money
will be gone.
(groaning)
(grunts)
Look, Smithers,
the money
and a very stupid man
are still here.
Burns, if
I didn't know better,
I'd think you were
trying to bribe me.
Is there some confusion
about this?
Take it, take it, take it,
you poor shmo.
Mr. Burns, I'm going
to overlook this felony.
However, I will not overlook
the 342 violations
I have observed
at your plant today.
Either bring this place
up to code
or we'll
shut it down.
Good day.
(sighs)
Oh, well.
A little dab of paint here,
a little spackle there...
How much could it possibly
cost to fix this place up?
Hmm. Approximately
$56 million, sir.
-56 million?!
-Don't hit me, sir.
Oh, that I had the strength
to take it out on you, Smithers.
Now, please go.
I would be alone.
♪ Once I built a railroad ♪
♪ Made it run... ♪
(sniffles)
♪ Made it race against time ♪
♪ Once I built a railroad ♪
♪ Now it's done ♪
♪ Brother,
can you spare a dime? ♪
♪ Half a million boots
went slogging through hell ♪
♪ I was a kid
with a drum... ♪
Empty-- bah!
(shrieks)
Uh... just resting my eyes.
Oh. Heh.
Holy moly! 9:30.
Hello, Marge.
Sorry I didn't call, but it's
been a madhouse down here.
Yeah, these 12-hour days
are killing me.
Echo!
(echoing)
Echo, echo, echo...
(Homer chuckles)
BURNS: ♪ Hey, don't
you remember? ♪
-Huh?
-♪ They called me Al ♪
♪ It was Al,
all the time ♪
♪ Hey, don't
you remember? ♪
♪ I'm your pal ♪
♪ Buddy, can you
spare a dime? ♪
(crying)
Hmm? What the..
Uh... Mr. Burns?
(both scream)
Sorry sir, it's just me,
Homer Simpson.
Is everything all right?
(sniffs)
Working late, Simpson?
Uh... yes, sir.
You and I are
a dying breed, Simpson.
I'm going to share
something with you.
Hop in.
Ooh! Cushy.
Homer, they're trying
to shut us down.
They say we're
contaminating the planet.
Well, nobody's perfect.
Can't the government
just get off our backs?
You know, I was
just telling the wife
that if I was governor,
I'd do things a lot differently.
Oh, get off
your soapbox, Simpson!
Do you realize how much
it costs to run for office?
More than any
honest man could afford!
I bet you could
afford it, though.
(growling)
D-Don't g-get me wrong.
I mean, you're
an honest man.
I just meant
that you could afford
to run for governor
if you felt like it.
Of course,
I'm just rambling
because you keep staring at me
like that, but it's true.
I mean, if you were governor
you could decide
what's safe and what isn't.
Where we going, sir?
BURNS: To create a new
and better world.
HOMER: If it's on the way, could
you drop me off at my house?
Well, he's got my vote.
Homer, we're
a Mary Bailey family.
Mary Bailey isn't going to fire me
if I don't vote for her.
I'm for Monty Burns.
Ooh! A political discussion
at our table.
I feel like a Kennedy.
Well, frankly,
I don't see how
one of the most despicable
men who ever lived
has a chance against
Mary Bailey,
the most
beloved governor
our great state
has ever known.
MAN: Now, here's the problem
as I see it.
While Governor Bailey
is beloved by all
98% of the voters
rate you as
despicable or worse.
That's why we've assembled
the finest campaign team
money can buy.
This is your
speech writer
your joke writer,
your spin doctor
your makeup man
and your personal trainer.
Their job-- to turn
this Mr. Burns
into this.
Why are my teeth
showing like that?
Because you're smiling.
Ah, excellent!
This is exactly the kind of trickery
I'm paying you for.
But-but how do we turn your average
Joe Six-pack against Mary Bailey?
With this team
of investigators--
your muckraker,
your character assassin
-your mudslinger, your garbologist.
-Hello.
Their job is
to turn Mary Bailey
from this
into this.
Ah, visually, it's helped so
much. Thank you.
But first
there's a burning issue
that we need to address and
neutralize immediately.
BURNS:
D'oh!
I hate that fish.
MAN (on telvision): Thank you for watching
Movie for a Dreary Afternoon.
Please stay tuned for a paid
political announcement
brought to you by the friends of
Montgomery Burns.
Burns? Change the channel.
-You change it.
-No, you change it.
I changed it
last week.
Fine, be a jerk.
Then we'll just
sit here and watch it.
Oh, no, an election?
It's one
of those deals
where they close the bars,
isn't it?
Sorry, Barney.
I wonder if he's
going to say anything
about that
horrible fish?
Oh Marge, what's the big deal?
I'll bet before the papers
blew this out
of proportion
you didn't even know
how many eyes a fish had.
(irritated grunt)
30 seconds to air,
Mr. Burns.
Now, remember
to smile.
BURNS:
I am smiling.
You'll have to do
better than that.
(grunting)
How's this?
There you go.
I'm going to
be sore tomorrow.
Well, we've done
all we can, Mr. Burns.
-The rest is up to you.
-Oh, don't worry.
By the time this paid
political announcement is done,
every Johnny Lunchpail
in this whole stupid state
will be eating
out of my hand.
Oh, hello, friends.
I'm Montgomery Burns,
your next governor.
And I'm here to talk to you about
my little friend, here, Blinky.
Many of you consider him to be
a hideous genetic mutation.
Well, nothing could be
further from the truth.
But don't take
my word for it.
Let's ask an actor portraying
Charles Darwin what he thinks.
-Hello, Mr. Burns.
-Oh, hello, Charles.
Be a good fellow,
and tell our viewers
about your theory
of natural selection.
Glad to, Mr. Burns.
You see, every so often,
mother nature changes
her animals
giving them bigger teeth,
sharper claws, longer legs
or, in this case,
a third eye.
And if
these variations
turn out to be an improvement
the new animals
thrive and multiply
and spread across
the face of the Earth.
So you're saying this fish
might have an advantage
over other fish?
It may in fact,
be a kind of superfish.
I wouldn't mind having
a third eye. Would you?
(chuckles) No.
You see friends, if our anti-nuclear
nay-sayers and choose-up-siders
were to come upon an elephant
frolicking in the waters
next to our
nuclear power plant
they'd probably blame
his ridiculous nose
on the nuclear bogeyman.
The truth is, this fish
is a miracle of nature
with a taste
that can't be beat.
Mm-mmm!
So, to summarize...
say what you want about me.
I can take the slings
and arrows,
but stop slandering
poor, defenseless Blinky.
Good night
and God bless.
♪ Only a moron
wouldn't cast his vote ♪
♪ for Mon-teee Burns! ♪
Wow! Superfish!
I wish the government
would get off his back.
That Burns is just
what this state needs--
young blood!
I hope Burns and I can count
on your support, honey?
Homer, I'm
a Bailey booster.
Oh yeah? Well, I'm
a Burns booster. Ow!
Congratulations
Mr. Burns,
The latest polls show
you're up six points.
Ah. Giving me a total of...
Six, but
we're on our way.
MARY BAILEY: My worthy opponent
seems to think that the voters
of this state
are gullible fools.
I, however
prefer to rely
on their intelligence
and good judgment.
Interesting strategy.
Good luck.
And I say taxes
are too high!
(cheering)
(crowd cheering)
Have you found any dirt
on Mary Bailey?
Well, we've gone through
her garbage.
-We talked to her maid.
-And so far,
the only negative thing
we have found
was from some guy who dated
her when she was 16.
Ah! And?
He uh, he felt her up.
Bah!
Not good enough.
BURNS: We're going to
send a message
to those bureaucrats down
there in the state capital!
Is your boss
governor yet?
Not yet, son, not yet.
The voters now see you
as imperial and God-like.
Hot dog.
But there's a downside to it.
The latest polls indicate
you're in danger of losing touch
with the common man.
Oh, dear. Heaven forefend!
Which is why the night
before the election
we want you to have dinner at
the home of one of your workers.
Oh, I get your angle.
Every Joe Meatball
and Sally Housecoat
in this God-forsaken state
will see me
hunkering down for chow
with Eddie Punchclock.
The media will
have a field day.
CAMPAIGN MANAGER:
The only question is
can we find someone
common enough?
(belches)
Ugh.
Well, I-- I knew there
would be sacrifices.
(belches)
(crunching)
Oh, great toast, Marge!
Mmm. Oh, by the way,
the night before the election
-Mr. Burns is coming over for dinner.
-What?
And some reporters
and camera crew,
but you don't need
to feed them.
Cool man! A media circus.
Absolutely not.
Come on, Marge.
Mm-mmm, I'm going to be
ringing doorbells
for Mary Bailey that night.
D'oh!
Kids, please leave the room.
I don't want you
to see this.
Uh-oh.
Please, please, please,
please, please, please.
(irritated groan)
We're hoping that
one of the children
might pop up with a question
about the upcoming election.
Little girl, do you think you can
memorize this by dinnertime tomorrow?
"Mr. Burns, your campaign
seems to have
"the momentum
of a runaway freight train.
Why are you so popular?"
Very good.
Hmm. Well as long
as I'm asking something,
can I ask him
to assuage my fears
that he's contaminating
the planet
in a manner that may one day
render it uninhabitable?
No dear, the card
question will be fine.
Well, I think the non-card
question is a valid--
Marge!
Don't worry.
My daughter's very bright.
I'm sure she'll be able
to memorize your question
by dinnertime tomorrow.
And finally,
Mr. Burns wants you
to appear very
affectionate to him,
but we must remind you,
he hates being touched.
(grunts)
Mmm?
Marge, get back in bed.
No, I'm just fine
right here.
What's wrong?
I just want to snuggle.
Well, I don't feel
like snuggling.
What's that got
to do with it?
I don't wanna snuggle
with anybody
who's not letting me
express myself.
But you do get
to express yourself,
and the lovely home you keep
and the food you serve.
Hmm. Okay, Homer.
Fair enough.
You got it.
All right.
Good. That's it.
That's how I'm going
to express myself.
That's right.
Good night.
Huh?
(TV crew chattering)
Well, what do
we think?
Hey, hello, handsome.
Hey, get that stuff
off his face.
We're here to have dinner
with a common man,
not Tyrone Power.
Latest polls are in.
It's dead even.
Fifty-fifty.
This cornball stunt is gonna
put us over the top.
Whoa, he's here!
(doorbell rings)
Hello, Homer.
Marge, you look dazzling.
Oh, and look,
I've brought noodle kugel.
(dog barks)
(Homer shouts)
Uh, bad dog!
Bad neighbor dog.
Here, let me
help you up, Mr. Burns.
Watch it.
I love dogs.
Babies, too.
-(meows)
-(crowd gasping)
Kitty, kitty.
Are you all right,
Mr. Burns?
Oh, of course. A little roughhousing with
the pets is good for a man's appetite.
The latest polls
are in.
The statesman-like way
you handled the pet incident
has put you over the top.
You're ahead, 51 to 49.
Congratulations,
"Mr. Governor."
Excellent.
Bart, would you
like to say grace?
Dear God... we pay for
all this stuff ourselves,
so thanks for nothing.
(gasping)
(chuckles nervously)
Only an innocent child
could get away
with such blasphemy.
God bless them all.
Amen.
(chuckling)
He's smokin', he's smokin'.
Um, you know, Mr. Burns...
-my family and I, um...
-(burps)
feel like taxes
are too high.
Where do you stand on this
highly controversial issue?
Goodness, I didn't realize
this casual dinner
was going to turn into
a charged political debate.
I was only reading
what the card--
Homer, I agree with you,
and if I'm elected governor,
I will lower taxes
whether those bureaucrats
in the state capital
like it or not!
Lisa, do you
have a question
you would like to ask
your Uncle Montgomery?
Yes, sir.
A very inane one.
(Lisa sighs)
Mr. Burns,
your campaign
seems to have the momentum
of a runaway freight train.
Why are you so popular?
Ooh, a tough question,
but a fair one.
Lisa, there's no
single answer.
Some voters
respond to my integrity.
Others are more impressed
with my incorruptibility.
Still others by my
determination to lower taxes,
and the bureaucrats in the state capitol
can put that in their pipes and smoke it!
Oh, Mom, that felt awful.
I'm sorry, dear.
It will all be over soon.
But Mom, we've become
the tools of evil.
Lisa, you're learning many
lessons tonight and one of them is
to always give your mother
the benefit of the doubt.
BURNS: ...or fair shake,
or even a square deal.
(sniffing)
Mmm! Smells delightful.
(everyone gasps)
All right--
three-eyed fish!
Can I have your plate,
Mr. Burns?
(shudders)
Ptui!
(everyone gasps)
-Get a shot.
-I can't believe it.
He's blown it for sure.
Ruined before it
hit the ground.
Get me the City Desk.
Here's your headline, Phil--
"Burns can't swallow
own story."
The latest polls indicate
Burns' popularity
has plummeted to Earth
like so much half-chewed fish.
You must have a few tricks
left up your sleeve.
Smithers, boil some coffee.
We're not licked yet.
Yes, we are. Come on, boys,
the old guy's finished.
Wait! Come back.
You can't do this to me.
I'm Charles Montgomery Burns!
(grunting)
(straining)
Smithers, tip over
this table for me.
Yes, sir.
Homer...
Homer, make them stop.
Ahem!
Uh, Mr. Burns?
Shut up and wreck something!
Mr. Burns?
I hardly see
what destroying our
meager possessions
is going to accomplish.
She's right.
Take me home, Smithers.
We'll destroy
something tasteful.
Ironic isn't it, Smithers?
This anonymous clan
of slack-jawed troglodytes
has cost me the election,
and yet if I were
to have them killed,
I would be the one
to go to jail.
That's democracy for you.
You are noble and poetic
in defeat, sir.
Simpson, I shall make it
the focus of my remaining years
that your dreams
will go unfulfilled.
Uh-oh, you're busted, Dad.
HOMER: Oh. My dreams
will go unfulfilled?
Oh, no. I don't like
the sound of that one bit.
That means I have
nothing to hope for.
Marge, make it
better, please?
Can't you
make it better? Huh?
Homer, when
a man's biggest dreams
include seconds on dessert,
occasional snuggling,
and sleeping till noon
on weekends,
no one man can destroy them.
Hey, you did it!
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.