(8-bit synthesized version
of theme song playing)
♪ ♪
(electronic bell dinging)
(synthesized whistle blows)
(blipping)
(rapid blipping)
♪ ♪
(synthesized saxophone playing)
(blipping)
(synthesized horn honks)
(tires screech)
(bell dings)
(synthesized scream)
♪ ♪
(synthesized meowing, barking)
(theme song ends)
(The Jetsons theme song playing)
♪ ♪
♪ Here's Homer Simpson ♪
♪ And the problem child ♪
(jazzy sax solo plays)
♪ Hip daughter Lisa ♪
♪ Marge, his wife ♪
(The Jetsons theme song ends)
(computer printer buzzing, scratching)
HOMER:
Marge! Stop that crazy thing!
I've printed out our driving plan.
If we work together,
we can get Bart to his sports,
Lisa to her music,
and Maggie to the five birthday parties
she's invited to today.
I'm not spending
my precious Saturday
chauffeuring those overprivileged kids
to a better life than I ever had.
I need a ride to Cub Scouts.
Why are you asking me?
Is your thumb broken?
(screams)
(tires screeching)
Have him back
by Father's Day!
Homie, are you dressed?
You have soccer setup
in 20 minutes!
Homie?
-(phone ringing)
-(Homer gasping)
Moe, quick-- beer me
before I answer the phone!
Ah, the first pour of the day.
Let me just tie on my apron,
limber up the old tap-pulling arm...
(grunting)
(phone continues ringing)
Ooh... eh...
I need it now!
(gulping)
(sighs)
Hey, Marge.
I'm supposed
to help drive the kids?
Oh, man,
I wish I knew that sooner,
but I just had a beer.
You're already drinking
at 8:00 in the morning?
How much have you had?
(whimpers)
Come on!
Whoo-hoo! Off the hook!
(sighing)
Oh, looks like this is all me.
Yeah, while you're at it,
can you pick me up some beer?
Oh...
♪ ♪
(siren wailing)
Well, we've got an hour.
Who wants coffee?
Okay, but I'm buying.
No, no, I insist.
I'm stealing.
♪ ♪
(revving engines)
(engines roar)
(tires screeching
at every stop)
(engines roaring)
See you at the bake sale, sucker!
So Sideshow Mel
is drinking here all afternoon.
When I show him the tab,
he says he left his wallet
in his other skirt,
and he pays me with this.
Hey, this is a ticket
to see Laney Fontaine.
She's the brassiest
broad on Broadway!
She's funny and vulgar
and full of Hollywood stories,
like, uh... Jimmy Stewart
was a super-nice guy.
Oh, geez, now I want to go.
Why can't ya?
I can't close down
the bar on a Saturday.
That's when you guys can drink,
'cause you're not working
for three days.
Hey, Moe,
I'll take care of the bar.
You did me a favor today.
Huh... well, okay.
Uh, let me just show you
where everything is. Uh...
Shotgun, shotgun shells,
blood mop, bag of lime,
and that's it.
Now, boys, I gotta get dressed
for the, uh... the-a-ter.
(laughs)
And done.
Dare I say it? Yippee.
Oh... I didn't know we
could decorate our cars.
No, no--
it's a "Here to There" smile.
When that's on my grille,
I'm getting paid
to drive people around.
So you're a taxi?
No... (laughs) no, no... no.
We're a social-media-based
rideshare service.
We bring the "fair"
back to "fares."
Those aren't air quotes.
My fingers start doing that
after they're around
the wheel all day.
Mm. Well, I drive all day,
and I don't get paid a thing.
With the money you make,
I could buy a fridge...
with an ice maker.
(mechanical rumbling)
(laughs, gasps)
(moans)
(laughs)
Do you want to work for us?
Sure!
Are you over 23?
(giggles)
Yes.
-And are you under 80?
-Yes!
-You're in!
-Oh!
(Grampa humming)
What the...?
When I was a young car,
I didn't sit around smiling,
like I had nothing
better to do.
(humming)
Man, Moe's barely got
two nickels to rub together.
(murmuring)
I know a way
we can make this
Moe's biggest
Saturday night ever.
How does Moe make money
if ladies drink free?
That's the beauty part.
This place is about to be
filled with guys buying beers,
hoping to meet ladies.
(chuckles)
Brilliant!
Oh, and thanks for telling me
what the beauty part of it was.
So they pull out my gall bladder,
zip me up.
I grabbed a cab,
tapped my understudy and said,
"Not tonight, honey."
And here's the song
I killed 'em with.
♪ ♪
(audience whoops, applauds)
♪ If this isn't love ♪
♪ The whole world is crazy ♪
♪ Who's this Patrick Swayze? ♪
(laughs)
She changed the lyrics!
For me!
(dog howls in distance)
Then came the bombs:
Tobacco Valley,
What Color
Is Your Tambourine,
and The Smell of Music--
but I'm still here.
And I'd like to dedicate
this song
to the one great
love of my life,
the man who was my third
and fifth husband-- but...
you never know
what the future holds.
Oh-ho!
(dance music throbbing,
lively conversations)
Huh. Not a man in sight.
We got the Cheery Red Tomatoes,
a bachelorette party...
Ooh! Lady Duff!
I am woman, hear me pour!
Oh, yeah!
There's no guys!
We haven't made any money.
Not yet, but at least
we're hearing
some interesting conversation
from those two book clubs.
Well, we thought
The Heaven Lovers' Club
was rich and spiritual.
We thought it was maybe
a little slow.
Oh, well, maybe I can
liven it up for ya!
(grunts)
(screaming)
Let me help you up.
Ow!
MOE (moaning):
Oh, yeah.
Okay, stop here, please.
So this is the charming tavern
you've been telling me about.
Yep, nice and cozy and...
Wha...?
(gasps)
My crap hole!
My precious crap hole!
Anyone tries to stop me,
and you'll see her lovely bones
all over the floor!
This is nuts.
Tell me you still work,
Love Tester.
(buzzing)
Oh, I'm ruined!
Sorry, Moe.
I love losers,
but only after they've
bounced at the bottom.
♪ 'Cause I'm the brassiest
piece of sass ♪
♪ In this whole...
damn... town! ♪
Hyah!
You guys cost me my chance
with a woman of a certain age!
(sobs)
Hey, come on, all is not lost.
This coaster's fine.
(howling)
You are not my friends.
To me,
you're just mouths drinking beers.
You can't mean that!
We don't look at you that way.
Yeah, I'm-I'm sorry
for snapping at you guys,
but... but I'm ruint!
I'll have to live
on my savings here.
All right,
who rubbed my nickels?!
Hey, wait a minute--
we can get you a job.
There's an opening
at the nuclear plant,
'cause of that guy
that defected to North Korea.
Good old Dae Ho.
Used to give me the pickles off
his sandwich.
And all I had to do
was let him copy some keys.
Moe, can you pass
a background check?
Um...
Eh...
Er, uh...
Sure.
Well, then, you're in.
How far do they go back?
Six months.
Okay, I'm gonna apply in a week.
(text alert chimes)
Oh, Mom!
Someone wants you
to give them a ride.
At last! I'll earn money
for schlepping.
Wow, your mom has a job
and my dad still doesn't?
Just wait till winter comes, son.
There'll be driveways to salt!
Long, long driveways.
Thanks for the lift.
It's nice to know
I can get a ride
without having to put out.
You're welcome.
You know, if you really want
to get your belly button pierced,
go see a professional.
I'm ready for you, babe.
(clacking)
I'm gonna have
this done properly,
at a kiosk in the mall.
I'm Shauna.
Welcome to Springfield Nuclear,
Szyslak.
We'll start you off in Janitorial,
but there is room
for advancement.
Hey, I sure appreciate this,
fellas.
What you guys did to me,
then for me,
I'll never forget-slash-forgive,
so thanks a lot.
Also...
(angrily) thanks a lot!
What's for dinner, Mom?
I-I'm-I'm sorry,
but I'm not your mother.
Hey, I'm the one payin'.
Fine! There's meat loaf.
Mmm! What's meat loaf?
Left... left, left!
Left...
Left, left!
Left, left...
Eh... left!
Flamingos turn pink
from eating shrimp.
Cats have over
a hundred vocal cords.
The Golden Gate Bridge
is the longest span
between two towers.
Why are you telling me
all these things?
Isn't this Cash Cab?
No!
Oh! It's never Cash Cab.
Oh...
Faster!
Eh, slower.
Hard a-port!
Disco Stu says hang a "U"!
Make a louie up here at the...
-Stop sign!
-Blood bank!
Girl with big...
...punching bags?
So, for the love of God,
get me to Mexico!
Hey, swabbie,
you've missed spots there,
another one there,
and... there!
Every other spot is be-grimed!
It's called a checkerboard floor,
ya unwrapped mummy.
-You're f...
-Sir...
the NRC is here
for a surprise inspection.
We are gonna search this place
from top to bottom.
(shrieks)
That's where all the problems are.
I'll handle this, uh...
You're the head inspector, huh?
Yes, I am.
How come, on your badge,
you got a mustache,
but now you're not
wearing one, huh?
Oh, I was Freddie Mercury
in a Queen cover band,
but, uh, then I got demoted
to Brian May.
Yeah, well, I'm thrilled for your
musical career and everything,
but, uh, we got no way of knowing
if this is you.
I mean,
we gotta be careful here.
This is one of them, uh,
highly sensitive joints.
It'll take me weeks
to grow that mustache back.
Or years, to get a new badge!
Yeah, well,
that's your problem, ain't it?
You will see us again,
in God knows when.
Young man, how do you fit
such brilliance
into such an ugly, ethnic head?
Well, if you own a bar,
you either keep it clean
or learn to deal with inspectors.
And Moe don't clean.
Interesting attitude for a janitor.
What say we make you the new
supervisor of Sector 7G?
Me, a supervisor?
I feel like I overdosed
and went to heaven!
(laughs)
Those smart cars
are cutting into our business.
We used to get uber
amounts of work
giving people lifts.
(splutters)
I come to America to drive taxi.
Now my cab sits empty,
like Sochi Marriott.
Well, boss, the main problem
is Marge Simpson!
She's prompt, courteous
and a joy to ride with.
How do you know so much?
Oh, she, uh,
drives me to work every day.
And unlike the rest
of you cowards,
she's not afraid to parallel park.
(laughing, whooping)
Whoa, fellas,
that is not acceptable.
This is a nuclear plant!
Huh. No one was in there.
Look, Moe, the least you could let me do
is anything I want.
All right, let me be honest
with youse.
After all the money this plant lost
on that nitwit, Elon Musk,
they're looking for cutbacks,
so I've been going over your record.
(whimpers)
Yeah, the only reason
you haven't been fired
is because your file here
was holding up a sofa
that was missing a leg.
Well, that's the logic--
where's the affection?
Well, as supervisor,
I can't fraternize with the, uh,
what's the word...?
Scum.
Anyway, because I am your friend,
you are safe.
But...
you're gonna be reassigned.
Smithers, "what profit a man
if he gain the world,
and lose his soul?"
Seriously, I need an amount.
In round dollars.
(knocking on door)
Plant watering guy.
Yes, yes, go ahead.
Uh, and be careful
with the Venus flytrap.
All right.
They say you catch
more flies with honey.
I say, with flytraps.
(muffled)
What do I do now?
Just lean into it.
It'll be over soon,
one way or another.
(muffled)
Oh, all right.
D'oh.
Hey, guys, you mind if I join you?
They ran out of Beaujolais Cru
in the executive dining room,
and I ain't drinkin' white
with my coq-au-freakin'-vin.
I think I'd rather
sit somewhere else.
Yeah, I'm gonna take my lunch
back to the core.
Now they won't even
have lunch with me?
Well, you know, people can
kind of act like they're in grade school.
Oh, now you gotta throw your
grade school education in my face?
You know, Moe,
you're a real jerk!
I didn't mind so much
when it came with beer!
I don't need youse!
I'm all the company I need! Heh!
Oh! Oh!
I just lost my appetite.
Marge, which can
makes me look cooler--
the Drizzler or Mr. Drip?
(Marge groans wearily)
Aw, your leaves are drooping.
Here, let me turn that gloom
into bloom.
(whimsically)
♪ Dee-dee, doo-doo, doo... ♪
(moaning with satisfaction)
Homer Simpson!
Working with those plants
is great!
It's helped you get in touch
with your feminine side.
Feminine?!
(shrieks)
I didn't mean
to use that word!
I-It's okay to have
a feminine side!
It's good, in fact.
Oh...
♪ It was rainin' hard
in Springfield ♪
♪ I needed one more fare
to make my night ♪
(phone dings)
♪ I got a push notification
on my smartphone ♪
♪ Passenger ahead,
race: white ♪
Mind if we drive
in silence for a bit?
Whatever you want.
(sighs heavily)
(groaning dramatically)
♪ I asked if there was
somewhere I could take him ♪
♪ He said, "Just drive me,
Lady Blue" ♪
♪ I said, "I've had my share
of unhappy fares" ♪
♪ He said,
"I sure miss slingin' brew" ♪
Moe, I think we'd both
be a lot happier
if we quit our new jobs.
You know,
I think you're right there, Midge.
I'm gonna build my bar back up,
better than ever!
(hearty chuckle)
How hard can it be, eh?
Oh, God, this is so much worse
than I remember!
So, you drop off your lover
and go back to stealing our jobs.
He's not my lover.
Let the man speak!
Medallions!
Air fresheners!
(gasping)
Step away from
the social-media-enabled,
peer-to-peer
ride share platform.
(shouting fearfully)
Now, promise me you'll leave her be
and wipe down
your backseats annually...
Aw, come on!
(gunshot)
Okeydoke.
Now beat it.
Uh, I think it might
be time to hang up
the old beaded seat cover,
there.
Yep. And I know a place
that could use this smile.
Whew!
It's sure great to see you
jerking our suds again, Moe.
Yeah,
I figured out that the best way
for me to get along
with most people
is to be kept behind
a two-foot trunk of solid oak.
(chuckles)
Looks more like poplar to me.
Why, youse correcting me on
my knowledge of wood products?
Don't you slide me down the bar!
(thudding)
So good to be back.
MOE: Oh, shut up.
Well, I'm back where I belong, eh?
(deep voice)
You're not alone anymore.
What the hell was that?
Oh, you'll find out.
(theme song playing)
Shh!
Subtitled by Tara Strebe