CHORUS:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(theme music playing)
(bell ringing)
(whistle blowing)
(beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(playing off-key)
(horn honking)
D-ohh! (screams)
(all yelling)
(crows cawing)
(whistle blowing)
Ah, lunch time.
Well, let's see what I've
packed for myself today.
One bouillon cube.
One Concord grape...
One Philly cheesesteak...
And a jar of garlic pickles.
(chuckling)
No one will want to kiss me
after these, eh, Smithers?
Well, it's their loss, Sir.
(chuckling)
Yes.
(grunting)
Allow me, Sir.
(sighs) It's no use.
Shall I send out
for some Chinese?
No, those people
are all gristle.
I want this jar open.
(grunting)
(breathing heavily)
Worthless old geezers.
Phew... next.
All righty, I'll just...
(grunting)
You stinking...
(indistinct ranting)
(sputtering)
(sighing)
Oh, for goodness sake.
What we need around here
is some fresh blood.
Would you like me
to drain Simpson
while he's passed out, Sir?
No, no. To attract the top
grads
we'll need to make
a recruitment film,
a picture that showcases
our cutting-edge technology.
A talkie, Sir?
Ah, yes, brilliant.
That's just the kind
of far-out gimmick we need.
And... action.
Wow, what a graduation.
I'll say.
But with college behind us
we'll need careers,
and good ones.
What about chestnut roasting?
People always need chestnuts.
Or begging.
I know a place that'll
saw your legs off.
Slow down, fellas.
I've got a way
we can keep our legs
and still have a bright future.
Now you're dreaming.
Oh, am I?
Of course. Nuclear power.
It's the job of tomorrow...
Today.
Really?
Well, that settles it.
For all those reasons and more
let us choose
an electrifying career in...
-line.
-(sighs)
Nuclear power.
Oh, you dunderheaded stooges
are the worst bunch of...
Hey.
Pretty good, huh?
Well, it's better than that
last Barbara Streisand movie.
I didn't quite get
the point of it, Dad.
Why would Lenny want someone
to saw his legs off?
Well, there were script problems
from day one.
Didn't seem like anybody
even read the script.
That was the problem.
The important thing is
after all these years
of paying my dues
I'm finally getting
some decent parts.
You're joining
the Screen Actors Guild?
I didn't choose to be
a gifted actor, Marge.
It chose me.
I'm merely a vessel through
which genius flows.
Now help me make up some
phony credits.
-Fat guy number three?
-Good, good.
Hey, Dad, it says they
need your full name.
You only put down
your middle initial.
Hey, what the heck is
your middle name, anyway?
You know... I have no idea.
Hey, Dad, what does
the "J" stand for?
How should I know?
(grunting)
It was your mother's job
to name you
and love you and such.
I was mainly in it
for the spanking.
But I can't ask Mom.
She's on the run from the law.
Serves her right
for being a '60s radical--
Though she was a demon
in the sack.
(chuckling)
Uh, so, Dad, regarding that
form
why not just make up
a middle name?
You might as well.
You already made up
a phony film credit.
No. Homer Simpson does not lie
twice on the same form.
He never has
and he never will.
You lied dozens of times
on our mortgage application.
Yeah, but they were all part
of a single ball of lies.
The point is, I'm a grown man
and I deserve a middle name.
Hmm, I know where
we might find your
missing moniker.
It's a bit of a drive,
but on the way
we can have a nice
father-son chat.
Great.
I'll go shoot myself
for bringing this up.
This is the hippie commune
your mother ran off to
when life with me
became a living hell.
Wow, look at this place.
There's a pond
for skinny-dipping
a tire for skinny-swinging.
I can actually feel
the good vibrations.
(buzzing)
Ouch.
I remember them.
Seth and Munchie.
Look at those filthy,
lazy, flea-ridden...
Oh, hi there.
Hey, check it out.
Is that... Abe Simpson?
Geez, man, we haven't
seen you since Woodstock.
You went to Woodstock?
Your mother dragged us both
to that Godforsaken love-fest...
(playing "Star Spangled
Banner")
Boo! Bring on sha na na.
Whoa, mellow out, Abe.
Little Homer's trying to
groove.
(imitating guitar sounds)
Shame on you, boy.
Put some damn pants on
and then pull 'em down
'cause it's time for a
spanking.
Get a load
of Captain Bringdown.
Whoa.
Yeah, whoa.
But I want to play in the mud
and be a hippie.
Never. What you need's
a good long hitch in Vietnam.
There must be an enlistment tent
around here somewhere.
If I'd left it up to your
mother
you'd have ended up
in a hellhole like this--
just lying around, never
working
without a care in your head,
full of long, luxurious
hippie hair...
Oh, Homer J., how do
you keep your hair
so rich and full?
Lather, rinse, and repeat.
Always repeat.
Homer J., will you
teach us to make love?
Wow, I could have
lived like that?
You know, Homer,
your mom was
a pretty groovy chick.
And a demon in the sack.
(chuckling)
Oh, you heard about that, eh?
(laughs)
Heh. Anyway,
I--I still think about her
every time I walk by that mural
she painted.
Oh, my mother painted
that for me?
Oh, my God.
My middle name is
right behind that shrub.
I'll finally know
what "J" stands for.
From this moment forth,
I will be known as Homer...
Jay Simpson.
(sniffling)
It's so beautiful.
What a magical gift
for my mother to leave me.
She also left her old poncho.
Get off of there, Ginsberg.
(grunting)
I'll treasure this
poncho forever.
Uh, you might want
to wash that.
The dog has a lot
of skin and bladder problems.
All right,
we got what we came for
plus that stink rag to boot.
Now, let's hit the road.
ABE: Just lyin' around...
never workin'...
without a care in...
My head full of long,
luxurious hippie hair.
-I'll do it!
-What?
I'm going to be a hippie,
just like Mom wanted.
I'm going to let my spirit soar
and love all of God's
creatures.
Get off, you stupid dog.
(growling)
Okay. If I'm gonna be
a real hippy,
I have to learn from the
master.
Mr. Bob Flower-child Hope.
Hey, peace, man,
far out groovy, I'm a hippy.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Miss Jill St. John.
(crowd cheering)
Hey, Bob, I just came
to invite you to the love-in.
(gurgles)
I got you a date
with the perfect flower child-
Phyllis Diller.
(audience laughing)
Let's get it on.
(cackling)
Now I know
how Dean Rusk feels.
Good night, everybody.
Bummer. Love-in. Dean Rusk.
By George, I've got it!
Dad, do you mind?
Your feet are really
close to my potato.
Your potato?
You can't, like,
own a potato, man.
It's one
of Mother Earth's creatures.
(loud burp)
Homer, excuse yourself.
No way, narc.
Bodily functions
are a natural thing.
Not to mention hilarious.
(rude armpit noise)
You know, I really
don't appreciate
being called a narc,
and that poncho is filthy.
Let me dry-clean it for you.
(whimpering)
Why do you have
to turn everything
into one big plastic hassle?
Marge, you've got
too many hang-ups,
like the whole shaving trip.
Come on.
I want to see those legs
all furry and gross.
That ain't going to happen,
bub.
Well, at least lose the bra.
Free the "Springfield Two,"
Marge!
Free the "Springfield Two"!
I think you've had
too much strawberry wine.
(muttering)
WOMAN (shrieking) : Help!
Oh, I've never seen
anything like--
my eyes have been soiled.
Come on, Maude.
The human wang
is a beautiful thing.
Homer, for God's sakes,
put your poncho on.
Okay, okay.
(mutters) Narc.
(grunting noises)
-Oh!
-Ooh!
Heads up!
Hey, it's Homer Jay.
My man,
you've gone granola.
Right on.
Join the hack.
(grunting)
That was cool.
Think I'll stick around.
We've got everything
we need right here--
Good times, sunshine, free
love.
(purring growl)
(bell rings)
Okay, time to get back to work.
Work? But you're hippies.
Oh, we were on a break.
Time is money, man.
Huh?
What is this place?
We are the largest
organic juice company
in Springfield.
We grow our own vegetables
and process them right here
and we give half
the profits to war orphans.
Profits, profits, profits!
What kind of hippies are you?
Peter Fonda must be spinning
in his grave.
We're just trying
to pay the bills, Homer.
I mean, we're still
hippies at heart.
Oh, yeah?
When's the last time
you freaked out
the establishment?
You guys are total sellouts!
Wait. Don't you work
for a nuclear power plant?
Look, we can sit here all day
and play the blame game
or we can start
freaking people out.
Come on.
Where's your freak bus?
I drive a Saturn.
HOMER: A Saturn?
We used to have a bus.
In a way, the '60s ended
the day we sold it--
December 31, 1969.
Yeah, an old-time freak-out
sounds tempting, Homer,
but we've got
a big order to fill.
Fine.
I guess the juice business
is more important
than the ideals
our hippie forefathers
refused to go to war
and die for.
(sighs)
I suppose we could duck out
for a couple of hours.
Hey, we'll call it
a business trip
and write off the mileage.
Now your
freak flag's flying!
Let the freak-out begin!
Woo-hoo!
♪ Good sense, innocence,
cripplin' mankind ♪
♪ Dead kings, many things... ♪
Oh.
We're never going to freak
anybody out with this music.
I brought something
from my personal stash
that'll blow some minds.
♪ Uptown girl ♪
♪ She's been living
in her uptown world ♪
♪ I'll bet she never... ♪
Uh, can you turn that
down just a little?
Hey, square,
expand your mind.
The doors of perception
are open for business.
(chuckles)
Thanks for the tip, Homer.
Never fear!
The cosmic fool is here
to blow the lid off your
conformist, button-down world.
(high-pitched laughter)
Weirdos.
Hi, Marge.
We're freaking out squares.
Oh, lord.
What's in your
brand-new bag, mama?
Uh, it's that pair
of dockers you wanted--
48 waist with
the balloon seat, right?
(groans) Marge,
not in front of the hippies.
(bells tinkling)
Uh-oh. I don't like
the sound of that.
(bells tinkling)
(Homer screaming)Oh, please,
God, don't let them come in here.
(Homer screaming)
Hear ye! Hear ye!
The intergalactic jester
proclaims
this conformity factory closed.
(kids cheering)
Whoo-hoo!
Hmm. 15 years of loyal service
and this is how they tell me--
A jester with an
invisible proclamation.
(rock music playing)
That was fun.
I don't know if we actually
freaked anyone out, but...
No, no, no. Marge was
definitely freaked out.
Thanks, Homer.
It was nice to reconnect
with our hippie roots,
if only for a...
What the hell?
Oh, no!
Oh, man!
Your frisbee jammed
the juicilator, Homer.
Our entire shipment is ruined.
Uh, uh, pretty, uh, freaky,
huh?
The only people who are
going to be freaked out
are our stockholders.
I'm sensing some negative
vibes here, but I promise
tomorrow's freak-out
will go a lot smoother.
There won't be
any more freak-outs.
You're not a hippie
and you never were.
Yes, b--but the poncho?
Please, Homer,
just leave us alone.
How could you let me
turn into you?
B--but the poncho.
(mocking)
B--but the poncho!
Hit the road, square.
(grunts)
Uh-oh.
Oh!
Oh, for crying out loud!
Stunned league officials say
point-shaving may have occurred
in as many as three
Harlem Globetrotters games.
And in business news,
Groovy Grove Juice Corporation
has announced
it will miss delivery
on its third-quarter shipment.
A spokesman attributed
the production shutdown
to a half-witted oaf.
Ah, it was sweet of those guys
to blame an oaf,
but really, it was my fault.
I just don't have the discipline
to be a hippie.
Ooh, does this mean you're going
to start showering again?
Perhaps... in time.
Ah, cheer up, Dad.
You make a great hippie.
Ah, you're just saying that.
No, really. You're lazy
and self-righteous.
And the soles of your
feet are jet black.
Well, I do walk through
pretty much anything.
Oh, you kids are sweet.
I know you feel bad
about the juice incident,
but I'm sure you
can make up for it somehow.
That's it! Somehow!
Sleep, gentle hippies, sleep.
Let old Homer Jay
set things right.
♪ It's the time of the season ♪
♪ And let me try
with pleasured hand ♪
♪ To take you in the sun
to promised lands ♪
♪ To show you every one ♪
♪ It's the time of the season
for loving... ♪
(shrieks)
Good morning, Starshine, Seth.
(both gasp)
What's going on?
What happened
to our crops?
I picked them, juiced them
and delivered them
to every store in town.
Your business is saved.
But there weren't
enough vegetables left
to fill that order.
(chuckles)
That's what I thought at first,
but then I found the other
garden behind the barn--
The one with
the camouflage netting.
Uh-oh.
Homer, those were
our personal vegetables.
Well, now the whole town
can benefit
from their nutrients.
♪ One pill makes you larger ♪
♪ And one pill makes you small
♪
Fergie!
Willie, you complete me.
Saints be praised.
Oh, closer....
I've always dreamed
of this moment.
(moaning)
(groaning)
(yells)
♪ And if you go
chasing rabbits ♪
(yelling)
Ah!
♪ And you know
you're going to fall ♪
♪ Tell them a hookah... ♪
Whoo! Thanks, Pinky.
You've always
been there for me.
♪ ...Has given you the call ♪
♪ Call Alice ♪
-Huh?
-(giggling)
Morning, Ned.
Pucker up, Ned. Mwah.
(yelling)
(both laughing)
(laughter continues)
We are so old.
Yeah.
(both giggling)
LOU: (laughing) Whee!
(laughing)
Lou? Lou, are you all right?
The electric yellow has got me
by the brain banana.
I see.
My God.
It's nothing but carrots
and peyote.
Hmm. Damn long-hairs
never learn, Chief.
Yeah, it's time
for an old-fashioned
hippie ass-whomping.
(sirens waling)
Attention, hippies.
Come out peacefully
so we can smash your drug mill
and all your
worldly possessions.
Officer, please.
We can explain.
Not so fast, pig!
We're making a stand--
a freaky stand.
You can smash this drug barn
all you want,
but first you'll have to smash
our heads open like ripe melons.
This man does not represent us.
All right, boys.
Set your nightsticks on
"whomp."
Um, mine's stuck on "twirl."
Oh, for the love of... There.
Now, let's crack some skulls.
Seth, Munchie, they can destroy
our bodies and our ponchos,
but they can never silence
our song of protest.
♪ Uptown girl ♪
♪ She's been living in
her white bread world... ♪
-Come on, guys.
-(all grunt)
Forget the clubs.
Just shoot him.
(rifles clicking)
Look at yourselves
pointing guns
at your fellow men.
Hatred is a cage
that keeps us from soaring free.
Yes, the '60s
may be dead and gone
and its spirit
long since extinguished,
but its ideals live on--
Freedom!
Love!
And peace.
-(gunshot)
-Ow!
Doctor, will he be all right?
Yes, he was lucky.
If that had been a gladiola,
he'd be dead right now.
Why don't you just pull it out?
(chuckles)
I'm a doctor, not a gardener.
Can't you just prune some
of the leaves so I can watch TV?
What did I just say?
(slow instrumental music
playing)
♪ Uptown girl ♪
♪ She's my uptown girl ♪
♪ I know that I'm in love ♪
♪ With an uptown girl ♪
-HOMER: I buried Flanders.
-MARGE: Shh.
Captioned by
Visual Data Media Services