♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
ANNOUNCER: "Movie For A Rained-Out
Ballgame" now returns to
Dyan Cannon, Troy McClure
and the Muppets
in the 1977 film...
O princess fair,
wilst thou grant me
thine dainty hoof
in marriage?
O Sir Lies-A-Lot,
I will!
Mmm.
(sexy growl)
Unhand the swine, you swain!
Come, piggy.
Back to Hamelot.
Not now, frog.
Me and Iron Pants
are just getting acquainted.
(both grunting)
Dad, what's a Muppet?
Well, it's not quite a mop,
and it's not quite a puppet,
but, man...
(laughing)
So, to answer your question,
I don't know.
BART: Why'd they make
that one Muppet out of leather?
That's not a leather Muppet.
That's Troy McClure.
Oh, back in the '70s, he was
quite the teen heartthrob.
Yeah. Who'd have thought he'd
turn out to be such a weirdo?
What are you talking about?
You know--
his bizarre personal life.
Those weird things they say
he does down at the aquarium.
-Why, I heard...
-Oh, Homer, that's just an urban legend.
People don't do that
type of thing with fish.
Troy McClure's
a perfect gentleman
like Bing Crosby or J.F.K.
I wonder where Troy is now?
TROY: Hey, these guys
are all over the road.
-(siren blaring)
-(animal yelping)
All right, Captain Rush-Rush.
Out of the car. Ow!
Oh, I'm seeing stars here.
No, just one.
Hi, I'm Troy McClure.
You may remember me
from such films as
The Greatest Story Ever Hulaed
and They Came
to Burgle Carnegie Hall.
Uh... 'fraid not.
License, please.
Says here you need
corrective lenses.
Put those glasses on, mister.
You wouldn't ask
a handsome man like me
to wear glasses.
It'd be a crime against nature.
(groans)
Gaa! Well, they do kind of
make you look like a nerd.
Tell you what, just go down to the D.M.V.
tomorrow and try to pass that eye test.
I'll tear up this ticket but I'm still
going to have to ask you for a bribe.
Hello, Marge. Hello, Marge.
How come no Chippendales dancers
ever come in to renew
their licenses?
They carpool.
That's the problem.
Hey, I came here
to get this revoked.
Troy McClure?
I thought he disappeared
after that scandal
at the aquarium.
Hey, I thought you said
Troy McClure was dead.
No, what I said was he
sleeps with the fishes.
-You see...
-Uh, Tony, please, no.
I just ate a whole plate
of dingamagoo.
Whoa! Troy McClure!
Oh..! Hello, beautiful.
John Law tells me I might need
to wear these glasses.
You? Nonsense.
You're Troy McClure.
I remember you from such
films as Meet Joe Blow
and Give My Remains
to Broadway.
Stars like you
don't need glasses.
Yech!
Now, Mr. McClure,
would you like to take off
those glasses
and read the top line?
Uh... "W"
seven...
star, pound...
duh...
Look, Miss Bouvier.
As an actor, I depend on
my remarkable looks.
If you could find it
in your heart to pass me,
I'm sure I could find
some way to repay you.
(gulping)
Mubble.
Say, by buying you dinner?
That took a lot of class.
All these celebrities on
the walls-- I just know
a big star like you
is up there somewhere.
Uh, yes, I'm over there.
Selma (grunting):
Hmm...
Hmm?
Hm-mmm.
-Ohm...
-(yowls)
So, working at the D.M.V.
must be very interesting.
Well, uh, I think I'm getting
repetitive stress disorder
from scratching my butt all day.
(clearing throat)
Being a huge movie star
must be good, too.
What are you
working on now?
I've been reading
a lot of scripts lately.
You know, it's a lot cheaper
than going to the movies.
Well, thanks for holding up
your end of the bargain.
I had a pretty good time.
Yeah, me too.
You need a ride somewhere?
Hey, get a load of this.
Troy McClure
and what looks like a date.
Here you go, boys.
A little something
for Page One.
Hey, Homer, isn't this
your sister-in-law
on a date
with Troy McClure?
Troy McClure.
He's a washed-up movie star.
He could be dating
washed-up supermodels.
Well, I don't know.
Maybe those rumors
about his fish fetish
weren't true after all.
Ah, this changes
everything.
I'd pay to see him
in a movie now.
If only that
were possible.
(phone ringing)
Troy, my man,
it's MacArthur Parker.
MacArthur Parker, the agent?
MacArthur Parker, my agent?
Just checking in, my friend.
So, how's my favorite client?
We haven't spoken
in eight years.
Yes. So, I saw
the papers today, Troy.
Looking good.
That wholesome stuff
really helps
when I'm trying
to find you work.
You haven't found me work
in 12 years.
Oh, you...
Uh, jury duty is work.
And, listen,
you keep getting seen in public
with human females,
and I can get you work
in the entertainment industry.
Hey...
Hello, Selma Bouvier?
It's Troy McClure.
You may remember me
from such dates
as last night's dinner.
That's right, boys,
Troy's back from the gutter
and he's brought
someone with him.
(theatrical laughter)
That's too funny.
I can't remember when I've heard
a funnier anecdote.
Okay, now, you tell one.
Well, not much happens to me,
but I once had dinner
with a movie star,
and it was the most wonderful
night of my life.
Really?
Who was it, George Segal?
I hear he plays the banjo.
Um, yeah...
(gasping)
(crowd murmurs)
Excuse me, I ordered a Zima,
not emphysema.
Please, don't smoke
in our restaurant.
We don't serve
contemporary California cuisine
in your lungs.
Troy, uh, I'm sorry
I ruined our evening.
I have to go now.
Oh, my God.
(labored breathing)
Oh, God, I'm such a fool.
Got a light?
(both coughing)
Oh...
Sounds like you're really
falling for him.
What's the matter,
I'm not fun enough for you?
Patty. Go on, Selma,
tell me more.
I don't want to jinx it, Marge,
but this could be it.
He asked me out again
this Friday.
He's taking me
to a special screening
of his latest film.
You know,
smoke actually smells good
when it's coming
out of you.
Oh, I'm all out.
Here. Try one of my cigars.
Mmm.
My God, it's like
five cigarettes at once!
Oh. My head is swimming.
That's not cigars, baby.
That's love.
(echoing movie dialogue)
No longer canst I
conceal my love,
my wimpled turtledove.
-Whoa!
O princess fair,
wilst thou grant me
thine dainty hoof in marriage?
Oh, Troy, I will!
Mmm, mmm... Whoa.
Just a second, baby.
-Mmm, mmm...
Tonight,
'70s leading man Troy McClure
has finally met the woman
of his dreams.
We may remem-- A woman! Huh!
Okay. We may remember Troy
from such films
as The Verdict Was Mail Fraud,
and Leper in the Backfield.
(chuckling)
With his high-profile romance,
Troy's managed to shake
the rumors
that have dogged his career,
and with news
of his upcoming wedding,
rumor has it he's up
for some very choice roles.
Looks like you were wrong
when you called him
a washed-up deviant,
eh, Lori?
(chuckles)
All right.
SELMA:
Make sure my iguana's okay.
Selma, Jub Jub
is fantastic.
He's everywhere
you want to be.
Welcome to your
new home, baby.
It's fantastic!
Garbage collection is Monday.
If you want to throw out a box,
you have to cut it up.
It's so modern...
it's ultramodern.
Like living in
the not-too-distant future.
Now, you make yourself
at home here.
I'll be sleeping downstairs
in the visitors center.
Oh... okay.
I'll see you in the morning.
And get ready for tennis.
It comes on at 10.
(clicks tongue)
(ringing)
Troy, Mac Parker.
Ever hear of
Planet of the Apes?
Uh... the movie or the planet?
The brand-new
multimillion-dollar musical,
and you are starring...
as the human.
It's the part
I was born to play, baby.
Help. The human's
about to escape.
Get your paws off me,
you dirty ape.
(gasping)
He can talk.
He can talk, he can talk,
he can talk,
he can talk, he can talk.
♪ I can sing! ♪
Ooh! Help me, Dr. Zaius.
("Rock Me Amadeus"
by Falco playing)
♪ Dr. Zaius, Dr. Zaius ♪
♪ Oh, Dr. Zaius ♪
♪ What's wrong with me? ♪
♪ I think you're crazy ♪
♪ Want a second opinion ♪
♪ You're also lazy ♪
♪ Dr. Zaius, Dr. Zaius ♪
♪ Oh, Dr. Zaius ♪
♪ Can I play the piano
anymore? ♪
♪ Of course you can ♪
♪ Well, I
couldn't before... ♪
This play has everything.
Oh, I love legitimate theater.
♪ I hate every ape I see ♪
♪ From chimpan-a
to chimpanzee ♪
♪ No, you'll never
make a monkey
♪ Out of me ♪
♪ Oh, my God, I was wrong ♪
♪ It was Earth all along ♪
♪ You've finally made
a monkey ♪
♪ Yes, we finally made
♪ Yes, you finally ♪
♪ Made a monkey ♪
♪ Out of me ♪
I love you, Dr. Zaius.
(cheering and applause)
Thank you.
It's great to be back.
I just want to say,
I wouldn't be here
without the support
of a very special lady,
my always outrageous
fiancée, Selma.
Take a bow, Sugar Beet.
Oh, well. Thank you.
Down in front!
My good looks paid
for that pool,
and my talent filled it
with water.
Hi, I'm Troy McClure,
your future uncle.
Hi. I remember you
from such filmstrips
as Locker Room Towel Fight:
The Blinding of Larry Driscoll.
You know, I was one of the first
to speak out against horseplay.
-Uh-huh.
-Remember when we were kids,
we used to dream
about our ideal husbands?
Who knew the dream
would come true for one of us?
Oh, come on.
Guess which one?
I know, I know.
It's Selma, right?
TROY (slurring words):
Yeah. It's a good idea, Homer,
but they've already made some
movies about World War II.
Ah, hell.
Well, what about Dracula?
Homer, I'm really touched
you invited me out on the town.
You're going to be
a four-star brother-in-law.
Troy, buddy, I got to know.
What's a great guy like you
want to marry a guy like Selma?
-Come here, Homer.
-Okay.
I'll let you in
on a little secret.
(whispering)
(laughing)
And do you, Selma Bouvier
Terwilliger Bouvier
take the fabulous
Troy McClure
to be your lawful
wedded husband?
-I already told you, yes.
-If anyone here knows why
this couple should not be wed
in holy matrimony,
let him speak now
or forever hold his peace.
(humming Rock Part 2 by Gary Glitter to
himself): ♪ Dah, dah, dah-dah-dah, hey! ♪
♪ Dah-dah, dah-dah ♪
♪ Dah, dah, dah-dah-dah, hey! ♪
♪ Dah-dah ♪
I now pronounce you
husband and wife.
You may now kiss each other.
♪♪
This is the best day
of my life.
It's a good day
for me, too, baby.
Now, smile.
We're going to be
on every newsstand
in the country.
Hey, look what
I snagged, Marge--
the candy bride and groom
from the wedding cake.
(metallic crunching)
Oh!
Mmm... pointy.
It was a beautiful wedding.
I've never seen Selma happier.
That reminds me.
Troy said something interesting
last night at the bar.
Apparently, he doesn't
really love Selma,
and the marriage is just a sham
to help his career.
Well, enough talk.
Let's snuggle.
What? Oh, my God!
HOMER: Marge, could you close
your eyes?
I'm trying to sleep.
There.
This better be important.
It's my wedding night.
I'm trying to sleep.
Hey, sleep is for has-beens
my friend.
and you're about to have
a very crowded schedule.
This marriage scam is
paying off big time.
-Phone for you.
-T. McC.
Troy, darling, come to bed.
I want to see
the Troy McClure I remember
from such films
as Make-Out King of Montana
and The Electric Gigolo.
(low chuckling)
Yeah, in a minute, darling.
Well, she may be helping
my career
but she's starting
to cramp my style.
Oh, who cares?
The offers are rolling in.
Paramount wants you
for a buddy comedy
with Rob Lowe and Hugh Grant.
-Those sick freaks?
-Okay, then get this.
I think they want you
to play McBain's sidekick
in, brace yourself,
the new McBain movie.
McBain's sidekick? Hot damn!
I'm going to Sea World!
Selma...
about you and Troy--
we're not sure
he's... all he seems.
Marge is right.
He's wrong for you.
Better you find out
sooner than later.
Wrong for me? How?
Oh, I get it.
My sisters have come down
with a case
of the green-eyed gazongas.
I guess
I shouldn't be surprised.
You're stuck
in a menial job
you'll be doing ten
years after you die.
And you're
tied down to a man
who'd have to bathe
to be a slob.
Selma, Troy doesn't
love you at all.
He's only using you
to squelch the rumors
about his bizarre personal life
and further his career.
(grumbles) You don't know
what you're talking about.
I have to go now
and see Troy.
(door opens, closes)
(tires screech)
Is this a sham marriage?
Sure, baby,
is that a problema?
You married me just
to help your career?
You make it sound so sordid.
Look, don't we have
a good time together?
Yes, but--
Don't you have everything
you ever wanted here--
money, security, a big,
hot, flat rock for Jub Jub?
But... don't you love me?
Sure, I do, like I love Fresca.
Isn't that enough?
The only difference
between our marriage
and anyone else's is,
we know ours is a sham.
Are you gay?
Gay? I wish.
If I were gay,
there'd be no problem.
No, what I have is
a romantic abnormality--
One so unbelievable
that it must be hidden
from the public at all costs.
-You see--
-Stop.
You're asking me to live a lie.
I don't know
if I can do that.
It's remarkably easy.
Just smile for the cameras
and enjoy Mr. Troy's Wild Ride.
You'll go to the right parties,
meet the right people.
Sure, you'll be a sham wife,
but you'll be the envy
of every other
sham wife in town.
So, what do you say, baby?
Tell me again
about Mr. Troy's Wild Ride.
One day my lady Selma's
going to have a star
right next to mine.
So, watch out,
Laszlo Panaflex.
Yay! Yay! Yay!
Tonight, all Hollywood's
wondering who'll be chosen
to co-star
in the big new McBain picture,
McBain IV-- Fatal Discharge.
(rings)
Oh, you watching?
Mac, you gotta
get me that part.
I will, but you got
to do something for me.
Problem is, the big parts these days
are all going to family men.
But I already
got married.
Yeah, but for a role like this,
you got to pour it on.
You and, uh, wife have
got to have a baby.
A baby, eh?
What do I do?
I'll send you over
a pamphlet.
Listen, you can't buy
that kind of P.R.
But you can get it for nothing
by having a baby,
which by the way,
your insurance will cover,
except for the deductible,
which I'll reimburse you for
if you get the part,
which you will,
if you have a baby.
C'est Troy bien.
Okay. Now listen.
Let's talk baby names.
You can't use Montana,
Dakota or Florida.
-They're taken.
-Mmm. Oregon?
Oh, Pacific Northwest,
very hot.
Having a child?
That's a big step.
You bet it is.
Think what it'll mean.
Not just the McBain movie,
but maybe my own fragrance--
Smellin' of Troy.
It is probably
my last chance to be a mommy.
-Cigarette, Mrs. McClure?
-You bet.
From now on,
she's smoking for two.
Ah, come here, Tiger.
(sexy growl)
Would you like some wine?
Yes.
(weak growl)
Uh, why don't you
come over here
and make yourself
more comfortable?
No. Why don't you
come over here
and make yourself
comfortable?
I'm sorry.
This whole concept's
foreign to me.
Who knew a baby
would be so much work?
Having a baby
isn't supposed to be work.
It's supposed to be
an expression of the feelings
we're supposed to have
for each other.
Oh, like how we built
that snowman together
in that Newport ad?
Remember how alive with pleasure
they said we were?
Look, I'm sorry.
A loveless marriage
is one thing.
We're not hurting anybody.
But bringing a child
into a loveless family
is something I just can't do.
Oh, great. We'll adopt.
I'll call my agent.
He'll find some kid
who wants in on the deal.
Good-bye, Troy.
I'll always remember you...
but not from your films.
Come on, Jub Jub.
Let's go home,
and I'll microwave you
some nice roaches.
(croaks)
In a bold move that
has stunned Hollywood insiders
newly divorced comeback kid,
Troy McClure
has turned down
the supporting lead
in McBain IV to direct and star
in his own pet project--
The Contrabulus Fabtraption
of Professor Horatio Hufnagel.
Will the gambit pay off?
20th Century-Fox
is betting it will.
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.