The Simpsons
D'oh!
Won't you marry me, Bill?
I got the wedding gown bill
Because weddings are nice
Let's never miss
the school bus again.
That was
The 5th Dimension with
Weddings are Nice.
You know what
else is nice, Marty?
What's that, Bill?
The KBBL Prize Posse!
Damn dirty ape!
If our
Wampum Wagon spots your
KBBL Party Penguin,
you'll win $40!
Did you hear that, Pengy?
$40!
Hey!
There's the Wampum Wagon!
End of the line, boys!
Look out,
because it's zooming!
If we're late for school,
we'll miss our free
federal breakfast!
Big deal. It's just
saltines and fig paste.
Ew! Saltines!
Hey, Cora.
I heard science
is working on a donut
that actually
burns off calories.
How's that going?
What?
Never mind.
Just refill this
with jelly, will you?
Thanks.
You're an angel.
What?
Hey, check it out.
Wiggum's cruiser.
Wow! Tear gas,
riot club, police hat.
With rain baggy!
Oh, man.
That would really
keep your head dry.
Have you ever
been in a police car?
Not in the front.
Hey, I just had
this crazy idea!
Really? What?
What's this thing?
"Miranda Rights Teleprompter. "
Check this out!
You there!
Put your hands up!
Me? Okay.
Now, drop your pants.
Yeah, but...
But my hands are up.
Hula out of them.
All right, Officer.
What the heck is
going on out there?
Officer Sniffy?
Come in, Sniffy.
Do you read me?
It's me, Clancy.
No! Get away!
Uh-oh.
Hey, somebody's
stealing my car!
What?
Look out!
Soup!
That's why
you young athletes
are so promising.
Now, who'd like
to buy a trophy?
Finally, some recognition.
All right.
You two are under arrest
for joyriding.
You have
the right to remain, um...
Uh...
Silent?
That doesn't sound right.
I love our court days.
It's about
the only thing we do
as a family anymore.
Hey, Karie.
Hey, Lisa.
Your Honor,
please don't send
my son to juvie.
He's basically a good kid.
He's just weak.
Morally and in
the upper body.
Hmm.
Please let me slip
through the cracks.
Well,
you look like a good student,
what with those glasses,
and I suppose
boys will be boys.
Case dismissed.
Good old Judge Snyder.
Next defendant,
Bartholomew J. Simpson.
Well, show time.
Why, hello, Bart.
Say, are those new shoes?
Yes, they are, Roy.
Judge Snyder?
While we're young?
Oh. Sorry. Oh, my.
Looks like you
were the ringleader
in this car theft!
And that's a felony!
Yes, sir.
On the other hand,
I was young once.
I'll bring the car around.
And I suppose
boys will be...
Oops.
My vacation just started.
All rise
for the Honorable
Judge Constance Harm.
Uh-oh.
Silence in my courtroom!
Grand theft auto?
It was an accident, ma'am.
Don't spit on my cupcake
and tell me it's frosting.
What did she say
about cupcakes?
According to this,
your father was
driving you to school?
Then where was he
when you stole
the police car?
Your Honor, I was
chasing the KBBL Party
Penguin Prize Patrol.
You abandoned
your son to win $40?
And a Blue Oyster
Cult medallion. Cool.
And that was more important
than keeping your son
out of trouble?
Your Honor,
if I may sing a little bit
of Don't Fear the Reaper,
I think
you'll agree that...
I'm familiar with B.O.C.
But you have got a boy here
who is crying out
for adult supervision!
I couldn't agree more.
Perhaps some sort
of court-appointed
babysitter or "au pair. "
Sorry, bub.
That crow won't caw.
It won't?
I hereby order you
to be tethered to your son!
Tethered?
Tethered.
Report to room five.
Room five?
There we go.
How's that?
It's a little tight.
Sir, you are not
a size four.
I used to be.
This punishment
is so cruel.
And unusual.
Can that judge
do this to us?
Creative sentencing
is common these days.
That's why Bill Clinton
is our new mailman.
Dang magazines.
Well, maybe it'll be fun.
You'll get to spend
more time together.
Make sure your father
takes his mood medication.
I'll medicate you... Honey.
You know, this could be fun.
Race you to the kitchen,
my little tether ball.
You're on,
Rope-a-Dope!
Today we're going to
talk about predicates
and predicate nominatives.
Boring!
Mr. Simpson,
I'm trying to teach.
Come on.
These kids are never
gonna use that stuff.
Will you please
just go back to sleep?
Fine.
All right, now,
who can pick out
the predicate
in this sentence?
What's wrong
with him now, Bart?
Night terrors, ma'am.
Cobras!
Okay, Son, concentrate.
Shut out everything
but the sound
of my criticism.
Swing!
Hey, hey! Run, Bart!
Pump your thighs!
Pump them!
Hurry up, Dad!
I'm with you, Son.
Safe!
Wow. My first home run.
That's my boy.
Come on, hug me.
Cobras! Cobras!
I thought I would
hate working nights,
but it's so peaceful.
And there's no one
here to squeal on me
for shooting mice.
Can I ask you
something, Dad?
Sure, boy.
The town keeps
getting bigger.
Will there always be
enough electricity?
Oh, Son, you know
that's none of your business.
Say, is that our house?
Uh, I don't think our
house has a steeple.
Yeah.
I forget things sometimes.
Really?
You like skateboards?
Mmm-hmm.
We're sure learning
a lot about each other.
Yeah. This tether
has some pluses.
My head! I need a beer.
I hit my head, Moe.
One beer, coming up.
Hey, hey,
no kids in the bar!
Since when?
The heat's been on
since them Bush girls
were in here.
All right, all right.
Come on, Bart.
I'm cold and scared.
That's my little slugger.
Come on, Dad. Let's go.
Hey, knock it off!
These pants cost $600.
Really?
Yeah. They're Italian.
All right, hand them over.
Moe, what the...
Yeah, I rob now.
There's a new
judge in town
with a hard-nosed
approach to juvenile crime.
Punish the parents.
It's about time.
Oh.
Kids are running wild, Kent.
And I blame
Mr. and Mrs. Neverspank.
Uh-oh. We'll have to
bleep their names.
You'll bleep nothing.
Parents, it's time
to take control.
If you can't cope,
you'll wear the rope.
Well, you can tell
she's never had kids.
Look how high and firm
her breasts are.
Granted.
But you gotta admit,
constant supervision
has been good for Bart.
He might even
make the honor roll,
if Dad can control
his night terrors.
Well, that's
a pretty big if, honey.
Come on, Dad.
I gotta go to
the bathroom.
I just got comfortable.
Use the bottle.
No! I don't want
you going in a bottle.
That's what hobos do.
Come on, Homer.
No.
Mom!
Oh, geez.
Homer, just take
him to the bathroom.
Fine! I don't know why
we even have a bottle!
Somebody tell me!
Would you mind?
I'm trying to do
my homework.
Son, it's a little chilly.
Maybe you
should wrap a blanket
around your head.
Homie, no. We can't.
What's the...
What's the big deal?
He sees
a thousand times worse
on that Animal Channel!
I don't want him to see us...
Expressing our love.
Why not? Kids are
very visual these days!
No!
But...
The lady said no.
Hey, shut up.
You shut up.
Ow!
Why, you...
What'd you do that for?
Because I... Ow!
You... Ow!
Ah!
Ow!
Oh, yeah?
I'm sleeping
in the bathtub.
Why, you little...
Ow! Ow! Ow!
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
That really hurt.
I can't take it anymore!
Mom, you cut the tether.
We're free!
Your mother set us free!
Woo-hoo!
Don't celebrate too much.
Hey, what...
Who said that?
That's right.
It's me, Judge Harm,
through the magic
of fiber optics.
Hey, how about that?
Quiet, Tubsy!
You violated my order.
But Constance,
it only happened because...
Hey, hey, if I want
a cock and bull story,
I'll read Hemingway.
Don't be mad at Homer.
I was the one
who cut the rope.
Are you threatening
me with that knife?
No!
Wait. I'm to blame, Judge.
You see,
I was pressuring my wife
to make love
in front of our son,
you're gonna laugh
when you hear this,
when suddenly...
Well, I thought
Dad was the problem,
but apparently Mom is
no prize pig herself.
It's a miracle
poor Bartholomew isn't
robbing banks and
chasing sweet Lady H.
I'm a latchkey kid.
You are not!
Quiet, little girl!
You two need to wake up
and smell the java,
and the first step
is to admit that
you're bad parents.
I admit it.
Homer, no.
We're not bad parents.
Yes, you are!
Just say it!
No, I won't!
And frankly, Judge,
I think you're a bully!
You do, huh?
You're so busy
thinking up crazy ways
to punish people,
you can't see how
much I love my kids.
Your Honor, I'd like
to be tried separately.
I don't mean to be
disrespectful, Judge Harm,
but we are not bad parents,
and there isn't
a tether in this world
with enough fiber optics
to make me say we are.
Hmm.
She's such a butthole.
Sorry!
Just... Just let me get...
Ow!
Damn it!
Poor Mom and Dad.
Do you think it's fair
that you're always
getting into trouble
yet Mom and Dad
are being punished?
No, it's terrible.
Well, why don't you do
something about it?
After wrestling.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I don't believe
what I am seeing.
Doctor Bonebreak
just married Rumble-lina,
and they're already
whaling on each other!
When are you gonna start
taking responsibility
for your actions?
'Cause I felt like it.
You're not even listening.
I know you are,
but what am I?
Haven't we been
humiliated enough?
Not yet, no.
Today the judge
wants you to bend over
so people can spank you
from their cars.
Well, that explains the sign.
Yeah! Ooh!
Here comes a car.
Yarr, ye scurvy dogs!
Ow!
Worst parents ever!
Ha-ha!
Hey! No extension cords!
You know,
we could get out of
these stupid things
if you'd just tell the judge
you're a bad mother.
And you don't even
have to say "bad. "
It could be
"negligent" or "unfit"
or "drugged up. "
I just can't do that, Homer.
It's a matter of principle,
and I need you to
support me in this.
You're right.
It's time to stand up
to that firm-breasted judge.
But first,
we've gotta break
out of these stocks.
Easy. Easy.
I want goggles, too!
Shh!
You'll wake up Flanders.
What the...
Hey, Marge, surf's up!
You're using my table saw
to violate a court order?
Well, we tried
all those other tools.
Gee, I always like
to help you, Homer,
but I don't want
to be an accessory to
some sort of shady doings.
And it does
raise a whole host
of ethical questions,
such as...
Woo-hoo!
Now, time for "Operation
Judge-Get-Back-At. "
If that costume shop
knew we were using
these burglar
outfits for real,
they'd be furious.
Okay. She lives at
1 Ocean View Drive.
Let's start skulking.
Oh.
It's only the milkman.
Hey, maybe I should
be a milkman!
Concentrate, Homer.
This address must be wrong.
No! No, there it is!
She lives in a houseboat?
Wow! She is so cool!
We hate her, Homer.
I know. I know.
Fight the power.
Let's do this thing.
Cops!
Ain't that sweet, Chief?
It sure is, Lou.
Those two longshoremen
found love.
Let's go.
Look at her in there,
washing her body.
Get away from that window
and help me with this banner.
I hate to call
a judge dirty names,
but there's only
one way to describe
a nasty super witch like her.
Let's get out of here!
It's just a friendly seal.
Shh.
No, we can't play now.
Shut up!
What is it, Pancho?
Is someone out there?
You can't hide from me.
She's gonna find us!
Oh, Lord,
guide this cinder block.
Homer, no!
Oh-oh.
My house!
Hey, how you doing?
That quilt was made
by my grandmother!
So... It cost you nothing.
Shut up!
You two are not
only horrible parents,
you're violent criminals,
and I'm gonna lock you up
till frogs do fractions.
Your Honor,
may I say something?
Well,
it is highly unorthodox.
So, no!
Please, Your Honor?
Oh, I can't resist
that look.
You remind me of me
when I was a little boy.
Your Honor,
it's not easy
being my parents.
I'm always
screwing up in school
and getting in trouble
with the law.
But if I grow up to be
a halfway-decent person,
I know it'll be because
of my mom and dad.
Everyone else
might give up on me,
but my parents never will.
That's my brother.
Um... Did she say
she used to be a dude?
So, Your Honor,
if you're going to punish
anyone in this
courtroom today,
I ask that you punish me.
Okay, I will!
Bartholomew Simpson,
I hereby sentence you to
five years in juvenile hall!
Well,
I'm back from vacation.
But I was just
about to bang my gavel,
making the sentence official.
Sorry, I've already
put my clown down.
But I was just going to...
The clown is down.
Judge Snyder,
motion to declare a writ
of boys will be boys.
Motion granted.
Case dismissed!
Woo-hoo!
All right,
we got lucky that time,
but I want
everyone in this family
to raise your hand
and promise
not to break the law
for one full year.
We promise.
That was close.
Please drive off me.
What's that noise?
Uh...
Just the radio, dear.
Dang me, dang me
They ought to take
a rope and hang me
High from the highest tree
Woman, would you weep for me
All our times have come
Here but now they're gone
Seasons don't fear the reaper
Nor do the wind,
the sun or the rain
We can be like they are
Come on, baby
Don't fear the reaper
Baby, take my hand
Cobras!
English - US - PSDH