(SINGING) The Simpsons
(TIRES SCREECHING)
D'oh!
(SCREAMS)
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
(SUCKING)
I used to love
Springfield Park.
But it's gotten so run-down.
(MEN MOANING)
(DOG HOWLING)
Oh, the "prid" is gone.
(SIGHS IN DISGUST)
This whole place
is disgusting.
I agree.
Hey, aren't you
that Crazy Cat Lady?
Yes, I am.
But thanks to this
psychoactive medication,
I enjoy brief
moments of lucidity.
Those are just
Reese's Pieces.
(CRAZED RAVING)
(CATS MEOWING)
(ALL SCREAMING)
I know how to save this park.
I'm gonna organize
a charity carnival.
Uh, Mom? Looks like
someone beat you to it.
God, that Junior League
burns me up.
Step right up and
bid on items donated
by local businesses.
Oh, I only got $100.
I better bid shrewdly.
First up is this video camera.
$100.
$100.50.
Sold.
Damn it!
(GRUNTING)
I never win anything.
Ooh, here's something
I'm good at.
(HUMMING)
(ALARM RINGING)
HOMER: Knee... Left...
Ding...
(BELL DINGING)
Hmm!
Hmm.
Yes!
Check it out, fat-wad.
I'm better than you,
and I'm only 10.
(ALL CHATTERING)
(LAUGHS)
Fat-wad, I love it.
(PEOPLE TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
Easy... Gentle...
(THUDDING)
(SPLASHING)
Ay, caramba!
Mmm-hmm.
I'm number one.
I beat my son.
Victory is mine.
So, kiss my behind.
(SCATTING)
In your face.
(SCATTING CONTINUES)
My son flips frogs
like a girl, yeah.
(SCATTING)
Who's your daddy?
(SCATTING CONTINUES)
Hey, Homer.
Do fries come
with that shake?
Sure do.
Mmm.
(CHUCKUNG)
(PEOPLE CHEERING)
(SCATTING)
(YELPING)
I'm happy-
(PEOPLE CHEERING)
(LAUGHING CRAZILY)
He makes me look cool.
And cool, lam not.
May I upload your footage
onto my website?
Well, sir, I don't
believe we've ever met.
My name is Jeff Albertson.
But everyone calls
me Comic Book Guy.
Well, I'll just
call you "friend."
Here's your tape,
friend.
(SENSUAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(LASER SHOTS FIRED)
(GIRLS SCREAMING)
What should we click on next?
JIMBO: "Boxer shot by wife"?
"Beauty pageant diarrhea"?
KEARNEY: Here's a new one.
"Big-ass Baryshnikov."
(CLICKING)
(GRUNTING)
(ALL LAUGHING)
Now to send this
spaz around the world.
(CLICKING)
(LAUGHING IN FRENCH ACCENT)
(LAUGHING IN JAPANESE ACCENT)
(LAUGHING IN BOTSWANAN ACCENT)
(MIMICKING SEAL LAUGHTER)
Stupid Internet.
Whole world laughing at me.
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
Look at the American
computer monkey.
Dance, monkey. Dance.
(ROARING)
Basta. Basta.
Take my picture with
the Internet Mama Luke.
(ROARING)
(GIBBERING)
(BEEPING)
The Internet wasn't
created for mockery.
It was supposed to help
researchers at different
universities share data sets.
It was.
(DOOR BELL RINGING)
Hello. I'm Deion Overstreet.
The running back for
the San Antonio Cow Skulls?
Five-time rushing leader,
two-time MVP,
and star of
a Disney Channel movie.
I played the gentle giant,
"Stay-off-drugs-ia."
I know why you're here.
You want to see
me humiliate myself
with my stupid dance.
Well, fine.
(SCATTING)
Wrong.
Side step. Side step.
Shuffle.
I want to buy the rights
to that dance for $1,000.
Woo-hoo! But why?
My workmanlike touchdowns
never make the highlight reel.
But if I add your
shameless shenanigans,
I'll be on ESPN every night.
You want to do my dance
after you score?
Damn straight.
And I'll buy any other
dances you got, too.
Woo-hoo! (SCATTING)
(SIGHS)
(SCATTING CONTINUES)
"L" is for loser,
which describes you, sir.
Don't try to stop me.
Just enjoy the view, sir.
"The view, sir.
Then show ass." Got it.
Honey, I bet you're wondering
why Daddy's not at work again.
The answer may surprise you.
I have a new job
choreographing end zone
dances for a professional
football player.
Looks like all you're
teaching is obnoxiousness
and poor sportsmanship.
Don't forget showboating.
That's the cornerstone
of my pyramid of success.
Ooh!
I forgot crotch grabbing.
That'll be the sun.
Mmm-hmm.
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
Grandpa, will you
take me fishing?
Sorry, Jimmy.
Your grandma and I
are going to have
old people sex.
Thank you, Jammitin.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
Oh! There's nothing
but filth on TV.
But with this
new video camera,
we can make our
own entertainment.
Now, boys, we're gonna
film the world's first,
and some would say,
best murder mystery.
The story of Cain and Abel.
Daddy, if Cain and Abel were
Adam and Eve's only children,
how did they make more babies?
Did they make babies
with their mother
or with each other?
Your mouth is hopin'
for a soapin', boy.
Now stop asking
silly questions
and go kill your brother.
(WHIMPERS)
After you prance
across the goal line,
you hurl the other team's
mascot to the ground
and drive your
cleats into his neck.
(CROWD CHEERING)
You're going down,
you potato-eating pansy.
Homer, are you sure we aren't
crossing a line here?
I happen to know
that the person inside
that leprechaun suit
is a single mother.
Deion, this is Timmy Thomas.
(WHISPERING) He has
Timmy Thomas disease.
Mr. Overstreet,
could you do an
obnoxious end zone
dance for me today?
(COUGHING)
Please?
(CROWD CHEERING)
Yay!
(GONNA MAKE YOU SWEAT PLAYING)
(CHOMPING)
How do you like me now?
(BLOWS WHISTLE)
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Hello.
Homer, this is LeBron James.
The fans love my dunks,
but they hate my dancing.
(CROWD BOOING)
I think I can fit you in.
Let's see.
Lenny, can I move you
from Wednesday at noon
to Sunday at 6:00?
Homer, you know
that's when I play
with neighborhood dogs.
All right, all right.
I'll work it out.
Aw, you guys are
what it's all about.
Reverend, thanks for
turning the church into
a "he-without-sineplex."
What the...
Oh, I get it.
(PROJECTOR WHIRRING)
Boys, I just talked to God.
He's vacuuming heaven
to get it ready for when
dead people show up.
And he'd like you both
to render a sacrifice.
I shall sacrifice
my finest grains
and livestock.
(BUZZING)
Behold, I have found
favor with the Lord.
So shall my knife find
favor with thy belly.
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(LAUGHING EVILLY)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
Now, I must bury my son
while you wander the earth
forever with the mark of
evil upon your face.
(CROWD GASPS)
(ALL CHEERING)
(GROANS)
Ned, your film
was a masterpiece.
It turned me from an atheist
to a hooray-theist.
Uh, sir, you have revealed
to me a world of faith
beyond the world of science.
I would pay to see
it again, and again,
and again, and again,
but not six times.
I also would pay
to see it again.
Me, too.
Here's some guy's wallet.
I am that guy.
Smithers, we could
make a fortune with
these Bible pictures.
And I've been looking
for a way to launder
the money I made
selling club soda
as flu vaccine.
Everyone seemed so happy.
But, I'm surprised at Ned.
He left out all the good times
Cain and Abel had
when they were growing up.
He's just being
true to the Bible,
which is pretty violent.
And sexy.
King David stole
someone else's wife.
Mary Magdalene was a hooker.
Bart, how do you
know these things?
It's all in this book.
(BART LAUGHS)
(GROANS)
HOMER: Welcome to
the Homer Simpson
Showboating Academy.
Today we're working
on poor sportsmanship.
First, I want you to
hurl a ball at the
nearest authority figure.
Nicely done.
Oh, my God.
It's my hero,
Michelle Kwan.
You remind me of
a young Dorothy Hamill.
(GASPS)
I didn't know you could talk.
Lisa, could you
pass the salad?
And it's James with the steal.
(CREAKING)
(G LASS S HATTE RS)
(GROANS)
Who wants to help
me clear the table?
(SPEAKING IN MANDARIN)
Wait a second.
I've read that you speak
excellent English.
Shut up, kid. I got
a good thing going here.
(GULPING)
Oh, my. Ned's next movie
seems even bloodier
than the last one.
Now there's no need
to actually whip him.
We can put the sound in later.
No. As your financial backer,
I insist upon reality.
Pharaoh didn't put
the sound in later.
But who'd know
the difference?
The people being whipped.
(YELLING)
(GROANS)
Hey, Lovejoy.
You could take a
lesson from Flanders.
You know,
inject your services
with a little razzle-dazzle.
I already do,
if by "razzle"
you mean piety
and by "dazzle" you mean
scriptural accuracy.
What a tool.
I am richer than you.
(TRUMPETS PLAYING)
Look out, Jonah.
It's a whale.
(ROARING)
Jonah!Jonah!Jonah!
Yarr!
The only just solution
is to cut the baby in half.
(PIERCING FLESH)
Wait a minute.
I've killed a baby.
I'm a monster.
(GROWLS)
I can't take anymore.
Ned, there's more to the Bible
than blood and gore.
Oh, I guess you'd rather
see a film about a liberal
European wizard school
or the latest sexcapade
of Miss Ashley Judd.
Well, I don't like this movie.
And I'm gonna boycott
your financier, Mr. Burns.
Oh, really?
And what would you use
instead of nuclear power?
Solar.
Hydroelectric.
A mix of conservation
and wind.
Who told you about those?
A talking tree
in a commercial.
Ah.
Well, I know when
I've been licked.
Sorry, Ned.
This movie will
never be seen again.
Dis-embroider
the crew jackets.
We can still send them back.
Mmm-hmm.
Welcome to Jock Center.
Tonight, the Clipper
and the stripper,
a Jones that's chipper,
and did Joe Torre
shoot Flipper?
But first, professional
sports continues its downward
march into the gutter.
(LAUGHS)
This is either
about me or steroids.
Thanks to professional
jerk-ass, Homer Simpson,
athletes are now taunting
and boasting just to get
on our highlight reel.
Disgusting. Now
here's our highlight reel.
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYING)
Art comes from pain.
Your pain.
Beware the wrath of Kwan.
Everyone sucks but me.
Oh, yeah. Cheer for Tom.
Give all your love to Tom.
(LAUGHS)
I'm the worst thing
to happen to sports since Fox.
Master,
you are truly a fool.
Homer Simpson, we work for
the commissioner of football.
And he wants to see you.
I want to see him, too.
Maybe he can tell me
how to get this off.
It soaked through
to the other side.
MAN: The commissioner's
in here with all the owners.
Homer,
we think you're fabulous.
Since the players began
your rowdy rump-shaking,
our ratings are up 62%.
Plus we're making
millions in player fines,
which I'm gonna use
to bankroll a musical
about the J. Geils Band.
(ALL CHEERING)
RICH TEXAN:
That's right, J. Geils.
Here's why we called you in.
We want you
to produce this year's
Super Bowl Half-time Show.
Wow. At last,
my pathetic little
life has a meaning.
(CHUCKLES)
You suckers,
I would've done it for free.
Fine. Do it for free.
Damn it.
Well, I'll still do it.
(CHUCKLES) Suckers.
I would've paid you.
Fine. Pay us.
Oh, damn it.
Will you take a check?
No.
Damn it.
Mmm-hmm.
ANNOUNCER: The Super Bowl
Half-time Show.
From its humble origins
in Super Bowl I...
(TROMBONE PLAYING)
...to the marriage of
Pac-Man and Ms. Pac-Man
in Super Bowl XVI.
I now pronounce
you Pac-Man and wife.
(SINGING) Let's get physical,
physical
I wanna get physical
Let's get into physical
(TURNS OFF TV)
Oh, every single Super Bowl
Half-time Show has been great.
Oh, Homie, don't worry.
I'm sure you'll come
up with a great idea.
I don't know.
It's a lot of pressure.
(LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
Do many people
watch the Super Bowl?
Billions.
Oh.
(GUITAR PLAYING)
(ELEPHANT TRUMPETING)
We're ready for
rehearsal, Mr. Simpson.
So what do we do?
(MEGAPHONE SWITCHES ON)
Ah...
Uh...
Oh, man, I have no
idea what I'm doing.
I wonder if other Super Bowl
producers waited till
3:00 in the morning
the night before to plan
their half-time shows.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
A church.
Maybe the homeless people
sleeping on the floor
will have some ideas.
Flanders?
Well, I guess you've got
some late night problems, too.
Yeah. I made a great film.
But I'm having trouble
getting it out there.
I'm like Michael Moore,
except I'm skinny,
myjeans are washed,
and God loves me.
(SIGHS) I just wish
I could find some way
to spread my message.
Have you tried checking
the oil filter?
Are you even listening to me?
Sure. I'd be happy to
tell you my problem.
I've got a venue
the whole world
will be watching
and nothing to fill it with.
Wait a minute.
You've got a medium,
and I've got a message.
Maybe God brought us
together for a reason.
Yeah. You help me and I,
in turn, am helped by you.
ANNOUNCER: And so,
ladies and gentlemen,
we have come to the start
of Super Bowl X-X-X-I-X.
This brand new $300 million
stadium was completed
just one short week ago.
And it's scheduled
for demolition
early next month.
America's priorities
are a joke. Now,
Here's the kickoff.
Wow. All these people
are gonna see Dad's show.
Oh, I paid $1,000
for this seat.
And I can't even see the game.
Just poke through.
(SLURPS)
Hmm.
(CROWD CHEERING)
(GUNSHOT)
ANNOUNCER: And that's the gun.
We head into half-time
with the thrilling
score of 55 to 6.
But don't stop watching
in the second half.
Points count double.
And now, the eagerly awaited
Super Bowl Half-time Show.
Sponsored by
the new Ford pick-ups,
Citibank, and Moe's Tavern.
How could you afford this?
I hustled a lot of pool.
Hey, you want to play?
I gotta warn ya.
I ain't that good. (LAUGHS)
All right.
Sucker.
(GRUNTS)
Who's the sucker now? Huh?
Time for Homer's
half-time show.
Get ready, Frank.
Frank went to
the men's room.
I'm Joe.
HOMER: We now take you
back through the ages
to a time before TV,
before cowboys,
before dinosaurs.
The time of the Bible.
The children of God
once lived according to
their father's laws.
But then
a shadow of wickedness
fell across the land
as represented by this
cloud of white pesticide.
(ALL COUGHING)
But there was one
righteous man, Noah.
Oh, mighty God, send a flood
to destroy this wickedness.
Hey, you guys think
Homer's mad at me?
I waved at him in
the parking lot and
he stared right through me.
I left the People's
Republic for this?
Yo, Michelle,
you got a boyfriend?
Not in here, I don't.
After 40 days and 40 nights,
the rain stopped.
And Noah set
forth a single dove.
(WHIMPERS)
(WHIMPERING CONTINUES)
So God blessed
Noah and his sons.
And said to them,
"Never again
shall there be a flood
to destroy the earth.
"I set my rainbow
in the cloud.
"And it shall be a sign
of the covenant between
God and man." Thank you.
(SPLASHING)
(CROWD BOOING)
All over America today,
viewers were outraged
by the Super Bowl Half-time
Show's blatant display
of religion and decency.
You try to raise your kids
as secular humanists
But these showbiz types
keep shoving religion
down our throats.
Mommy,
why wasn't I baptized?
You see? You see?
I thought America
was hungry for meaning.
I should've just sent
a crocodile into space
like I originally planned.
Oh.
Homie, I think you did great.
And to celebrate,
I made omelets from the eggs
people threw at our house.
Dig in, everybody.
Omelets for dinner?
This is the best
day of my life.
Really? Didn't you just sign
a $90 million contract?
That was a good day, too.
HOMER: Welcome to
the Homer Simpson
Showboating Academy.
Today we're working on
poor sportsmanship.
But I like to stand
for good sportsmanship.
Quiet, you.
Yes, sir.