♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
D'oh!
-Ahh!
-(tires screech)
(honking)
Hymns here. I got hymns here.
Get 'em while they're Holy.
Fresh from God's brain
to your mouth.
(chuckles)
And now, please rise
for our opening hymn.
Uh...
"In the Garden of Eden"
by I-ron Butterfly.
♪♪ (organ plays
"In A Gadda Davida")
♪ In the Garden of Eden,
honey ♪
♪ Don't you know
that I love you ♪
♪ In the Garden of Eden,
baby ♪
♪ Don't you know that
I'll always be true ♪
(laughs)
Hey Marge, remember when
we used to make out
to this hymn?
(giggles)
Shh...
♪♪
♪ Oh, won't you
come with me? ♪
♪ And take my hand ♪
Wait a minute, this sounds
like rock and/or roll.
(organist riffing)
I know one of you is responsible
for this, so repeat after me:
"If I withhold the truth,
may I go straight to hell,
"where I will eat naught
but burning hot coals
and drink naught
but burning hot cola."
Where fiery demons will
punch me in the back.
Where my soul will be
chopped into confetti
and strewn upon a parade of
murderers and single mothers.
Where my tongue will be
torn out by ravenous birds.
(shrieking)
Bart did it!
That Bart right there!
Milhouse!
Milhouse, you did
the right thing.
Bart, come with me
for punishment.
You, too, snitchy.
Now I want you to clean every
one of these organ pipes
that you have befouled
with your "popular music."
(door closing)
You shank.
How could you
tell on me?
Well, I didn't want hungry
birds pecking my soul forever.
Soul? Come on, Milhouse,
there's no such thing as a soul.
It's just something
they made up to scare kids
like the bogeyman
or Michael Jackson.
But every religion
says there's a soul, Bart.
Why would they lie?
What would
they have to gain?
I don't hear scrubbing.
Well, if your soul's real,
where is it?
It's kind of in here.
And when you sneeze
that's your soul
trying to escape.
Saying "God bless you"
crams it back in.
And when you die,
it squirms out and flies away.
Uh-huh. What if you die
in a submarine
at the bottom
of the ocean?
Oh, it can swim.
It's even got wheels in case
you die in the desert
and it has to drive
to the cemetery.
How can someone with glasses
that thick be so stupid?
Listen, you don't have a soul,
I don't have a soul.
There's no such thing
as a soul.
Fine.
If you're so sure
about that
why don't you sell
your soul to me?
How much you got?
-Five bucks.
-Deal.
There you go.
One soul.
Pleasure doing
business with you.
Anytime, chum... p.
All right, where would you
kids like to eat tonight?
The Spaghetti Laboratory!
Face Stuffers!
Professor V.J. Cornucopia's
Fantastic Foodmagorium
and Great American Steakery.
Well, what about this place?
"Moe's."
(screams)
Natural light!
Get it off me! Get it off me.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I thought this was
a family restaurant.
Oh, it is. It is.
Just, uh... pull them
stools up to the pool table.
Daddy, this place
smells like tinkle.
Mm-hmm.
I think we'll just go to
the Texas Cheesecake
Depository.
Everybody is going to family
restaurants these days.
Seems nobody wants to hang out
in a dank pit no more.
You ain't thinking of getting
rid of the dank, are you, Moe?
Ah, maybe I am.
But, Moe, the dank, the dank.
Yeah, family restaurants.
That's where
the big bucks are.
I could turn this joint
into a place
where you wouldn't be ashamed
to bring your family, huh?
I'm not ashamed.
Hey, put a coaster
under that.
Oh, Lisa.
There's a little present
for you lying in the driveway.
Oh, boy! Really?
(gasps)
(roaring)
(screaming)
Oh, no!
It's dripping funny-smelling
water all over me!
(sighs)
I wasted five bucks on these.
Where did you get
five bucks?
I want five bucks.
I sold my soul
to Milhouse.
What? How could you
do that?
Your soul is the most
valuable part of you.
You believe in
that junk?
Well, whether or not the soul
is physically real, Bart,
it's the symbol of everything
fine inside us.
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
Poor, gullible Lisa.
I'll keep my
crappy sponges, thanks.
Bart, your soul is the only
part of you that lasts forever.
For five dollars,
Milhouse could own you
for a zillion years.
Well, if you think
he got such a good deal,
I'll sell you my
conscience for 4.50.
I'll throw in my sense
of decency too.
It's a Bart Sales Event.
Everything about me must go.
Hey boy, how you doing?
(growling)
Man, what's gotten
into you?
(hissing)
Geez, you're pretty uppity
for someone who
eats bugs all day.
Stupid automatic door.
BOTH:
Thank you, door.
Some ice cream guy
is going to see that
and it will
blow his mind.
Let me try.
(blowing)
Way to breathe,
no-breath.
This is getting weird.
Sanjay, to the entrance
with the Windex.
So c'mon, I need
a name that says
"friendly,
all-American cooking."
How about
Chairman Moe's
Magic Wok?
BARNEY: I like it.
Nah. I want
something that says
people can have a nice,
relaxing time.
I got it!
Madman Moe's
Pressure Cooker.
BARNEY: I like it.
Hey, how about
Uncle Moe's Family Feedbag?
BARNEY: I hate it.
(truck horn blaring)
Oh, boy.
The deep fryer's here.
I got it used
from the Navy.
You could flash fry
a buffalo in 40 seconds.
40 seconds?
But I want it now.
♪ The Itchy and
Scratchy Show ♪
(sighs)
Whoa!
(screaming)
(laughing)
I know that's funny,
but I'm just not laughing.
Hmm?
Pablo Neruda said laughter
is the language of the soul.
I am familiar with the works
of Pablo Neruda.
I think we should do a test.
HOMER: ♪ Oh, do-do-do ♪
♪ I'm just walking... ♪
Whoa!
D'oh!
-(laughing)
-(Homer yelling)
Well?
Nope. I don't
feel a thing.
That's creepy,
Bart.
I think you really did
lose your soul.
-Good boy. Ow!
-(growling)
Who's doin' that?
Hmm?
Nothing.
Ow! Help me! Ow!
Why isn't anybody--
Ow! Helping?
-(doorbell rings)
-Hi, is Milhouse home?
He's playing in the dirt
with his Army men.
Oh, and a white
piece of paper, I believe.
(gasps)
Cover me, Sarge.
I'm going after Bart's soul.
(imitating gun fire)
If the Ayatollah can't
have it, no one can.
(imitating engine)
Uh, uh, you know, Milhouse...
(smugly)
Yes?
Bet you're getting tired
of that soul, huh?
No.
Well, suppose someone
wanted to buy it from you?
Ohh. You want
to buy it back, Bart?
Sure. No problem.
-50 bucks.
-What?!
Who's stupid now? Huh?
(maniacal laughing)
If you like good food,
good fun
and a whole lot of
crazy crap on the walls
then come on down to
Uncle Moe's Family Feedbag.
ANNOUNCER: At Moe's, we serve good,
old-fashioned home cooking
deep-fried to perfection.
Now that's "Moe" like it.
So bring the whole family--
Mom, Dad, kids...
uh, no old people.
They're not covered
by our insurance.
It's fun.
And remember our guarantee:
if I'm not smiling
when your check comes,
your meal's on me,
Uncle Moe.
♪ Come to Uncle Moe's
for family fun ♪
♪ It's good, good, good,
good, good, good, good ♪
Mmm. Sounds good.
(humming)
Hmm...
Bart, what's wrong?
There's something
a little off
about your hug.
Mom, I need to tell
you something.
I kind of--
Uh, uh, uh.
Let me guess.
A mother can always tell.
Mm-hmm.
Hmm.
It's not fear
of nuclear war.
Mm-hmm.
It's not swim test anxiety.
It almost feels like
you're missing something--
something important.
Like I don't have a soul?
(laughing)
Ah, honey,
you're not a monster.
GIRL:
My soul's my best friend.
GIRL 2: My soul's like a toy
that never breaks.
(cackles)
My soul can take your soul!
♪ Bart sold his soul,
and that's just swell ♪
♪ Now he's going
straight to ♪
♪ Hello operator,
give me number nine ♪
♪ And if you disconnect... ♪
No soul, huh?
Don't worry.
I'm still behind you.
Ha-ha.
Ahoy there, friends.
Everybody find
a first mate.
Oh, I choose Martin.
Wait. Wait for me!
(singsongy) Bart, it's time
to end this dream,
and don't forget
the standard scream.
(screaming)
An alligator with sunglasses?
Now I've seen everything.
Hiya, folks.
Welcome to Uncle Moe's.
Ah, look at all
the cute little minors.
Wow. That's Moe.
The guy from the ad.
Right this way, Homer.
And he knows my name.
Street signs indoors?
(giggles)
Whatever.
Now Rod, you order
anything you want
for your big ten-o.
Million Dollar Birthday Fries.
Uh-oh.
Moe gets so excited
when you order
his Million Dollar
Birthday Fries
he just has to celebrate.
Here you go.
Here I am, Uncle Moe.
Thank you, ma'am.
This'll be a treat.
Uncle Moe,
here I am, while you eat.
Please take the fries
off my head, kid.
The basket is extremely hot.
How are the southwestern
pizza fingers?
They're, um...
"awesomely outrageous."
Oh, these look good.
Guilt-free
steak fish filets.
No, no, let me level
with you, Marge.
That's just our name
for bottom-feeding
suction eel.
You don't want that.
Why don't you try
Moe's Hobo Chicken Chili?
I start with the best part,
the neck,
and then I add
secret hobo spices.
Ooh, tres bien.
Yeah.
(giggles)
What the hell are you doing,
you little freak?!
(crying)
Oh, sorry, kid.
Sorry.
I'm not used to the
laughter of children.
It cuts through me
like a dentist's drill.
But no, no, that was funny,
that was funny
taking away my dignity
like that.
Ha, ha, ha.
I would like
to say grace.
(clears throat)
Lord, have mercy
on my soul
and Mom's soul
and Dad's soul
and Maggie's soul
and that every soul
in Christendom-- Uh!
Bart!
I can't take
this anymore.
I want my soul,
and I want it now.
Bart, you didn't finish
your spaghetti and Moe Balls.
HOMER'S BRAIN:
Silence, you fool.
It can be ours.
Run, boy!
Run.
(chewing)
Run for your life... boy.
Milhouse! Milhouse.
You win!
I want this nightmare to end!
(creaking)
(deep breathing)
(sinister voice)
Leave this place.
You are in great danger.
Where's Milhouse?
The one you call
Milhouse is gone.
(normal voice) He went to his
grandma's place
while we're spraying
for potato bugs.
Oh. When Milhouse left
did you notice if he was
carrying a piece of paper?
Oh, yeah. You don't forget
a thing like that.
(alarm sounding)
Oh, God.
Here you go!
Here I am, Uncle Moe!
Thank you, ma'am.
This will be a treat.
Uncle Moe! Here I am!
-While you eat!
-Yay!
Now do it
for Terri.
What? It's your
birthday too?
BOTH: We're twins.
(sighs)
Here you go.
Here I am.
Eat your fries.
Eat them.
Here's you.
Ah, geez. And you got
the stink lines and everything.
Oh, dude,
you did not smile.
We eat for free.
Come on, Shoshanna,
let's roll.
(chuckles)
But I sang you
the potato stuffings.
Come on, I sang you
the potato stuffings!
Look at the vein
on that guy's forehead.
He's gonna blow.
(alarm sounding)
Unky Moe?
What... is it,
sweetheart?
My "sodie" is too cold.
My "teef" hurt.
Your "teef" hurt, huh?
Your "teef" hurt?
Well, that's
too freaking bad!
Ya hear me?
I'll tell you
where you can put your
freaking "sodie" too!
(all gasping)
-Ow! My freaking ears!
-(gasps)
Oh, let's go, dear.
I expect that type
of language at Denny's
but not here.
Come on, folks, wait!
Please, come back!
Please, I got a new
offer.
Whenever Uncle Moe threatens you
you get a free
steak... fish.
(sighs)
Okay. Okay.
Milhouse's grandmother
lives on 257th Street
and I'm on Third.
(groans)
(horn blaring)
(pop!)
Well finally, a little luck.
(squeaking)
(evil laugh)
(crashing)
(yelling gibberish)
Son, you wait here
while Daddy tries
to talk some sense into
this raving derelict.
(gibberish)
Now slow down,
slow down.
Who's been stealing
your thoughts?
-Hello, Ralph.
-(gasps)
Um, hi, Bart.
I know you from school.
Yes.
A simple proposition, Ralph:
how would you like
to make a dollar?
Uh... I don't know.
All you have to do
is sign a paper
that says I can
have your soul.
I need a soul, Ralph.
Any soul.
Yours.
(whimpers)
(crying)
Hey, what's going on
over there?
(hissing)
(pounding on wood)
Go on, take it all.
Get it all out of here.
You know, Moe,
you might want
to keep the fire
extinguishers.
Nah. Too many
bad memories.
Well, look on the
bright side, Moe.
You still got us.
Yeah. You know, that actually
makes me feel a little better.
HOMER: Why?
That was the problem
in the first place.
You were going broke
because we were
your only customers.
Wasn't that the problem
in the first place?
That you were
going broke?
Moe? Moe?
Hey, Moe?
Oh, you're thinking
about all the money
you blew, aren't you?
What was it,
$50,000, $60,000?
Moe? Look,
maybe it would help
if you went over
all the mistakes you made
from the beginning.
-Moe?
-What?!
Let me get a pad.
(snoring)
(knocking on door)
A caller at this hour?
You dial 9-1,
then when I say so,
dial 1 again.
(panting)
Milhouse, please.
Bart, I can't play now.
It's 2:00 A.M.
Milhouse, I got to
have my soul back.
I'll do
anything you want.
Uh... well...
Milhouse,
give him back his soul.
I've got work tomorrow.
I'm really sorry.
I kinda traded
your soul to the guy
at the comic book store.
But look, I got
some cool Pogs.
Alf Pogs.
Remember Alf?
He's back,
in Pog form.
You traded my soul
for Pogs?!
No-o-o-o!
GRANDMOTHER:
Close that door.
You're letting
the heat out.
FATHER:
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
If you're waiting for
the "Hi & Lois" signing
it has been moved
to the Springfield Coliseum.
Please, you have
something of mine
on a little piece of paper.
Oh. So you're Bart Simpson, eh?
Well,
since my breakfast burrito
is congealing rapidly,
I will be blunt.
You're too late.
I sold your soul
last night.
Yes, yes, I found a buyer
right away for that item.
Who?
I'm not at liberty
to divulge the party
but they were most interested
in having possession
of a little boy's soul.
Excuse me.
No banging your head
on the display case, please.
It contains
a very rare "Mary Worth"
in which she has
advised a friend
to commit suicide.
Thank you.
Are you there, God?
It's me, Bart Simpson.
I know I never paid too much
attention in church
but I could really use
some of that good stuff now.
I'm afraid.
I'm afraid
some weirdo's got my soul
and I don't know
what they're doing to it.
I just want it back.
Please.
(sobbing)
(whimpers)
I hope you can hear this.
Lisa? You bought this?
With the change
in my piggy bank.
There's no change
in your piggy bank.
Not in any of the ones
you know about.
Oh, Lis, thank you.
Happy to do it.
But you know Bart,
some philosophers
believe that nobody
is born with a soul,
that you have to earn one
through suffering
and thought
and prayer
like you did
last night.
Uh-huh.
(gulping)
Ha! It's like punting on the
Thames. Stroke. Stroke.
Oh!
(laughing)
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.