♪ The Simpsons ♪
-(chalk screeches)
-(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(tires screeching)
(horn honks)
(tires screech)
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
TV HOST: Okay, the capital
of North Dakota
is named after what
German ruler?
-Hitler!
-Hitler, North Dakota?
-Bismarck.
-TV CONTESTANT: Bismarck
Hitler?!
Hey, I'm still
beating you, boy.
Okay, the colors of
the Italian flag
are red, white and what?
-Blue! Orange! Red! Purple!
-Yellow! Black!
Black! Green!
-TV CONTESTANT: Green.
-I was right!
TV HOST:
Okay, we'll be right back
with more
Grade School Challenge,
after this important message.
I used to think
that losing my hair
was as inevitable
as the tides.
Then I found out
about Dimoxinil
the new miracle breakthrough
in hair regrowth.
(gasps)
Miracle breakthrough?
There's been
a miracle breakthrough?!
The odds are Dimoxinil
can help me grow
as much or as little hair
as I want to.
Hey, today
I'm going to do it.
ANNOUNCER: For your free brochure,
send five dollars to Dimoxinil
485 Hair Plaza,
Hair City, Utah.
Hair. Hair.
Just like everybody else.
You know, some women
find bald men quite virile.
Marge, weren't you listening?
This is a miracle breakthrough
not one of these cheap-o,
sucker deals.
Allow me to present the Dimoxinil
action set in its entirety.
A six-month supply
of the drug,
the gravity boots,
scalp massager,
and your t-shirt.
Great, great, great.
How much? How much? How much?
$1,000.
A thousand bucks?!
I can't afford that.
Well, we do have a product
which is more
in your price range.
However, I must assure
you that any hair growth
you experience
while using it
will be purely coincidental.
A thousand bucks...
Of all the rip-off
screw job,
gyp joint...
(cries)
Forget you, pal.
Thanks for nothing.
(sobbing)
So I say, "Forget you, pal!
Thanks for nothing!"
and I stormed
right out of there.
Ha! That's telling him, Homer.
D'oh! I'm out of tartar sauce.
They call this a portion?
Hey, Lenny, are you going to use
all of your tartar sauce?
Dry fish sticks.
This sucks.
Quit complaining, chrome dome.
Oh! If I had hair,
you wouldn't be
calling me that.
LENNY: Homer, don't be
a sap all of your life.
Just fill out a few medical
insurance forms creatively.
Charge that Dimoxinil stuff
to the company.
But it's a thousand bucks.
Burns would can my butt
in no time flat.
Ooh, a thousand bucks!
So what?
To Mr. Burns, that's one
less ivory back scratcher.
Yeah. Besides, you pay money
into the insurance fund every week.
What do you ever
get out of it?
Nothing.
Well, that newsletter.
Exactly.
Why should you get nothing
while some guy who loses
a finger hits the jackpot?
You got me.
Uh, I'd like to charge
that Dimoxinil stuff
to my health insurance.
Look buddy, I don't know
who put you up to this
but no insurance plan
in this state
covers something
as frivolous as Dimoxinil.
(radio blasting)
Meet me in the alley
in 15 minutes.
Come alone.
(humming)
Dear God, give a bald guy
a break. Amen.
(yawning)
(gargling)
(swishing)
(humming)
(gasping)
I have hair.
I have hair!
Look! Look!
Good morning, Springfield!
Good morning,
Mr. And Mrs. Winfield!
Why don't you get a haircut,
you hippie!
Good morning, Moe's Tavern!
Hey, it's
the president.
Good morning, everybody!
ALL:
Good morning.
Good morning, everybody!
Good morning, Springfield!
-Dimoxinil!
(jubilant laughter)
(gasping)
(laughter)
(tires screech)
Well, Homer Simpson.
Why-why-why, you haven't
been here in 20 years.
Hey, you got rid of
the sideburns.
(chuckling)
Give me the usual.
MARGE:
He's much happier at work
and, well,
just between us girls
well, he hasn't been
this frisky in years.
I don't want
to think about it.
HOMER:
Daddy's home, Sugar.
(giggling and cooing)
HOMER:
Come here, you.
MARGE: Ooh! Oh, Homie,
my sisters are here.
HOMER: Ah, dinner with three
beautiful women.
I must be in heaven.
This is Homer?
Oh, my.
Patty,
stop drooling.
Heh.
Look who's talking.
Hey, there's something's
different about you, Homer.
Did you lose some weight?
Yeah, you look like
you got a tan or something.
I know what it is.
A new tie.
(Homer laughing)
BURNS: Morons, pathetic morons
in my employ,
stealing my precious money.
This is hopeless. None of these
cretins deserves a promotion.
It's in the union
contract, sir.
One token promotion
from within per year.
Wait! Who is that
young go-getter?
SMITHERS: Well, it sort of
looks like Homer Simpson
only more dynamic
and resourceful.
Simpson, huh?
Hmm.
An unspoiled lump of clay
to mold in my own image.
Our new junior executive.
Bring him to me!
SMITHERS (on P.A.):
Attention! Homer Simpson.
You have been promoted.
You are now an executive.
Take three minutes to say
good-bye to your former friends
and report to room 503
for reassignment
to a better life.
Well, your resume
seems in order.
Besides typing and stuff
do you have any other qualifications
I should know about?
I give great back rubs
to harried executives.
Here, let me show you.
Uh, no, no.
That'll be fine.
Thank you. Good-bye.
HOMER: Hello?
Hello, Homie.
How's my big,
important executive?
Oh Marge, every woman
I interview
for the secretary job
makes kissy faces at me.
Hmm...
Hello, Mr. Simpson.
I'm Karl.
He sounds good. Hire him.
-I'll call ya' back, Marge.
-Simpson.
Meeting in the
board room tomorrow at 2:00.
Just sit there and keep
your mouth shut, got it?
Yes, Mr. Smithers.
He thinks he's so big.
-You don't belong here.
-Huh?
You don't belong here.
You're a fraud,
and a phony,
and it's only a matter of time
until they find you out.
-(gasps) Who told you?
-You did.
You told me with the way
you slump your shoulders.
The way you talk
into your chest.
The way you
smother yourself
in bargain basement
lime green polyester.
I want you
to say to yourself
"I deserve this."
"I love it."
"I am nature's
greatest miracle."
Go ahead, say it.
-I-I deser...
-Trust me, Homer.
-I-- Uh...
-Take a step and say it!
I... deserve this.
-Louder!
-I deserve this!
-Shout it!
-I am nature's greatest miracle!
I'll need three weeks vacation
and moving expenses.
You've got it, buddy!
Let's go shopping!
(gasps)
Ooh... beauty.
A man's suit
should make him
feel like a prince.
It should cry out to
the world, "Here I am."
"Don't judge me. Love me."
Do any of these
suits do that?
No.
Woo! I like this.
No, no, no,
stand naturally, Mr. Simpson.
Let it all
hang out.
You, conceal it.
(Marge humming)
Mom and Dad
have been smooching again.
Got to run, Marge.
Can't be late!
Happy Anniversary, Homer.
What? Our anniversary?
Are you sure?
Well, don't worry, Homie.
This year you have an excuse
for not remembering
-what with your job and--
-(knock on door)
Happy Anniversary,
Mrs. Homer Simpson!
♪ You are so beautiful ♪
♪ to me, yeah ♪
♪ to me ♪
♪ Can't you see ♪
-Oh, Homer.
-(telephone rings)
-Hello?
-Mr. Simpson, it's Karl.
Ah, it sounds like
everything has arrived.
-Wonderful.
-You did this?
Yes, sir. I hope I didn't
overstep my bounds.
♪ You are so beautiful ♪
♪ to me ♪
I love you, Homer!
I love you, Karl--
Uh, Marge.
Proceed, Smithers.
Our first issue, sir,
is our low productivity
and record-high
worker accident rate.
Guh! Any suggestions?
A round of layoffs might
wake up the idiots.
We could put caffeine
in the water cooler.
Hmm, well, those
are my ideas!
You people don't think,
you regurgitate!
That's why I promoted someone
who's in touch with the workers.
-You.
-I think you mean him, sir.
You then. How would you improve
the workers' situation?
Well, I--
Well, sir, for one thing,
we had a problem
every Tuesday
when the cafeteria
would serve fish sticks.
Fish sticks! What in blazes
are you talking about?
Well sir, they cut
the head off the fish
and chop up the rest into sticks and
then put seasoned bread crumbs--
I know what fish sticks are!
Get to the point!
Well, you only get
this tiny
little cup of tartar sauce to dip 'em in
and I always run out.
Will you stop
wasting our time, Simpson?
Shut up, Smithers.
Can't you see
what he's saying?
A happy worker
is a busy worker.
Three cents' worth
of tartar sauce
could save us thousands
of man-hours in labor.
I like the cut
of your jib, Simpson.
Let the fools
have their tartar sauce.
HOMER: Enjoy your tartar sauce,
boys. Enjoy!
Give me your plates.
Don't crowd.
Plenty for everybody!
Hmm, brilliant.
Who could ever have imagined
that Simpson's sweeping reforms
would pay off so quickly?
You know sir, accidents decreased
by exactly the number
that Simpson himself has known
or suspected to have caused last month.
And our output level
was just as high
during Simpson's
last vacation.
My dear, tired old Smithers...
do I detect a note of jealousy?
(laughing)
It is time.
Give Simpson...
the key.
KARL: Mr. Simpson don't sit on that
filthy thing one second longer.
They've given you... the key.
HOMER (gasps):
The key?!
-He's got the key.
-Who's got the key?
(all gasping)
(bird chirping)
KARL: Stunning.
Absolutely stunning.
(toilet flushes)
Oh! Hey, ho, men.
You know I was watching
the Dumont last night
and I happened to catch
a fascinating documentary
on Rommel, The Desert Fox.
Now there's a man
who could get things done.
Towel, please, Simpson.
-Allow me, sir.
-I said Simpson.
Uh... sure thing,
Mr. Burns.
Well done, Simpson.
Now walk behind me
down the hallway.
Can do, sir.
SMITHERS: Hmm.
"$1,000?
"Dimoxinil?
Keep brain from freezing?"
Now I've got you, Simpson.
(laughing)
MARGE: Hmm Homer, between your hair
care products and new wardrobe
we're not saving anything
for a rainy day.
Rainy day! There's never going
to be a rainy day, Marge.
There's not a cloud
in the Simpson sky.
And what does
my little girl want?
An absence of mood swings
and some stability in my life.
Uh... how about a pony?
Okay.
BURNS:
I want you to weave
that patented Simpson magic
with my executives.
A short speech. Work, work, work.
You know.
Uh, well, okay.
What the hey?
Excellent. Set you
to your task, Simpson.
Hmm. Uh, Mr. Burns,
it is my sad duty
to report that one
of your executives
has bilked the company
insurance plan out of $1,000.
What?
Blast his hide to Hades!
Ooh! and I was going to buy
that ivory back scratcher.
How did he do it?
He charged the company
for Dimoxinil.
It's a baldness cure.
Thank you very much,
professor science.
I know what Dimoxinil is.
Now, go and make an example
of this hooligan.
With pleasure, sir.
Karl, you got to help me.
Mr. Burns wants me
to make some speech
to his executives, and--
-Ahem.
-What do you want?
Oh, just thought
I'd drop by
-to tell you that you're fired.
-What?
Our company does not
look kindly upon $1,000
worth of insurance fraud.
Clean out your desk
by noon, Simpson.
(moans)
Wait, Mr. Smithers.
Homer Simpson is innocent.
I did this.
-You did?
-What are you talking about?
Mr. Simpson was unaware
of any impropriety.
I take full responsibility.
Really? Oh.
Well, then... you're fired,
whoever you are.
Here's your $1,000.
(groans) Hey, what do you care
if this guy's bald?
My reasons... are my own.
Karl, you saved me. Why?
Have I done something
extraordinary here today?
No. I did what
I was born to do.
What any good soldier
would have done
when a live grenade
threatened his commander.
I threw myself upon it
and bore its terrible brunt.
Oh, thanks, Karl.
I don't know what to say.
Just walk me to my car.
Bye, Karl.
I'm going to miss you.
Bye, Mr. Simpson.
Oh, Mr. Simpson, did you
bring an umbrella today?
D'oh! No.
Here.
(Karl sneezes)
Okay, okay, okay, you're broke.
You're flat broke.
You don't have Karl anymore.
He's not here, but you've got your hair.
That's right.
It's all about hair.
Oh, that big speech.
(thunder rumbles)
Oh-ho.
BART: Hey, what's happening,
hep cats?
-No way!
-It's gotta be a fake.
It's like realsville,
Daddy-o. Heh.
Bart!
What are you doing?
Uh-oh.
-Aah!
-Why, you little...
-Uh-oh.
-(growls)
-(Bart screaming)
(Homer shouting incoherently)
Aah!
Boy... must... die!
I love you, Dad.
D'oh!
Dirty trick.
Okay. I'm not gonna kill you,
but I'm going to
tell you three things
that are going to haunt you
for the rest of your days.
You've ruined your father.
You've crippled your family,
and baldness is hereditary.
It is?!
(sobbing)
Oh, Homer, why don't you
just call the pharmacy and--
I don't have 1,000 bucks!
But you do, don't you, Marge?
You do. You do.
You've been squirreling it
away, haven't you?
Saving it for a rainy day, that's what
you've said, right, right, right?
Homer!
(sobbing)
Dad is taking this
in a less-than-heroic fashion.
Oh, Homie, I'm so sorry.
(shuddering sigh)
Got that big speech in
five minutes, Simpson, huh?
You're not going
to hang yourself, are you?
D'oh!
Huh?
KARL:
"Dear Mr. Simpson
"I've taken the liberty
of preparing your speech
"on the enclosed
numbered three-by-five cards.
"all the big words
are spelled...
"pho-en-ne-net-tically.
"God bless you.
"You are one of Springfield's
very special creatures.
Your obedient servant, Karl."
Good luck, sir.
Ah! Karl.
So that wasn't just
a sweet voice
I heard inside my head.
What are you doing here?
I just came to say good-bye
to the gals in the typing pool.
Yeah, well.
Thanks for the speech, Karl
but I can't give it.
Look at me.
I guess I haven't
taught you anything.
-What do you mean?
-Don't you see?
The tartar sauce,
the bathroom key,
drying your boss's hands.
You did it all.
It was never the hair.
You did it because you believed
you could, and you still can.
No, I can't.
I'm just a big fool.
-Oh no, you're not.
-How do you know?
Because my mother taught me
never to kiss a fool.
Karl.
Now go get them, tiger.
(growls)
And now, with some
fresh insights,
one of the rising young stars
of our nuclear family,
Homer Simpson.
(applause)
What in blazes?
Who is that old geezer?
And what has he done
with Homer Simpson?
He is Homer Simpson, sir.
(clears throat)
Uh, a lot of you
would think I was crazy
if I did this.
He's crazy!
Yet we at this power plant
are doing this
every hour of every day.
Bloated inventories,
outmoded production methods.
I can save this company
millions of dollars a year.
How?
Through Jiko Kandri
the Japanese art
of self-management.
This bald man
has no ideas.
If this is a joke,
I'm not laughing.
Some nerve, telling us
how to run the plant.
He doesn't even have hair.
...inefficiently
mining uranium
that can be purchased quite
cheaply on the foreign markets.
The long-term benefits
more than offsetting
the one-time cost
for a net savings
of five thousand, two...
(mumbling)
...lots of money.
Mr. Burns' office.
Right now.
Dead man coming through.
MR. BURNS:
Well, well, well
our dashing
young "junior" executive.
You made a hollow mockery of
our morning meeting, Simpson.
I should fire you on the spot.
But...
I'm not going to.
Uh, why?
Simpsons, how old
do you think I am?
I don't know. 102?
I'm only 81.
You may find this
hard to believe
but in my salad days,
my crowning glory
was a bright shock
of strawberry blonde curls.
Oh, I was big man on campus
until my senior year,
when I became as bald
as a plucked chicken.
You see, Simpson
I, too, know the sting
of male pattern baldness.
That's why I'm giving you
your old job back.
What? Oh, thank you,
thank you, thank you.
Now get out of here
before I reconsider.
Oh. Better hurry up.
(Homer mumbling)
Homer, are you
still awake?
I've never been
more awake in my life.
What's wrong?
Are you kidding?
I'm stuck
in that dead-end job again.
The kids are going to hate me
'cause I can't buy 'em
all that stuff I promised them,
and you're not going
to love me as much
'cause I'm ugly and bald.
Oh, Homer.
Your job has always
put food on our table
and the kids
will get over it.
And?
And what about loving me?
Oh, Homer, I--
-Come here.
-Why?
-Oh.
♪ You are so beautiful to me ♪
♪ You are so
beautiful to me ♪
♪ Can't you see? ♪
Aw.
♪ You're everything
that I hope for ♪
♪ I'm everything
you need ♪
-♪ You are so beautiful ♪
-♪ I am so beautiful ♪
-♪ to me ♪
-♪ to you ♪
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.