(theme music playing)
CHORUS: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
(whistle blows)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
(tires screeching)
(honking horn)
D'oh!
(tires screeching)
-Whee!
-Whoo-hoo!
-Ya-haa!
-Yee-- Oh! D'oh!
Son of a diddly!
-(rock music playing)
-HOMER: Mm-hmm.
(humming)
-MARGE: Breakfast!
-(whistling)
Breakfast? (giggling)
Aww... cereal?
You know I like my breakfast fried
or chicken-fried.
It's a healthy cereal
from Europe,Meus-lix.
(all shuddering)
They also make Juice-lix.
(grunting)
-(doorbell rings)
-That's Milhouse.
-(ringing frantically)
-And it sounds like he has big news!
-Yech!
-(groans)
I'll get us out of this. Say, Dad.
Wanna go see my project
for the school science fair?
No, Lisa.
But I sure don't wanna
eat this crappy breakfast.
(snickers)
Meet Linguo, the grammar robot.
I built him all by myself.
If you misuse language,
he'll correct you.
Well, let's put him
to the test.
Me love beer.
I love beer.
-Oh, he loves beer. Here, little fella.
-Dad, no!
Error.
I'm sorry. I thought he was a party robot.
Oh! This is why
I can't have nice things.
(groaning) Every time I design a robot,
somebody comes along and--
-(sniffing)
-(humming)
-Ooh! Can I have a brownie?
-They're for after dinner.
-Ooh! Can I have dinner?
-You can't have a brownie, period.
-Homer wants a brownie. I'm gonna get one.
-No.
-Coming in from the left.
-Stop it.
-Or is it the right?
-Homer!
Look out for the reach-around!
Hup, hup, ah, oh!
He shoots, he sc-- (screams) My thumb!
-Oh, God! Oh, God! Oh, God!
-I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
(groaning) Sorry doesn't
put thumbs on the hand, Marge!
Well, calm down. If we hurry,
they can reattach your thumb.
Reattach a thumb? This isn't Gattaca!
-We've just gotta get your thumb to the--
-(both gasp)
MARGE: Where did it go?
-(gasps)
-(growling)
OK, boy. Drop the thumb.
(growling)
Nobody's gonna tackle you.
(grunts)
D'oh! Come back with my thumb!
(dial tone)
9-1-1. This better be good.
I cut off my husband's thumb.
Attempted murder?
You'll burn for this--
burn in jail!
-It was an accident!
-Yeah, yeah. Save it for Dateline Tuesday.
Uh, what's your address
so I can come arrest you?
Arrest me? Um, my address...
it's, um, 123 Fake Street.
"123 Fake Street." Got it.
-Come on! Come on, boy.
-(barking)
Oh, please give it back!
You want people food?
I can get you people food.
-(barks)
-Oh!
I have nothing he wants!
And Harry Potter
and all his wizard friends...
went straight to hell
for practicing witchcraft.
Yay!
-(barks)
-What the diddlio?
-Give me back my thumb!
-(barking)
-(grunts)
-(whimpers)
(whistle tooting)
(gasps, grunts)
(crying)
MARGE:
We've gotta get to the hospital, Homer!
OK. If the doctor asks
why you cut it off,
you caught me in bed
with four beautiful women.
-Let's just say that Bart did it.
-(crash)
Oh, doodlebugs.
My Ferrari!
I had to do awful things to pay for her.
-(grunts)
-Homer, help!
HOMER (whispering):
Marge! Over here!
-(tires screeching)
-(yelling)
(door sensor dinging)
I'm sorry, Homer. Your H.M.O.
doesn't cover this type of injury.
But I have finger insurance!
-A thumb is not a finger.
-Isn't there anything you can do?
Well, I could cut off the other thumb
for a sense of symmetry.
Symmetry, eh?
Hibbert's really losing it.
We're going to Dr. Nick's.
We need more ice.
My thumb is fading fast!
Quick!
Moe, Marge cut off my thumb!
No problem. Just stick
the old eye-gouger in the pickle brine.
That'll keep your thumb
fresh and delicious.
Thanks, Moe.
Hey, ah, hey, ain't you
going to have a beer?
Well, I really shouldn't, what with
my massive blood loss and all.
Although I do like
the occasional beer.
(gulps)
Did you ever see
that Blue Man Group?
Total rip-off of the Smurfs.
And the Smurfs-- They suck!
(sniffing) Uh-oh. I smell gangrene.
-We gotta wake him up.
-A little coffee'll do the trick.
(muttering) What?
Ooh! I gotta get to Dr. Nick's!
Where's Marge?
Oh, that is so rude.
Oh! I know. I'll hitchhike!
Oh, why isn't this working?
(country music playing
on car stereo)
-Hey, thanks for stopping.
-T'ain't nothin'.
You and me share
a common infirmity.
If anyone ever tells you
a hog won't eat a finger, they's lyin'.
-(tires screeching)
-(clucking)
Oh, crap! It's on fire!
Inflammable means flammable?
What a country!
Can you drive me to
Shelbyville Hospital?
-I reckon so.
-(tires screeching)
Hey! Somebody done
"stoleded" my wheels!
Thanks a lot.
Now I gotta walk to Shelbyville.
(horn honking)
(moans) It's too late.
Well, old friend, we always knew
this day would come.
Say good-bye to your brother.
-(explosion)
-What the hell!
(gasps) Linguo... dead?
Linguo...
is...
-dead.
-(powering off)
Son of a diddly!
(new Age meditation
music playing)
MARGE: Breakfast!
-(doorbell rings)
-That's Milhouse.
-(ringing frantically)
-And it sounds like he has big news!
-Yech!
-(groans)
I'll get us out of this.
Say, Dad.
Wanna go see my project
for the school science fair?
No, Lisa.
But I sure don't wanna eat
this crappy breakfast.
-Here, little fella.
-Dad, no!
Error.
I'm sorry. I thought he was a party robot.
Oh! This is why
I can't have nice things!
(groaning)
Every time I design a robot,
somebody comes along and--
(sniffing)
Hang on, Linguo.
You'll be up and conjugating in no time.
HOMER (screams): My thumb!
Quiet, please.
Some of us are trying to weld.
Almost done. Just lay still.
-Lie still.
-I knew that. Just testing.
Sentence fragment.
"Sentence fragment"
is also a sentence fragment.
-Must conserve battery power.
-(powers off)
-Just come on.
-(horn honking)
Uh-oh! The bus!
Hey, stop! Wait!
Oh! Any day
but science project day!
Kiss first place good-bye,
Lisa!
-(sinister laughter)
-(electrical crackling)
Oh, no!
Somebody took my bike! (groans)
Mom, I need a ride to school!
MARGE:
We gotta get to the hospital, Homer!
(groans)
(music from Run Lola Run
playing)
(screams)
Idiot!
You almost ran over a viewer!
And she's in our key demo!
Sorry about that, kid. Need a ride?
-Can you take me to school, Krusty?
-Hop in.
Hey, moron.
Springfield Elementary, and step on it.
(chittering)
(siren wails)
Hey, Teeny, you know where
123 Fake Street is?
(chittering)
Ah, it's OK.
Hey, we got the same hat.
-Thanks, Mr. Teeny.
-(chitters)
-Wha--
-(speaking French) La grenouille
mange le pamplemousse.
ALL: La grenouille
(in English) Huh?
This isn't Miss Hoover's class.
I do not know this Mademoiselle "'oovair"
of which you speak.
What's happening? Where am I?
Sacre bleu!
What a foolish question!
You are at West Springfield
Elementary School.
West Springfield?
I'm at the wrong school!
-(all laughing)
-En Français.
(haughty laughter)
(gasps) Sorry.
I was rushing because
I'm in the wrong school.
(giggles) Can you believe that?
It's understandable.
All the schools in this area
were built from identical plans.
I guess they didn't have
enough money to hire I.M. Pei.
Oh. You know about I.M. Pei?
I.M. impressed.
(both laughing and snorting)
-My name's Thelonious.
-As in Monk?
Yes. The esoteric appeal
is worth the beatings.
-What do your friends call you?
-I don't really have any friends.
(gasps) Just like me!
("Happy Together" playing)
Oh, my God!
It's 11:15!
We've been spinning for hours.
I've got to get to my school
and hand in Linguo.
Oh, but I don't want
to leave you.
You must. You can't sacrifice
grades for romance.
-That's not the girl I fell for.
-Will I ever see you again?
Of course you will... at the magnet
high school. Now, go.
(music from Run Lola Run
playing)
(panting)
Hmm. It's noon.
That's about when Dad
gets the brew shakes.
My dad's not here?
I need a ride to school!
-Yeah, yeah. We all got problems.
-(whimpering)
Chief Wiggum, can you drive me to school?
It's an emergency!
Ah, no can do, doll face.
I got an informant wearing a wire.
(chuckles) Just like on Nash Bridges.
We're trying to get the goods
on some smugglers.
(frequency whirring)
FAT TONY: Why, I'd be delighted
to sell you some illegally smuggled goods.
-That sounds like Fat Tony.
-Only one way to be sure.
Fat Tony, is that you? Fat Tony?
FAT TONY: Hey, where's that voice
coming from?
-MAN 1: This guy's wearing a wire!
-MAN 2: Take him out!
(gunfire)
My bad. I can't work
my answering machine either.
(chuckles) Now I need a new informant.
Say, Lisa, people trust you.
How would you like to be a snitch?
-The pay stinks, but--
-(footsteps receding)
Oh.
Quick! Moe, Marge cut off my thumb!
(music from Run Lola Run playing)
-(horn honking)
-Lisa!
Mom, where'd you get that car?
I stole it from McBain after I cut off
your father's thumb.
Can you take me to school, please?
Not right now.
Your father's in there, and--
HOMER: Did you ever
see that Blue Man Group?
Oh, he's on the Blue Man Group again.
Come on. We've got lots of time.
-(engine sputters, stalls)
-Oh, no!
We're out of gas. I couldn't figure out
this stupid Italian gas gauge.
Oh, I've gotta get to school!
(country song playing on car stereo)
Hmm. Let's hitch a ride with that hick.
(both panting)
Abracathumbra!
(laughing)
Dang! You could be
one of them TV magic queers.
-(tires screeching)
-(clucking)
Shoo!
Mom, I have to get to school!
It's 10 to 3:00!
Well, I've already borrowed one car.
Let's go!
Somebody done stoleded my wheels.
Thanks a lot!
Now I gotta walk to Shelbyville.
There's the school!
First place, here I come.
(gasps) Look out!
Bart!
-(tires screeching)
-(gasps, screams)
Son of a diddly!
Hey, hey! Hey, hey! Hey, hey!
Lazy, huh? Get him, boys!
-(music playing)
-Wake up! Wake up! Wake up!
OK, OK!
MARGE: Breakfast!
-(doorbell rings)
-That's Milhouse.
-(ringing frantically)
-And it sounds like he has big news!
-I found something awesome in the woods!
-Is it a dead body?
-It's cooler than a million dead bodies!
-(snickers)
You take my sister's bike.
Let's see. Front door. Back door.
Skinner's. Flanders'. Your house.
Ah! Lisa's bike.
-What's it like riding a girl's bike?
-It's disturbingly comfortable.
Whoa! How'd you find it?
-This is where I come to cry.
-Cool.
Wow! Sacks!
Burlap sacks!
It gets better. They're full of fireworks!
Bottle rockets, Frog-Launchers,
Weeping Mommas...
Tijuana Toilet Crackers!
Three, two, one. Gnomes, blow up.
(both laughing hysterically)
(grunting loudly)
-(high-pitched screaming)
-We're not ready!
(sinister chuckle)
-(grunts)
-Uh-oh.
So what are we doing,
a lengthening or a widening?
Yargh, uh... let's make it both.
-Yargh!
-Don't worry. It's inflammable.
Let's keep this our little secret.
-(siren wailing)
-Oh, we gotta hide!
We'll be safe in here.
Here we are. 123 Fake Street.
The home of Knifey Wifey.
Hey, Chief, can I hold my gun sideways?
It looks so cool.
(chuckling) Ah, sure.
Whatever you want, birthday boy.
OK, drop the knife, Stabatha! I--
-(both grunt)
-Great grilled-cheese ghost!
We've uncovered a hard-core cracker house.
There's enough Chinese sky candy here...
to put you boys away for a long time.
I can't go to juvie.
They use guys like me as currency!
Yeah. They'll pass you around like--
Well, like currency, like you said.
Maybe we can make you boys a deal.
Your mission is to find
the fireworks smugglers
and get them to say
something incriminating on this tape.
Hootie and the Blowfish?
Yeah. It's cheaper than blank tape.
Great idea to smuggle fireworks, boss.
Yeah, I was gettin' sick
of running those unions.
So much paperwork.
Knock-knock. Excuse me.
My friend and I were interested
in purchasing quality fireworks.
Yes, we are.
Why, I'd be delighted to sell you
some illegally smuggled goods.
WIGGUM (on radio): Fat Tony, is that you?
Fat Tony?
-Hey, where's that voice coming from?
-This guy's wearing a wire!
Take him out!
(grunting)
Whoa!
-WIGGUM: My bad.
-(grunts)
MAN 1: Hey, there they are!
Gentlemen, remove your guns
from your holsters.
-Shoulder or ankle?
-Surprise me.
-(both whimpering)
-(groaning)
Milhouse, quick!
(gasps) Look out!
Bart!
-(tires screeching)
-(gasps, screams)
(clunks)
-Ow! Mom!
-MILHOUSE: Hurry up, Bart!
(tires screeching)
(both panting, gasping)
You ain't goin' nowhere!
You leave those boys alone!
-(grunts)
-(yelling)
Hey, they's throwin' robots!
They are throwing robots.
He's disrespecting us. Shut up-a you face!
Shut up your face.
-What's the matter you?
-You ain't so big.
Me and him are gonna
whack you in the labonza!
Um-uh... mm... Bad grammar overload!
Error! Error!
-(explosion)
-What the hell!
(gasps) Linguo... dead?
(both shuddering)
It's all right, boys.
Oh, thank goodness everyone's OK.
Except your thumb,
and Lisa's science project.
I couldn't help but notice
your respective predicaments.
Perhaps I may offer a bipartite solution.
There you go. Enjoy your thumb.
LISA: As the circulation returns,
the subject prepares
for a long and painful recovery.
It's lucky for me that Legs
was an experienced Mob doctor.
He once pulled a slug out of my arm
and inserted it into a stoolie's brain.
That's a first place
science project, Lisa.
(all cheering)
Boy, this sure was one crazy day.
-Right, Mr. Teeny?
-(chuckling)
(all laughing)
(chittering loudly)
(theme music playing)
-(laughter)
-FRENCH TEACHER: En Francais.
(haughty laughter)
Captioned by
Visual Data Media Services