CHOIR: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(exclaiming)
(school bell ringing)
(Barney belches)
(whistle blows)
(yells)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
(grunts)
♪ ♪
Why, you little...!
(grunting)
Good evening. It is with great
sadness I inform you
that America and China
have declared war,
and a massive nuclear attack
is expected
to reach our shores
within the hour.
-(shrieks)
-(chuckles)
That's the sort
of hypothetical emergency
today's disaster preparedness
drill is designed
to get us ready for.
Hmm?
(sighs)
All Springfielders should now
move off the streets
and inside their homes.
Please avoid
the superstitious panic
which marked
the recent lunar eclipse.
(Homer chuckles)
Sorry, Dad.
I was afraid the dragon
wouldn't cough
the moon back up.
You idjit! The dragon always
coughs the moon back up!
I know it's futile,
but I must again point out
there is no dragon.
Then why am I paying
$800 a year in dragon insurance?
Again, I maintain
that money would be
better spent
on car insurance.
Lisa, everyone knows
dragons do not attack cars.
Geez, pick up a book.
(splutters) I pick up books
like you pick up beers!
Then you have
a serious reading problem.
Now remember,
this is only a drill.
Ah! The missiles really are coming!
The so-called drill is just a way
to get you into shelters
without causing total chaos!
Is what I would say,
if this weren't a drill.
This is not a drill!
Now we're supposed
to stay down
in our storm cellar
for three hours.
So do your farting now.
Homie, what if that was
the last thing you ever said?
Don't worry.
My last words will be
"I can outrun that lion."
(sighs)
(Homer humming)
HOMER:
All right, everybody in.
All right, who's the wisenheimer
that's been eating
the powdered food?
Not me.
(coughs)
Two can play at that game.
(grunts)
(gagging)
I can do this!
(groans)
Boy, I told you
an hour ago,
stop that!
But Bunkerball
is keeping us sane!
Do we really have to sit here
the whole time?
I mean, if we went out now,
it might be cool
to see the town empty.
Yeah, I could sneak into
the school and write whatever
I want on the chalkboard!
I could see a planetarium show
without the secondhand
marijuana!
And I can drive drunk
while I'm actually sober!
(tires squealing)
It's fun, but not as fun.
That's odd.
Why are all those cars
parked at City Hall?
BART:
Ay caramba!
If I didn't know better,
I'd say it's a town meeting.
Not without us, it isn't.
Pull over.
Welcome to this secret meeting,
made possible
by the fake disaster drill.
And a special thanks
for the hard work
of the Mystery And Secrecy
Committee.
We have names, you know.
Quit complaining!
You only meet once a month!
Yes, but the meetings last
eight hours!
Shut up! Shut up!
This is the most
fun I have!
And now for the reason
we are here.
What's going on?
Why is there
a picture of us?
This isn't good.
Oh, honey,
why must you always assume
that a huge picture of us
at a secret meeting we weren't
told about is a bad thing?
The results are in: this town
has voted unanimously
to get rid of Springfield's
unending nightmare:
the Simpsons.
ALL:
D'oh!
They're here!
The monsters are here!
Moe, it's me, Marge.
I'm your friend.
The monster queen
is coming on to me!
Why would you want
to banish us from Springfield?
Yeah.
We're like family to you.
I'm talking to you,
headphone-bus-driver guy.
I'll have you know
I'm also a hair donor!
Salma Hayek wore me
to the Oscars!
This is not about who wore
whose hair where.
We are here
to banish the Simpsons,
although we are not pleased
to be doing so.
-I am!
-Me, too.
I feel like a kid at Christmas!
I believe you know my position.
I know we're all happy.
I'm just trying
to spare their feelings.
Those freaks have no feelings!
Even baby never cry!
MAN:
She's a freak!
What baby does that?!
Why would an entire town
go to all this fuss
to get rid of one family?
What have we done
that's so terrible?
I'm glad you asked.
The simple fact is
the city is going broke
cleaning up after Homer's
drunken shenanigans...
(audience clamoring)
We won! Whoo-hoo!
Homer, that is not
banishment-hearing behavior!
...Bart's pranks,
which dwindle in humor
as they rise in destruction...
(audience booing)
...and Lisa's environmental
initiatives...
(audience clamoring)
If I may speak.
Mm-hmm.
We're not monsters.
We're just people.
People who love each other
and love this town,
(voice breaks)
the only place we've ever called home.
Thank you.
(sobs)
Marge, you are a sweet woman
and you make us see your family
in a more forgiving light.
Thank you.
Which is why you're
the worst Simpson of all!
-Huh?!
-ALL: Yeah, yeah!
Now, now, now
just a second here.
Now, I know we're not perfect.
but, uh, I believe it was
Sammy Hagar who said...
SIDESHOW MEL:
Silence!
D'oh!
That was an "inside me" bone!
(grunts)
(audience clamoring)
Make way for Captain Coolerhead!
Now, I like a good old-fashioned
witch trial
as much as the next person,
but I do not think
we should be so quick
to judge our longtime
neighbors.
Not so fast, Flanders.
We knew you'd be
the voice of mercy,
and we're prepared
to answer your concerns.
(grunts)
Any other objections?
I withdraw my... diddily.
(sighs)
(cheering)
(band playing "Happy Days
Are Here Again")
Oh... I always thought
"tarred and feathered"
was just a figure of speech.
Good luck patching potholes
and stuffing pillows now!
(clears throat)
Simpson, in accordance
with article six,
section two
of the town charter...
Wait! If you banish us,
you shall be cursed
with a thousand-year drought.
(thunder crashing)
I mean, a thousand-year flood!
D'oh! I mean, a thousand years
of perfect weather.
Just get out.
♪ I'm a rolling stone ♪
♪ All alone and lost ♪
(over radio)
♪ For a life of sin ♪
♪ I have paid the cost... ♪
(music fades out)
Oh, that was the last
Springfield radio station.
Now we just get
Shelbyville talk radio.
RADIO ANNOUNCER:
If you see a Simpson,
do not try to reason with it.
Just kill it and turn
in the pelt for a free soda.
Soda, eh?
Mmm.
Dad, where are we going?
Do we have a plan?
(sobbing)
Oh, let's face it.
I'm the one that's
brought this fate upon us.
And there's only one way out:
I've gotta man up.
Okay, manning up...
manning up.
Manning...
oh, girling down!
(sobbing)
Girling down!
Hey, Henrietta Hippo,
I've got to drain the inchworm.
(sighs)
Fine.
(Bart humming)
(rifle cocks)
Please, put that down.
BART:
I just got started.
Not you. Him!
You best get back
where you belong.
Please, sir, we've been
thrown out of a place
we've always called home.
We just want to live out
our lives in peace.
Rejected by society, huh?
Well, why didn't you say so?
Welcome to the off-the-grid
unincorporated settlement
we proudly call "The Outlands."
(gasping, gun cocking)
We've found a new home.
When God shuts a door,
he opens a window.
Oh, I wouldn't be
openin' no windows.
Coyotes will take
your baby.
(coyote howls)
MOUNTAIN MAN:
♪ The Outlands ♪
(The Simpsons
opening theme playing)
(groans)
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
-(horses neigh)
-(Homer grunts)
(theme music ends)
Eh, I'm sick of watching Fox.
Let's get some fresh air.
I got the ATVs right out back.
Should I get
my helmet?
Helmet?
That's Springfield talk.
(starter cranking,
engine stalling)
Is there gas in these?
Springfield talk!
Well, how are we supposed
to get fuel?
Private plane crashes.
Ah, smell that
unpolluted air!
You know,
I'm glad we're in exile.
Yep, I never realized
how much I hated
every single one of my
friends and relatives.
I don't think this place
is so great.
(hissing)
I'm trying to make
the best of things,
but I'm worried Maggie
is falling in with a bad crowd.
(babies chanting)
I miss our home,
and I want to go back.
It's not perfect here,
but it is close to nature
and if you have
an ax to grind,
WikiLeaks is right over there.
(radar pinging)
How're you doin',
Mr. Assange?
That's my personal
information,
and you have no right
to know about it.
Hey, but we're neighbors.
would you like to come over
for a movie sometime?
Is it Iraqi journalists
being murdered?
Don't be ridiculous.
It's an Afghan wedding
being bombed.
Aw...
Well I've got a really big
secret for you.
(loud whisper)
I'm not wearing any underwear.
You know, you should
really get out less.
(beeping)
(beep)
He's no Ned Flanders.
And I miss
the Springfield sign
and how every street
is a dead end.
God help me, I even
miss Helen Lovejoy
criticizing my brownies.
(crying)
Hey, baby, banned forever
doesn't mean you can't
go back sometimes.
-Yes, it does.
-Pipe down, boy!
(whispers) I'm sneaking you
back into Springfield.
(whistling a melody)
(imitates Burns)
Oh, Smithers?
(exhales sharply)
Homie, these disguises
won't fool anyone.
Pish tosh, Smithers,
and fiddle-dee-dee!
(normal voice)
Heh-heh, nailed it.
WIGGUM:
Hold it right there.
Mr. Burns, you might catch
a cold out this late.
You want my jacket?
Here, let me warm
my gun up for you.
(like Burns)
Excellent!
Yeah, it wouldn't be you
if you didn't say "excellent."
(loud gulping)
(slurring) You know what's great
about you, Marge?
After all these years, you can
still shinny up the donut
and then pull me
up after you.
Look! A shooting star!
-(loud boom)
-(sighs)
You ever wonder if there are donut
shops on other planets?
On a night like tonight,
I have to believe there are.
(grumbles)
(grunts)
Strike! Whoo-hoo!
Want to make out
over the foul line?
Ever since the day we met.
The old homestead.
Remember when we moved in
(like Walter Matthau):
and I talked like this?
(giggles)
Ooh, ooh...
-Mmm, mmm, mmm...
-(giggling)
(chuckles)
Eh, there's no sex
like fugitive sex.
Home sweet squat.
Yeah. This place is awesome,
but it's not puppy-safe.
And my little guy's
coming home tomorrow.
(drill whirring in distance)
(trembling)
Someone's downstairs!
Shh. I think I heard
a pair of underpants
being picked up
off the ground.
Big ones.
(all gasp)
It's them!
Bart's mom and the fat guy!
Let's turn them in!
WIGGUM (over bullhorn):
Not so fast.
This case was already cracked
by the last person you'd expect:
the Chief of Police!
You really thought
you could fool me
with that
Burns and Smithers getup.
I mean, I'm not the sharpest
pencil in the... pencil thing,
but I'm least as smart as a cat.
-Right, Lou?
-Uh, what breed, Chief?
I mean, I saw an Abyssinian once
who could change channels.
Eh, that is pretty smart.
All right,
you caught us.
What are you gonna do about it,
throw us out of town again?
Crucify them!
And screw the boulder in tight!
Make them write monologue jokes!
Cancel their subscription
to the opera!
We hate opera!
Then get them a subscription
to the opera!
No...!
I say shoot 'em!
Now, hold on
just a minute.
Nobody said anything
about shooting.
I did, just now.
That's right, you did.
Well, all right.
-(hammers cock)
-Okay.
Don't even bother
shooting us.
We've found a new
place that we love,
a place that may not
have indoor plumbing,
but it's got something
we treasure more.
Yeah! Non-jerks!
(all gasp)
Maybe he's right--
we are jerks.
You want I should spray
some of my Jerk Off on you?
Uh... it's okay.
In our new community,
people accept others
for who they are.
I thought I wanted
to come back to my house,
but instead,
I'm going to go back to my home.
Well, bah to them!
Let's go, Smithers.
(chuckles)
Getting a little clingy, aren't we?
-(chattering)
-Oh, all right.
That's all it took?
I just had to ask?
(humming a melody)
Well, I've tightened the bolt.
I think we're good.
You sure this
is a good idea?
This is the Outlands, boy.
Ideas aren't good or bad,
they're just free.
Power on!
(loud whooshing)
I was wrong--
there are bad ideas!
There are
terrible ideas!
(Homer screaming)
-(whooshing)
-HOMER: Now I'm over here!
-(mewing)
-(gasps)
I'm on it.
♪♪
-(blows landing)
-Ow! (grunts)
Lenny Lenford.
You're a long way
from your bar stool.
I'm... I'm here as a friend,
looking for
a better way of life.
(whooshing)
-(whooshing stops)
-(grunting)
Mm.
-Hey, Lenny. Welcome aboard.
-Whew!
Now, I got to warn you,
if you find a little black thing
on your pillow, it won't be a mint.
I don't mind-- I want
a fresh start, and so does Carl.
Get her off!
(laughs)
Let her slice off the tip of your ear,
-and she'll go right to sleep.
-No.
That's not a choice
you get to make.
Ooh, this is pretty tasty.
Yup. And I like how it's
dissolving a hole in the cup.
(sizzling)
Hey, guys!
What can I getcha?
Forget it! We don't need
some big-city bartender
charging us an arm and a leg
for something we can do ourselves.
Sure, sure,
I understand.
But if you change your minds,
I'll be here in this cave.
(humming)
I got a funny feeling
our paradise
is about to get ruined
by unwanted guests.
I probably shouldn't have given
this place five stars on Yelp.
Well, I rented that plane.
♪♪
(grunts)
Oh, that tears it.
I am not comfortable
being this close to medical care.
Out of here.
What are you doing here?
I, uh, heard
everything was going great
in your new Eden,
with one flaw:
you lack a corrupt
city government.
True, true.
And a school system
that teaches to the tests,
sneaks the kids the answers
and still fails.
Stop! Stop!
This is everything
we put behind us.
You can't leave
civilization, Marge!
Humanity is an inexorable
upward march!
Or was till
the year 2000.
Well, I did miss a few
things about the grid...
like everything!
(all grunting)
Maureen Dowd, we've got
a lot of catching up to do.
♪♪
I'm sure someone will come back
and tell me where they went.
(wind whistling softly)
If I go inside,
they might not find me.
♪ We'll meet again ♪
♪ Don't know where ♪
♪ Don't know when ♪
♪ But I know ♪
♪ We'll meet again ♪
♪ Some sunny day... ♪
(helicopter blades whirring)
Aw, come on, man,
we wouldn't leave you behind.
Bless you, boy!
-Ow!
-Accident.
Here comes another one.
-(loud thump)
-Ow!
-(thump)
It's nice to be wanted.
MOUNTAIN MAN:
♪ The Outlands ♪
Subtitled by A. Vandelay