♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-(screams)
-(tires screech)
What a perfect outing
for a beautiful autumn day.
I feel sorry for everyone
who's cooped up inside
watching the seventh game
of the world series.
(sarcastically) Yeah. They won't
learn anything about apples today.
...and the cider mill operated
continuously until 1941
when its workers left to
fight in the second world war.
When they returned,
the old girl was
just as they'd left her
only now, she was infested
with thousands
upon thousands of rats.
(disgusted murmuring)
Right.
And if you listen
real carefully,
you can still hear them
gnawing away at the apples
and splashing around
in the toilets.
And that concludes
this portion of the tour.
(coins jingling)
One of the most
historically significant
fruit presses
in this part of the state.
Based on a German design
but modified
for larger American apples...
Well, if god didn't make
little green apples
it's Homer Simpson.
How long
have you been here?
20 of the suckiest minutes
of my life.
Oh, sucking down
the cider, huh?
Hey, word to the wise--
Season pass.
Pays for itself
after the 16th visit.
You know, most people
don't know the difference
between apple cider
and apple juice, but I do.
Here's a little trick
to help you remember.
If it's clear and yella,
you've got juice there, fella.
If it's tangy and brown,
you're in cider town.
Now, there's two exceptions,
and it gets tricky here...
HOMER'S BRAIN: Ohh!
You can stay, but I'm leaving.
...can be yellow if they're
using late season apples.
And, of course, in Canada,
the whole thing's flip-flopped.
Oh my, I better get you
some cider.
Next to spring and winter
fall is my absolute
favorite season.
Just look at all
this beautiful "foilage".
It's not "foilage," Mom.
It's "foliage."
Foliage.
That's what I said, "foilage".
It doesn't take
a "nucular" scientist
to pronounce "foilage".
(exasperated sigh)
Honestly, Smithers
I don't know why Harvard
even bothers to show up.
They barely even won.
Their cheating was
even more rampant
than last year, sir.
Well, I say let Harvard have
its football and academics.
Yale will always be first
in gentlemanly club life.
Why, every friend I have,
I made right here.
Hello, Burnsie.
It's your old roomie, Dink.
(groans)
Steady... Steady...
(screeching)
Oh-ho!
Nicely played, sir.
MAN (on PA):
Attention, passengers.
The train has been
temporarily delayed
because of a discarded couch
on the tracks.
Looks like
some sort of a couch.
This might
take a while, Smithers.
Why don't you get drunk
and stumble around
comically
for my amusement?
I'll be a one-man conga line.
Customers. Thank God.
Papa needs
a new pair of everything.
Hey, how you doing?
Welcome to scenic Waynesport
and remember your visit
with a googly-eyed walnut.
How about a googly-eyed rock?
Some nice local squash candy?
A stretched-out Pepsi bottle?
Come on.
If this stuff
is too nice for you,
I've got some crap.
(humming drunkenly)
Hey, Casey Jones,
where's this train headed?
Springfield.
Yeah, yeah.
What state?
(train whistle blows)
I can honestly say
that was the most fun
I've ever had.
The mill, the history,
all that gorgeous... foliage.
I can't "excape" Lisa,
our little walking "libary".
Can't they get a pole
for that sign?
That's a hitchhiker,
Homer.
Ooh!
Let's pick him up.
No!
What if he's crazy?
And what if he's not?
Then we'd look like idiots.
We're not picking him up.
-Oh, yes, we are.
-There's not enough room.
Yes, there is.
I just don't think
it's a good idea.
And I think it's
the best idea I've ever had.
We're picking up the weirdo,
and that's final.
Hey, you folks are
all right.
Man, it was rough
getting a ride out there.
The only car
that stopped was a hearse
that thought I fell out.
It was rough, I tell you.
Careful of the apple pie
on the seat.
Uh-oh!
Grandpa, are you sitting
on the pie?
I sure hope so.
I'm looking for this guy.
Anybody know who he is?
Yeah, sure, we know him.
That's Mr. Burns.
He tried to kill our puppies.
He sexually harassed me.
He stole my fiancee.
He made fun of my weight.
Okay, so there's been
a little friction.
Know his address?
Ho, this guy's got more bread
than a prison meat loaf.
He's rich, I tell you.
I never seen a place
with a walk-in mailbox.
Hey, who am I talking to?
(doorbell rings)
Yes?
Yeah. Uh...
Hi. My name is Larry.
I'm here to see Mr. Burns.
Well, I hate
to break it to you, Larry
but if Mr. Burns
ever wants to see a stranger
he will observe him
through a powerful telescope.
-Now--
-Smithers, what's going on?
How dare you interrupt
my lime rickey!
(loud slurping)
State your business.
Well, uh... Sheesh, uh...
I'm a little nervous here.
What I'm trying to say
is I'm--
You're what?
Selling light bulbs?
Worried about the whales?
Keen on Jesus?
Out with it.
Well, Mr. Burns, I'm your son.
Oh, and I stepped on
one of your peacocks.
You got a paper towel?
It's true.
He is my son.
Hey, now you're talking.
Good God.
Pop, don't get me wrong,
it's great to be here.
But how does a guy
like you wind up
with a son like me?
Larry, my lad,
I've gone over this story
in my mind a million times.
It was 1941.
The-- No, '39.
My 25th Yale reunion.
Who should appear
but the unrequited love
of my college years,
Mimsie Bancroft.
Of course, by then, Mimsie
had her share of wrinkles
and a gray hair or two
but my adoring eyes
saw past those
minor imperfections
to her 21-year-old
daughter, lily.
I took Lily
to the local cinematorium
where our passions
were inflamed
by Clark Gable's reckless
use of the word "Damn".
We sneaked into
the nearby Peabody Museum.
There, under the smiling eyes
of four stuffed eskimos
we expressed
our love physically
as was the style
at the time.
How do you like that?
I have been in a museum.
So, what happened
with you and ma?
There was
a terrible scandal.
Lily's family forced her
to give you up
and bundled her off to
a convent in the south seas.
I never heard
from her again.
But I prattle on.
Tell me everything
about your life.
Oh, what's to tell?
I was at the orphanage
till I was 18.
Then I got my job
at a souvenir stand.
Oh, and once,
I saw a blimp.
Well, you must be tired.
Let me
show you your room.
Oh, is this posh!
Pop, nobody's
ever been so nice to me.
Yes, yes.
All right.
(chuckles)
Good to see you too.
Now then,
in case you get bored,
here's the playroom.
You can't just eat the orange
and throw the peel away!
A man's not a piece of fruit!
This show was supposed
to close last week!
Close this show!
Close it, I say.
Hey, don't worry about it.
You're all right.
-(shrieks)
-Huh?
Hey, you're
that hitchhiker.
What are you doing here?
Learning
the family business.
I'm Larry Burns,
the boss' son.
Uh-oh!
Yeah, relax.
I don't want to work.
I'm so lazy, I took
lessons on a player piano.
Wow, that's really lazy.
Lazy?
You're not kidding.
I'm like a rug on valium.
I'm talkin' lazy.
So lazy.
And Larry and I have
so much in common, Marge,
way more than
you and me.
If I could be stranded
on an island with anyone
it would definitely be Larry.
I think
we've heard enough
about Larry Burns
for one evening.
Why? It's not like
anything interesting happened
to anyone else today.
Hey, Pop, this crowd
is pretty swanky.
I'm not gonna fit in here.
Nonsense, Larry.
Your blood is bluer
than any of theirs.
Just give them a snootful
of the old Burns charm.
Oh, Admiral Carstairs.
I'd like you to meet
my son, Larry.
Hey, skipper,
good to meet you.
Where'd you start out,
on the Merrimack?
Hey, I should talk.
I hope I look that
good when I'm 200.
Such insubordination!
Larry, please.
He's very sensitive
about his age.
Oh, Monty,
this must be the son
I've heard
so much about.
Larry, you must meet
our daughter, the debutante.
She came out last spring.
Whoa! Put her back in.
She's not done yet.
Hmph!
Smithers, there's something
a bit odd about young Larry.
I can't quite put
my finger on it.
Well, he is a bit rough
around the edges, sir.
One might blame his truly
heroic intake of cocktails.
Pull up a seat, Pop.
You, too, Chuckles.
I mean,
the food ain't great
but the portions
are terrific.
Hey, I'm kidding. Relax.
Hey, give my regards
to Mrs. Boy-ar-dee.
(groans)
A total lack of refinement.
Smithers, send for the boys
at Yale admissions, hmm?
Well, did you meet Larry?
Oh, yes.
He made light
of my weight problem.
Then suggested my motto
should be "Semper fudge."
At that point,
he told me to "Relax."
How were his test scores?
Let's just say this--
He spelled "Yale"
with a six.
I see. Well, I--
Oh, you know,
I just remembered
it's time
for my annual donation.
I wonder
how much I should give.
Well, frankly,
test scores like Larry's
would call for a
very generous contribution.
For example, a score of 400
would require a donation
of new football uniforms
300, a new dormitory,
and in Larry's case
we would need
an international airport.
Yale could use an international airport,
Mr. Burns.
Are you mad?
I'm not made of airports!
Get out!
Summon my son at once.
Uh...
It appears
he's gone drinkin', sir.
(growls)
Everybody go nuts!
I'm buying!
Hey, handsome,
send the bill to my dad.
Okay, but the last guy
who charged a drink to Burns
turned up in a landfill.
Yeah, but it was worth it.
(belches)
What's everybody
in this burg
have against my dad?
He's a pussycat.
I tell you,
he's a doll-baby.
Come on over,
I'll show you.
(loud chewing)
Oh, this is some party.
If it gets any livelier,
a funeral's
going to break out.
Quiet, you.
Nobody likes a comedian.
Geez. Come on, Dad.
We got company.
Make with the yakkety-yak-yak.
(quietly):
Oh... "Yakkety-yak-yak."
You, foodbag.
Do you have a son?
Yes, sir, I do.
And is he a constant
disappointment?
Does he bring home nitwits
and make you talk to them?
Oh, all the time!
Have you ever heard
of this kid Milhouse?
He's a little wiener--
Fascinating.
Good night.
Dad, what's
with you tonight?
I mean, I'm getting
frostbite over here.
I'll tell you
what's with me.
The humiliation of having
a coarse, boorish
ignoramus for a son!
(quietly):
Uh, I should go.
What's the matter, Pop?
Don't you love me anymore?
(door slams)
Sheesh, Dad and I,
we started out great
but now it's falling apart
like a Chinese motorcycle.
It's so unfair.
You're everything
a dad could hope for.
Yeah, I tell you,
I don't get no regard.
No regard at all.
No esteem, either.
Larry, there's
only one sure way
to make him realize
how much he loves you.
And that...
is a phony kidnapping.
Yeah, right.
I don't know.
Maybe I should
just leave town.
(sing-song)
Phony kidnapping.
Nah.
I know what I got to do.
I got to clean up my act.
No more joking around
all the time.
No more slacking off at work.
And most important:
no more booze.
I know I can do it.
"Your son has been kidnapped."
I can't believe someone
would kidnap my Larry.
I won't rest until
he's returned to me.
Not to be impertinent, sir,
but didn't you want Larry
out of your life as recently
as two hours ago?
It's the principle, Smithers.
Nobody steals
from Montgomery Burns
whether it be
my Sunday newspaper
or my loutish oaf
of a son.
All right, Mr. B.,
when the kidnappers call
with the ransom demand
you tell them
you'll leave the money
under the big net in the park.
And then down comes
the net, right, chief?
Hey, I like it.
I like it a lot.
Hmm?
What are you doing
in the basement?
It's like you're hiding out
down here.
Hiding out?
Marge, you've been reading
too many hideout books.
What's that hitchhiker
doing here?
Is every drifter we meet
going to move in with us?
Of course not.
We'll decide that on
a drifter-by-drifter basis.
He's not a drifter, Mom.
That's Mr. Burns's son, Larry.
He's great at pointing out
everyone's foibles.
Hey! How are you doing?
Hoo, look at your hair.
What happened?
You saw yourself in the mirror?
He's kidding, Mom.
But seriously, I'd love
to have hair like yours.
I just can't get
the zoning permits.
Hey, that reminds me, Mom--
Buckingham palace called.
They want their hat back.
(grumbles)
Hey, kids, how about
a hand for your mom?
She's all right.
-Yeah, Mom!
-All right, Mom!
Oh. Yeah. Thank you.
(phone ringing)
Ahoy-hoy?
(voice buzzing)
Hello, Mr. Burns.
This is the kidnapper.
Do you miss your son?
Yes, I'm missing
one son.
Return it immediately.
If you really
love Larry, prove it,
and you can
have him back today.
Oh, how much proof
do you need?
5,000? 6,000?
I swear,
that's all I've got.
Don't you care
about your son?
This is more important
than money.
More important
than money?
Who is this?
Uh... just a second.
Beautiful. Eddie, did you
trace the phone number?
Sure did, chief.
555... Aw, geez,
that's got to be phony.
Hey, I think I got a pai gow.
I hate pai gow.
Can't we just play quang jong?
Can't we just
go upstairs?
Homer: No!
This is Kent Brockman
in Choppercopter 6
with a special report.
Montgomery Burns's son
has been kidnapped.
Kidnapped?
Marge, it's not
a real kidnapping.
It's a simple hoax
to win a father's love.
You know how I feel
about hoaxes.
Still?
I want you to take
Larry back
to Mr. Burns right now
before you get in
a lot of trouble.
What!?
But, Marge, it's
broad daylight
and there's
cops everywhere.
No excuses.
Just do it.
Oh!
Of course
we'll bring you updates
just as soon as they--
Oh, wait a minute!
There they are!
Larry Burns and his kidnapper.
(screams)
Appearing in broad daylight
with police everywhere--
Ladies and gentlemen, there's
only one word for that:
Idiocy.
(groans)
(sirens wailing)
(panting)
We've got to find
someplace to hide.
The abandoned warehouse.
D'oh!
Stupid economic recovery.
Hey, buy a costume
or get out, fellas.
We've got to find someplace
no one will ever go.
Hello!
CHILD:
Drive faster, Grandma!
Grandma's gaining on us!
(chuckles) They'll never look
for us here.
This place is emptier
than a Scottish pay toilet.
Shh!
Some people are trying
to watch the movie.
You don't like it,
call the cops.
(laughing)
(both laughing)
(sirens wailing)
This is Kent Brockman,
live from the Aztec theater
where police have learned
that kidnapper Homer Simpson
and hostage Larry Burns
are inside talking loudly.
Oh, give yourself up, Homie!
No, Dad!
Shoot your way out!
(gunfire)
(screaming)
A bloody end
for Homer Simpson...
is just one of several
possible outcomes
according to our
computer simulation.
Now here's how it would look
if the police killed him
with a barrage of baseballs.
We've got to go
down there and help dad.
HOMER: Ouch! Oooch!
Eeech! Ouch! Oooch!
Oh, stop it!
Shh.
(sticky footsteps)
(crunching)
Still warm.
-They can't be far.
-(door opens)
Chief!
(sticky sounds)
(grunts)
WIGGUM:
Don't be a fool, Simpson.
Let the kid go.
The negotiations have failed.
Shoot him!
(hammer cocking)
Wait!
(all gasping)
WOMAN: Wait? What do
you mean, wait?
I mean,
Homer's no kidnapper.
He's the best friend
I ever had.
We faked the whole thing.
(shocked murmuring)
I should have known
you're the only one
stupid enough
to kidnap you.
Now get down here
so I can spank you
in front of this
gawking rabble.
Smithers, take off
my belt.
With pleasure, sir.
Hold on, Mr. Burns.
Maybe we did fake
a kidnapping
but is that really
such a crime?
All your son wanted
was a little attention,
a little love.
I'm a father myself, sir.
And sure,
sometimes my kids
can be obnoxious...
or boring... or stinky
but they can always count
on one thing:
their father's
unconditional love.
Well, how about it, Pop?
I know it's tough
but can you love me
for what I am?
Uh...
Well...
There, there, sonny boy.
I suppose I have been
a bit--
Oh, no, I can't do it.
It's just not me.
I'm sorry, Larry
I can't be the family
that you need.
Aw, that's okay.
I got a wife and kids.
Oh, that reminds me.
They're probably wondering
where I went.
I told them I'm going
for coffee.
That was a week ago.
Well, Son, delighted
to have met you.
It's good to know
that there's another
kidney out there for me.
You got it, Pop.
Just let me run a few
pints through it first.
As long as everybody's here...
Let's party!
(all cheering)
♪ Any way you want it,
that's the way you need it ♪
♪ Any way you want it ♪
Who's playing
that music?
And where is all that liquor
coming from?
It's a party, Marge.
It doesn't have
to make sense.
♪ She loves to move,
she loves to groove ♪
Oh, yeah!
♪ She loves
the lovin' things ♪
♪ Oh, all night ♪
♪ All night ♪
♪ Oh, every night ♪
♪ So hold tight ♪
♪ Hold tight ♪
♪ Oh, baby, hold tight ♪
♪ She said
any way you want it ♪
♪ That's the way
you need it ♪
♪ Any way you want it ♪
♪ She said
any way you want it ♪
♪ That's the way
you need it ♪
♪ Any way you want it ♪
♪ I was alone ♪
♪ I never knew ♪
♪ What good love could do ♪
♪ Then we touched ♪
♪ Then we sang ♪
♪ About the lovin' things ♪
♪ Oh, all night ♪
♪ All night ♪
♪ Oh, every night... ♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.