The Simpsons
D'oh!
Manjula, why did you bring
the octuplets to work?
This is supposed to be
our special time together.
Some special time.
I get
to stand around
watching you sell
fatty poisons to
overfed Americans.
You'd think that would
deter me, but no.
Look. Please, can you
just take the children home?
The porno magazine buyers are
too embarrassed to make their
move. Look.
Come on.
All right.
Let's go, children.
Cleanup in
all the aisles.
Welcome, steady customer.
I see you are ready
for the Civil War
reenactment.
I need some supplies.
A keg of beer and a six-pack
to hold me until I tap
the keg.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Are you sure
you don't want to come?
In a Civil War
reenactment, we need
lots of Indians to shoot.
I don't know which part
of that sentence to
correct first.
But I cannot come.
I work 22 hours a day
and then I
go home to a wife
who will not touch me.
The Indian rope trick
has become the Indian
nope trick.
The Squishee Lady!
Oh, my God.
I know you must
get this all the time,
but can I suggest a flavor?
Go ahead.
Grape.
Mmm.
Hello, Annette.
How's life, handsome?
Oh, take a penny,
leave a penny.
Hey, she called me
"handsome. "
She likes you.
Put in a good word
for grape.
Come on, guys!
We're gonna be late!
Okay, okay.
Don't go Mary Todd on us.
Come on, Barney.
If you're
gonna be General Grant,
you have to have a drink.
Yeah, but I'm
a recovering alcoholic, so...
One drink won't hurt.
Hey, you're right.
I was afraid it would
start me drinking again,
but it didn't!
Mmm-hmm.
The second battle
of Springfield was
fought by the North,
the South,
and the East
to keep Springfield
in, out of,
and next
to the Union,
respectively.
Now, the actual battle
was fought over there
where that man
is standing,
but he won't move,
so we'll do it here.
Very good. And now,
let the battle be joined.
Bang, bang.
Pow, pow.
Hit with stick.
Die, you bastard.
Whoa. Whoa, damn it.
For me, the war is over!
This battlefield is
rife with inaccuracy.
You, dead people,
stop playing cards!
And Stonewall Jackson,
stop rollerblading!
The South will boogie again!
This was supposed
to be a mock battle!
Mock! Don't worry.
I'm just gonna drain
the area around your wound.
So cold. So cold.
We are gathered
here this Memorial Day
to once again honor
you World War II veterans.
Truly, you are
the greatest generation.
Keep it coming, Brokaw!
Lauding
your legacy
is a labor of love.
You're damn right, it is!
You can't thank us enough!
Every generation stinks
but ours!
Uh-oh.
Sounds like America's
enemies are at it again.
Greatest generation
to the rescue!
And when I come back,
I want a foot rub!
Yes, master.
General, I hereby surrender.
Ow! Not the pointed end,
you dumbass!
Reinforcements!
Tanks? Oh, this is
just too inaccurate.
Well, then you're
definitely not going
to like my
steam-powered
super spider.
With the stepping
and the squishing and
the webs made of nylon.
The nylon
has been released!
Now, you just
take the kids home.
I've gotta return this keg.
Are you sure you can
get your deposit back?
It's in pretty bad shape.
Why do you always take
the side of local merchants?
Now, Apu,
when you gave me
this keg, it had dents.
And here's proof.
Hey. Apu?
That giggle is none of
my business, or is it?
Squishee Lady,
you've had less than
eight kids, haven't you?
Haven't you?
Please do the Hindu
that you do so well.
Avert your eyes, eunuch.
What's a eunuch?
"Unique... Unite... "
Homie, what's wrong?
Nothing. Nothing.
There's nothing
eating me up inside.
Oh. It must
be something big.
Hmm.
Something you did?
No! Something you saw?
Apu is having
an affair?
I know.
Can you believe it?
Oh, Manjula's
just gonna die!
How did you find out?
In my role as customer,
I saw the whole thing.
Oh, this is so awkward.
Today's the day
we play badminton with them.
Oh, I hope
no one makes
any double entendres.
Oh, Apu,
you keep scoring
while my back is turned.
Are you sure
you're not cheating?
Now, Manjula,
do you want me to
find another partner?
No! No, no, let's
just keep playing.
What's the score?
Dirty love.
I mean 30-love!
I mean,
anyone for penis?
I'll just get
the shuttlecock.
Oh!
Here, guys.
Why don't we play this?
Marge, why are you crying?
You're not in
any physical pain,
the only kind of pain
a man can understand.
We have
to do something to
save that marriage.
Maybe I should
just tell Manjula.
Or you could talk to Apu.
He already knows.
Let's tell Krusty.
What would
that accomplish?
That guy's hilarious.
His reaction would
be priceless.
Apu is cheating.
That's sad.
All those kids.
I think he's building
to something.
So anyway,
if you take that bottle
down and pass it around...
I know. I know.
There will be 47 bottles
of beer on the wall. Yes.
Homer, you did not
bring me here for this.
What is it that
you want to tell me?
Okay. This isn't easy, so
I'm just gonna come out
and say it.
Let's say this
pepper got married
to this salt shaker,
and along comes
sexy Mrs. Dash.
Homie, it's
11:00 at night.
Have you told him yet?
A girl in the bar!
What do we do?
Watch and learn,
you dinks.
Ma'am.
Is there something
you want to tell me?
I saw you and
that Squishee Lady
canoodling like
junkyard rabbits!
It's true.
It only
happened once,
but I am so ashamed.
I am scum.
Yes, you are scum.
What do you think
I should do?
Tell that woman it's over
between you and her.
Yes. First thing
in the morning,
I promise.
Hey, Marge, you care
for a tropical drink?
Sure.
Is that Windex?
It's Windelle.
I can't afford Windex.
Okay, Apu,
be strong.
Before you measure
my syrup levels,
I must talk to you.
While you talk,
I'm just
gonna help myself
to some licorice rope.
As much as I enjoy
your company, and
I truly do,
I must insist that from
this point forward,
we not...
Oh, my goodness!
What are you doing?
Whoa, ha-mahatama, hatama,
hatama, hatama, hatama,
hatama, hatama.
Not tonight.
I said not tonight.
Wait, something's wrong.
Why aren't you
pressuring me
for sex?
Oh, I'm just happy
to lie here
appreciating
and respecting you.
Okay, Buster,
what is going on?
Nothing! How can you even
accuse me of repeated
infidelity?
I am so angry, I could just,
I could fall asleep! I...
...completely innocent.
Apu! Come here a moment!
This better be good because
you are interrupting
my faithfulness...
Oh, boy.
I took the tape out of
the store surveillance
camera. Look.
Oh, Apu,
scratch and win!
Mmm!
That's good adultery!
Oh, I am
so sorry, Manjula.
Oh! Get out
of my home, Apu!
I always thought
karma was baloney,
but not anymore.
Caramel baloney.
Hey, Kirk Van Houten.
I live across the way.
If you don't like
losing at cribbage,
stay out of my place.
Okay.
No, no!
I'll let you win.
God, I'm really lonely.
Welcome back to
Inside The Actors Studio.
We've met
Rainier Wolfcastle,
actor, novelist,
barbecue sauce
spokesman.
Now can we meet McBain?
Let me get into character.
Okay, I'm McBain.
All right, Mendoza!
I'll give you
the Maxwell Circuit
if you put down my daughter.
It's a pleasure to
eat your lead, good sir.
Kids, we want to talk
to you about something.
You might hear from
your friends or co-workers
that Apu isn't
living at home anymore.
I just wish there was
something we could do.
Oh.
Oh, Homer,
are you thinking
what I'm thinking?
You bet I am.
You can run,
but you can't glide!
USA! USA!
Tonight, we invite both
Manjula and Apu for dinner,
but we don't tell them
the other one's coming.
And Krusty.
We gotta invite Krusty.
I keep telling you,
off-camera,
he's a desperately
unhappy man.
But if we
remind Apu and Manjula
of why they fell in love,
maybe they can
work out their problems.
Yeah! 'Cause if they don't...
Manjula, we've got
a special guest
for you.
Is it my
husband's whore?
Even better!
This is going great!
Look who's here!
It's this thing!
I am Ganesh, your god.
I am truly screwed.
I order you
to get back together
or I'll suck your blood!
Blah, blah!
Bart,
stick to the script.
Don't be a jerk.
You're the jerk.
You're the jerk!
I know you have all gone
to a lot of trouble to
meddle in my affairs,
but you
cannot change my mind
with one night of blasphemy
and store-bought tandoori.
Or should I say blandoori?
Manjula, please.
I have known we were
meant to be together
ever since my mother
forced me to marry you.
If you give me
another chance,
I'll do anything
to make it up to you.
Mmm.
Come here, you.
These are divorce papers!
Consider yourself served!
Hey, pally. Where do
you want the Fudge Mahal?
Uh, we didn't order that.
Can I lick your fingers?
Meet me at the mail slot.
I have to warn you,
Apu does not have
very much money.
Are you absolutely sure?
Because legally,
I am allowed to
shake him
by the ankles and
see what falls out.
It's established in the case
of Lawyers v. Justice.
That was
a wonderful day for us.
Now, we have
eight children.
Will that affect
the settlement?
Perhaps.
No offense,
but you remind me
of the monkey man
who slaughtered
my family's chickens.
Yes. I get that a lot.
I have to think
all of this over.
I still have
feelings for Apu.
I understand.
Who is Apu?
The face of divorce is not
as beautiful as I had hoped.
Perhaps there
is another way.
When will you humans learn
that your feelings, as you
call them,
can stand in the way
of big cash payoffs?
Manjula, come quick!
The octuplets said
their first words.
Mommy...
Will...
You...
Let...
Daddy...
Come...
Back?
Cookie!
Oh. They miss their father.
Are you sure you don't
want to take him back?
Well, I do, but I don't
want him to think that
I am a doormat.
I need payback!
All right!
Girls night out!
Exotic male dancers
at the Golden Banana!
No. I want him to suffer.
Oh. Well, when Homer
does something wrong,
I write a list of ways
he can make it up to me.
Then I shred the list
and put it in his food.
All right.
We will write a list.
At the Golden Banana?
No!
Oh.
Over, under, round and round
so your feet won't touch
the ground.
Now let's see
what awaits me
in the next life.
First I was a tiger, a snake,
a clod, a goat with a hat,
then me.
A tapeworm,
then assistant
to Lorne Michaels!
It's going to be
a rough couple
of lifetimes.
Manjula!
Oh, Apu,
you are such
a Brahma queen.
Have you come
to forgive me?
I am willing to
take you back...
Really?
Provided you
complete these tasks.
"Number one,
break up with
Squishee girl. "
Well, that's a no-brainer.
"Number two, lose weight.
"Number three, get cartoon
published in New Yorker.
"Number four,
legally change name
to Slime Q. Slimedog.
"Number five, wear
nametag that says same. "
I know
a great nametag place.
They do fabulous work.
It's where I got this.
So our relationship is over,
is that what you're saying?
Yes, I'm afraid so.
Well, we had fun.
Hey, Apu,
I think she likes you.
This Squishee's awful.
I only sell Smooshies now.
Squishees reminded me
of my misdeeds.
My Smooshie tastes
like a shopping bag.
Mine tastes
like dog fur!
Yes, but look
at the deliveryman.
He is hideous.
Oh, a challenge!
Wait a minute!
This isn't on the list!
It's been on my list
for a long time!
Not bad, eh?
I bought the issue for
Richard Avedon's
pictures of Lenny.
"Eliza, where the devil
are my slippers?"
Bravo! Bravo!
"My Fair Lady performed
with all-octuplet cast. "
Done.
Good show! Yeah!
Yeah!
It was magic.
He took a Cockney flower girl
and turned her into
My Fair Lady.
I liked all the roles
filled by minority actors.
Why, I didn't
even notice.
Apu, you have
completed the list.
You may now move
back with your family
and your
never-ending disgrace.
Wait, wait!
You forgot to
eat a light bulb.
Thank you very much,
you big fat blabbermouth!
I... Sorry, sorry.
It's been a rough month.
Here you go.
Don't worry, I soaked it
in the toilet to soften it up.
So, back in the old bed.
I never realized
it was so wide.
Yes, back to our
marital closeness.
Maybe we can't rush things.
Oh, Apu, I want us
to be a family again.
But it will take some time.
We will know when it feels
right again.
Whenever you are ready.
ENGLISH - US - PSDH