(panting)
D'oh!
(tires screech)
(grunts)
(bull bellows)
(all panting)
(bellows)
(snorts)
♪ The Simpsons 25x16 ♪
You Don't Have to Live Like a Referee
Original Air Date on
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
Children, you're
in for a treat.
Today's assembly is devoted
to a special kind of history.
(kids booing)
Living history.
(kids booing louder)
End this madness!
We have two guests who have
come from Springfield!
We come from Springfield!
Illinois! 1858.
Please welcome, here to debate
the important issues of the day,
Stephen Douglas
and Abraham Lincoln!
I appear before you
today for the purpose
of discussing the leading
political topics
which now agitate
the public mind.
(kids booing)
Hit the dirt, squirt!
Well, it seems the, uh...
the good landowners
of Springfield Elementary are rejecting
Mr. Douglas's position on tariffs.
Get a room!
I shared beds with men
all the time.
(chuckles):
It was a common practice.
Ooh, common practice.
(kids laugh, Milhouse gasps)
Please, good people! These are
times of powerful passion.
(grunting)
Why are you
concussing yourself?
Why are you concussing
yourself?
Now, fellow countrymen, a house
divided against itself...
Ow!
Guess what, I also
play Frankenstein!
(growls)
(kids screaming)
Douglas is getting away!
Skinner!
I have seven other principals, and I've
never yelled their names, not even once.
You know what
these kids lack?
Well, certainly not
a caring superintendent.
(chuckles): Well, I, uh...
(clears throat)
Respect. That's what
these kids lack.
So we will hold a contest to make
them tell us who they respect...
who their heroes are.
A contest? But, sir, we don't
have any money to pay for prizes.
We had to rent out our multipurpose room
to a Japanese-American social club.
(pachinko machines ringing)
Tanpatsu!
The answer is simple, Seymour:
Get a corporate sponsor.
But don't worry, you won't
have to compromise yourself.
So, from now on, our
cafeteria will only serve
delicious Stuffwich's heroes,
hoagies and torpedoes.
What about po' boys?
Sorry, Nelson. Poor boys such
as yourself will go hungry.
Now please welcome the
star of Stuffwich's ads...
who lost 400 pounds eating
only Stuffwich subs...
Ezra!
Tell us your hero, and you could win
a Stuffwich college scholarship.
(kids exclaim)
Then you can be
a hero like me.
- What makes you a hero?
- I don't eat as much as I did!
NELSON: So the chained-up dude cuts off his
own foot to save his family from Jigsaw!
(voice breaking):
My hero is my mom's boyfriend
who took me to that
movie when I was three.
I call him Uncle
Rob because...
he robbed us!
(sobbing)
(giggles)
Madame Curie, we just might
have this one in the bag.
(Ralph giggles)
(laughs)
My hero... or should
I say heroine...
dazzled the early 20th century
with her scientific discoveries...
(gasps)
Okay, calm down.
Maybe he's talking
about Margaret Mead.
...in the field
of radioactivity!
(gasps)
I give you Madame Marie
Sklodowska-Curie!
("La Marseillaise" playing)
(gasps)
No! No, no, no, no!
(sobbing)
Martin took my topic.
What do I do?
Oh, just make a
speech about Dad.
Everyone does that.
Everyone does that
with good dads.
But with our Dad, it's like
climbing Mount Everest.
You either plant your flag at the top of
the world or get frozen in agony forever.
Either way,
hell of a show.
(music plays, kids cheering)
People, please! Martin
has left the building.
He had an orthodontist
appointment.
(groans)
Okay, Dad's my hero.
Why is he my hero?
♪ We can be heroes ♪
♪ Just for one day ♪
♪ We can be heroes... ♪
(grunts)
Marge, it happened again!
SKINNER (over P.A.):
Lisa? Lisa Simpson?
You have ten seconds
to get to the podium.
I'm allowed to eat these!
Our final contestant is Lisa Simpson,
who was last seen leaving in tears.
- Near tears.
- But not in them?
No. My hero
isn't famous...
(scoffs)
Loser.
- ...isn't rich...
- Pathetic.
...and isn't in any
history books.
- He makes me sick.
- He's my dad.
What?!
He worked two jobs
to get me a pony,
he started me playing the
saxophone you all love...
(murmuring dubiously)
...and anyone can
put a Band-Aid on,
but my Dad knows how to take
it off so it doesn't hurt.
- Well, ah.
- Oh.
The trick is: Wait
several weeks.
And when my Dad was a soccer referee,
he had the guts to red card me,
his only talking daughter,
because he knew I was diving.
In the history of soccer,
he is the only parent to ever
take sides against his own kid,
and he was right.
He made me a better person,
because that's what heroes do.
That's what heroes do.
(microphone feedback squeals)
(crowd cheering)
I'm so glad I was
forced to come.
People, people...
we have a tie!
(clamoring)
Yes, which means
that nobody wins.
The money goes back in
the school general fund.
But we will put both
speeches online.
Behind a paywall.
Now, please fold up your
chairs and stack them.
♪ Cause I'm a grade
school hero ♪
♪ Lisa never lies ♪
♪ I'm a grade
school hero ♪
♪ And heroes never die ♪
♪ Just one guitar! ♪
♪ Slung way down low! ♪
♪ Yeah, one guitar! ♪
♪ Where did my lawnmower go? ♪
Well, look who's back.
- Hmm.
- Hey, Dad.
Lisa, your speech was one of the nicest
things anyone's ever done for me.
When did you come
up with the idea?
You must've worked
on it for days.
Oh, Dad, you don't
want the details.
No one wants to see the
sausage being made.
There's sausage being made?!
Where?!
Homie, there's someone
here to see you.
Coming!
I haven't forgotten
about the sausage.
Mr. Simpson, I am the executive vice
president of the World Football Federation.
Ooh!
What you Americans call
"soccer."
D'oh!
I'm sure you are familiar
with the World Cup,
the quadrennial drama
unmatched on the planet!
Oh, yeah. That's the thing
the guys at the dry cleaners
get so excited about
every four years.
I'm afraid there has been an epidemic of
referees being bribed to throw games.
From the premier leagues to the
playgrounds, all has been tainted.
We need a symbol of
integrity like yourself.
Of course I am, but
how do you know?
Oh, your daughter's speech
went viral.
(shrieks)
No, no, I mean it
spread like wildfire.
Much better.
Mr. Simpson,
please help us.
The rot is everywhere.
In fact, I see that I myself
am about to be arrested
for corruption.
You will have to take
it from here, Peter.
Yes, I will take good
care of your wife.
Wait, what-what
does that mean?
Mr. Simpson, I am the new executive
vice president of the WFF.
We need outsiders like you
to come to the World Cup,
as our guest, and ref
our games properly.
Well, no one has ever
questioned my professionalism.
Except at my profession.
(groans)
What do you
think, sweetie?
Dad, they're offering us
an all-expenses-paid trip
to the greatest sporting
event on Earth!
The 2008 Super Bowl?
Oh, I wish.
Eli Manning's pass
to David Tyree.
But about the World Cup,
I need your answer now.
Oh, sure, why not?
"Congratulations on your purchase
of a FootMaster-brand soccer ball."
Thanks, book!
Look, you got us
a free trip.
Just slack off and cash your
check like you always do.
I believe the sweet little girl
in 21-D would disagree with you.
- What the...?!
- I switched with her, Dad.
My TV didn't work!
Now I can watch
my premium HBO!
(groans)
(humming)
Well, look at you, using
approved electronic devices.
To try to avoid any
misunderstandings in Brazil
like we had the last time,
I'm learning the language.
. COMPUTER: Olá.
- Olá!
Eu amo o Brasil.
Eu amo o Brasil!
O que é um país
encantador.
PILOT: Will you
please turn that off?
It's annoying the hell
out of the flight crew.
I was just trying
to learn the...
Everyone thinks they can learn
our language on the plane.
Do you know how
disrespectful that is?
(groans)
All right, just for that
attitude, turbulence.
(plane rattling)
(fanfare plays)
ANNOUNCER 1: Live from Sao Paulo, we
bring you the World Cup Round Robin
Group F Opening-Round
Match!
Today's game is between our host
country, football powerhouse Brazil...
CROWD:
♪ Olé, olé-olé-olé. ♪
...and Luxemburg, whose
entire nation has turned up.
(wind whistling)
Got to hurry. I've got
998 square miles to rob!
Ha-ha!
The mighty Brazilian squad
features the greatest master
of the fake injury soccer
has ever known: El Divo!
(screams)
(crowd gasps, cheers)
Now let's play
human foosball!
(whistle blows)
ANNOUNCER 2: And with Brazil maintaining
an insurmountable one-goal lead,
with 28 minutes to play,
let's take a look at the refs.
It says here, "Homer Simpson was recruited
for his honesty and utter disinterest."
ANNOUNCER 2: How did he get
those shorts on over that arse?
ANNOUNCER 1: Rumor has it, they
employed a team of pullers.
(whistle blows, crowd cheers)
Brazil wins it! And a
fairly-called match it was.
In choosing Homer Simpson, the
World Cup has met its goal...!
Andres Cantor, you know
that is incorrect usage.
I have no control...!
This job has
taken its toll...!
Eu gostaria de um...
Hang on, hang on.
...placa de...
Here you go, honey.
How'd you eat the meat
without the vegetables?
Well, the stomach
wants what it wants.
(burps)
Oh, I need some air.
Ah, Brazil.
I couldn't stay afraid
of you forever.
The only thing that keeps
me from living here
is that fish that swims
up your pee stream.
That is a deal breaker.
Homer Simpson!
I would like to congratulate you
on your fine officiating today.
Thanks. I still can't believe
the yellow and red cards
don't stand for
mustard and ketchup.
Your disbelief will
fade with time.
But now, I would like to know if you
are as incorruptível as they say.
(heavenly music plays)
Oh, that is where I
left my cell phone.
Well?
You don't know the new me
of the last few days at all!
We will get to him.
We have our ways.
Well, what other ways
besides guns and money?
We have two ways.
Two very good ways.
♪ Samba! ♪
Red card!
Let me give that
back to you.
Get out of here!
(crowd cheering)
♪
ANNOUNCER 1:
And as Homer officiates,
looks like we've got a little
action on the bribe cam.
(crowd cheering)
♪
Man, Krusty should get
some of these letters.
(groans)
While you were out, the gamblers
sent up gold-frosted donuts,
a chocolate bowling ball
and a fresh pork sandwich.
Oh. How fresh?
(pig squeals)
Oh! Where's your mother?
Went to practice her Portuguese.
Mm...
"Selecionar conta..."
Ooh, ooh, "select
account."
Uh, perhaps you could
select the English option?
I did not pay $7.99 for an app so
I could use the English option.
You Americans, you really
throw your $7.99s around.
You know, you're
pretty rude.
(chuckles)
Stupid lady.
Give the donuts to
the hotel staff.
Release the pig and the
bowling ball into the wild.
Dad, is it hard for you to
turn these bribes down?
Yes. But knowing that Lisa
chose me as her hero,
without ever considering any
other hero, keeps me strong.
Why so quiet?
I'm just examining what
kind of person I am
and whether I should destroy
your happiness forever.
- Eh, why not?
- I'm listening.
- And it better be devastating.
- You weren't Lisa's hero.
She just swapped you in at the last minute
because someone else did her real hero.
Oh, my God.
That's... that's
shattering.
And now I'm a man in pain
in the naughtiest city
since San Francisco
turned all nerdy.
(groans)
Where are you going?
To drink until there's
no pain left in my soul.
But first I'm gonna eat off
someone else's room service tray
that was left in the hall.
Now that's a broken man.
Hmm.
- What the hell are you doing?
- It's okay. I'm an American.
Oh. Oh. Okay.
So, the rumors are true.
We knew you'd find out your daughter's
original speech topic was Marie Curie.
And now we need you to fix
the greatest game of all:
The World Cup Final.
Fine. Marge is always
complaining I never fix things.
- Give me another.
- All right.
But we've run out
of sugarcane.
I carry my own.
All right, Homer. To begin
your descent into hell,
let us enjoy this pirated
copy of Man of Steel.
But beware: Superman
was never less fun.
(laughs evilly)
ANNOUNCER 2:
Here it is, the World Cup Final!
DRY CLEANER GUYS:
Yay!
ANNOUNCER 2: Will it be a German
Blitzkrieg or a Brazilian waxing?
- Nazis!
- Nazi harborers!
Guys, you're both right.
All right, just so there
are no misunderstandings,
you make sure Brazil wins, and
we give you one million dollars.
If I bet it, I
could double it.
But on who?
You know that Brazil
is going to win.
Oh, thanks for telling me!
I was gonna tape it.
Remember, I'll
be watching.
Wave a Brazilian flag so you
stand out in the crowd.
Don't do it, Dad.
Don't cheat.
You're a funny one to
tell me about deception.
I'm sorry you weren't
my first choice.
In fact...
(sighs)
I had my doubts about
using you at all.
Well, if we're gonna be
brutally honest,
that drawing you made of me when you were
three was far from a perfect likeness.
- You put it on the fridge!
- It was pity-fridged!
All right, you're hurt.
I understand.
But when I made you my hero,
you lived up to it and more.
You became the hero I
thought you could be, Dad.
Oh. Oh, come here.
Everything's right
with the world.
Except that you're about to
double-cross some gangsters.
That's all right, brain.
If I die, I'll be doing the
thing I love the most:
Trying not to get killed.
ANNOUNCER 2: This match is tighter
than two dogs on a summer morn.
There's no score at all. Even the
slightest pebble could start a landslide.
ANNOUNCER 1:
And El Divo goes down!
In the box! Will Homer award
a penalty kick to Brazil?
Do it. Do it!
Call the penalty!
No penalty!
He dove, Dad!
(grunts)
No penalty!
(crowd booing)
I repeat, no penalty!
No penalty.
ANNOUNCER 1: The game, plus two hours
of funeral time, is about to conclude.
And with Germany
the victor, two-nil,
in an unprecedented
display of rectitude
and stubbornness by
one Homer Simpson.
I've never seen the
Brazilians so depressed.
(sadly):
♪ Olé... ♪
♪ Olé, olé, olé... ♪
You broke a deal with us.
And we have lost a fortune!
(gasps)
Well, at least I'll
die the American way.
In a foreign country
wearing short pants.
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
I want to say something!
You have one minute. Wait!
Let it get to the 12.
N... now.
Um...
(speaking Portuguese)
How's she doing that?
I don't know, but
she's my new hero.
Yeah, I was a little surprised
I wasn't considered before.
Ah, your fluency
is impressive.
You can help my son learn
Hebrew for his bar mitzvah.
But I'm still killing
your husband.
First, mazel tov.
Second, don't!
Please, please!
I'm a mother.
Surely you have
a mother, too.
I do have a mother.
- Oh, she's right there.
- I'm sorry, my son.
We owe a debt to the Simpsons
that can never be repaid.
All that she did was
switch seats on a plane.
On a 15-hour flight!
You are free to go.
(dirge playing)
No penalty.
Fine.
(birds squawking)
Wow, the Amazon is
just like I pictured it
after seeing all those
pictures online.
I've never seen
anything so beautiful.
(chainsaw buzzing)
The best thing is I can get
locally-sourced monkey meat.
(hooting)
(shrieks)
Okay, Teeny. Take
care of part two.
(gun cocks)
(hooting, grunting)
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
Shh!