♪ The Simpsons ♪
(chalk screeches)
(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(tires screeching)
(horn honks)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
MAN: Principal Skinner,
"The Happiest Place on Earth"
is a registered
Disneyland copyright.
Well, gentlemen,
it's just a small
school carnival.
And it's heading for
a great big lawsuit.
You made a big mistake,
Skinner.
Well, so did you.
You got an ex-Green Beret mad.
(gasps)
(grunting)
(groaning)
(gasps)
(grunts)
Copyright expired.
And begin.
This sucks.
(yells)
(laughs)
Pick the red, get ahead.
Pick the black,
sets you back.
Hmm, I don't recall
authorizing this booth.
Good-bye, gentlemen.
(gasping)
(coughing)
Get your haggis right here.
Chopped heart and lungs,
boiled in a real
sheep's stomach.
Tastes as good as it sounds.
Good for what ails you.
Hag--
(groans)
I'd say 53 years old
and 420 pounds.
Ha, ha! You lose.
36 and 239.
Oh.
♪♪ (loud rock music)
Hey, Otto, man
I dare you
to make this go faster.
Ooh, challenge accepted.
(screaming)
I'll be in Mexico
till this thing blows over.
(yelling)
Oh, boy!
A spookhouse.
Hand over
all your money.
(grunting)
Was it scary?
(painfully)
Uh-huh.
Ooh-hoo, baby!
BART: Uh-oh.
So, girlie,
you like roller-skating?
-No.
-Yeah,
everybody loves
roller-skating.
Okay.
You can turn around now.
(gasps)
(people laughing)
Oh, my God.
I'm ugly.
Now in a moment,
we'll be raffling off
our grand prize...
a ride on the famous
Duff Beer blimp.
A ride on the Duff blimp.
You see the circular
pattern on those fields?
That's from
central pivot irrigation.
Wow.
Now, let's see
what's happening
at the Super Bowl.
CROWD (chanting):
Homer! Homer! Homer! Homer!
MAN: Oops! Sorry.
(chanting continues)
Homer. Homer. Homer.
But first,
our second-prize winner,
and the recipient of
this handsome shoe buffer...
Ned Flanders!
(gasps)
Oh, it's no fair.
We'll never have
a buffer.
We have one at home.
You never use it.
Well, I want that one.
And the winner
of the blimp ride is...
Homer Simpson!
Oh, my God!
(whimpers)
♪ Hey, there, blimpy boy ♪
♪ Flying through the sky
so fancy-free ♪
(crying)
Honey, what's wrong?
Dad, do you think I'm ugly?
What are you
talking about?
(laughs)
Oh, Lisa, this isn't real.
It's just how you might look
if you were a cartoon character.
I'm an ugmo!
Now, that's not true.
You're cute as a bug's ear.
Fathers have
to say that stuff.
Dad, am I cute
as a bug's ear?
No! You're homely
as a mule's butt!
There, see?
I'd like to be alone, please.
(sobbing)
Moe, have you
ever felt unattractive?
Hmm, no.
How about you,
Barney?
Not for a second.
(belches)
Yeah... I need help.
BOTH: Whee! Whee!
Whee! Whee!
Whee-e-e!
I guess every father thinks
his daughter is the cutest.
Well, now there's a way
to prove it.
Wow, president
of Laramie Cigarettes
Jack Larson.
This year
Laramie is sponsoring
the Little Miss Springfield
pageant.
You see,
government regulations
prohibit us
from advertising on TV...
Ahh...
that sweet Carolina smoke.
But they can't prohibit us
from holding a beauty pageant
for little girls
age seven to nine.
Lisa's age
seven to nine.
Your daughter
could be crowned
Little Miss Springfield
by our host,
the maitre 'd of glee
Krusty the Clown.
I heartily endorse
this event or product.
What a feeling!
I'm as happy as a smoker
taking that first puff
in the morning.
That could be Lisa.
The Little Miss Springfield
pageant--
only $250 to enter.
Oh...
Hey, Barney.
Will you give me 250 bucks
for this blimp ticket?
Sure.
(gasps) Where did you
get all the money?
From some scientist.
Since they stopped testing
on animals,
a guy like me
can really clean up.
(gulping)
I'm hideous.
Lisa, I know a song
that will cheer you up.
♪ There once was
an ugly duckling ♪
So you think I'm ugly?
No, no!
I meant you were one of
the good-looking ducks...
that makes fun of the ugly one.
(groans)
Lisa, if you could have
one wish, what would it be?
To shut myself off
from the world
and never be seen
by human eyes again.
Uh, was your second wish
to be entered in
the Little Miss Springfield
pageant?
What are you talking about?
I sent in an application
for you.
I couldn't find
a big enough photo,
so I sent in that funny drawing
of you on roller skates.
How could you?!
I won't do it!
(sobbing)
Homer, Lisa's already
sensitive about her looks.
This is the last thing
she needs.
But I think she'll win.
Dad, have you seen the girls
they have in those contests?
Hubba, hubba!
(panting)
(howls)
Hey, nobody's prettier
than my little girl.
Hmm. You're looking at her
through a father's eyes.
Well, if I could gouge out
somebody else's eyes
and shove them
into my sockets,
I would, but to me
she's beautiful.
That is so sweet.
Honey, no one's going to
force you to do anything,
but do you know
how your father
got the money to enter you
in this pageant?
Nope.
He sold his ride
on the Duff blimp.
But that ride
meant everything to him.
♪ Hey, there, blimpy boy ♪
♪ Flying through the sky
so fancy-free ♪
I'll do it.
Did you see
Tina Epstein?
Whoa. If you're gonna binge,
you'd better purge.
Uh-oh.
Amber Dempsey.
In the same week,
she was Pork Princess
and Little Miss Kosher.
She's beautiful.
Wait, she's about to
bring out the big guns.
Eyelash implants.
I thought those
were illegal.
Not in Paraguay.
There's no way I can
beat this girl.
She's the Jack Nicklaus
of the pageant circuit.
Oh, I don't know
that she's as attractive
as Jack Nicklaus.
(humming)
I meant because they both
win all the time, Mom.
Oh. Well, yes.
That's what I meant, too.
Well, tell you what.
This afternoon, I'll take you
to the beauty parlor
and show you just
how lovely you can be.
And later, I'll teach you
the tricks of the trade--
taping your swimsuit
to your butt,
petroleum jelly on your teeth
for that frictionless smile,
and the ancient art
of padding.
(purring)
Are we done?
We are just warming up.
Oh. Isn't this dangerous?
Don't worry.
I am well protected.
Boy, when Lisa comes in
I want you to
make a big fuss
over how she looks.
She'll see through me
like grandma's underpants.
No, she won't.
When it comes
to compliments,
women are ravenous,
bloodsucking monsters,
always wanting
more, more, more!
And if you give it to them,
you'll get plenty back
in return.
Like what?
I'll tell you when you're older.
(laughs)
(door closes)
Is that Lisa?
Ooh, I got
to call heaven.
There's
an angel missing.
And who's your little
school friend?
Wait a minute--
that's Mom!
Oh, my goodness.
Aren't they nice!
Thank you.
I know two fellows
who are going to get
a special dinner tonight.
-Hey, hey!
-Woo-hoo!
Dad, you know anything else
about women?
Nope, that's it.
Hey, brush head.
You've been nursing that
thing for an hour.
You know,
I was just wondering
how someone who works
in an ice cream store
keeps such a trim figure.
I've misjudged you.
♪♪ (piano)
I said, "Step, pause,
turn, pause,
pivot, step, step."
not, "Step, pause, turn,
pause, pivot, step, pause."
Oh, shudder.
And the winner is...
Lisa Simpson!
(gasps)
Okay, wipe away
a tear...
hug the loser...
and now,
for your triumphant walk
down the runway.
(shoes squeaking)
Whoa.
(yelling)
It's hopeless.
There's nothing to it.
Give me those heels.
Heel, toe. Heel, toe.
Heel, toe.
Do you really think I can win?
Hey, I'm starting to think
I can win.
But those other girls
are prettier than me.
Lis, as your brother,
this is the hardest thing
I've ever had to say.
You're not ugly.
Oh, Bart!
♪♪
♪ Out on our own ♪
♪ Making it work ♪
♪ Gasping for air ♪
♪ Having it all ♪
My name is Amber Dempsey.
When I grow up,
I want to be a sweetie pie.
(applause)
I am Pahusacheta
Nahasapeemapetilon
and tonight I will be playing
"MacArthur Park"
on the tabla.
(laughing)
No, I am serious.
Yes, judges,
there's your queen.
Who's watching
the Kwik-E-Mart?
(both gasp)
(groaning)
(laughing)
My name is Lisa Simpson,
and I want to be
Little Miss Springfield
so I can make our town
a better place.
Yeah, clean up this stink hole!
(panting)
Krusty. About time
you got here.
Yeah, yeah, what is this?
The Republican fundraiser?
♪ Check it out ♪
♪ Hey, look at us ♪
♪ Making a wish ♪
♪ Dreaming a dream ♪
♪ Little Miss Springfield ♪
♪ Which one will it be? ♪
GIRLS: Me!
Oh, that brisket's
not sitting right.
♪ And I'll never have
that recipe again ♪
♪ Oh, no ♪
(scattered applause)
Oh, that just kept going, huh?
And now, here's...
Lisa Simpson!
They'll love you
just as much as I do.
Thanks, Dad.
Mmm!
Some people say
that to love your country
is old-fashioned,
uncool, real Melvin.
Well, to them I say--
♪ Oh, beautiful ♪
♪ For spacious skies ♪
♪ For Amber waves of grain ♪
One, two, three, four!
♪ Left a good job
in the city ♪
♪ Working for the man
every night and day ♪
(cheering)
This is my favorite part
of the pageant because...
What does that say?
Oh. It gives me a chance
to visit with the girls
personality...
uh, personally.
Amber, do you think
the Bill of Rights
is a good thing
or a bad thing?
Um...
Take your time,
dear.
Good thing.
ALL: Aw...
And now it's time to name
our runner-up,
who, if the winner
doesn't fulfill her duties...
blah, blah, blah.
And don't say
it will never happen,
because we all remember
that thing with what's her name.
Click, click.
You know.
Okay, the runner-up is...
(drum roll)
Hmm.
Lisa Simpson!
Which means Amber Dempsey
is the new
Little Miss Springfield!
(applause)
♪♪
♪ "L,"
the losers in her wake ♪
♪ "I," the income
she will make ♪
♪ "T" is for her
tooth filled mouth ♪
♪ "T," is for her
MAN (on TV):
Coming up next:
A new fad that's
sweeping the nation--
wasting food.
But first,
let's join the new
Little Miss Springfield,
Amber Dempsey
as she helps open
the Danish superchain, Shop.
Scott, everyone is here,
from the mayor's
illegitimate son
to our own Duff blimp.
Hi. Can I drive?
Well, I can't see
the harm.
(Barney yelling)
Oh, the humanity!
Anyway,
to turn on the store's
severe tire damage spikes,
here's
Little Miss Springfield.
Oh dear, it would be a shame
if that pretty dress got wet.
I'd say
the greater danger
is her scepter acting
as a lightning rod...
unless it's made
out of plastic.
(thunder booming)
Nope. Metal.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Little Miss Springfield
has been struck
by lightning.
Doctor, what is
Amber's condition?
Oh, she'll be fine.
In fact,
she's already won
the Little Miss
Intensive Care pageant.
Congratulations, Lisa.
You're the new
Little Miss Springfield.
Here's your scepter.
Whoop!
(laughs)
Just kidding.
Here you go.
Whoop!
(laughs)
Just kidding.
(thunder booming)
I deserved that.
That doesn't look
like her body.
The torso
used to be Dr. Ruth.
Her head is on a pike
in the chamber of horrors.
(boys whistling)
Hi, fellas.
Love that chewing gum walk.
Very Wrigley.
As Little Miss Springfield,
it's my pleasure
to welcome you to America,
the land of opportunity.
Actually,
they're being deported.
♪♪ (mournful tune)
EMCEE: And now, let's give
a big Fort Springfield welcome
to Mr. Bob Hope.
What's the mayor's name?
-Quimby.
-Beautiful.
Hello, this is Bob
"What the hell am I doing
in Springfield?" Hope.
Hey, how about
that Mayor Quimby?
He's some golfer.
His golf ball
spends more time underwater
than Greg Louganis.
And now,
I want to show you
what you're fighting for--
if there was a war on--
Little Miss Springfield.
Isn't she beautiful?
Little Miss Springfield?
First Tony Randall cancels,
now this.
SOLDIER:
Hey, what gives here?
(helicopter whirring)
MAN:
We want Miss Springfield.
Hey, set me down
at that boat show.
I'm gonna be riding
on a pack of cigarettes?
Mm-hmm. We think
you're the perfect spokesmodel
for Laramie's.
It's part
of our new campaign.
Mmm... classy.
(gasping)
You see, Lisa, it's been
an unlucky year for Laramie.
A lot of people who smoke
our product have been...
well, dying.
And we need young smokers
to take their place.
I don't want to be a spokesperson
for a cigarette company.
But you're a role model
to young people
and we're thinking
of retiring Menthol Moose.
(hacking cough)
(hocks and spits)
♪♪ (march)
Bless you, boys.
Homer, those are
ice cream men.
I know.
(crowd exclaiming
and applauding)
(gasping)
Stop this float!
(grunting)
What's the holdup? Go!
I'm tired of being
a corporate shill.
(grunting)
From now on, I will speak out
against the evils in society
from dognapping
to cigarettes.
LISA: Before I sing
the national anthem
I'd like to say that
college football diverts funds
badly needed
for education and the arts.
(crowd murmuring)
Is that true?
Let's get 'em!
(angry whining)
Let's get out of here!
Gentlemen, we need
to get Lisa Simpson out
and Amber Dempsey back in,
but this glorified
crossing guard of a police chief
won't get off
his big fat can.
Is it okay if I open
these potato chips?
(sneers)
Gentlemen, our prayers
have been answered.
Take a look at our
Little Miss Springfield's
pageant application.
Roxie, bring in
a bottle of champagne.
And some dip for these chips...
or something.
Lisa Simpson is no longer
Little Miss Springfield.
She was stripped of her crown
in a ceremony earlier today.
Well, that's obviously
the wrong footage.
Uh... but it does
seem the father
of the deposed beauty queen,
Homer Simpson,
filled out the pageant
application incorrectly.
In the area under
"Do not write in this space,"
he wrote, "Okay."
If it wasn't for me,
you'd still be queen.
-You must hate me.
-Dad, do you remember
why you entered me
in that pageant?
I don't know.
Was I drunk?
Possibly,
but the point is
you wanted me
to feel better about myself,
and I do.
-Really?
-Uh-huh.
Will you remember this
the next time
I wreck your life?
It's a deal.
And now, my
exclusive interview
with his holiness,
Pope John Paul II.
That's it.
I cannot work
under these conditions.
If anybody wants me,
I'll be downstairs
at MacDougal's.
Call the weekend guy.
I don't care.
(door slamming)
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.