♪ The Simpsons ♪
(chalk screeches)
(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(tires screeching)
(horn honks)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
♪♪ (suspenseful)
Ahh.
(rumbling)
Why, you little--!
♪♪ ("Raiders of
the Lost Ark" theme)
What the--?
D'oh!
(laughing)
(babbling)
Hey, Bart, look at this.
My dad took me to
Circus of Values last night
and said I could get
anything I wanted.
Cool-- An oversize
novelty billiard ball.
Yeah, you shake it up
and it tells the future.
-Really?
-Uh-huh.
Will I pass my English test?
"Outlook not so good."
Wow, it does work!
Let me try.
Will... I get
beat up today?
"All signs point to yes."
That ball knows everything.
(grunts, groaning)
Hey, I got a good one.
Will Milhouse and I
be friends
till we're
toothless old men
with hair coming out
of our ears?
"Don't count on it."
Will Milhouse and I be friends
when we're high school dropouts
living off Uncle Sucker?
"It looks doubtful."
Will Milhouse and I be friends
at the end of the day?
(gasping)
What could come between
two bestest buddies like us?
Samantha, I've always
been suspicious
of transfer students.
Other principals try to unload
problem cases that way.
Lord knows I do.
I'm a good student,
Principal Skinner.
Yeah, sure, and they told me
I'd get a big parade
when I got back from 'Nam.
Instead, they spat on me.
I can still feel it searing.
So, let's just see
what the permanent record
has to say, shall we?
No detention, fairly good
attendance record...
I see you beat that bed-wetting
problem in the second grade.
That's in there?
Don't worry.
They'll forget...
just like they forgot about me
in that tiger cage
for 18 agonizing months.
Every night I wake up screaming.
Well, let's meet
your classmates.
Hey, Bart, was this thing
right about your test?
To those who doubt the power
of the magic eight ball
I say, behold my "F".
Attention, class.
I have a new student for you.
Great, another student.
Just keep packing them in,
Seymour.
I think we should discuss
this later, Edna.
Now, it's never easy
to come to a new school,
so let's make her feel
right at home.
Please say a big
elementary school hello
to Samantha Stinky.
(kids laughing)
Stanky.
Oh, right.
How embarrassing for you.
Well, good-bye.
I'm sure this is
a little scary for you, dear.
-Uh-huh.
-So, why don't you
stand up in front of the class
and tell us about yourself?
I'll be grading you
on grammar and poise.
We just moved here from Phoenix.
My dad's owns
a home security company.
He came to Springfield
because of its high crime rate
and lackluster police force.
All my friends
are back in Phoenix
and this town has a weird smell
that you're all probably used to
but I'm not.
It'll take you
about six weeks, dear.
Hey, Milhouse, would you
like a Wet Willie?
Sure.
Eww!
(laughing)
Victim number four.
Hey, Louis, can I interest you
in a Wet Willie?
LOUIS:
Sure... Aah!
When I find out who
hit me with that ball
I'm gonna tear them a new--
Whoa!
Class, in order to explain
why your hormones
will soon make you
an easy target
for every smooth-talking
lothario
with his own car
and tight jeans,
I will now show
a short sex education film.
Ezekiel and Ishmael,
in accordance with
your parents' wishes
you may step out
into the hall
and pray for our souls.
Hello.
I'm actor Troy McClure.
You kids might remember me
from such educational films
as "Lead Paint:
Delicious but Deadly"
and "Here Comes
the Metric System."
I'm here to provide
the facts about sex
in a frank and
straightforward manner.
And now, here's...
This is Fuzzy Bunny.
About a year ago
he noticed
his voice was changing,
he had terrible acne,
and had fur where
there was no fur before.
He also noticed
Fluffy Bunny.
Boring.
TROY MCCLURE:
Fluffy and Fuzzy went to the park,
the ice cream social,
the boat show,
and various other
wholesome activities,
and they never
ruined their fun
by giving in to their
throbbing biological urges.
Then came the big day.
Fluffy and Fuzzy
got married.
That night came
the honeymoon.
♪♪ (funky, sexy jazz)
ALL: Eww!
She's faking it.
The most satisfying
part of the night
was knowing that
they waited.
Nine months later
Fluffy gave birth
to 14 beautiful bunnies.
Eight survive.
And now that you know
how it's done...
don't do it.
♪♪ (funky, sexy jazz)
-Any questions?
-Mrs. Krabappel,
how come you don't
live with Mr. Krabappel?
Because Mr. Krabappel
chased something small
and fluffy down a rabbit hole.
How do we know
when we fall in love?
Oh, don't you worry.
Most of you
will never fall in love
and marry out of fear
of dying alone.
How would I go about creating
a half man,
half monkey-type creature?
I'm sorry,
that would be playing God.
God, shmod--
I want my monkey man.
(bell ringing)
Uh... that's a nice dress.
My dad makes me wear it.
I hate it.
Well, I hate it too.
-Uh... can I walk you home?
-Okay.
Everybody on.
No shoving.
Just kidding.
You can shove all you want.
Hey, wait, Otto man,
you can't leave.
Milhouse isn't here yet.
Sorry, Bart dude,
no time.
My girlfriend's dancing topless
at the airport bar
from 4:15 to 4:20.
Hey, Bart.
Milhouse, what
a pleasant surprise.
Hi.
Hey, what's with the skirt?
I've brought friends
to this tree house before.
Yeah, but never a girl.
What if I want
to strut around nude?
Maybe I should go.
No, that's okay,
you can stay.
You can read comics with us.
Let's see,
something for the lady...
Ah-- "Radioactive Man
vs. The Swamp Hag".
Got any girl comics
like "Bonnie Crane,
Girl Attorney,"
"Punkin and Dunkin,
the Twinkle Twins,"
or "Li'l Knee Socks"?
No, but my sister's
got a wide selection
of crappy comics.
Eww!
You guys want to see
something gross?
(gasping)
ANNOUNCER:
Tonight on Smartline:
"I'm okay. You're too fat."
Here's your host,
Kent Brockman.
Good evening.
Did you know that 34 million
American adults are obese?
Taken together
that excess blubber
could fill the Grand Canyon
two-fifths of the way up.
That may not sound
impressive
but keep in mind,
it is a very big canyon.
This sucks. Where's
that channel changer?
(grunting)
Oh.
I'll give it a chance.
Americans have grown up
with the image
of the jolly fat man--
Dom Deluise
Alfred Hitchcock,
and, of course,
Santa Claus.
But in real life
Santa would be suffering
from gall stones,
hypertension, impotence,
and diabetes.
Hmm.
I wish they had never
invented fried cheese.
We got to widen
the hole.
Make it snappy--
The chain's starting to give.
(chain creaking)
(labored breathing)
WOMAN: We take 18 ounces
of sizzling ground beef...
Ooh!
...and soak it
in rich creamery butter.
Then we top it off with
bacon, ham, and a fried egg.
We call it
The Good Morning burger.
(shuddering moan)
I've got to help him.
Okay, Milhouse,
I'll trade your
Carl Yastrzemski baseball card
for my Omar Vzocel.
Deal.
Next on the trading block,
your Mickey Mantle, 1958,
for my picture
of Homer on the couch.
Milhouse, I've got to go.
My dad thinks I'm having
my braces examined.
Well, you kind of
sort of are.
Milhouse, we're living
in the age of cooties.
I can't believe
the risk you're running.
Besides, what's so great
about kissing?
Bart, it's not
just the kissing.
A lot of it is
waiting to kiss.
You know, like when you
open an Eskimo Pie
and you wait just a
little bit for it to melt?
But she doesn't melt.
Oh, yes, she does.
WOMAN: We start with pure
milk chocolate...
Chocolate...
...add a layer
of farm-fresh honey...
Oh, sweet.
...then we sprinkle on
four kinds of sugar...
(ecstatic groan)
...and dip it
in rich creamery butter.
Dad, what if I told you
you could lose weight
without dieting
or lifting a finger?
I'd say you're
a lying scumbag.
Why, sweetie?
According to Eternity magazine
you can lose weight through
subliminal learning.
That's where an idea is
subtly implanted in your head
without you even knowing it.
Oh, Lisa, that's a load
of rich creamery butter.
They'll send you tapes
you listen to
while you sleep.
As you hear new age music,
a powerful message
goes to your brain
telling you to eat less.
Lose weight and listen
to new age music? Wow.
What do you think, Marge?
Oh, Homer, I love you
just the way you are.
Lisa, what's that number?
Operator, I'd like to place
an order for my husband.
Would he like to lose weight,
stop smoking,
learn the state capitals,
master hostage negotiations...
Hmm... hostage negotiations.
Listen, Tabbouleh, we're
ignoring all your demands.
What do you say to that?
(machine gun fire)
Better give me
the weight loss tape.
We're out of
"Subliminally Slim."
MAN: Eh... just send them
the vocabulary builder.
Here you go, fatso.
HOMER: So long, stomach.
We've had a lot
of great memories.
♪ Memories ♪
♪ Pressed between the pages
of my mind ♪
♪ Memories ♪
♪ Sweetened through the ages,
just like wine ♪
(yawning)
(snoring)
Hello. This is
Dr. Marvin Monroe.
Let's build your
vocabulary. "A."
Abattoir:
Slaughterhouse.
"The cow was slaughtered
in the abattoir."
(Homer munching)
Homer, has the weight loss tape
reduced your appetite?
Lamentably, no.
My gastronomic rapacity
knows no satiety.
Don't you usually play
with Milhouse after school?
He has a girlfriend.
Milhouse?
Yeah. All they do is kiss.
How cute.
They don't open
their mouths, do they?
No.
How cute.
-Hey, Martin.
-Bart?
This is the first time anyone
has ever sat next to me
since I successfully
lobbied
to have the school day
extended by 20 minutes.
Listen, Martin, right now
I'm looking for a friend
who won't leave me
for a girl.
That's me. I'm just as
unpopular with the ladies
as I am with the chaps.
Yeah, right.
Anyway, do you wanna do
something after school?
It's a date.
Everyone, Bart and I
would like to announce
that we are friends.
(loud laughter)
Now, Bart, would you care
to listen to me play the lute?
Uh... sure.
♪ Come home,
my bonny warrior ♪
♪ For now ♪
♪ The nets are
full o' fish ♪
MARGE: I don't know
if that tape is working.
You ate three desserts
tonight.
Forbearance is the watchword.
That triumvirate of Twinkies
merely overwhelmed my resolve.
There's another thing I've been
wanting to talk to you about.
Tut, tut, gentle Marge.
For here in the boudoir
the gourmand
metamorphosizes into...
the voluptuary!
(growls)
What in God's name
are you talking about?
Oh.
♪ The Itchy
& Scratchy show! ♪
♪♪ ("Wedding March")
Mmm...
(screams)
(laughing)
Heh...
Hey, guys.
Wow, that really
took my mind off
those awful,
transforming space mutants.
Good.
Man, I could sure go
for a snack.
Me too.
(screaming)
D'oh!
Hey, I've got an idea.
Why don't the three of us go
spit on the principal's car?
Listen, Bart,
there's such a thing
as spending
too much time together.
Oh, fine.
I'm tired of watching
you two lip wrestle.
There's plenty of other ways
to be grossed out in this town.
(sobbing)
-Bart, wait.
-Yeah?
Uh...
could we still use
your tree house?
What? Get bent.
If her father catches us,
he'll kill her.
All right, Milhouse.
You can use my tree house.
Thanks, Bart.
(singsongy)
Samantha and Milhouse sitting in a tree,
about to lose
their privacy.
(fiendish laughter)
(touch tones)
Now there's a
Machiavellian countenance.
Ooh, a sextet of ale!
Hello, Mr. Stanky?
I have some shocking news
about your daughter Samantha.
Who am I?
Let's just say I'm
a concerned prude
with a lot of time on his hands.
(kissing sounds)
I bet you had peanut butter
for breakfast.
(laughs)
Yeah.
-Samantha!
-Dad!
Noooooo!
Samantha, you're my little girl
and sometimes my imagination
runs away with me.
Just-- Just tell me
what happened.
-Well, Milhouse and I--
-That's enough!
I'm putting you in
an all-girl school.
You're never going to see
that boy again.
Milhouse!
Samantha!
(weeping)
Well, Milhouse, 'tis better
to have loved and lost...
yadda, yadda, yadda.
Let's go to the arcade.
How could this happen?
We started out
like Romeo and Juliet
but it ended up
in tragedy.
Hierospacy:
Predicting the future
through the study
of animal entrails.
Dad! Do you know
what today is?
The vernal equinox?
No, it's two weeks
since you got that
subliminal weight-loss tape.
Let's get you on the scale.
You've gained 13 pounds.
Disingenuous mountebanks with
their subliminal chicanery--
A pox on them!
There stands a broken man.
It's recess everywhere
but in his heart.
Hey, Bart, according
to this magazine
in another million years
man will have
an extra finger.
Five fingers?
Ooh-- Freak show!
Listen, Lis, I need some
advice and Mom's not here.
-Why didn't you go to Dad?
-I did,
but I couldn't understand
what the hell he was saying.
Lisa, I feel terrible.
I ratted on my best friend
and he doesn't even know
I did it.
Well, according to
Eternity magazine
the feeling of guilt
has been linked
to the neural-transmitter
gamephenomene.
Dow chemical is developing
a minty gel
which will eliminate
excess guilt,
but unfortunately
it won't be on the market
for another six months,
so I guess you're gonna
have to bite the bullet
and confess to Milhouse.
(groans)
Bart, I'm glad you're here.
Milhouse could use
a friend like you.
(nervous laugh)
(sobbing)
Milhouse?
Bart, I didn't want you
to see me cry.
Oh, come on.
I've seen you cry
a million times.
You cry when
you scrape your knee.
You cry when they're out
of chocolate milk.
You cry when you're doing
long division
and you have
a remainder left over.
Well, I didn't want you
to see me cry this time.
Listen, Milhouse, I got
a confession to make.
I'm the one who narked
on your kissing.
What?!
(growling)
(grunting)
Milhouse is out of bed
and full of beans.
Whoa, it's a miracle!
(groans)
(both gasping)
Well, I bet the eight ball
didn't see that one coming.
Yeah.
Marge...
where's that...
metal dealie...
you use to...
dig... food?
You mean, a spoon?
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
(loud chomping)
Oh, this is good.
(children laughing)
Are you sure
you want to do this?
I can't stop thinking
about her.
Even these gates remind me
of her braces.
BART: How are we gonna
find her?
MILHOUSE: She said she'd be
wearing a plaid jumper.
Milhouse!
Samantha!
I went to Circus of Values
and bought you a ten-gallon tub
of gummi bears.
(grunts)
Hey, Samantha,
I'm sorry about
getting you thrown
in the penguin house.
That's all right, Bart.
I love Saint Sebastian's.
It's run by a group of
French Canadian nuns.
They're very nice except
they never let me out.
♪♪ (singing "Dominique"
in French)
Samantha,
ne pas des boys.
(ringing)
I have to go now,
Milhouse.
I'd better not.
It's 50 rosaries
a kiss.
Oh, okay.
Oh, what the heck.
Bart, think I can ever find
another one like her?
You're asking
the wrong guy, Milhouse.
They all look alike to me.
Now, let's go whip donuts
at old people.
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.