-CHOIR: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
-Yee-haw!
(exclaiming)
(school bell ringing)
(Barney belches)
(whistle blows)
(yells)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
(gunfire)
(tires screeching)
-(horn honking)
-(Grampa shouts)
D'oh!
(tires screeching)
(grunts)
♪♪
(groans)
(cawing)
Ew.
(classical music playing)
BART: Dad, what are you watching?
I think it's a Terrence Malick movie.
No, you're watching Baby Poindexter,
the most educational DVD available
at the checkout aisle
at the grocery store.
Finally, a kid's show that isn't
trying to sell you something.
Which reminds me,
we need to order more rectangles.
FEMALE NARRATOR: Friends.
(bells jingling)
Friends.
Colleagues.
(gasps) Don't watch that DVD.
I threw that away because studies show
it doesn't do any good.
Look at me.
Maybe instead of watching TV
with the kids,
you could take them outside.
What are you doing?
This so-called educational DVD
may have even stunted
the development of the kids
who watched it.
Wait a minute.
Didn't Bart and I both watch this thing
when we were little?
I'm afraid so.
Well, the obvious question is,
why did I turn out
so academically superior
while Bart...
While Bart turned out
so wonderful in his own way.
That's the way people talk about Ralph.
Ralph, whose favorite color
is peanut butter.
I wish I knew what happened.
(horn honking)
(imitates honking horn)
But now that I know better,
no DVDs for you kids.
Just educational television.
NARRATOR:
We return to Ice-Road Hand-Fishing.
This has been our way of life
since we were pitched
the idea by reality show producers.
Welcome to Thieving-Bear Chopper-Hunt.
-Okay, no TV at all.
-ALL: What?
Honey, this sounds
like a noble experiment,
but like Prohibition,
it will end in a hail of bullets.
Fine. No TV for 24 hours.
24 hours?
Where'd you pull that crazy number?
We can do without TV for a day.
We're taking Maggie
to a children's book store,
where she can learn the old-fashioned way.
The way children did from 1910 to 2002.
(grunting)
Homer, a little help?
I'm on it.
Hmm. Hmm.
If I buy you,
why do I need all these books?
Shut up, shut up, shut up!
Instead of watching TV,
we can read children's books
written by TV stars.
Who's Milli Vanilli?
I don't know, kid. I didn't write this.
No refunds.
Look, Maggie, they have a story lady.
One day, Silly Sally said,
"Let's have a sloppy, gloppy supper."
First, they slurped their soup.
Slurp, slurp, slurp.
Then they chewed their bread.
Chew, chew, chew.
More soup?
Oh, I could slurp this soup forever.
Slurp, slurp...
Sorry, folks, she doesn't even work here.
(grunting)
HOMER: "Spot the hidden objects."
Boy, you're pretty pushy
for a book I just met.
Gotcha.
(laughing)
Candy cane in the umbrella stand:
oldest trick in the book.
Okay, let's see.
Ah, ah. (mutters)
Have you seen Lisa and Maggie?
If they're not a trumpet
or a rolling pin, then no.
Yip!
Homie, help me find them.
Okay, now to see if I can
apply my book knowledge
to the real world.
Got them.
Wow, no TV for 24 hours?
I couldn't get through a day without
Doctors Oz, Phil and Gupta.
You're right. I'm bored.
-Epoxy fight!
-(groans)
What the hell is an epoxy fight?
Oh.
Don't worry, I'll clean it up.
Get me some whip cream
and a safety scissors.
Don't worry, all I need
is a cigarette lighter
and some sandpaper.
(sanding)
All right, let's just use a razor.
(gasps)
Oh, my God.
You look just like your dad.
Let's see how far we can take this.
And finally the tie.
I always wanted to wear a necktie.
Mom says they make you more...
(in Kirk's voice) ...of a man.
Now sing the alphabet song.
(voice alternating with each letter)
♪ A-B-C-D-E-F-G ♪
♪ H-I-J-K-L-M-N-O... ♪
What if we Van Houten to the max?
(in Duffman's voice)
Whoa, that's a little too tight. Oh, yeah.
Nah, back to the sweet spot.
Milhouse,
if people believe you're a grown-up,
we can do anything.
(in Kirk's voice) Like we go to a movie
theater and pay full price?
That would be awesome!
Okay, first, tone it down.
Time to teach you to be a man.
What, now I'm not pulling it off?
("Here Comes Your Man" by Pixies playing)
♪ Here comes your man ♪
♪ Here comes
your man ♪
And put the gas bill on auto-pay.
Nice.
Time for your final test.
(Homer grunting)
(computer chiming)
Oh, great.
Another invasive Skype from Mil... Huh?
Hello, Lisa. This is my daddy.
I mean, um, Kirk Van Houten.
May I speak to your father, please?
He's right here.
Homer, Bart would like to spend
the night at our house,
and he has my permission.
Sure. What do I care?
-Not so fast!
-Huh?
I also want to say that
Bart is a remarkable boy,
and I disapprove of your fathering
and of your fat stomach.
Oh, well, uh... sorry.
Give him anything he wants--
bigger allowance, a new bike--
just do it.
Whatever you say, sir.
Dad, why are you kowtowing
to Mr. Van Houten?
Sometimes it's just so nice
to have a man take charge.
And in ten years, make Lisa
go to the prom with Milhouse.
Dad.
Grown-ups have their reasons.
(aggravated groan)
Now, I want you to eat
a gallon of ice cream
in under two minutes.
But I just did that.
You now have one minute, 55 seconds.
(Bart and Milhouse laugh)
I'm going to like being an adult. (laughs)
(groaning)
Now you're the same height as your dad.
(in normal voice)
I can reach the poisons now,
each with an inviting skull
and crossbones.
Kirk, you're wearing
that shirt I bought you.
I thought you didn't like it.
(in Kirk's voice)
I love when you buy me clothes.
You know what's itchy and what's not.
Oh, Kirk Evelyn Van Houten.
(humming happily)
(in regular voice)
I wish my dad
could have been here
to see my parents kiss.
Now, did you get Kirk's license?
-Uh-huh.
-Ay, caramba!
I rented a truck.
I'm driving a truck.
I crashed a truck.
I rented another truck.
Hey, Simpson, don't you have
a lame dad of your own?
(in Kirk's voice)
Uh, I-I'd give you all my money,
but my wallet is Velcroed too tight.
You're the wussiest adult I've ever seen.
An adult-- he's buying it.
Kirk, remember,
you have the superpowers
of a middle-aged man.
Hello, Mr. Kirk.
I want to buy this beer, uh, cigarettes,
magazines with boobs
and three pairs of sunglasses.
Polarized.
I suspect you are buying
for underage bullies,
but as that is 98% of my business,
I say, "Thank you, sir. Come again."
Yo, Bart.
Your grown-man friend is all right.
We should start threatening more adults.
Wouldn't that make us
criminals instead of bullies?
Let's beat up a philosopher
until he gives us the answer.
-Oh, good idea.
-Yeah, I'm in.
I made my mom happy
and got through the
bullies without a punch.
Being an adult is super easy.
Hmm, hmm... hmm.
-(pops)
-(chuckles)
You dope.
It says those are for her pleasure.
Now it's time for me to live my fantasy
with mature themes.
I'll go behind that curtain a boy
but come out a man.
Hmm, more money for schools.
That could translate into more homework.
I know this is highly illegal,
but you're not leaving
this booth till you punch yes.
Don't bother screaming for help.
This is a municipal off-cycle election.
There's no one for miles.
(wolf howling)
Don't forget your sticker.
(evil chuckling)
Uh, hey, bartender.
We'd like two milks,
and then you can tell us
where babies come from.
Oh, well, in my case,
my mom was hit with a voodoo curse.
I gestated for five years,
then I popped out backwards and on fire.
-Really?
-Oh, yeah, keep my tail
-right here in this jar.
-(both gasp)
Good times.
Mom, I think Maggie misses TV.
You know, Mom, I was thinking
we could take Maggie downtown.
The Jazz Hole is featuring
a Dizzy Gillespie tribute band.
(gasps) Their trumpeter
has the puffiest cheeks.
I don't think so.
The U.S. Embassy has warned people
not to go to downtown Springfield.
I get it. Middle child,
never do what I want.
Hmm.
Okay, I also know of a puppet show.
Long before the Teutonic slaughters
visited upon our people,
there was the massacre by Mstislov
of Kiev in 1132.
(screaming)
Maybe we should go.
Nobody leave till every puppet dead.
Bart, you wanted to show me something?
Just one sec. Nelson gave me
some notes on a prank I'm doing.
Now, I asked you here because
I know a cool grown-up
who will take you to that club
in the city.
Really? Who?
(in Kirk's voice)
Hello, Lisa.
Milhouse?
Milhouse? Who's Milhouse?
I mean, he-he's my son.
Well, Milhouse,
you might get past the bouncer
at the jazz club,
because they're in no position
to turn anyone away,
but it doesn't matter,
'cause we can't pay
for the gas
and the cover fee anyway.
Au contraire, starfish hair.
The Baby Poindexter Company
is being forced to pay
a settlement to any parent
who had enough misguided love
to buy their videos.
They're not gonna write a check
to a couple of kids.
Then I will be your guys' dad.
(screams)
Thanks, but lowering your voice
and standing on paint cans
doesn't make you man enough to be my dad.
HOMER: Marge, can I get a subscription
to Highlights magazine?
MARGE:
Homer, that's for children.
HOMER:
Where does it say that?
MARGE:
Read the rest of the title.
HOMER:
Highlightsfor... d'oh!
(Homer humming)
Oh, dang it.
I lost my other earring.
Leave it to me.
-Earring.
-Oh.
-Thimble from Monopoly game.
-Wondered where that was.
-$25 casino chip.
-Oh.
-The smallest nesting doll.
Can you find anything
you like in this bed?
Just my honey pie.
Want to split it while we snuggle?
Mm-hmm.
(Homer chewing loudly)
MARGE:
Now what are you doing?
HOMER:
Licking the wrapper.
There you go, one adult
and two children one-way downtown.
Um, as adults, what do we do now?
Shake hands?
If you like.
And that's how you do it. (chuckles)
Now, remember, I can't sit backwards
or I get sick.
Well, if I look at your face, I get sick.
Young man, apologize to your sister.
Make me, baldy.
Why, you little...
(grunting)
(in normal voice)
My adulthood!
(grunting)
I never thought I'd say this,
but that is conduct
unbecoming of a bus station.
Where'd your babies go?
Your intellect-deadening DVDs
turned my brother's brain to jelly.
Pretty shapes tell me to kill everybody.
Looks like you're entitled
to the full rebate of $19.95.
That's all you pay
for screwing up a child for life?
(in Kirk's voice)
Kids, let me handle this.
Uh, we'd like it in singles
and nickels, please.
Terrific. Just need your signature.
-In cursive?
-"X" is fine.
In cursive?
Oh, it's just enough to get home.
I'm hungry now.
Hey, I'm walking on paint cans all day.
Give me a break.
Guys, look, free breakfast
if we sit through a sales pitch.
Just remember, Milhouse,
do not buy the condo.
But what if we can't afford
not to buy it?
Waldo, Waldo, Waldo.
Homer, Bart said the kids were
going to the Van Houtens',
but Luann just told me
they're supposed to be here.
They've disappeared.
We'll get those kids back.
Because we just bought them new shoes.
Waldo, Waldo.
Do you think Lisa went to that jazz club
I wouldn't take her to?
How many kids will jazz corrupt?
(tires squealing)
...lap pool and fully-equipped gym
with eucalyptus towels.
Now, let me give you
the 14 different apartment configurations.
The hacienda,
the urban oasis,
castle in the sky,
Connecticut sunset...
Lady, my stomach's full,
and I want to go.
That's how it works in this country.
-(beeps)
-If you try to leave,
you'll find the doors are locked.
Well, before our dad signs any contracts,
he has a surprise for you.
Oh, I hope it's that he's single.
(laughs) I'm single.
Though, some days,
I have a girl buddy on field trips.
You're a bit of a freak.
I like that.
(giggling)
You're the adult.
-(grunts)
-(lock clicks)
LISA: Kirk, don't you have
something to tell her?
Just looking for a casual hookup?
Yeah, for my Thomas the Tank Engines.
Ooh, I love how I don't exactly understand
what you're saying.
Homie, do you see anything?
No. I'm sorry.
It's... Wait a minute.
When I said you needed a software update,
it was not a criticism.
We found what we're looking for.
The kids?
Sure, they could be here.
Who knows?
(tires squealing)
Ooh, I love how your arms
are too short and thin for your legs.
Just like a crocodile.
(in Duffman's voice)
I'm feeling a strange,
refreshing brew of emotions.
Oh, yeah.
-(grunts)
-Milhouse?
(in normal voice)
How'd you know it was me?
The top of your head has a 5:00 shadow.
(gasp) Your hair is growing back.
Tell me your secret.
He's ten years old.
Oh, there's always a catch.
Is anyone here going to buy a condo?
It's gonna be yes, but don't rush me.
And worst of all, you cast my vote.
Who did you vote for
in the nonpartisan judicial election?
Williamson.
No, no, no.
I'm really sorry, Dad,
but I have to say,
it was pretty cool having your life.
You mean that?
I'd be happy to wind up
just like you.
I hope you remember that
when I can't pay for your college.
Now, how would you like to go
to your own parent-teacher interview
while I see a movie?
I'd like that.
Son, promise you will never look like me.
I sure hope not.
Why, you little...
That's not a heart-warming
thing to end on!
♪ Here comes your man ♪
-(murmuring)
-Shh!
Subtitled by A. Vandelay