CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
NELSON:
Haw-haw!
D'oh!
(tires screeching)
(grunts)
(gentle lullaby version of
"The Simpsons Theme" playing)
(sucking)
(humming)
(screaming)
♪ ♪
NARRATOR:
It was the biggest scandal
in the history
of Springfield sports.
Never has someone fallen from
such heights to such lows,
except maybe for that
tightrope walker who sneezed.
That was terrible.
This situation
is a disgusting mockery
of a repulsive joke that would
make me sick to my stomach
if there was there was one good restaurant
in this town,
which there is not!
(stammers)
There is nothing to vomit.
NARRATOR: And all because
of one young man.
Okay, so I shaved points
in basketball.
Just don't make
a big production of it.
NARRATOR:
This is 22 for 30.
(dramatic orchestral music)
My son is a handful.
Can you say that on TV?
No one ever thought he'd work
for gamblers with the mob.
I always thought he'd work
In the morning,
we saw the horrors
of the beaches at Iwo Jima.
DIRECTOR:
This is a sports documentary.
I'm getting there!
In my unit, they called me
"Quarterback."
Because when I borrowed a quarter,
I never gave it back.
At the end of the war,
I had a buck 75, and no friends.
(distorted) I remember it
like it was yesterday.
Or maybe the day before that.
It all started with a prank.
Bart had no idea
where it would lead.
This voice is scaring me.
I need Puppy Goo-Goo!
(normal voice)
Safety kiss!
I think I'll be okay.
(distorted)
I love you.
(distorted scream)
Yeah, so here was the quote,
unquote "prank."
Bart sent out a memo telling
everyone to wear white
for some nonsense called
Polar Bear Remembrance Day.
(chuckles) Yes.
Then the little dickens
sent Skinner
a different memo
telling him to wear
a floral shirt in honor
of King Kamehameha's birthday.
(stammers)
Had it ended there, fine.
Pleasant conclusion
to a busy week.
But it didn't end there.
Now, don't worry,
all the bees want are flowers.
(bees buzzing)
Willie, kill the bees!
Not till I hear their side of it.
NARRATOR: Bart received
the longest detention in history.
Bored, he began to shoot baskets,
a talent that would irrevocably
make his life better.
Then worse, then better,
then the same.
♪ Wish I had a rabbit
in a hat with a bat ♪
♪ And a '64 Impala ♪
♪ I wish I was, like,
six-foot-nine ♪
♪ So I can get with Leoshi,
'cause she don't know me ♪
♪ But, yo, she's really fine ♪
♪ You know I see her
all the time ♪
♪ Everywhere I go,
and even in my dreams ♪
♪ I can scheme up ways
to make her mine ♪
♪ 'Cause I know
she's livin' phat ♪
♪ Her boyfriend's tall
and he plays ball ♪
♪ So how am I gonna
compete with that? ♪
A troubled young man
who was good at basketball.
I'd never heard of such a thing.
Of course, his detention
was commuted,
and he was made
a starter on the team.
That's my son! My son!
Which is, of course,
another version of me!
(crowd cheering)
Him! Me! Us! Me!
NARRATOR: Everywhere Bart went,
he was given star treatment.
At school...
(grunts)
...at the public pool...
(Bart laughing)
(Bart grunts)
It's really not
that dangerous.
(laughing)
NARRATOR:
...with local merchants.
Oh, young basketball star,
I have something
special for you.
The new 7,200-ounce Squishy.
NARRATOR: But not everyone was
celebrating the Bart-mitzvah.
I got an assignment:
write an article
on the school's new hero,
Bart Simpson.
(sighs) This is worse than
when we were square-dance
partners in gym.
♪ Grab your partner
nice and slow ♪
♪ Allemande left and ♪
(slows, distorts)
♪ Do-si-doh ♪
♪ That's the last time
I had work ♪
♪ Now I'm just a homeless jerk ♪
♪ Allemande left and prance to the right ♪
(cat yowls)
♪ I need a place
to spend the night ♪
NARRATOR:
Springfield had never won
a championship in any sport.
The only banner on the gym wall
was one that came
with the building.
But now, there was a shot.
I was so proud of Bart,
I did anything I could
to help him practice.
Mm!
But then it happened.
Fame went to Bart's head.
Just once, I'd like to see
science go to his head.
He's got more D's
than Dolly Parton!
I'm not sure what that means,
but please use the joke.
I paid someone 25 bucks for it.
(music playing over earbuds)
Bart Simpson,
can ya please join the team?
Man, I am the team.
Aw, that tears it!
I'm not coaching anymore!
I'm going back
to what I love doing:
drowning gophers.
(whistling)
Aah! What was that for?!
Our new coach will be
parent-volunteer
and Bart owner, Homer Simpson.
(reporters gasp)
Do you know anything
about basketball?
Why the change?
What is your basketball
philosophy?
Shower at home so no one
makes fun of your weenie.
I learned that from
the late great Red Auerbach.
No more questions!
D'oh!
What the hell is that thing
doing in a gym?!
Your new coach, everybody!
Bart got a coach
who would kiss his butt
like one cheek was Kobe
and the other Kareem.
Well, there is no "I" in "team."
There's no "U" in "effort."
There's no "X" in "dog"!
What do Oscar the Grouch's
feet look like?
Nobody knows!
I have a TV for Bart Simpson.
(sighs)
Just put it with the others.
I'm worried he's getting
a little spoiled.
HOMER:
Oh, that's ridiculous.
Excuse me, sir.
Bart says no unauthorized
photography.
Don't look directly at him!
(Taser zapping)
♪ ♪
NARRATOR:
As Bart's showboating veered
ever closer to globetrotting,
the disrespect grew.
Can you clean that for me, Coach?
And that, and that, and those,
and that, and that.
What are you looking at?
HOMER:
What the...?!
NARRATOR: But after one
showboat shot too many,
Homer Simpson had something
he'd never had before: enough.
Uh, son, some of the other
parents are complaining.
Apparently, they're attached
to their children,
and they want to see
them touch the ball.
They can touch it
in the team photo.
I'm going to draw up a play.
One where you pass.
Why don't you pass a physical,
you boozy bag of goo?
Marge is right.
You're getting spoiled!
Before you strangle me, maybe
you should check the scoreboard.
I'm your dad
and your coach.
And because no one else
would, your godfather.
So hit the bench!
NARRATOR:
When we return, the interesting part.
From now on, you're going
to be a team player,
no more important
than anyone.
Except Milhouse.
I'm on the team
'cause it's my ball.
NARRATOR: Certain people
had begun to notice
Bart's unhappiness.
People with criminal backgrounds.
They had more records
than Dolly Parton.
Man, that is a joke
that keeps on giving.
This is gonna
break my heart, but...
(groans)
Yeah, the kid was ripe
for criminal exploitation.
And in this town,
the other cops are pathetic.
Fat, lazy.
You want to find one?
Just follow the sound
of a milkshake being sucked.
(slurping)
There's no belt that fits me.
I'm wearing police tape
around my waist.
I saw the kid was upset,
so I took him for cannoli.
That's not a crime.
(whispers)
You don't know what a crime is.
Not that I'd know
what a crime is.
(whispers indistinctly)
What's with all
the psst-psst-psst?
Have you sprung a leak,
or do you want to?
(whispers) I don't think
that's advisable to say that.
I've been told
I was just kidding.
Fat Tony, enjoy this-a
cannoli on-a the house.
It's like eating the
bone-a marrow of an angel.
Mwah! Mwah! Mwah!
NARRATOR: They talked about
life and basketball,
a game Fat Tony
had always loved.
Basketball is just like life.
It's filled with a court, shooting,
and guards.
(whispers indistinctly)
Basketball is nothing like life.
NARRATOR: Fat Tony saw
an opening, and he took it.
FAT TONY:
BART:
BOTH:
NARRATOR:
And at his next game,
Bart did a very odd thing.
DREDERICK TATUM: And with Springfield
up by a meager one point,
star guard Bart Simpson
is just dribbling,
he's not shooting,
with two minutes to go.
♪ ♪
I don't know how,
but Homer gained 12 pounds
chewing towels.
I put jelly on 'em.
(whistle blows)
Time expired!
Bart didn't know it,
but he was point shaving.
That's when a player
wins the game,
but makes sure his team
doesn't cover the spread.
The team's happy, the gamblers
are happy, everybody wins.
The only unhappy person
is someone like me,
who has to explain the thing.
Well, at least you'll let me
play my saxophone.
(inhales deeply)
Good thing you cut that song.
Did you know I once took a train
halfway across Cleveland?
NARRATOR:
This is not a video trick.
He really just stopped moving,
but Bart had just gotten started.
♪ ♪
You could be an accessory
to a crime, you know.
Are you letting
your anger at Dad
make you into
a patsy for the mob?
Hey, Bart Simpson
is nobody's patsy.
Hey, Bart, Fat Tony says to win
by less than six points.
Here's a list of acceptable
point differentials.
It could be five, four, three...
You realize you're
having this conversation
in front of a reporter.
Hey, I don't see no reporter.
I see a little girl with
futile dreams of fitting in.
Gee whiz, you don't
have to be so mean.
That's the business I'm in!
Whoa! Hey!
(calliope music playing)
Shoot! Shoot!
Just like I drew it up!
Okay, here's a shot:
you're not bald, your hair left
out of embarrassment.
-Why, you little...!
-(choking)
(crowd gasps)
(crowd cheers)
(buzzer blares)
I'll teach you
to win the game!
You stupid buzzer-beating,
clutch-shooting...
Oh, come on, man.
-...ice water in your veins...
-I'm taking my talents to Shelbyville.
...here comes
the post-game interview!
This is the first thing you've done
as a coach.
You have to give them credit!
They played hard!
-People are gonna hear about this, Dad.
-I'm so proud of these boys,
-and especially our sixth man...
-You're still nicer than Bobby Knight.
...the fans!
All right, let me hear your side.
Sorry, my side
is exclusive to my charity,
The American Fart Association.
Why, you little...!
(grunting)
(laughing)
Checkmate.
(laughs)
D'oh!
NARRATOR: But the boy who could
spin a ball with his doodle
was about to learn
a very tough lesson.
BART:
FAT TONY:
NARRATOR: Fat Tony denied
he'd made any money,
but this FBI footage
suggests otherwise.
I thought I was just
keeping the score down
to get back at my Dad,
but Fat Tony was betting
against us, every game.
I was a patsy.
Ow! She didn't mean that.
D'oh! Ow! Ow!
I was scared. Milhouse scared.
Why do you keep cutting to me?
And then it got worse.
Fat Tony told me to lose the finals.
Not win by a little, but lose... or else.
"Or else"?
My client does not
speak like that.
Yeah, now drop the subject,
or else.
Edit that out, or else.
I-I'm gonna stop talking...
or else.
Damn it.
NARRATOR:
What did Fat Tony say to Bart?
His capo, Johnny Tightlips,
refused to talk.
Anyone here own a black
Lincoln Continental,
license plate,
"Zero to Say"?
It's being towed.
Sir, you're the only one here.
I saw you get out of it.
Yeah, maybe it is.
Maybe I am.
Maybe you did.
Or maybe it's not.
And I'm not, and you didn't.
But you didn't hear this, that,
or the other thing.
Or maybe you did.
Hey! My granny's in there!
Shaving points was one thing,
but he wanted me to lose.
I let down my team.
I let down my town.
So, I guess this is where
I break down and cry.
(crying)
Hey, I'm the one
who's supposed to cry.
No. This is my story.
-Tighten on me.
Fine. Tighten on him
then rack focus to me.
Dad, this is supposed to be
about us getting together.
Fine. Tighten on him.
Rack focus to me.
Cut to a wide shot.
Split screen with Marge.
Truck in, nice and slow.
Then cut to a "B" roll of me
eating a tuna fish sandwich.
Dad, how did you
learn these things?
Son, show business
is everybody's business.
Dutch angle, photo negative
and freeze!
I'm a excommation point!
In the gym that night, you could
cut the tension with a knife,
but, uh, we don't allow
knives in school,
not even in metaphors.
♪ We got to fight
the powers that be ♪
♪ Fight the power ♪
(crowd cheering)
ANGER WATKINS:
Another bucket by Bart Simpson!
His sloppy play
is a distant memory,
like Nelson's father.
Yeah, interesting
side note:
Nelson left a ticket for his
father in case he showed up.
And he did show up,
but then he sold the ticket
without seeing Nelson,
and he skipped town again.
You believe that?
Rejected!
Like I've been rejected.
Nothing but net!
Which is what my mom
wears in the strip club.
It was in the third quarter
when the game really got weird,
and I got a low bar for weird.
(grunts)
Bart went to shoot,
and took a hard foul
from his own best friend.
♪ ♪
Let's just say Bart wasn't the only one
Fat Tony had gotten to.
This was my bobblehead.
They got to him, in my bedroom,
where he bobbled.
Hey, let's just say
that bobblehead
won't be attending
no more giveaway days.
You keep shooting your mouth,
you'll wind up in that building
going up on Third Street.
It's a Third Street address,
but actually you enter on Lincoln.
Yet another secret revealed!
I'm sorry, Dad.
I was a jerk.
The good thing
about being a kid
is you get to make mistakes so
you don't make them as an adult.
Thanks, Dad.
But don't you still
make mistakes?
The best one was you, son. Aw.
Now go win that game!
NARRATOR:
And win he did.
He blew our net budget
for the next ten years.
(buzzer blares)
NARRATOR:
But not everyone was cheering.
Is he going for a gun?
(sighs)
Oh.
-Get me a gun.
-(screams)
We thought we
were goners.
Our lives flashed
before our eyes.
I had a lot of crazy jobs.
And then the cavalry came
on her stupid high horse.
LISA:
Let them go.
Really? And what
do you have on me?
The goods.
The goods?
Oh, that sounds bad.
Fat Tony, may I speak
to you in Italian?
I don't know Italian.
How about Sicilian?
That's a language?
How about I say it
like Porky Pig?
E-ba-dee, e-ba-dee, e-ba-dee,
e-ba-dee, e-ba-dee...
Say what you got to say.
Turns out I'm the hero
of this documentary.
I think that deserves a chyron.
It happens that
Fat Tony had a secret,
a secret I had uncovered
with a little bit of research.
I wondered,
if Fat Tony liked basketball so much,
why didn't he play?
Turns out he had.
For a girls' team.
And if there's one thing
a Mafia boss doesn't want known,
it's that he was
the third-string shooting guard
on the Springfield Little Debbies.
You keep quiet
about what you know.
All of you keep quiet!
Keep quiet about what, boss?
The man-Spanx you wear?
Your high school nickname,
Robert DeZero?
The way you cried
at Toy Story 2?
That's not even the sad one.
What? What?
Why do you keep talking?
I'm sorry.
It's a nervous condition.
Can you give me the name
of that secret shrink you see?
So, we made a deal.
I'd forget if Fat Tony forgave.
But now the secret's out.
It's in a documentary.
No one watches those,
unless it's a documentary
where a rich guy kills people
and no one knows about it.
As far as you know.
(chuckles)
BURNS:
I'm guilty, guilty, guilty.
SMITHERS:
Sir, you know you're on mic.
BURNS: Who is this Mike
you're speaking of?
We'll kill him, too!
NARRATOR: But all sports stories
have an upside,
unless you're
a Detroit Lions fan.
So this young man,
showboat and friend of the mob,
gets off with not even
a slap on the wrist.
It's a travesty
wrapped in outrage,
marinated in a sauce
of everything's gone to hell!
I admit, it was fun.
For a short time,
we had our own little superstar.
And he kept playing.
Then he ran up
against one tall kid,
and found out
he really wasn't that good.
But Lisa, Lisa had a real
talent for journalism.
Whatever that gets us.
Homer, we have to end
on something sweet.
(lovingly)
Whatever that gets us.
-♪ Now basketball is my favorite sport ♪
-♪ Uh-huh ♪
♪ I like the way they dribble
up and down the court ♪
-♪ Come On ♪
-(whistle blows)
♪ I keep it so fresh
on the microphone ♪
♪ I like no interruption
when the game is on ♪
♪ Game's on ♪
♪ I like slam dunks
that take me to the hoop ♪
Sorry, y'all.
♪ I like the pick-and-roll,
I like the give-and-go ♪
♪ And it's basketball,
Bow Wow, let's go... ♪
Yeah. Nothing but nerd.
♪ All around the world ♪
-♪ We love that basketball ♪
-♪ Yeah... ♪
No, I didn't!
♪ Basketball... ♪
I admit it, I was a total boob.
Oh! Why do I keep going there?
-♪ Let's go ♪
-♪ They're playing basketball ♪
♪ All around the world ♪
♪ We love that basketball... ♪
NARRATOR:
And Nelson's dad came back.
And I should know.
He's me.
Haw-haw!
(gasps) Papa!
(crying)
So, you're making narrator money.
That's right,
and I brought Nelson a gift.
Sleeves for my vest!
Son, you look just like
a parole officer.
NARRATOR:
And so we were a family again,
just long enough
to take this picture.
Shh!
Subtitled by Jimmy Boots