CHORUS SINGS:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
Aah!
(school bell ringing)
(burps)
(whistle blows)
(yells)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
(grunts)
Whoa.
(gunfire)
(tires screeching)
(horn honking, Grampa shouts)
D’oh!
-(tires screeching)
-D’oh!
(grunts)
ALL:
Hmm?
Aha!
(Simpsons panting)
(squeaking)
Hmm.
(gasps)
(Lisa screams, Bart cheers)
(grunts)
(groans)
(squeaking)
Hmm.
(glass shatters,
electrical crackling)
(humming)
(grunting)
Yes!
(laughter)
Oh, Marge,
how did you ever come up
with an idea
like "crazy bowling"?
I Googled "girls having fun,"
and after wading through
97,000 pages of porn,
I found "crazy bowling."
Hmm, that’s odd.
There isn’t a single man in
this whole bowling alley.
(gibbering)
...the pin!
(meows)
It’s pretty sad
when I can’t pick up a guy
on Super Nacho Tuesday.
Where’d they all go?
Oh, you know men-- probably
at a baseball game or a bar.
(wind whistling,
crickets chirping)
♪ They did the monster ma... ♪
(skipping):
(cheering)
Come on, you pansies!
I’ve seen fiercer fights
in Parliament!
Yes, what is this, Prime
Minister’s Question Time?
Yeah, is it that?
(Willie and Mel grunt)
(all cheering)
(cheering)
(groans)
(both grunt)
(laughs)
(all grunt)
(both grunting)
(bones crunch, man screams)
(crowd cheering)
Whoo-hoo!
There’s no better violence
than self-inflicted violence.
Ow!
(groans)
Thanks for bringing
me here, Dad.
I’ll remember this
day on my deathbed.
(both sigh happily)
Not everyone has
a deathbed, son.
You could die suddenly.
Wow. Maybe some punk kid will
shoot me to get into a gang.
Maybe.
Three hours of half-naked guys
fighting like animals.
Just like the
ancient Romans.
Yeah, except their empire
was falling apart.
(laughs)
Stupid Romans.
Ask him.
Sir, could you sign my program
with a swear word?
Uh, yes,
filthy but obscure with a subtle
scatological undertone.
Sure, no problem.
$25, please.
Pay the man, boy.
(grumbling)
Now, listen, son,
I know we saw some awesome
beat-downs tonight,
but remember:
don’t try this at home.
Do it at the schoolyard.
Someplace where, if you get
hurt, we can sue not just them
but the school,
the county, the state,
and that jackass
Joe Biden.
(cheering)
Python neck clinch
and... out.
Maybe I was promoted to
green belt too early.
Next victim.
Ding, ding, ding!
Here we go.
(horn honks)
Where’s your brother?
I don’t know,
chasing ducks, buried alive?
He’ll be missed.
Let’s move;
I got to collect pine cones.
KIDS (chanting):
Die, die, die!
-Just follow
the dies, Mom.
-(groans)
(kids cheering)
(gasps)
(sobbing):
Why me?
Why me?!
Bart Simpson!
I’m glad your father
isn’t here to see this.
ALL:
Kill, kill, kill, kill!
HOMER (alone):
Kill, kill, kill, kill, kill,
(whispering):
kill, kill, kill...
Bart, let him go.
But Mom, I’m winning.
Look at this--
his lunch money.
God didn’t give you legs so
you could use them as scissors.
Well,
I was just doing the moves
I learned
from Ultimate Punching.
(gasps)
Ultimate Punching?!
"Ultimate" makes
everything worse.
Not Frisbee.
Otto, don’t you have
a sack to hacky?
Indeed I do.
One...
Aw, I messed up.
Aw, I messed up!
Okay, I’m going to put a stop
to this Ultimate Punching.
You can’t stop
an entire sport.
You’d need
several other mothers,
some sympathetic school
officials and clergymen...
-Uh-huh.
-A place to meet...
-Some snacks...
-What else?
-A phone tree is invaluable.
How you fixed for staplers?
Those fliers don’t stick
to phone poles by
themselves, you know.
Nelson, you really have
a knack for this.
Well, when I grow up,
I hope to go into
event planning.
Oh, maybe someday
you can do Lisa’s wedding.
Oh, I’d like that.
(crowd cheering,
whistling)
-Oh, my God.
-Ooh, so violent.
-Bumped his nose!
-Oh, he hit him.
(grunting)
This goes on for a while.
Call me a killjoy,
but I think that because
this is not to my taste,
no one else should be able
to enjoy it.
I’m all over that.
-(all agreeing)
-Mm-hmm!
Mom, don’t do this.
This sport is as fun for me
as having kids is for you.
Tell her, Dad.
You love Ultimate Punching
even more than I do.
Ultimate Punching is
exploitative, violent,
and a bad influence
on our young people.
Studies have shown
your mother is right.
What the...?
(sniffs)
Chocolate,
whipped cream, cherries--
she got to you
with a piece
of Black Forest cake.
It wasn’t just a piece,
it was the whole cake!
(sobbing):
Frosting like snow
on the eaves of a
Bavarian castle!
(sobbing)
Glad you didn’t come cheap.
I couldn’t help it!
She knew my one
weakness-- that I’m weak!
WOMEN (chanting):
One, two, we say boo!
Three, four, stop the gore!
Five, six, who’s got tix?
Seven, eight,
use that gate.
(Homer and Bart giggling)
Ooh!
We need to take this
into the belly of the beast.
Mr. Scalper,
give me a ticket.
I am not a scalper.
I am a dude whose 200 friends
did not show up.
(annoyed grunt)
What do we do now?
Let’s talk about Marge
behind her back.
Have you ever noticed
how that baby of hers
never says a thing?
I think it saw
something awful.
-Me, too.
-That’s exactly
what it is.
-Oh, what else
could it be?
-Mm-mm-mm.
Hmm.
That woman has
natural breasts.
This can’t be good.
(gate rattling)
I’m Marge Simpson,
and I will not rest
until you tear down
this septagon.
CROWD:
What?! Boo!
Crazy dame.
Nobody tears down
the septagon.
Except for the arena crew
because Hufflesnuffs on Ice
needs the space
tomorrow.
Whoa, whoa, wait a minute,
I have a better idea.
Marge, I’m Chett Englebrecht,
UPKCC founder, commissioner,
and public face of the sport.
(roaring):
Yeah-ah!
(crowd roaring)
Pleased to meet you, Chett.
(all booing)
Guys, please.
When you yell like that,
no one can hear me.
(booing louder)
Chett, I’m here to ask
you one simple thing:
please go out of business
and donate all your profits
to charity.
ALL:
Boo!
At least in other sports,
they’re trying to put a
ball in a net or a zone,
but in this sport they don’t put
anything in anything,
and if they did,
I wouldn’t want to see it.
Hmm.
Okay, you win.
ALL:
What?!
Annoying lady,
you make a great point.
I am going to shut down
this sport.
-Really?
-If you meet me
in the septagon,
fight me, and beat me.
What?!
That’s crazy.
What’s wrong, Marge?
Do you have
to ask your husband?
(crowd laughing heartily)
-MAN: Good one!
-MAN 2: Zing!
(donkey brays)
That flattens my soda pop.
You’re on.
(crowd cheering)
What’d I miss?
Mmm, nothin’.
Mom, you can’t fight that guy.
Yeah, Marge, he’ll
knock your block off--
your beautiful block.
Thank you, Homie.
Listen, of all the crazy things
I’ve ever done,
this is the craziest,
and you’re doing it.
I can’t back out.
This is for a cause
that’s bigger than I am.
If Gandhi could go
without eating
for a whole three-hour movie,
I can do this.
Besides,
I’m a woman.
He’ll probably
go easy on me.
Or kick the crap out of you.
Watch your
language, moron.
Hmm?
(hard rock guitar riffs playing)
(laughing)
(grunts nervously)
If I’m going to open a can
of whup-tushy,
I’d better get in shape
with some rhythmic gymnastics.
-(classical piano playing)
-Ah!
Ah!
Aha!
♪ Ah-la! ♪
♪ La-la-la-la-la! ♪
Someone’s got
to stop her
from going through
with this fight.
This goes against every
feminist bone in my body,
but Dad, can’t you control
your woman?
How can I control her?
I have nothing
to withhold!
Oh, man, now she’s writing
cutesy things
with the ribbon.
(classical melody continues)
(sighs)
Ah-ah!
Homer, this is bad.
One unlucky punch
and Marge could be
bedridden for life.
Unable to move anything
but her left toe.
Yeah.
Oh, Marge, if only I knew
what these paintings meant.
(sobbing)
I know the woman I loved is
still in there somewhere,
behind all this nonsense.
We’ve gotta get Marge some
professional training.
Carl, do you know heavyweight
champ Drederick Tatum?
What? You think just
’cause I’m black
I know all other
black people?
Well, I, uh, uh...
Actually, Drederick and I
are very good friends.
We met through
Dr. Hibbert
at a party at Bleeding
Gums Murphy’s house.
Well, Marge, you have definitely
come to the right crib.
I’m always happy
to impart
my pugilistic prowess
to a punching parvenu.
Now, the first lesson will
be to work the tattoos.
Flaming skull.
Obama.
Scooby-Doo. Scooby-Doo.
Scooby-Doo.
Now, work
"The Lord’s Prayer."
I’m gonna order
some lion food.
Hello? Yeah,
how you doin’?
I’d like to order
two gazelles, an impala,
and throw in a couple
of wildebeests.
Oh, and a two-liter bottle
of diet cherry cola.
You just have
one-liter bottles?
Okay, cancel
the whole order.
The second element of mixed
martial arts is jujitsu,
in which we use an
opponent’s strength
against himself.
But I sneak some of my
strength in there, too.
(chuckles)
Now, attack me
with great anger!
(karate yell)
Surprising move!
(groans)
Next: Homer, hajime!
(karate yell)
Mmm? Hmm?
Now, we stick foot in mouth,
tie arms like pretzel,
and pop discs in spine
like bubble wrap.
(popping)
(chuckles)
Is he okay?
Oh, he feels no pain.
(muffled screams)
Sorry, my English
is not so good.
I mean, he feels
only pain.
(muffled screech)
(classical music plays)
Back when I wrestled at Yale,
I was in the lightest
weight category--
"ether weight."
Now, get ready to
face the wrath
of the "New Haven Nuisance!"
CHORUS:
♪ Boola Boola, Boola Boola ♪
♪ Boola Boola... ♪
(grunting)
(grunts, gasps)
Side-mount!
Takedown! Advantage!
Reversal! Reversal!
Clinch! Clinch, I say!
(sighing):
Listen,
I’m late
for a PTA meeting.
In order to save money,
the following presidents
will no longer be taught:
Buchanan, Fillmore,
Pierce, Bush, Bush--
could you please stop that?
Saratoga slam!
Aristotle’s dilemma!
Knickerbocker
knucklebreaker!
And so on.
(snoring)
Marge, I bet
we got ten minutes
till the kids wake up.
(both moaning)
-Marge! Marge! Marge!
-Huh?
(gasp, scream)
Tomorrow night your bedroom
will be the septagon.
Your sleeping pill
will be my punches.
By the way, what’s that book
you’re reading?
Eat, Pray, Love.
More like "Beat, Slay, Shove!"
The fireworks begin tomorrow!
(fireworks whistling, popping)
I said tomorrow!
No can do.
We’re out of fireworks.
Why’d you shoot ’em off now?
I have trouble concentrating.
I should be on antidepressants.
Ugh. Where was I?
"Beat, Slay, Shove."
Right-- "Beat, Slay, Shove!"
The fireworks start tomorrow!
(fireworks whistling, popping)
I found some more,
but that was it!
Mmm.
A lot of people think
bullies are born awesome,
but the fact is,
we have to train.
You don’t get garlic knots like
these unless you work the bag.
(whistling)
-(grunts)
-(groans)
-(giggles)
-Is there someone in there?
It’s my own fault.
I looked them in the eye when
I gave them my lunch money.
Someone should tell
your principal!
I’m well aware
of the situation.
(electric organ playing
melodramatic melody)
Mom,
I came here to tell you
it’s not too late
to back out.
I can’t back out,
because if I fight him
tomorrow,
it’ll be a less violent world
for you kids in the future.
There must be
a better way.
HOMER:
There certainly is!
Marge Simpson reporting
for duty!
(Marge-like murmuring)
Dad, I keep telling you,
that won’t work.
Let’s go, Marge.
My class reunion starts
in an hour.
Uh, Moe, I have
a confession to make.
I’m just Homer
dressed as Marge.
Yeah, but last year I took
Barney dressed as Marge.
Think how much better
they’ll think you look.
Mmm?
Well, you’d better
not leave me
and talk to your
old friends all night.
Keep talkin’ like that
and I’ll leave you
here right now!
(fanfare playing)
Krusty, I’m honored
you invited me tonight.
Yeah, I thought
a noisy public place
would be the best spot
to tell you
that I’ve been
dating your wife.
(gasps)
What?!
Also, could you tell her
I’m dumping her?
After 11 years,
the thrill is gone.
I... I... uh...
Marge, I tried my best to
talk you out of this.
But since you’re going through
with it, I beg you,
just stay out of his way
and don’t get hurt.
And, Mom, if you punch
him in the junk,
you’ll get no disrespect
from me.
Hey, Bart, did you know
that’s a haiku?
BART:
Huh?
(grunts)
-(bell clanging in arena)
-(groans)
(audience chattering)
Time to square off in the ring--
that is, The Septagon!
In this corner,
weighing in at...
Nobody needs to know that!
Skip ahead!
Stands the "Mom
I’d Like To Fight"--
Marge Simpson!
(cheering, applause,
whistling)
And four obtuse angles over,
weighing in at 115 pounds,
Chett Englebrecht!
CROWD (chanting):
Chett! Chett! Chett!
And, now... let’s begin
to rumba!
We’ve been ready for hours!
I had car trouble!
(clangs)
(cheering)
Don’t worry, Marge.
Don’t want to hurt you.
-(sighing) I knew it!
-Pow!
(groans)
That’s the first time I ever hit
a woman I didn’t love. Wow.
(groaning)
Nine... aah!
Come on! Come on!
Get back on your feet!
I believe in you!
I’m doin’ it, Moe!
Not you.
Oh, thank God.
The pressure’s off.
(panting)
I’ll save you,
Marge!
(groans)
(gagging)
(grunting)
Hit my Mom, will ya?
Well, I’m gonna knock you out
and moon your corpse.
-(crowd booing)
-Heck, I’ll fight anyone.
Except a man
my own size.
(whimpering)
(sighs, grunts)
(gasps)
Yeah!
(all cheering)
(grunting)
That’s... my... son.
(screeching)
(yelling, grunting)
Whoo-hoo!
(sighs)
(grunts)
(groans)
Tap out!
Don’t make me
break your arm!
Lady, why don’t you break out
the lipstick and kiss my ass?
There sure is a
lot o’ talkin’
for a professional fight.
Eh, that’s what you get
when you fight a woman.
Yap, yap, yap.
And they spend all day
eating bonbons
and watching
General Hospital.
Which, by the way,
has never been better.
Mmm! Mmm!
Okay, I give!
I give! I give!
You’re better
than me!
Really?
Ooh, thank you.
Now, let me go...
turn your back and take a bow.
Okeydoke.
(giggles)
(cheering, applause, whistling)
Thank you!
Mmm!
(gasps)
(groans)
(cheering)
I’d just like to say one thing.
I only agreed to this fight
because I wanted
to stop the violence.
And sure I got into great shape
and met some fun people,
but I ended up discovering
my own dark side.
So from now on,
the only thing I’m fighting is
this cold I’m coming down with.
(sneezing)
Mom, that’s
a beautiful thought.
Yeah, well,
I wish somebody would’ve
stuck around to hear it.
Where did they all go?
Two drunk guys were
fighting outside
and everyone went
to watch.
Ooh, ooh, can
I go, Marge?
Can I? Can I?
No. Let’s go home.
We can enjoy some mixed
"marital" arts.
Oh, no holds barred.
(both laugh)
-Hey, Lise...
-Yeah?
I don’t know when we’ll
be in a septagon again.
Want to settle
this bad blood
that’s been going on between us
since you were born?
You’re on.
(wailing rock chords
playing on electric guitar)
(both grunting)
-(grunts)
-(groans)
(satisfied snicker)
JAUNTY CHORUS:
♪ Boola Boola, Boola Boola ♪
♪ Boola Boola,
Boola Boola ♪
♪ When we’re through
with those poor fellows ♪
♪ They will holler Boola, Boo ♪
(lively
accordion interlude)
♪ Boola Boola, Boola Boola ♪
♪ Boola Boola,
Boola Boola ♪
♪ When we’re through with... ♪
Shh!
Enhanced by Fotokem