♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-(screams)
-(tires screech)
(printer whirs, beeps)
MAN:
May I offer my condolences
on the untimely passing
of your great Aunt Hortense.
As her only living heirs
you stand to inherit
her entire estate.
(crying)
Poor Aunt Hortense!
(cries)
(softly)
Whoo-hoo!
(crying)
The only stipulation
is that you spend one night
in a haunted house.
Oh. Isn't that somewhat unusual?
No. It's a standard clause.
Well, luckily,
there's no such thing as ghosts.
Yes, there's no
such thing as ghosts.
(all yawning)
Best night's sleep
I ever had.
Their tap water
tasted better
than ours.
Here you go.
$100 each.
The rest goes
to Ann Landers
as was stipulated
in your Aunt's will.
Hmm?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I must have
continued talking
after you left
the office.
I do that sometimes.
(diabolical laugh)
Oh, my!
What are you going to spend
your money on, kids?
There's a special on tacos
down at The Tacomat:
a hundred tacos for a hundred dollars.
I'm gonna get that.
I'm going to
contribute my money
to the Corporation
for Public Broadcasting.
Tacos?!
Public broadcasting?!
I won't have you kids throwing
your money away like that.
You're both coming downtown with me and
you're gonna put that money in the bank.
Boy, I sure could go for
100 tacos right about now.
No!
Yes, this should provide
adequate sustenance
for the Dr. Who marathon.
MARGE:
You'll feel better knowing
your money's in the hands
of professionals.
(muffled)
Ook Ook.
Are you folks ready
to go ape?
Mom?
A professional
in an ape mask
is still a professional.
And you'll find
that saving for your future
is far more thrilling
than any roller coaster.
Really? Wow! I should have
started a long time ago!
Mm-hmm. Now fill out
these forms.
I'm sure you'll find them
more exciting
than a weekend with Batman.
I got their new Thrifty
Saver savings account.
2.3% annual interest instead
of the normal 2.25.
So a year from now,
I'll have an extra nickel.
I got the account
where you get free
customized checks.
I chose the Hindenburg
flip-book series.
Cool!
Mmm. Checking accounts aren't
really for children, Bart.
No, Mom. I can handle it.
Let's see.
"Pay to the order of..."
Lisa-- one cent and no cents.
And now, the old John Hancock.
There you go.
Thank you.
MILHOUSE:
$1 million!
Thanks, Bart!
I owe you one.
That's a postdated
check remember.
Don't cash it till
the year 10,000.
Okay.
(watch ticks)
Excellent!
As soon as the check clears,
I'll let you go.
-Krusty!
That's it.
No more autographs.
I gotta go.
They're naming
a new sandwich after me
at my restaurant.
Oh!
That's okay, Bart.
You can share mine.
Quick-- press against me while
the ink's still wet.
No need. I'm going to
get Krusty's autograph
the easy way.
If he wants these 25 cents
he'll have to endorse the check
by signing it on the back.
Then, when my monthly
bank statement comes
I'll get the check back
complete with autograph.
No fuss, no muss.
That's a good plan,
but it won't impress
girls like this.
-Ew!
(laughing heartily)
Lisa's autograph...
Apu's autograph...
Oh, what do you know?
Jimbo's real name is Corky.
And...
Krusty!
Hey! "Cayman Islands
Offshore Holding Corporation"?
Krusty was supposed
to sign this.
Take it back
and make him sign it.
Ah, no, no.
Stamping the back
of a check
is perfectly legal,
little boy.
Many people do it
to save time.
You see, in this case,
instead of writing out his name
Krusty has stamped the name
of his Cayman Islands
Holding Corporation
on the... hmm.
Ah, excuse me a minute.
(chuckles)
Oh, I'm sorry.
I can't divulge information
about that customer's
secret illegal account.
Oh, crap. I shouldn't have
said he was a customer.
Oh, crap! I shouldn't have
said it was a secret.
Oh, crap!
I certainly shouldn't
have said it was illegal.
Ah. It's too hot today.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
I bought this popcorn
fair and square!
Sorry, the bank is...
Oh, kid!
Gosh, I meant to tell you.
Turns out that Krusty
is one of the biggest
tax cheats in history,
and they nailed him--
all thanks to you.
-(gasps)
-Some might say you're a hero, kid.
Not me, however.
I love Krusty.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Krusty the Clown...
was arrested today
for massive tax fraud.
Krusty's years of tax avoision
would never have cah--
Avoision? It's a crime.
Look it up.
-...would never have--
-VOICE (in headset): Evasion.
I don't say "evasion."
I say "avoision."
...would never have come
to light if not for
a crafty, little boy
named Bart Simpson.
Krusty's my hero.
How could I do this
to him?
It is a tragedy
for all us kids,
but, Bart, you can't
beat yourself up.
Yeah. There'll be
enough people
to do that for me
at recess tomorrow.
Oh, I can't go to jail!
I got a swanky lifestyle.
I'm used to the best.
Krusty, this is America.
We don't send our celebrities to jail.
We're just going
to garnish your salary.
Garnish my celery?
Please, Krusty, no jokes.
Who's joking?
Oy! Oh, I don't know
what you're saying.
It all sounds
so crazy to me.
It simply means we'll be
taking part of your salary
until your debt
is repaid.
Say, 75% for 40 years.
But I don't plan
to live that long.
Better make it 95%.
Ah... oh... oy!
The Internal Revenue Service
presents:
(chortling)
Hey, hey, kids!
Now, that the feds
are calling the shots,
this show's got to be
a lot more cost-effective.
So we had to cut down
on the frills
like sets, props, costumes
and Sideshow Mel.
But that doesn't mean
we can't have fun.
For example, I sure wish
somebody would give me
a banana cream pie.
Yeah!
Uh...
I guess we can't afford pies
right now.
Well, throw something!
(screams)
Oh, that corner...
(groaning)
Um, I'll have
four tax burgers,
one I.R.S.-wich,
withhold the lettuce
three dependent-sized sodas,
and a fico-ccino.
Fill out Schedule B.
You should receive
your burgers
in six to eight
weeks.
(mumbling)
Eh, let's see here...
Add Schedule B, divide 53...
take away...
Hey, Marge, what were your
gambling losses last year?
MARGE:
$700.
They took my money.
They wrecked my show.
They buried a bunch
of stinking veterans
in my family plot,
but at least I still got
my memories.
Those are locked up safe
in my fabulous mansion.
And now, lot number 66,
a handmade leather suitcase
carried by the Krustofsky family
upon their arrival
at Ellis Island in 1902.
A priceless heirloom
and historic piece of Krustiana.
What am I bid?
40 cents.
I got 40 cents.
40 cents over there,
40 cents over here.
Who'll give me 50?
Do I hear 50, 50?
Sold for 40 cents.
40 cents?
Ach! My Grampa Zev
would turn over in his grave
if it wasn't filled
with some veteran.
Lot 67,
32 cartons of pornography.
-Ten cents.
-12!
12 cents to our phone bidder
in Japan.
-Any advance?
-All I brought is a dime.
I didn't know
there would be pornography.
Sold for 12 cents.
Oh, my beloved pornography.
I can't watch this anymore.
I'm going to bed.
How much for Krusty's bed?
-Half a buck!
-Sold!
Goodnight, everybody.
ALL:
Good night, Moe!
(groaning)
And now, lot number 2,380,
Krusty's private plane,
The I'm On A Rolla Gay.
KRUSTY:
But I love that plane.
I used to fly to Vegas
in it with Dean Martin.
One night, he looked out
the window,
and the moon hit his eye
like a big pizza pie.
We wrote a song about it,
but it ended up infringing
on one he recorded years before.
Hey Selma, that plane
would go great
with your
new suitcase.
Nah, I just bought it
to soak my feet in.
(moaning)
Krusty. Hi.
Is it okay
if I sit down here?
Go ahead, kid.
Knock yourself out.
I'm sorry
for all the trouble
I've caused you, Krusty.
But, you know,
my Mom says
God never closes a door
without opening a window.
No offense, kid,
but your Mom's a dingbat.
There's no
silver lining here.
I was a big cheese.
A huge cheese!
But now look at me.
I got to ride the bus
like a schnook!
I got to live in
an apartment like an idiot!
I got to wait in line
with nobodies
to buy groceries
from a failure!
It doesn't matter how you live
or what you did wrong.
As long as you're on TV,
people will respect you.
Respect? Bah!
What good is respect
without the moolah
to back it up?
Everywhere I go,
I see teachers in Ferraris,
research scientists
drinking champagne.
I tried to drink a Coke
on the bus
and they took away my pass!
That's no life
for a famous clown.
Well, if it'll make you
feel any better, Krusty,
you can punch me in the face.
Nah, forget it!
Go home, kid.
-(buzzing in distance)
-(bell dings)
Shiva H. Vishnu!
Where is that noise
coming from?
(Krusty bawling)
Well, I must say I've had
a lovely evening, Agnes.
I don't suppose
I could come in
for a cup of...
Seymour!
Mother...
(gasps)
Superintendent
Chalmers!
Skinner!
What I wouldn't give
for something to interrupt
this awkward moment.
(Krusty bawling)
That will do nicely.
(bawling continues)
You got to hand it to Krusty.
Yeah, even with all his problems
he's still willing to do
something unbelievably dangerous
just to entertain his fans.
-Wow!
Oh, that's my Krusty.
I got a feeling
he'll be all right.
Oh, my God!
Krusty's shoes!
Okay, folks,
show's over.
Nothing to see here.
Show's...
Oh, my God!
A horrible plane crash!
Hey, everybody, get a load
of this flaming wreckage!
Come on,
crowd around.
Crowd around. Don't be shy.
Crowd around.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Krusty the Clown...
is dead.
(all gasp)
I can't believe Krusty
is really gone.
Don't worry, son.
I'm sure he's up
in heaven right now
laughing it up with all
the other celebrities.
John Dillinger, Ty Cobb,
Joseph Stalin...
(sighs)
I wish I were dead.
We're gathered to mourn
the passing
of Herschel Shmoikel Krustofsky
beloved entertainer
and dear friend.
Hello, I'm Troy McClure.
You might remember me from such
show business funerals
as "Andre the Giant:
We Hardly Knew Ye"
and "Shemp Howard:
Today We Mourn a Stooge."
Now, Krusty's closest friend
and sidekick,
Sideshow Mel.
I'll miss you, Krusty
I, and all the other
sideshows...
except Sideshow Bob.
But in the midst
of our sorrow
we can take comfort
in the fact
that your elevated
blood alcohol level
probably helped you
burn up quicker.
Since you left us
no earthly remains,
it is my sad duty to unveil
this simple memorial.
Next in our cavalcade
of celebrity mourners...
Bob Newhart.
(clearing throat)
See, to tell you
the truth, um...
I was-- I'm just
killing time here.
I was waiting
for a...
well, a different--
different funeral
to start.
I'll handle it.
Bob Newhart, everybody!
(applause)
Oh, um...
(coughs)
Although, you know,
though I-I started my career
several years before,
uh, Krusty,
so, you know, I could never
really learn
anything directly from him--
Uh, still...
I think in a way,
in a very meaningful way,
that I, uh...
uh... all of us...
have, uh, have learned
from him.
You know, that is, by...
uh, by being a clown
on television for...
for... for so many years
even, even though
many of us, we-- we didn't--
we didn't watch his show.
-(clearing throat)
-(feedback squeals)
Th-thank you.
-(scattered applause)
-(sniffles)
Well, that's the funeral, folks.
We'll be sitting Shiva
at the Friar's Club
at 7 p.m. and again at 10.
You must be over 18
for the 10.
It gets a little blue.
And so Herschel Krustofsky
is gone, but not forgotten.
Today was the unveiling
of the new Krusty stamp.
Postal patrons
were asked to choose
between two competing designs:
one of Krusty's
heartwarming smile
and one of his fiery death.
By a nearly two-to-one vote,
the smiling Krusty was chosen.
(mechanical groaning)
(groaning continues)
Don't let Krusty's death
get you down, boy.
People die all the time.
Just like that.
Why, you could
wake up dead tomorrow.
Well, good night.
(switch clicks)
(gasps)
Krusty!
(humming)
Mom! I just saw Krusty!
Yes, dear, in your mind.
No, on the street.
On the street in your mind.
Why won't you believe me?
Sweetheart, maybe
you just want Krusty
to be alive so badly,
you think you see him everywhere.
I went through the same thing
when Lyndon Johnson died.
DR. HIBBERT: And these pills
will help with the queasiness.
Krusty?
Doctor Hibbert,
Who was that man?
Now Bart, telling you
would violate
the patient-doctor
privilege,
just as if
I were to tell you
that Jasper here has
five seconds to live.
What'd he say?
He said I'm next.
Am I going crazy?
I'm seeing Krusty everywhere.
Bart, you're seeing Krusty
everywhere because you want
to tell him you're sorry
for causing his death.
Would it help if I told you
you're not responsible for Krusty's death?
Yes. Yes, it would.
Well, I can't. You'll just have to learn
to live with your mental problem.
Wait a minute--
all those things I saw.
There's a connection.
The truck full
of nets and buckets...
the queasy guy...
the lobsters...
they all point
to one thing.
Follow me.
Arr, I've got some customers.
Call me back, Ishmael.
Ahoy there, minnows.
Ahoy, have you
seen this man?
Arr, that's Handsome Pete.
He dances for nickels.
Pete, ye got
some customers.
(playing "Sailor's Hornpipe")
No, we're looking
for this man,
Krusty the Clown.
Mmm. Narr, narr, narr.
It's hopeless, Bart.
We've searched up and down
these docks, from pier one
to that Pier 1
by pier 17.
Lisa, look.
A signature with stars
around it, just like Krusty's.
Rory B. Bellows.
Slip 8. Let's go.
(playing "Sailor's Hornpipe")
Not a quarter.
Darr,
he'll be dancing for hours.
Are you Rory B. Bellows?
Yes.
How about Krusty
the Clown?
Sorry, I don't do impressions.
Well, if you're not Krusty,
how come you have
the exact same signature as him?
I'm Rory Bellows,
I tell you
and I got a lot
of corroborating evidence
over... here
by the throttle!
(chuckling)
Oh... you know you two could
have said something
instead of letting me
make an ass of myself.
Hey, you got a pacemaker scar
just like Krusty.
And Krusty's superfluous
third nipple.
(groaning)
Can't you see I don't want
to be Krusty anymore?
That's why
I faked my death.
But we saw your plane crash.
Yeah, but I wasn't in it.
Just before I hit the mountain
I jumped out of the plane
into a carefully placed net.
(groaning)
So now that we've blown
your cover,
I guess you gotta come back
and do your show again.
Or kill us...
(nervous giggling)
I won't be coming back, kids.
I got a sweet life here.
The sea air
is clearing my lungs.
The sun is toasting my
pale skin a healthy brown,
and most important, I learned
that I don't need money
to be happy.
All that high living
just distracted me
from my true calling in life:
salvaging sunken barges
for scrap iron.
Sorry kids, there's nothing
left for me on dry land anymore.
But Krusty, what about all the kids
who depend on you
to brighten up
their afternoons?
Are you gonna turn
your back on them?
Yes!
Come on, Lis,
Krusty doesn't want our
attention anymore.
Let's go worship
somebody who has
the guts to be
a celebrity.
Yeah, Krusty doesn't
want to be a clown.
He's happy just being
another blue-collar Bozo.
Meh.
Krusty's tired
of having phonies around
pretending
to be his friends.
I'm sure he'll find
plenty of people
who'll like him
for who he is.
Uh... it could happen.
Nah, who needs friends?
The incessant beep of
the global positioning system
is all the companionship
I need.
-(chuckling)
-(beeping)
(screams)
Tell me where you are now,
you bastard!
All right, I admit it.
I miss the phonies,
but that's all I miss.
That and Shirley Jones
and Marty Ingels'
New Year's Eve party.
What about that
great feeling you get
from knowing you're better
than regular people?!
BART: What about being an
illiterate TV clown
who's still more respected
than all the scientists,
doctors and educators in
the country put together?
Yeah!
I'm not going to let those guys
hog all the respect
while I'm out here
in some stinking tub.
That's just what
those eggheads want.
Well, forget it, Poindexter.
'Cause Krusty's back in town!
(cheering)
So, Krusty,
what are you going to do
about your tax problem?
Don't sweat it.
The life of Rory B. Bellows
is insured
for a surprisingly
large amount.
(cackling laughter)
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.