CHORUS: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(theme music playing)
(bell ringing)
(whistle blows)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
(honking horn)
(tires screeching)
D'oh! (screams)
HOMER (grunting):
Give me a hand.
Our top story, the ozone hole
that devastated Brazil
last summer
is apparently wintering
in Springfield.
Whoo! Springfield rocks!
Residents are advised
to stay inside
unless you wear sunscreen
or are very, very hairy.
Experts recommend
a class-nine
or Robin Williams level
of hair coverage.
MILHOUSE: Help, somebody!
Oh!
(screaming)
Let me in, for the love of...
-(grunting)
-Are you OK?
MILHOUSE (nonchalantly):
I've been better.
Oh, I am so bored.
Oh, I can't wait till we're
teenagers. Then we'll be happy.
Well, we could play
Clam Traffic Jam
or The Game of County Seats.
Aw, the zoning disc is warped.
All right! Silly string!
Look, you're Milhouse.
Who wets their bed now,
Milhouse?
(laughs)
Ugh. I'll be in my room.
BART: There's got to be
something fun
in my parents' closet.
Want to dress up like ladies?
Uh, wouldn't that make us
kind of... fruity?
What's the matter?
Scared you might like it?
I'll show you who's scared.
Oh, wow, this really hides
my thighs. (growls lewdly)
(both laughing)
BOTH: ♪ Sisters are doing it
for themselves ♪
-(knocking on door)
-HOMER: Hey, why is this door locked?
Oh, no, it's Dad!
(grunts)
(groaning)
(gasps)
What's going on?
And I want a non-gay
explanation.
Uh, we're drunk,
really drunk.
Oh, thank God.
(groans)
-Clear.
-(screams)
Why are you doing that?
Oh. It's good
for the batteries.
Now, I'm afraid your son
has cracked his coccyx.
(all laughing)
I'm sorry. How long
will he take to recover?
He'll have to wear this
fanny cast for quite some time.
But don't worry, son. It fits
snugly under your clothes.
Do all these people have
to watch me?
Now, son, this is
a teaching hospital
which is why I equipped
the seat of your cast
with a viewing window.
Oh, my. Now, that's something.
He should exercise more.
(grunting)
Oh!
Uh, little help?
SKINNER: Bart,
stop fooling around.
Principal Skinner,
I thought public schools
were required to have
access ramps for the disabled.
Technically, yes, but the building costs
would be astronomical.
Did I hear the world
"astronomical"?
If so, my construction outfit,
Valdazzo Brothers Olive Oil,
is poised to help.
No, no, no, no.
We're not building anything.
How can you say that
when construction
has already begun?
-(tires screech)
-(power drill clattering)
How did those trucks
get here so fast?
In order to avoid certain
"legal complications,"
the trucks are always rolling.
Now for
the groundbreaking ceremony.
(shutter clicks)
Good lord, do we really need
all those ramps?
Who's to say?
Does a peacock need
all those feathers?
Look, you're getting
a little philosophical for me.
I suppose so. They say
it happens in the autumn years.
Be that as it may...
Get your hand off my car.
This is a proud day.
Now when people ask
if we're in compliance
with the Americans
with Disabilities Act of 1975,
I can say we are closer
than ever before!
(all cheering)
Thank you.
To inaugurate our ramp system,
here's the first of what I hope
will be many disabled students,
Bart Simpson.
-I'm proud of you, boy.
-What the...
-Bart, where's your wheelchair?
-Don't need it any more.
Doctor says my butt bone's
stronger than ever.
(grunting)
Ta-da!
-(weak applause)
-MAN: That's interesting.
Well, at least we're prepared
for the new millennium.
By God, the whole thing's
made of bread sticks!
And paint and shellac.
It's all itemized in this bill.
$200,000? Are you mad?
I don't get mad. I get stabby.
The good news
is we need no longer fear
vicious mob reprisals.
(honking horn)
But due to lack of funds,
Springfield Elementary
is closed forever.
ALL: Yay!
Oh, you're cheering now,
but someday you'll--
ALL: Yay!
I'm just going to stop trying.
-How could you close the school?
-What will become of our kids?
-Where are the refreshments?
-Now, you keep asking me that
and I keep telling you
"over there."
(clears throat) As for the school,
we're exploring various options
to raise the $200,000 we need.
I've got a motor home
I never use.
Maybe we should raffle it off.
Maybe you should shut up.
Well, I... OK.
We could try selling liquor.
I'm doing great.
Please, sir, put some shoes on.
What? You don't like my bags?
People, these are
all good ideas.
No, they're not. They're
terrible, terrible ideas.
You're right. It's hopeless.
No one has that kind of money.
What about Mr. Burns?
Maybe he'll help us out.
Forget it.
He releases the hounds
on every charity
that comes to his door...
Feed The Children,
Save The Whales,
even Release The Hounds.
Well, maybe we can
pry open his wallet
with a slick, professional pitch.
(snaps fingers)
A school play!
Welcome to
the world premiere of...
The Nice Man Giveth.
Oh, focus!
It's a play, sir.
Hmm, which one of these
is the salt?
Too bad I'm an idiot
'cause my school closed.
Oh, well.
No, that's the rat poison!
And freeze!
Now, who in Springfield
will eat the poisoned broth?
Oh, it could be anyone,
even Mr. Burns.
This play really speaks to me.
(mimicking siren)
I can't take Mr. Burns
to the (lisping) hotpital
'cause I'm too dumb
to read a map.
Oh, why did my school
have to close?
Hmm.
Hello, I'm Dr. Stupid.
I'm going to take out
your liver bones.
(grunts)
Oops, you're dead.
I never liked that Dr. Stupid.
Mr. Burns, I'll be honest.
We had a hidden agenda tonight.
-(gasps) No!
-The holiday season is approaching,
and these children
need a school.
Charity, eh?
Yes, I'd be more than happy...
(all screaming)
Oh, it's doing
that thing again.
ANNOUNCER: We now return to
(speaking in Spanish)
(groans)
Daytime TV is muy estupido.
-(static crackles)
-Hey, our school's on TV.
Springfield Elementary
has reopened its doors.
(both gasp)
I'm with Jim Hope
of Kid First Industries
which has generously stepped in
to educate our children.
That's right, Kent. You know,
when public schools
drop the ball,
it's up to the private sector
to fall on that fumble
and run for the end zone.
Will you be replacing
the current teachers
and administrators?
Very much so, Kent.
But they've already received
an extremely generous
severance package.
"Valencia?"
(scoffs)
These are juice oranges!
Howdy, children. I'd like
to welcome you back to school!
-ALL: Boo!
-You know what? I agree.
-ALL: Wha...
-Your old school was boring.
That's why it failed, right?
Well, we're not going
to make you memorize
facts and dates.
No, no, no.
I'm going to find out
what you really love in life
and teach to that.
What are you
passionate about, partner?
-Boogers.
-(all laughing)
"Boogers"! (laughs)
That was great!
You know, humor is
a sign of intelligence.
-You're not mad?
-Hey, I'm here to make sure
that you get a kick
out of education.
Hyah!
STUDENTS: Yay!
He's rekindled my love affair
with books.
(Bart grunting)
Check it out. I'm breaking books
at a sixth-grade level.
-(grunts)
-Get 'em, boy!
Hit those smart-ass books!
Why don't you kick
some books, Lisa?
Bart broke all my books.
You know what our homework is?
Find a toy
and bring it to class.
Boy, that sounds fun.
I know, but I'm still
not going to do it.
Since Christmas is coming soon,
I thought we could talk
about our favorite toys.
Milhouse,
what have you got there?
My busy box.
It's got everything.
Vroom! Vroom! Vroom!
I'm calling Daddy.
Good for you.
Not being bound
by the recommended age.
What are you talking about?
Oh, jeez!
How about the rest of you?
What do you like
about those toys of yours?
They're special.
They're challenging.
(music playing backward)
Very good.
Now I want you all
to imagine the perfect toy.
-What would it be like?
-It should be soft and cuddly.
Yeah, with lots of firepower.
Its eyes should be telescopes.
No, periscopes.
No, microscopes!
Can you come back to me?
It should be full of surprises.
It should never stop dancing.
It should need accessories.
Now that's market research
you can take to the bank.
The money bank.
I just wish
those second graders
would stop jerking us around.
-Fun toys are fun.
-Well said, Ralph.
But we're trying to come up
with a name for a toy.
-Mrs. Fun?
-Not bad.
Fun?
Ralph, there are no right
or wrong answers,
but if you don't pipe down,
I'm giving you an "F."
The before teacher
yelled at me, too.
No one's yelling.
We're just brainstorming names.
Lisa, any ideas?
Oh, a name with fun?
Um, fungus?
Funzo? Attila the fun?
Lisa, are you doing math?
Uh, just a few Venn diagrams.
There's more under her chair.
(chuckles)
Lisa in trouble.
Ha, the ironing is delicious.
-The word is "irony."
-Huh?
Don't you think there's
something weird going on here?
We spend all day
selecting fabric swatches,
and then our guest speaker
was Phil from marketing.
Alls I know is I'm getting
straight As
and that ain't not bad.
(laughs)
That's not funny!
Huh? Oh.
(gasps)
They're spying on us.
Why would they do that?
-ROBOTIC VOICE: I see you.
-(gasps)
Give me a hug.
(screams)
This better be important, Lisa.
I left Ralphie alone
in the bathtub.
RALPH (on radio): Daddy,
I'm ready to get out now.
Over.
This broom closet
is not what it seems.
It's a secret surveillance room
guarded by a tiny evil robot.
Ugh. Is this going to be like
one of those horror movies
where we open the door
and everything's normal
and we think you're crazy
but then there really is
a killer robot
and the next morning you find
me impaled on a weathervane?
Is that what this is, Lisa?
To be fair, not all
evil robots are killers.
Listen, when you see
what's inside this...
(gasps)
I don't understand. I could
swear it was right here.
Yeah, right, mop top.
And I'm Ed Sullivan.
(imitating Ed Sullivan)
Really big shew...
No, no, I can do it better.
Really big shew, really big.
That's it.
Well, folks, that's
the end of Krusty's
nondenominational
holiday fun fest.
I want to thank my guests
Tea Leoni...
Beck...
The Dixie Chicks...
ALL: Merry Christmas, y'all.
KRUSTY: ...and Patrick Ewing
as the genie.
So have a merry Christmas,
happy Hanukkah, kwazy Kwanza,
a tip-top Tet, and a solemn,
dignified Ramadan.
Now a word from my God,
our sponsor.
ROBOTIC VOICE (singsongy):
I see you.
Give me a hug.
Hah! That's the doll
that attacked me.
TV ANNOUNCER: This Christmas,
everybody wants Funzo.
Funzo? I said
that name in class.
Funzo's soft and cuddly.
With lots of firepower.
-Aah! Ow
-Yes!
(imitating Nelson)
Haw haw!
ANNOUNCER: Funzo!
Funzo! Funzo!
If you don't have Funzo,
you're nothing.
Mom, I know what
I want for Christmas.
Bart, they lied to us.
Instead of giving us
an education,
they tricked us
into designing a toy.
Aren't you outraged?
No, but if you're going
to throw a spaz,
-I'll come with.
-Good.
Saddle up the bikes.
Get down. Security guard.
Hey, it's Gary Coleman.
But the menu said
"galaxy of prawns."
Three prawns
are hardly a galaxy.
What do you mean your hands are tied?
Let me talk to Mr. Kwan.
I want to see
how this turns out.
The phone's
not even plugged in.
All right, you listen
to me, Kwan...
Hang on, I got another call.
Yes, Mr. President. I can be
in Washington right away.
You people took advantage
of trusting school children.
How did you get past
Gary Coleman?
Let's just say he's
a few prawns short of a galaxy.
(shouting)
I'm sorry, Gary. There's
no longer a place for you here.
Whatchu talkin' about,
Miss Naegle?
That is so adorable.
You're rehired.
Sucker. I knew exactly
what she was talking about.
(snoring)
Lisa, I know you're mad,
but just for a damn minute
try to see this from a product
positioning standpoint.
Do you have any idea
how much pressure we're under
to come up with the new Furby
or Tickle Me Elmo?
And thanks to you, Funzo is the first doll
designed by children
for children, with all
the profits going to children.
Really?
Yeah, well, we're all
somebody's children.
But, hey, we did screw you a little.
So, here's a free Funzo.
-Deal.
-Oh, brother.
And I want
Funzo's Dream Fortress,
Funzo's Lower Back Pain Chair,
Funzo's European
Voltage Converter...
Why not get three?
Ah, three, it is.
(snaps)
(whirring)
Thanks, Funzo. You rock.
All righty.
It's always a party with Funzo.
I admit it's kind of cute,
but it'll never take
the place of Malibu Stacy.
(gasps)
Did you see that?
Yeah. Funzo makes playtime fun.
Hey, kids, it's...
(gagging)
Hey, why is it destroying
other toys?
They must have programmed it
to eliminate the competition.
-You mean like Microsoft?
-Exactly.
Come on, Bart, we've got
to warn everyone.
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
Boycott Funzo!
He's a toy-killing machine!
(chuckles)
That shy little imp?
-I have a flower for 'oo.
-ALL: Aww...
Oh, man, I got
to get me one of those.
Hey, I'm not waiting
till the store opens.
-(all shouting)
-WOMAN: Get out of the way!
Wow. Only 22 seconds
from muttering to door smash.
That projects to a profit of...
$370 million.
I'd still sleep a little easier
if I saw some trampling.
Ow! Ow! Ow! Hey! Ow!
Now, why would you wear cleats
to a store?
(glasses clink)
Well, I guess that's it.
Come Christmas eve,
there'll be a Funzo
under every tree.
Unless...
-So, who am I beating up?
-Nobody.
You're just going to break
into everyone's house
and steal their favorite toy.
Thus saving Christmas.
Now, let's see, this will make
three Christmases
I saved versus eight I ruined.
Two were kind of a draw...
Dad, Dad, you're driving
on the sidewalk.
-Sorry.
-(cat yowls)
(doorbell chimes)
♪ Joy to the world ♪
♪ The lord is come ♪
♪ Let earth receive her king ♪
-♪ Let every... ♪
-Season's greetings.
Peace out.
(doorbell chimes)
(singing quietly)
♪ Silent night... ♪
(loud crash)
(singing loudly)
♪ Holy night ♪
-(Homer screaming)
-♪ All is calm ♪
♪ All is bright ♪
♪ Round... ♪
Alrighty!
(to the tune of "Tiny Bubbles")
♪ Writhing Funzos ♪
♪ In my sack ♪
♪ Makes me happy
makes me hurt my back ♪
Just dump them
in the fire, Dad.
Yes. The madness ends here.
Huh! If I had a nickel
for every time I've heard that.
(grunting)
I'm very mad at 'oo.
(groans)
(all gasping)
Well, what do we have here?
Looks like the biggest rip-off
since Webster.
(yelps) Please, Mr. Coleman,
we can explain.
I'm listening.
Your toy company is evil.
Well, isn't it possible
for an evil company
to make people happy?
Are you saying the end
justifies the means?
That's a very glib
interpretation.
Hey, don't talk
to my sister that way.
No, Bart, he's right.
I did oversimplify.
Perhaps, but let's not get
bogged down in semantics.
I think what Lisa meant
to say is...
NARRATOR: And so
Gary Coleman and the Simpsons
argued long into the night...
and then, as day broke
the spirit of the season
entered their hearts.
Let's just agree that the
commercialization of Christmas
is at best a mixed blessing.
-Amen.
-ALL: Yeah, amen. Amen. Amen.
Love!
Hey, look out!
(shouting)
Well, there's something
you don't see every Christmas.
Hey, it is Christmas.
We'd better get home.
Hey, Dad,
what do you think of...
(whispering indistinctly)
Um, uh, Mr. Coleman,
I've been thinking,
uh, my wife always makes
too much stuffing
and sweet p'taters
and all, and...
Oh, heck.
Would you like to spend
Christmas with us?
No way. I'm having Christmas
at George Clooney's house.
Gary.
All right, I'll come.
NARRATOR: And Gary Coleman
was as good as his word.
As for old Mr. Burns,
he was visited by three ghosts
during the night and agreed
to fund the school
with some money he found
in his tuxedo pants...
Thank you, thank you. Humbug.
NARRATOR: ...while Moe, seeing
what the world would be like
if he had never been born
pulled his head
out of the oven
ad replaced it with
a plump Christmas goose.
Here, happy holidays there.
ALL: Merry Christmas, Moe.
Uh, listen, I kind of banged up
the jeep in the driveway.
Whatchu talkin' about, Moe?
(all laughing)
Whatchu talkin' 'bout,
everyone.
(theme music playing)
-(murmuring)
-Shh!
Captioned by
Visual Data Media Services