(exclaiming)
(school bell ringing)
(Barney burps)
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
(tires screech)
Not again!
(classical music playing)
♪ The Simpsons 25x04 ♪
YOLO
Original Air Date on November 10, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
Now, I, Bart Simpson, shall send
the first coaster down the track.
Hmm.
(Milhouse grunts)
(gasping)
No, for once, I
want to go first.
But, Milhouse, I already let
you push me on the swings.
And it's an honor,
but I'm doing this.
Ow! Knock it off, Milhouse!
(grunting)
(yells)
Eat safety bar!
(muffled):
Why are we best friends?
Because your seat
was behind mine!
(both grunting)
(groans)
(both crying)
Feels like this playdate's
gone on forever.
I'll handle this.
"Dear Weirdo,
pick up weirdo kid."
And send.
- Aah!
- (gasps)
Did you eat a peanut?
No, I just sniffed a nectarine.
It's okay.
I can breathe through
my tear ducts.
(whistling)
Tell me if this gets annoying.
(whistling continues)
I think I'm gonna throw up the
mac and cheese you fed me.
I'm not supposed to have it.
That's why I had so much.
HOMER:
What the...?!
If this kid's dad isn't here in one
second, he's going in the garbage can.
(car honks)
Hey, guys!
Who wants a whiff
of New Kirk Smell?
"YOLO"?
You Only Live Once.
Once again, cats have it better.
Kirk Van Houten. I hope you're
not having a midlife crisis.
Please. Just 'cause I bought a
new car, lost a little weight
and started taking a DJ class, everyone
thinks I'm having a midlife crisis.
Dad! You got me a skateboard?
It's for me. Now
get in the back.
And while you're there, use this
cream to massage the leather.
(leather squeaking)
To the tooth-whitening kiosk!
(laughing)
I'm sorry, but does Kirk
know how silly he looks?
Look at me!
I'm afraid of dying.
(laughs)
Oh, Homie.
I'm so glad you're happy with
your life just the way it is.
You've had the same job, same
car, same house for 20 years.
And that's all
you'll ever have.
A cycle you'll never
ever, ever, ever, ever,
ever change.
And you're okay with it!
Like I say night, after
night, after night...
nighty-night.
(birds chirping)
Kent Brockman is here
for your interview.
So, Kent, what brings you here?
The miraculous tale of how we lost,
then found, our Lost and Found box?
Actually, Principal Skinner, I'm
here to talk about something else...
cheating!
(chuckles)
I thought this was a puff piece.
You're wearing a sweater.
This journalism just turned...
- gotcha!
- (gasps)
That's right, Channel 6
will uncover the truth
in a five-part series
two minutes a day.
People, make room for your local
Emmy nomination certificates.
No, do not make room.
Except for Mr. Largo and his diet,
there's no cheating in this school.
These 30 identical "What I Did
This Summer" essays say different.
Um...
Myra, don't I have
another appointment?
Oh, this is your first
appointment ever.
Let's take a look
at this monitor.
This school is more corrupt
than the Italian parliament.
If these children
are our future,
then I, for one, do
not want to live.
NELSON (quietly):
Ha-ha.
Please don't air this.
I'll tell you the winners of
the kickball games in advance.
You can make a lot of
cabbage betting on K-ball.
And that's what we'll
end the story with.
No!
This is Kent Brockman.
Pleased with himself.
♪ You only live once
♪ Or so it seems
♪ No life for yourself
♪ And none for your dreams
♪ You work every day
♪ At a job so lame
♪ And every night
♪ The ending's the same.
♪ No dream will come true
♪ You only live once
(deep breath)
(crying to the tune of
"You Only Live Twice")
(higher-pitched crying)
Yeah, well, at least you
got your health, huh?
Now let's see if I can
take that away from you.
Your poison.
(groans)
I'm tired of living once.
I can't believe I'm saying this, but
I'm starting to regret saying "YOLO."
Marge, if you don't mind,
I'm gonna quit complaining
about my life and start
wallowing in the past.
Postage, marked in pesetas?
Who are those letters from?
My old pen pal from Spain.
- Eduardo.
MARGE: Hmm.
Back in fifth grade, you either had to
write to a foreigner or a prisoner.
I picked a foreigner because the
prisoners wrote back too fast.
We'd write each other with
our dreams of the future.
I was gonna be King of
Cheeseburger Mountain.
(sighs)
Did I change or did they stop making
mountains out of cheeseburgers?
Probably a little bit of both.
So sad.
(indistinct chatter)
(overlapping chatter)
What kind of moral example
is this dump for my boy?
(burps)
(crowd clamoring)
Please, calm down, everyone.
You know, maybe this
so-called cheating scandal
is actually an
opportunity to, uh...
(clears throat)
...initiate a-a dialogue
that would, uh, create
a teachable moment.
Uh, something,
something buzz word...
I got nothing.
Quick, get a picture
for the yearbook!
(crowd clamoring)
LISA:
I have a solution!
You took your sweet time
coming to our rescue, Lisa.
Maybe the best way to keep students from
cheating is to trust them not to cheat.
(crowd murmuring)
That's it?
That's all you've got?
Something I can
read on a tea box?
What I'm suggesting is
we create an honor code.
Oh, swell, more work
for the teachers.
The students would do it.
Let her speak!
If every student pledges not to
cheat, and to turn in any cheater,
no one will cheat the system
because they'll be the system.
ALL (chanting):
Honor code! Honor code!
I did it. I saved the day.
The same way I won that battle
in Vietnam. By fainting!
(doorbell rings)
If you're my wife's
secret lover, come in.
There's nothing I can
do for her anymore.
I am looking for my
amigo de la pluma.
Or "pen pal."
(gasps)
Eduardo? Is it really you?
Why are you here?
To save the soul
of Homer Simpson.
Now where is he, old man?
I'm Homer Simpson!
Ay, dios mio!
What has happened to you?
(speaking in Spanish)
Did your hair burn off in a fire
that trapped you in a candy factory?
I wish.
Marge Simpson.
It's so nice to meet a friend Homer met
through the mail who isn't a sea monkey.
Yes, Eduardo Barcelona.
Or in English, Eddie Miami.
Homie, I thought a visit from your
old pen pal would cheer you up.
Ah, how eagerly I would
wait for a letter
from the EstadosUnidos,
and Homer Simpson.
HOMER:
"Buenos días, Eduardo."
HOMER (continues):
(chuckles)
What happened to us, Eduardo?
We had so many things
we were going to do.
And I, my friend,
have been doing them.
Yeah, well, listen, pal.
I have my treasure...
my wife and my children.
Ooh!
I've had eight wives
and 200 children!
Among them artists, doctors
and revolutionary chefs.
Do you have a disrespectful son
who calls you by your first name?
I cannot imagine
such a creature.
Hey, Homer.
Did you just fart?
Did you just fart, sir.
BART:
Whatever.
Easy, easy, Homer.
I want to help you fulfill
some of your childhood dreams.
Really? Now?
I have two pizzas coming.
I wanted to see who
would get here first.
Now, Homer! Get your coat.
I asked him here
to cheer you up.
But I didn't think
you'd drop everything
to go gallivanting with
some, no offense, Spaniard.
I promise you one thing, madam.
When I return your
husband, he will be happy,
bringing a new sense of
adventure to your marriage...
and to the bedroom.
(panting)
I'm not used to strange men saying
the word "bedroom" around me.
Would you prefer, uh,
"sala deamor"?
That's even worse.
- Could you say it one more time?
- Sala de amor.
(gasps) Ooh!
Hello, children.
I hold before you a copy of
the school's new honor code.
(all groaning)
I know if I can get the toughest
kid in class to sign it,
the rest of you will sign it.
Milhouse?
- (grunts)
- He's not the toughest kid, I am!
Mm-hmm!
Now, the smartest kid.
Milhouse?
He's not the smartest kid.
I am.
Now the class nerd.
Milhouse?
(sighs): Oh.
(snickers)
Homer, are you prepared to achieve
the dreams of a ten year old?
I took the liberty of crossing
off the, uh, stupid ones.
Now, this book of your childhood
drawings will come to life.
Why are you doing this?
Wait, are you in love with me?
In love with the
concept of you, yes.
Woo-hoo! I'm an attractive
concept like Liberty!
(siren wailing)
(tires screech)
One more ride?
All right.
Don't forget to ring the bell.
(bell ringing)
(laughing, grunting)
I'm sick of pirates off the
street ruining my play!
I'm going back to my old career!
Care to see a dessert menu?
We have the best cobbler
since Daniel Day-Lewis.
How much did this
cost to restage?
They rented everything from
Comic Book Guy for ten bucks.
Don't stink up the Gorn head.
I need it for a Bar
Mitzvah later.
(birds chirping)
Now don't forget, this is the first
exam under the new honor code.
They're doing it. They're
self-proctoring.
Can't you say anything
in a normal way?
The answer, sadly, is not yes.
(crickets trilling)
I don't know what it is about
having all my dreams fulfilled,
but I feel great!
Oh, if you're happy I'm happy.
What? That doesn't sound happy.
I feel kind of, oh...
melancholy.
Mmm, melon collie.
(barking)
That's not helping.
Well, what was your
childhood dream?
Jumping on the bed.
But I never disobeyed
my parents.
- Till I married you.
- Let's do it.
Oh, I'm a little tired. Could
we just snuggle again?
We do that every night!
Come on! Jump on the bed
- (Homer giggling)
- Ooh, okay!
(both laughing)
Can I help you, stranger?
I am just watching
my friend and his wife
innocently pleasure
themselves in bed.
That sounds salty,
but you seem sweet.
I'm gonna call you Kettle Corn.
Eduardo, I haven't felt
this good in years.
You're like the Tooth Fairy.
Except you don't collect
human bones.
Yes, yes. Of course I don't.
- Here.
- So, that's it?
All my dreams, lived?
Eh... all but one.
Well, we've got to do it!
I never leave a job unfinished.
It's as true now as that week I
worked on the high school yearbook.
So much infighting. I had
to get out of there.
All right, Homer, we
shall do this thing.
The editor put in like six pictures of
this girl 'cause she was his girlfriend.
Everyone has a bad yearbook story.
They spelled my name wrong!
- Get over it! Ha!
- D'oh!
(propellers churning)
So don't do what I did.
That concludes our safety video.
(grunts)
Just step out that door and you can glide
to earth like your boyhood hero...
Rocky the Flying Squirrel.
Uh, actually, my hero was the
actress who provided Rocky's voice,
June Foray.
A true legend in the
voice-over community.
I'm just gonna stay on the plane
and think about her influence.
She has lived her life.
Now, you must live yours.
- No!
- Do not worry!
I will follow the
trail of your fear!
(Homer yells)
ANNOUNCER:
Will Homer make it?
Or will he leave a crater the size of
the one that destroyed the Yucatan?
Find out in our next
exciting installment:
Fat Splat...
or When You Squish Upon a Car.
Mmm, it's amazing.
Every day has the peace and
serenity of a flu outbreak.
(laughs)
Guess I'll be getting some
extra credit for this.
Lisa, I'm afraid you've gotten all
the extra credit we can give out.
So Willie has been
growing you a nice pumpkin.
Here it is, lass.
You want me to carve it
into a thank-o'-lantern?
No, this is good.
Well, this knife's got
to carve something.
(menacing music playing)
(grunting)
Homer!
(grunts thrice)
You don't have to flap.
Just glide on the wind.
Uh, okay.
Flap! Flap! Flap!
(grunts twice)
Yes, good, much better.
(groans)
I got Bart's backpack.
He got a hundred on his test?
That's impossible.
(gasps)
Is Bart cheating?
Are the Pope's
tweets infallible?
(laughs)
- Bart, I'm gonna tell!
- No, you're not.
Because if you tell people I cheated,
that means your system failed.
Oh, my God, you
found a loophole!
Why don't you put this much
inventiveness into your work?
Because then I'd be the one
thing I swore I wouldn't.
You.
(whistling)
I'm doing it! I'm flying like the
squirrel I always knew I was.
Ooh, indigo!
- MARGE: Homer?
- (yells gibberish)
It's me, talking
in your earphone.
Come down, Homie.
"You only live once" also
means when you die, you die!
(cries out)
What's going on?
Hello?
(goose honks)
Hmm? Hmm? Hmm?
(honks)
Are you mocking me?
You can listen to your
wife when you are dead.
Savor the moment.
Majestic eagle.
Just like me, unashamed
of his baldness.
(eagle cries)
So beautiful.
Aw, he probably sees a mouse
he wants to tear in half.
(grunts)
D'oh!
Stupid tallest building
in Springfield!
(grunting)
Hmm... (grunts)
Ha!
Whoa!
You've presented me
with quite a conundrum.
A word you should know since it was
on a vocabulary test you aced.
(giggles)
But after some thought,
all my worries went away.
I know the answer.
I'm gonna force you
to turn yourself in.
Good luck with that.
The only thing that'll change
my mind is a sign from God.
(Bart grunts)
Son, it was so beautiful!
I went faster than
the speed of sound.
(Homer yelling)
(grunts)
Well, Bart, is that
enough of a sign for you?
All right, I'll turn myself in.
It'll give me a chance to work
some more on the detention quilt.
(humming a tune)
(all grunting)
This patch is for all the
victims of atomic wedgies.
My friend,
you've lived your dreams.
No matter what, Homer
Simpson has done it.
And soon I hope I remember who Homer
Simpson is and his relationship to me.
But I have no regrets.
In fact, all this has given me a
sense of calm I've never had before.
That's the morphine.
Can you give me the
morphine forever?
No way!
A person on morphine
all the time
would constantly dissolve
in inappropriate laughter.
(laughs)
(sighs)
Eduardo? Eduardo! Eduardo!
(grunts)
Oh.
It was all just a dream.
EDUARDO: It was not just a dream. And
you said you'd drive me to the airport.
Oh, yeah.
Great. Um...
Do I drop you at the curb or do
I have to park and walk you in?
Go as far as your
heart will take you.
You are a good friend.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
♪ You only live once
♪ But that's okay
♪ You'll live quite long
♪ In the USA...
♪ But back to my point
♪ You only live once
♪ You've got years and years
♪ Unless it's just months.
Shh!