D'oh!
Fold down that...
and then up that...
and this and over there
and you have a beautiful swan!
What the...?!
This is Anger Watkins, and
you're watching basic cable's
angriest sports show.
Folks, this is difficult to say,
but, today, I'm angry!
I like how angry he is.
I want to broach a topic
that no one else has
the airtime to fill to discuss.
Greatest of All Time.
LeBron, Kobe or MJ?
I'll tell you
why you're all wrong!
Let's open the lines.
The producer says
I'm gonna go on.
Please, Sports Jesus,
guide my blather.
Welcome to Rage Nation.
What the hell is your problem?
First-time listener,
long-time caller.
So, I...
Give me a take!
Anger needs a take.
Who is number one?
John Stockton!
John Stockton?!
We're trying to have
our daily conversation
in which we rank
and re-rank three demigods,
and you bring John "Never Won a Title"
Stockton into the mix?!
Shame! For shame!
Die! Soon!
Goodbye.
Homer, you got flushed.
A man who don't know sports,
he ain't much of a man.
You're nothing to me now.
Just a husband and father.
Stupid Anger Watkins
flushing me
with an audio effect.
Why not eat your feelings
with a cheer-up kebab?
Let's see. Pizza slice,
summer sausage...
Here you go.
It was only a dumb call-in show.
Easy for you to say.
If that jerk
didn't like your sports notions,
listen to someone else.
The internet's full
of homemade sports shows.
Anyone could put one on,
- I mean, even...
- Don't say you.
Don't say you.
Even you.
Damn it.
Oh, yes. Of course!
An internet sports talk show!
But where could I find a host
who thinks
all my opinions are great?
Me.
Marge, prepare
a congratulations kebab.
These are hard as rocks.
Food fight!
This calls
for massive retaliation.
Use your quadratic equations,
men.
Oh, my God.
I'm having a flashback.
Good Lord, I'm reliving
the Tot Offensive.
Skinner...
I'll Heimlich you, sir.
Just be still so I can embrace
you from behind.
Get... off... me.
Shh, you're safe now.
Now, which of you little
hoodlums tossed the first tot?
- The nerd did it.
- Could be Lisa.
Principal Skinner, it wasn't me.
It was physics.
Is this true, Fizix?
I would've thought better of a
Turkemenistani exchange student.
I had nothing to do with it.
I came to this country
to escape food-based violence.
Lisa, one week's detention.
Welcome to Walkoff Homer!
This is Homer Simpson,
the rudest dude
on the InnerTube.
They say Muhammad Ali
was the greatest of all time,
but he never fought
Cassius Clay.
What was he afraid of?
Boom! Hot take.
And how come, in basketball,
they use the basket all the time
but you could literally play
football without any feet?
This show sucks.
I can't believe he's wasting
Flanders' Wi-Fi on this.
Here's a few things that bug me.
How can they call traveling
on a home team?
Why is soccer so stupid?
How can they play hockey
in a garden?
Why can't golfers carry
their own clubs?
Lazy jerks.
Moose Poo?!
Why, you hilarious...
Eat Sunset Rose!
Semi-gloss.
Seed bell?
Like that's gonna stop me.
Oh, so cute!
Look at...
Oh, my face! My face!
Let's give 'em
something to talk about
Something to talk about
Let's give 'em
something to talk about
What the hell's so funny?
We must come together...
to lower our carbon...
- Stupid boy.
- Dumb dad.
First, he ruins my life.
- Then he ruins my livestream.
- Me ruining his show was
- the only good part of his show.
- I'm gonna change the NHL
- with my idea...
- Fat goalie was his only good take.
- for morbidly obese goalies.
- Should've led with it.
Hello. #FirstImpression.
Oh, my God, a hipster!
Marge, bring him a microbrew!
- Quick!
- I'm on it!
The alluvial hops really bring
out the riparian bitterness.
He likes it.
- I think.
- I did like it.
My name's Warburton Parker.
I'm a stranger to you.
Why should you listen to me?
You don't know my backstory.
Well, here it is, colon,
as a child,
my only friend was my computer.
I was teased every day.
Then I became a pro snowboarder,
married a supermodel,
went into tech,
made a fortune,
bought the factories
where the kids who teased me's
parents worked
and shut the factories down.
Do you have a backstory?
Once, when I was six,
I ate a radio.
I like you,
but that won't get in the way.
Let me cut to the chase.
I make money from viral videos.
And you two have gone viral.
Raccoon in a revolving door viral.
You're right
to dance in such a fashion.
Because I'll show you
how to make videos
that will make you rich.
And me richer.
And me richest.
What are you doing here?
I get an alert
whenever anyone's getting rich.
Wow, 5.7 million views.
Wow! Good, not great.
That's the population
of Colorado.
Is that the Broncos one?
It is...
The question is,
how much money have you made?
Let's see.
Third quarter take...
- Factor in overhead.
- Of course.
- Overhead.
- Projections.
Apples to apples.
Figure net profit.
Got it. Nothing.
The question was rhetorical,
you idiots.
Sorry about the idiots thing.
But what you need to do
is monetize.
- Monetize! Monetize!
Monorail. Monorail.
Wait, what are we talking about?
Perhaps you are familiar
with the greatest viral video
of all time.
Monkey smells finger
and falls out of tree.
No, I've never seen...
Oh, my...
Oh, that monkey!
And the... the monkey!
He smelled his finger.
Then boom!
Smell.
That monkey
and that monkey's estate
made zero dollars.
Even less in monkey dollars.
If he had signed with me,
I mean, just hypothetically,
there would be,
oh, I don't know...
Monkey Finger Sniff T-shirts,
Monkey Finger Sniff
Finger Wipes,
Monkey Finger Sniff sponsorships
and a spot
on Weekend Update on SNL.
Host, Rami Malek or better.
Musical guest, Pitbull.
What this monkey didn't sniff
was opportunity.
In the next five minutes,
you'll get more views
than the entire
rebooted Murphy Brown.
Such high hopes.
Not the same without Eldin.
Now, this fight, you're
gonna get kickback from...
- Duff Beer?
- Look at your shirt.
Label to camera.
Hey, label to camera.
They're gonna love
this publicity.
You guys just earned
your first quarter.
First quarter revenue?
No. First quarter,
like the coin.
Halt and Catch Fire, boy!
Silicon Valley!
How the Web Was Won.
I'll give you another quarter
to shut up.
Monetize.
Look at us,
the bully,
the princess,
more bullies,
the Ralph
and me,
the smart kid no one gets.
Yet, maybe,
by the end of the day,
I'll realize
this is just what I needed.
This is what I needed
to break through the...
Lisa, you don't belong here.
Oh, thank God.
So long, delinquents!
Your detention is being held in
our new facility, the R.O.C.C.
Welcome to the Remote On-site
Correctional Center.
How can something be both remote
and on-site?
All right, wisenheimer.
You just earned yourself
a day in the hole.
The Holistic Obstinance
Lessening Environment.
There's nothing in here
but old Goosebumps books.
Fine. Read those.
They aren't scary.
They aren't scary!
What happened
to regular detention?
Well, because we could
no longer afford
any after-school activity,
the school district has
outsourced detention.
Welcome
to Misbehavior Solutions,
a Torture 500 company.
You privatized detention?
Lisa, you have to understand.
Anyone who's done anything
remotely poor
is in private prison.
Oh, did I say poor?
I meant wrong.
No more questions.
So, how's the monetizing going?
Pick a hand.
Pick again.
Not the same hand.
I'm not a magician.
It's in the other hand.
Please pick the other hand.
All right, I'm just gonna
show you the check.
Oh, my God!
$5,000!
This will come in handy
when I buy a boat!
Now, for the really big money,
I sold the location rights
to your next fight.
No, no, no.
This needs to be a discussion.
It's here in this
fried chicken restaurant.
End of discussion.
You see,
this place has an image problem.
They've had nine
salmonella deaths
and one fried pinky
in the past week.
Salmon-ella.
So they want you two,
you and you...
to change the conversation.
If there's a regional,
casual dining chain
that needs my help, I'm there!
My heroes.
Okay, kind of, you know,
fake nibble.
- Pretend you're enjoying the thighs.
- I am.
They're made of wax.
Whatever.
I'm on my fourth bucket.
Sad. Okay, just action.
Why, you little...
And escalate and escalate.
Views, views, views.
Yes!
Feel the burn.
Literally sit in it.
Would you like some onion rings?
I don't see why not.
Beautiful.
Look at those view numbers fly.
I shouldn't say this.
No, I'm gonna say it.
Okay, I say it a lot.
You two are more beloved
than Marathon-Diarrhea Guy.
- I love that guy.
- Best guy.
We have so many sick
sponsored fights lined up.
We're gonna make
Marathon-Diarrhea Guy look
like Dog on Washing Machine.
- I love that dog!
- Best dog.
Violence is the best.
Dad, you're holding my hand.
Is that weird?
I've seen it in books.
Say, boy, can I buy you a...?
Nah, I'm good, but thanks.
Give me a Duff, Moe.
Your money's no good here.
You're a celebrity now,
Mr. YouTube.
The biggest one
this bar has seen
since the snake
that ate three pool balls.
Got a picture of that.
See it?
Anything I can do for you.
Anything. You just name it.
Well, little more
than I thought you'd ask for,
but, no,
I respect the greed.
Now I'm going back to my people.
Hey, how you doing?
It's that kid from YouTube!
You, my friend,
are getting an escort.
Aw, isn't that cute?
Let's give the biggest one a gun
and take the week off.
Milhouse, why are you
in detention?
For using the metric side
of my ruler.
That seems pretty arbitrary.
Why am I here?
All I did was wear swim trunks
in the shower.
They're packing detention
with minor infractors.
But why?
Why do corporations do anything?
To help society.
We need you
to make kiddie license plates.
I need 100 Caitlyns,
100 Kaitlyns
and a thousand Kate Lynns.
Oh, my mom's picking me up.
She'll be frantic!
Oh, they said
I could pick him up at midnight.
You want something stamped?
How about this?
Strike! Strike! Strike!
How do you know about unions?
'Cause our history books end
in the 1930s.
Thanks, guys.
Hey, Dad!
Hey, son!
I kind of missed you.
I kind of missed you too.
Okay, they're hugging.
Excuse me, but I thought
the hate was real.
I have not been so angry
since I saw every Star Wars
since the second.
They are no longer my heroes!
Kumiko, we are changing
the Comic-Con costumes.
We're going back
to our old costumes...
Sailor Moon and the Moon.
Hey there, Chalmers.
Hey there, Skinner.
We will be here until dinner!
These Norma Rae-sinets
refuse to back down.
You can cut detention
with a knife.
In other news,
the Pope has died.
My corporation has a deal
with this school
to provide free kishly
happy workers.
You better fix this and fast.
I think I have an answer.
I know people who will do
anything for money
as long as it doesn't
involve kids...
the teachers.
Well, I been workin'
in a coal mine
Goin' down, down, down
Workin' in a coal mine
Whew, about to slip down
Goin' down, down, down
Workin' in a coal mine...
Take it from the Moon.
Bart and Homer have cratered.
I hate them and I...
So, because people think
you like each other,
you're has-beens.
Yesterday's views.
Deader than MySpace.
15 minutes of lame.
Why are you still here
around me?
Please help us.
It hurts so much to know
that no one is clicking me
or liking me.
They might have no opinion.
I can't live with that!
May I make an original
and groundbreaking observation
that no one
has ever said before?
There is one thing
that show business loves.
- Betty White?
- A comeback.
We are going to put you
out in front
of some of the greatest
influencers
and tastemakers alive.
We will remake
Bart and Homer Brand.
What do you say to BHB2?
Is it a drug?
Lay it on me.
It stands for
Bart Homer Brand 2, you moron.
Of course it is.
Is it a pill?
Or the other end?
This is the largest gathering
of social media influencers
in the western hemisphere.
There's Detonator,
the internet's leading
walkthrough gamer.
What's your side quest, Demon?
- Well, I...
- Terminate dialogue tree.
Return to main quest.
Hey, there's Leslie Sky.
She does makeup tutorials
with veiled white nationalism.
For the foundation,
we can either go with brown,
or skin color.
Oh, my God, it's Jurgen,
Southern Norway's
leading unboxer.
First we take the burger box
from the bag, yeah.
Carefully open the box
so it can be reclasped.
Robust hinging.
I am tired now.
And winter comes.
And now, to tell you
what you're gonna do.
Mortal Kombat, Live Online.
Doesn't mortal mean dead?
It can, but it's just
a figure of speech.
So we don't kill each other?
Oh, if you did,
that would be great.
But let's play it by ear.
Okay, guys,
when you're in combat,
definitely killing each other,
it's important to feature
your sponsored weapons.
Bart, you're promoting Netflix.
Got it?
And Trident gum.
Homer, you're repping
Axe Body Spray
and Trident Spearmint gum.
Do you get it, Homer?
The product things
match the words.
I don't know,
this seems kind of lame.
You know what's not lame?
An audience of 200 livestreams
while you kill your own father.
Or whatever.
Feel it out.
I don't know, I'm gonna need
some more inspiration.
Oh, my God, is it really you?
It is.
Ladies and gentlemen,
YouTubers, Instagrammers,
and homeless former Viners,
you loved them in their
smackdown at Panda Express.
Then they hugged
and you were like, what?
Homer and Bart Simpson!
Do I smell fear?
I'm not afraid of you.
You're smelling the refreshing
scent of Axe Body Spray.
Dark Temptation.
I don't know, Dad.
This just doesn't feel right.
I don't want to fight you.
Me neither, son.
Who'd have thought that two guys
from such different worlds
could connect like us?
Quit using your words!
Hello. I'm Homer Simpson.
And this is episode two of
Walkoff Homer.
Today's question.
Are sports talk shows a complete
and utter waste of time?
We will get
to the bottom of this
within the next five hours.
Five hours?!
I can't get my point across
in five hours.
My whole career depends on me
never quite getting
to the finish.
Because I know...