♪ The Simpsons ♪
-(chalk screeches)
-(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(tires screeching)
(horn honks)
(tires screech)
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
Hey, good evening, Ezron,
carver of graven images.
Ah, good evening,
Homer the Thief.
How is business?
Been a little slow
these past few months.
Not much to steal
in the desert, you know.
Ah, do not worry, my friend.
I figure we'll be
wandering out here
another two weeks tops.
(laughing)
Ah, good evening,
Zohar the Adulterer.
My wife sends her
warmest regards.
Ah yes. She is
a good woman-- very good.
Thank you,
my lusty friend.
(laughing)
(thunder clap)
Ooh,
Moses is back.
Quick!
Everybody look busy!
The Lord has
handed down to us
ten commandments
by which to live.
I will now read them
in no particular order.
"Thou shalt not make
any graven images."
Oh, my God!
"Thou shalt not
commit adultery."
Ah, well. Looks like
the party's over.
Hey, Moses,
keep 'em coming!
"Thou shalt not steal."
-D'oh!
-(laughing)
Sorry, Homer.
That is the most
dishonest thing
I've ever heard!
I should box
your ears!
(stammering)
You sneaky Pete!
-Easy, tiger.
-Hey, you easy!
Now get off my property!
Off!
Hey Flanders,
who put that bug
up your butt?
Oh! I wanted to subscribe
to that new arts
and crafts channel.
Well, sir, they send over this
flimflam man to install it.
You know what he did?
He offered
to hook me up illegally
to every cable channel
for only 50 bucks.
Boy, what's this world
coming to?
-That's exactly what I--
-Got to go!
Ooh!
Hey, stop, cable man!
Stop!
(tires screech)
What do you want?
I want free cable.
(chuckles)
So... this is okay, isn't it?
I mean everybody does it, right?
What? Oh, hey, if you're
having second thoughts,
just read this pamphlet.
(Homer reading)
Uh-huh.
"Myth: Cable piracy is wrong.
"Fact: Cable companies
are big, faceless corporations
which makes it okay."
(laughing)
WOMAN: ...sie the clown
is a treasure
that will last a lifetime.
Cable-- it's more wonderful
than I dared hope.
COMEDIAN:
Don't you hate it
when you go to the bathroom,
and there's no toilet paper?
(laughing)
Oh, it's funny
'cause it's true.
Oh! Hey. Hey, family.
Family, come here.
I have an announcement to make.
The Simpsons have cable!
-Cable?!
Far out, man!
That's right.
68 channels.
MTV for the kids,
VH-1 for us.
1,600 hours
of quality programming
every day.
Homer, we talked about
cable before.
You really think
we can afford it?
(chuckles)
Nothing a month.
Yeah, I think we can
swing that.
(groans)
Are you sure this is legal?
Don't worry Marge.
Take a look at this.
"Myth: It's only fair to pay
for quality, first-run movies.
"Fact: Most movies
shown on cable
get two stars or less
and are repeated ad nauseam."
Hmm, I don't know.
Marge.
WOMAN: Hear Me Roar,
the network for women.
In the next half-hour,
we'll show you
how to cut your
first aid bill in half
by making
your own Band-Aids.
Ooh, that's
a good idea.
Now before we begin,
you'll need five yards
of sterilized cotton...
MAN: El Momeo lo pone
en el sleeper hold!
Donde estan los medicos
de Mexico?
Ooh, pro wrestling
from Mexico.
You know, down there,
it's a real sport.
Oh, cool. This is where
"Jaws" eats the boat.
Whoa. This is where "Die Hard"
jumps through the window.
Whoa, this is where "Wall Street"
gets arrested. Ha-ha!
MAN: Mr. Speaker, if I could
call your attention
to the retroactive subsidy
appropriations override bill.
I refer you to page 4,500
and--
They must think people
will watch anything.
MAN:
Live from New Orleans!
This is the World Series
of Cockfighting.
Oh, son of a gun, we'll have big fun
on the Bayou tonight.
DAVEY: We'd get there quicker if
I drove my Dad's car.
GOLIATH:
I don't know, Davey.
Aren't you ready
for church, Homer?
Huh? Wha--?
Oh, okay.
(turns TV off)
Now, today's Christian
doesn't think he needs God.
He thinks he's got it made.
He's got his hi-fi,
his boob tube,
and his instant pizza pie.
Ooh, pizza.
All right, children.
Now, I don't want you
to get frightened,
but it's my responsibility
to teach you this.
Today's topic
will be Hell.
-(all exclaiming)
-BART: All right.
I've sat through mercy and
I've sat through forgiveness.
Finally, we get to
the good stuff.
Oh, Hell is
a terrible place.
Maggots are your sheet,
worms your blanket.
There's a lake of fire
burning with sulfur.
You'll be tormented
day and night forever and ever.
As a matter of fact,
If you actually saw hell,
you'd be so frightened
you would die.
(gasps)
-Oh, Miss Albright?
-Yes, Bart?
Wouldn't you eventually
get used to it,
like in a hot tub?
No.
Yes, Bart.
Are there pirates in hell?
Yes, thousands of them.
Ooh-ooh, baby.
So what you're saying is,
there's a down side
to the afterlife.
How does one steer clear of
this abode of the damned?
By obeying
The Ten Commandments.
Ten simple rules
that are easy
to live by.
(shuddering)
So, what did you children
learn about today?
-Hell.
-Bart!
Well that's what we learned about.
I sure as hell can't tell you
we learned about Hell
unless I say Hell, can I?
Well, the lad has a point.
-Hell, yes.
-Bart!
(singsongy)
Hell, Hell, Hell, Hell,
Hell, Hell, Hell,
Hell, Hell--
Bart, you're no longer
in Sunday School.
Don't swear.
(door opens, closes)
(cat screeches)
Hey, anybody up for a little
so-called pay TV?
-(turns TV on)
-(both chuckle)
Dad, are you sure
this isn't stealing?
Read the pamphlet, honey.
Hello, I'm Troy McClure.
You may remember me
from such movies as
"Cry Yuma" and
"Here Comes the Coast Guard."
But today, I'd like
to talk to you about
a pleasant tasting candy
that actually cleans and
straightens your teeth.
Oh, goody,
a program-length advertisement.
Wait a minute, Troy.
I'm a little confused.
Did you say,
"Cleans and straightens"?
There's no confusion, Tina,
just good science.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I'd like you to meet
the inventor,
-Dr. Nick Riviera.
-(applause)
Thank you, Troy.
Hi, everybody!
AUDIENCE:
Hi, Dr. Nick!
DR. NICK: Now,
could I have a volunteer?
Somebody with crooked,
yellow teeth.
(gasping)
(fire crackling)
(rumbling)
DEVIL: Come on, Lisa.
Watch a little cable
with us.
(evil chuckle)
It won't cost you
a thing.
(evil laugh)
Except your soul!
(screaming)
What's gotten
into Lisa?
Beats the hell
out of me.
-Bart!
-Ah!
♪♪ (Muzak on P.A.)
(gulps)
LISA: Mom, what
are you doing?
What? What do you mean?
Don't you remember
the eighth commandment?
Well, of course.
It's "Thou shalt not..."
um... "covet... graven...
images."
Something about "covet."
Thou shalt not steal!
MARGE: Oh.
Anything else?
Yes, I ate two grapes.
Please charge me for them.
Oh, two grapes?
Who cares?
Just charge me
something, please.
Yeah, okay, all right.
I need a price check
on two grapes.
Yeah, you heard me, Phil--
two measly,
stinking grapes.
MAN: If you didn't catch it
in the theater
or rent it, or see it
someplace else,
we've got it on
The Blockbuster Channel!
Dad, why is the world
such a cesspool of corruption?
Oh, great.
All right, what
makes you say that?
Well, at Sunday School,
we learned that stealing is a sin.
-Well, duh.
-But everybody does it.
I mean, we're stealing
cable as we speak.
Oh, uh... look
at it this way--
when you had
breakfast this morning,
did you pay for it?
-No.
-And did you pay for
-those clothes you're wearing?
-No, I didn't.
Well, run for the hills,
Ma Barker,
before I call the feds!
Dad, I think that's
pretty spurious.
Well, thank you, honey.
ANNOUNCER: Friday night
live from Las Vegas,
the ultimate match up.
Ooh!
It's Watson-Tatum Two.
This time, it's for money!
Oh, boy!
Only on the
Blockbuster Channel!
How can one,
little insulated wire
bring so much happiness?
(kissing)
(sighs)
LENNY:
Hey, big fight coming up.
CARL: Yeah, you want to
come over to my house
and listen to round-by-round
updates on the radio?
Oh, yeah, okay.
And then after the fight,
we can watch the still photos
on the 11:00 news.
Not too shabby.
What do you say, Homer?
Eh... we could do that,
uh, yeah...
or we could go over to my house
and watch the whole thing
live on cable TV!
-Wow!
-Get off!
-You're kidding me!
-Heh-heh.
Pass the pumice, please.
Um, he's Homer Simpson, sir--
one of your drones from Sector 7G.
Excellent!
I'm so keen on seeing
"Watson vs. Tatum Two,"
I'd even go to
an employee's house.
I can picture it now--
the screen door
rusting off its filthy hinges,
mangy dog staggering about
looking vainly
for a place to die.
Permission to
speak frankly, sir?
Permission granted.
Well, you are quite
wealthy--
Thank you, Smithers.
Your candor is most refreshing.
No, no, I mean, why don't you
pay for the fight yourself?
Dah! Smithers,
a big title fight is
one of those rare occasions
that I savor the sights,
the sounds and--
(sniffs)
Ah, yes--
the smells of other men.
You haven't lost
the common touch, sir.
So, Homer,
I hear you got the fight.
Yeah, that's right.
8:00, my place.
Come one, come all.
-All right!
-(bell dings)
All right! Moe, how come you
never got cable for the bar?
Well, it was either cable
or the mechanical bull.
I made my choice
and I stand by it.
Ooh! Somebody's
having a party.
Yeah. Friday night--
you want to come over?
Thank you, but this store
is open 24 hours.
It puts great demands
on my time.
Too bad. It's gonna be
a great fight.
Oh, the fight!
Why didn't you
say something?
I'll get my brother Sanjay
to cover for me.
He deplores violence
of all kinds.
LISA:
So, even if a man takes bread
to feed his starving family,
that would be stealing?
No. Well, it is if
he puts anything on it.
-Jelly, for example.
-I see.
Oh, come on, Lisa, now
you're here for a reason.
Is your father
stealing bread?
Maybe. I don't watch him
every minute.
But what I am sure of is,
we're getting cable for free.
Well, I'm afraid that
is stealing, Lisa,
and I think you
must do something. Hm.
Should I have my
father arrested?
Well, Lisa, on the surface,
that would appear to be
an ideal solution
to the problem,
but remember
the fifth commandment--
"Honor thy father
and thy mother."
Hmm, Lisa, I would like to
see you set an example
by not watching the offending
technology yourself.
Thank you, Reverend Lovejoy.
FEMALE: You're watching
Top Hat Entertainment--
adult programming,
all day, every day,
except in Florida and Utah.
Coming up next:
"Stardust Mammaries"
♪♪
Ay, caramba!
-HOMER: Bart!
-Dad!
Oh! Here's what
I was looking for.
MAN: ...Blue chips closed up
3 and 3 quarters.
Oil service stocks
slumped slightly...
Son, you shouldn't watch
that other channel.
It's only for
Mommies and Daddies
who love each other
very much.
I want you to promise me
you won't watch that channel
ever again.
-Okay.
-Promise me.
I promise I will never watch
that channel again.
Good boy.
Hi Dad. I think
stealing cable is wrong,
so I'm choosing
not to watch it
in the hope others
will follow my example
It's the last you'll hear
from me on the matter.
Thank you for your time.
Hey, Lisa...
Racing from Belmont?
Horsies!
-Sorry, I'd rather go to heaven.
-Hmm.
HOMER: There's something wrong
with that kid.
She's so moral.
Why can't she
be more like--
Well, not like Bart,
but there's gotta be
a happy medium.
Well, you know,
Bart was looking
at that racy movie today,
and Lisa's losing
a little respect for you.
Hmm. Maybe we should think
about unhooking the cable.
Unhook it?!
But I love cable.
Well, then maybe you
should pay for it.
D'oh! Look, look, Marge,
I can't afford it.
When I can afford
to pay for it, I will,
but I can't,
so I'm not going to.
Homer, I'm afraid that
cable has become
an evil presence in our home.
Marge, I never put my foot
down about anything--
-No.
-But I am severely tempted
to do it over this.
-Oh, Homer.
-Marge, I'm sorry.
-I think it's coming down.
-No, Homer--
It's coming down, my foot--
That's it, Marge!
It's coming down.
The cable stays.
The foot has spoken.
(loud thud)
-BOY: Lemonade? Please.
-Seen it.
-MAN: Cleans and straightens your teeth.
-♪♪ (rap)
-Seen it.
-I was poor like you--
Ugh, soccer.
Seen it.
-Hey, Simpson.
-What? Hey, how'd you get in here?
Well, your door wasn't locked
in any serious way.
I wonder if you'd be
interested in this car stereo?
A $500 value, but I'll let you
have it for 40 bucks.
Get out of my house! I don't
want to associate with criminals.
Well, maybe I'll go see
your neighbor.
He's not home.
Even better.
(locks clicking)
Are you sure
you want do this, Homer?
It doesn't
look friendly.
Marge, we can't be
too careful.
There are thieves everywhere,
and I'm not talking about
the small, forgivable stuff.
Come one, come all.
Top Hat Theater
is on the air.
The most beautiful women
in the world.
Just 50 cents.
I am your host, Bart Simpson.
You must be at least
eight years old to enter.
WOMAN: And now,
the Top Hat Channel
is honored to present
"Broadcast Nudes."
ALL: Ooh.
-Gross!
-Yet strangely compelling.
-HOMER: Huh?!
-It's a raid!
What the--
What are all these kids--
Hey! I know you.
Come back here!
Bart, you promised me you
wouldn't watch that trash.
Now go to your room!
Man, I wish I was an adult
so I could break the rules.
Oh, great.
(tires squeal)
-(cat screeches)
-Here.
I brought some imported
generic beer.
Oh, thank you, Barney.
How many people
are coming, Homer?
Just a select circle
of my friends.
Oh, hello, Mrs. Homer.
I brought an assortment
of jerkies.
Ooh, did you swipe
those from work?
Certainly not.
What has been implied here?
MAN: Oh, no sir,
there is no love lost
between these two warriors.
In fact,
we almost had a scuffle
earlier today
at the weigh-in.
I understand you have
a special motivation
going into this bout.
Yeah. I wanna dedicate
this fight
to my manager Vinnie
who got me here,
and then--
(sobbing)
passed away
just two weeks ago.
Any response to that?
Yeth, I would altho like
to dedicate thith fight
to the memory of
his deceased manager.
-You can't do that.
-I can do whatever I want.
You dedicate the fight
to your manager, man!
This is just incorrigible.
I just want to call
attention to the fact
that I'm not watching
this fight.
It's my form
of nonviolent protest.
(doorbell rings)
Hey, Homer.
I brought--
Ahh! Quick!
It's Moe!
I got to hide the mugs.
Well-- Will you--
Hey, go protest outside,
will you? Now!
Hey, Homer.
I brought you a mug.
Ooh!
Thank you, Moe.
I always wanted one of these.
Ahh!
Oh, Mr. Burns!
Bart, quick. Hide the stuff
I borrowed from work.
-Borrowed?
-All right, the stuff I stole from work.
Oh, okay.
Now, come on! Take all this
and this, put it in the closet.
-Will you quit staring at me like that?
-(doorbell rings)
Oh, hello, Simpson.
We were just
in the neighborhood
and thought we'd drop by.
Uh, hello, Mr. Burns.
Would you like
to watch the fight?
The fight? Well,
don't mind if I do.
Oh, Simpson, good news.
I brought some munchies.
Smithers, the Cheetos.
(both scream)
Our main event is set
to commence
in but a few scant minutes.
The anticipation...
-(screams)
-You Homer Simpson?
-Yeah.
-Word on the street
is that you have
an illegal cable hookup.
No. No, I--
It wasn't me.
It was my wife's--
my wife's idea.
-Yeah, yeah. (sobbing)
-Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey, settle down,
big fella.
We're just-- Whoa! We're just
wondering if we could watch the fight.
Oh, sure, sure.
Be my guest.
Lisa, I brought you
some lemonade for your protest.
Thanks, Mom.
It doesn't seem
to be going very well.
Well, don't give up.
When you love somebody
you have to have faith
that in the end,
they will do
the right thing.
ANNOUNCER: The challenger
learned how to fight
in the notorious projects
of Capitol City,
and honed his skills
while serving time
for aggravated assault
and manslaughter
in Springfield Prison.
All right!
A local boy.
CHALLENGER: For five years,
I was-- I was incarcerated
away from my family
and the mother to my children.
The conditions
were irrevocable.
COMMENTATOR:
Aggravated assault,
manslaughter,
stealing cable,
(echoing)
cable, cable...
(whimpering)
Marge! Lisa! Maggie!
Shake hands.
-Keep it clean.
-(bell dings)
Come on, boy.
(crowd cheering)
Excuse me.
I hate to interrupt
your judging me,
but I wanted you to know
I've made a couple of
really important decisions.
Number one,
I'm cutting the cable
as soon as the fight's over.
And number two,
I'm not very fond
of any of you.
-Well, back to the fight.
-Sit down, boy!
Dad, we may have
saved your soul.
Tatum is reeling from the
champs exquisite haymaker.
Yeah, at the worst
possible time.
ALL: ...eight, nine, ten.
(cheering)
ANNOUNCER:
This fight is history.
Stick a fork in it--
it's done.
A stunning knockout by
a thunderous bolo punch
in the closing seconds
of the 12th round,
and Drederick Tatum is the new
champion of the world.
Everyone to my place
for blueberry Squishees
-and microwave burritos.
-(cheering)
The greatest fight ever
and I missed it.
We're really proud
of you, Dad.
What a donnybrook,
eh, Mr. Burns?
Oh, hogwash. Why I once
watched Gentleman Jim Corbett
fight an Eskimo fellow
bare-knuckled for 113 rounds.
Back then, of course, if a fight
lasted less then 50 rounds
we demanded our nickel back.
Cable clippers, please.
Here you go, Homey.
LISA: Go for it, Dad.
Dad, I beg you to
reconsider.
Tractor pulls,
Atlanta Braves baseball
Joe Franklin!
Hmm...
Whoops.
Third time's a charm.
(static)
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.