CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
HOMER:
Come on, Marge, where's dinner?
What's the holdup in there?
♪ Pot-pot-pot-pot pot pies! ♪
A pie for Bart...
Come on, put them down already.
...a veggie pie for Lisa...
Why do you have to describe everything?
...a baby pie for Maggie.
The pies know who they're for.
-A dog pie for Santa's Little Helper.
-What? The dog...
The dog before me?
Now, be sure to cut it open first
so the pie has time to cool.
(screams) I'm done.
I know you're in a hurry to go to the bar
to watch football,
but first I want you
to put the kids to bed.
(groans loudly)
(strains, grunts)
"Everything after the tornado
was a dream. The end."
(tires screech)
ANNOUNCER: Going into halftime,
it's Springfield Atoms 7,
Boston Americans 10.
Oh, come on, we cannot lose again
to those no-good Boston cheaters!
I-I can't stand that
pretty-boy quarterback.
Thinks he's so handsome,
just 'cause he's drop-dead gorgeous.
The only reason Boston wins
is because they cheat!
Listening in on our team's headsets,
fattening our cheerleaders.
You know, for three games last year,
Boston used a volleyball painted brown.
(Boston accent)
That was never proven,
you Springfield screw-job.
Ugh, Boston fans.
In town for
the Dennis Lehane book tour.
Go kiss a Kennedy, you rule-
breaking cranberry squeezers!
We don't cheat.
We won 12 division titles in ten years,
fair and square.
You dorks are just jealous
of all our championship rings.
ALL:
Mwah! Mwah! Mwah! Mwah! Mwah!
You're the one who's jealous.
I only wish
I could be as jealous as you.
Geez, Jay, this place has got
more knobs than a hardware store.
I hate this town.
So don't I. Friggin' doorknobs.
-(laughter)
-Automatic.
BOTH:
Mwah, mwah, mwah.
ANNOUNCER:
It's fourth and long,
the Americans' last chance
for a miracle.
Come on, Springfield, put it away!
We're gonna win one.
We're finally gonna win one!
ANNOUNCER:
The QB handsomely takes the snap,
sexily steps back to pass,
and with God-given good looks,
fires it downfield!
But there's no one there to receive it!
(groaning)
(scoffs) Nice pass.
What a first-ballot hall-of-fame loser.
ANNOUNCER: But the ball is caught
by the Americans' mascot,
Flappy the Flag!
Flappy running unopposed into the end zone
for a surely illegal touchdown.
Throwing to the mascot?
After further review,
Flappy the Flag is listed
on the Americans' 53-man roster
and reported eligible.
The result of the play is a touchdown.
(crowd cheering)
ANNOUNCER: Once again,
the Americans found a way to win.
(chuckles) Oh, that'll put a smile
on Coach Bonderchuck's face.
(crowd cheering)
-(cheering)
-Oh, not again!
They cheated! You cheated!
Did not.
You got to cover the mascot.
Use your noggin. Play smart.
Flappy's on the roster.
(chanting)
On the roster!
On the roster! On the roster!
On the roster, my butt.
Once again, those Boston cheaters
think the rules don't apply to them.
And they're so smug about winning.
If I ever won anything,
I wouldn't be smug about it.
I'd be class all the way,
like Mark Harmon-- pure American elegance.
I tell ya, the next Boston fan I see,
I'm just gonna lose it.
Lose it so hard.
And-- What the...?!
What is... How could...
That hat! Your head!
That team.
My son!
Hey, Dad, caught the game last night.
Tough loss for your guys.
Guess we just wanted it more.
(sarcastically)
Oh, am I in the right house?
Because no one in my house
would ever be caught dead
wearing Boston Americans gear.
Dead!
I feel ya, Homer.
Sucks to be a loser.
Unlike the six-time
Mega-Bowl champion
Boston Americans.
Mwah! (smooches)
Ring, ring, ring.
(frustrated grunts)
Give me that hat.
(Homer growls)
(grunting, snorting)
Olé!
(sighs) Your father never
could resist an "olé."
Eh, he'll run out of steam soon.
(Homer groaning)
(laughing)
Get in.
(Milhouse and Nelson scream)
(gulps)
Look around, son.
This is your hometown.
And the Springfield Atoms
are your hometown team--
since 2003, when we stole them
in the middle of the night
from Portland.
What kind of life
can you have here
as a Boston fan?
See?
Why are you wearing
that Boston hat?
This is Atoms country, bro!
I would pluck out my own eyes
if I did not have a call-back
for a web-only
Olive Garden commercial.
They're just trying to hat-shame me.
Face it, Dad,
Boston is the Bart Simpson of cities.
All those awesome Southies
in The Departed,
those are my people.
People? The dog and the baby
are your people.
(sighs) It all goes back
to the Boston Tea Party,
a prank so kick-ass it started a country.
(tires screech)
Come on, pal, what do you say?
Just lose the hat.
For your old man.
Nope, I think I'll stick
with the bad boys.
Get it off before God sees.
(whimpering)
(groans) Oh!
And the people from Boston
are so obnoxious.
They think their stupid city
has the best everything:
bands, comedians, chowder,
their so-called cream pies,
which are actually cakes.
-And there's...
-Why don't you let me
take your mind off your problems?
And what's with Aerosmith?
That's not how you spell "arrow."
The... oh.
(both moaning)
(confused grunting)
(whimpering)
Oh, no.
Do your job, Homer.
(Homer screams)
Bart, you're my son.
There's no neck tattoo so crass,
no gender reassignment too ambiguous
that I would not love you.
Which is why I must show you
the error of your ways,
even if it means dragging
this family all the way to hell.
A vacation to Boston?
No, not a vay-cation,
a hate-cation!
Where you experience
the worst a place has to offer,
and then say, "Told ya!"
Hate-watching, hate-voting
and now a hate-cation?
Why can't everyone just enjoy
things they like?
Because things you like don't fill you
with delicious, delicious rage.
Hmm, I'm gonna love this trip.
I'm gonna love it right in your face.
That's it, build it up in your head.
High hopes just make
the hate-cation stronger.
You're crazy.
Boston can't be that bad.
(horns honking)
I've never loved hating anything so much!
(Boston accent)
Move your garbage car!
I got to get to the packy
before the Bs drop puck!
Told ya!
See, boy? Notice how Bostonians
aren't exactly ugly,
but they're not sexy either.
Homer, your negative attitude
is ruining this hate-cation.
So, what to hate first?
The Freedom Trail?
The touch tank
at the New England Aquarium?
Ooh, that could blow.
I want to go to Southie.
That part of town has
the towniest townies of any town.
(scoffs) You think your
Bostonians are so great?
Watch as your beloved hooligans
tear your innocent father limb from limb
with just the slightest provocation.
Listen up, you clam-gargling tea-tossers!
Fenway is a terrible ballpark!
Dad, don't!
Out of my way, ladies.
You're blocking my shot.
The seats at Fenway Park are too narrow,
and many of them face center field!
It's not charming, it's a teardown!
(Boston accent)
The bobbleheads!
They're tippin'!
(Boston accent)
Kid, mind the cart!
-The what?
-The cart!
The cot?
Cot!
(grunting)
No, don't struggle!
It only makes them bobble harder.
They keep coming.
Bobblehead Steven Wright,
bobblehead Aimee Mann,
bobblehead Bell Biv DeVoe!
The vibrations are killing him!
Don't worry, sweetheart,
I'm a doctor.
I'm also a doctor, kid.
(groaning)
Mm, so many doctors.
He's got a Pedro lodged in his airway.
(Homer gasps)
He'll be fine, ma'am.
And because of our state's
super-socialized health care,
no matter how much your husband
abuses his body,
someone else will pay for it.
What a relief for women
with hot-tempered,
accident-prone husbands.
Oh, yeah,
we got a whole surgical center
for injuries from falling off
icy roofs and gutters.
BOTH: Ooh.
While the doctors pull tiny
Bruins helmets out of your skin,
Lisa and I are going to explore
The Hub on our own.
Remember, this is a hate-cation.
You better go someplace bad.
Isn't Mayor Quimby
from somewhere around here?
(all muttering with thick accents)
People are so fit here.
Everyone looks like they're
in a financial services ad.
Free sunscreen? So progressive.
Do you vaccinate your children?
Of course.
But not stupid progressive.
-(low buzzing)
-What's that buzzing noise?
(gasps) It's-- It's nerds!
They've got every
recognized species of nerd!
A jester-hatted ferret preener!
A Wild West-afarian!
A Magic: The Gathering gathering!
Oculus rifters!
Yo-yo guys. Yo-yo girls!
A chain mail ping pong player.
(giggles, squeals)
So much education.
If they did a Real Housewives here,
it would be a total snooze.
Ah, it's like heaven for people
who don't believe in heaven.
HOMER:
What the crap is this BS?
What? I thought you'd want
to try candlepin bowling.
Hey, McCarthy, nice half-Worcester.
Get bent, McDonald.
A lot of wood to work with out there.
(sputters) Boston.
They even found a way to mess up bowling.
Just try it.
(groans)
Eh, all right.
(grunts)
None of the usual pain in my knees, back,
wrist, shoulder, neck, and chest.
(grunts)
(groans) One pin standing.
Story of my life.
Whoa there, pal.
Don't forget your third ball.
Hold on, wait.
Wait. Hold on.
Wait.
What?
This is candlepin bowling.
You get three.
Hmm? Hmm.
(grunts)
(gasps) Three balls.
I see it all so clearly now.
What, Dad? What is it?
This regional bowling
with its one extra roll
has knocked my misguided hate
into the gutter.
Mwah!
I like Boston!
Dad, you and me are real
father-son Southies, now.
Just like Ben and Casey Affleck.
Son, show me everything
this town has to offer.
("The Man in Me" by Bob Dylan playing)
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ La la la la la la la la la ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ La la la la la ♪
♪ La la la la ♪
♪ La la la la la la la ♪
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ La la la ♪
-♪ Ooh ♪
-♪ La la la la la la la la... ♪
(gulps)
You know, for a cake,
this Boston cream pie isn't so bad.
Look at them. So innocent.
Not Bart, but go on.
Homer,
I never dared dream
about living somewhere
that values education,
with great health care,
and everyone's outdoorsy
but still pallid.
If it weren't crazy,
I'd say we should be
raising our kids here.
But no. No, no. That's crazy!
Is it?
(gasps) But I never thought you,
of all people...
Honey, this could be the chance
we never thought we'd get.
The chance to knock down
all of life's pins.
Are you saying
what I think you're saying?
I am.
Fate is offering us a third ball.
Do you mean it?
Are we going to move to Boston?
I knew I didn't pay this month's
mortgage for a reason.
(both sigh)
(kisses)
(St. Elsewhere theme playing)
We did it! We really did it!
We made a life change.
I love these colonial quilts on the wall.
Now, I can take a nap standing up.
Check it out, kid.
This movie's my life now.
You want to rob the Harvard Coop?
Why don't we just break into Fort Knox?
These snobs think Mass Ave.
belongs to them.
It's our Ave.
Whoa! I got to get one of those
"X" necklaces to kiss.
This is all happening so fast.
Can we really afford to live in a city
with a symphony and a Pops?
(laughing)
Don't worry, baby.
I have a line on a sweet
safety inspector gig.
Very sweet.
HOMER (over P.A.):
Can I get a test on batch six?
I'm finally living my dream
of never not being around
batches of candy.
And unlike the nuclear plant,
if I screw up, no one gets hurt.
(screaming)
Are you sure
we have to go to school here?
I sort of thought I'd go
straight to running numbers
for the Irish mob.
Our school is in the heart
of what they once called
The Combat Zone.
The Combat Zone! Yes!
Combat rules!
BART: Charter what?
Here's my classroom.
The teacher
is Doris Kearns Goodwin.
Today, we explore Lincoln's 1861
suspension of habeas corpus,
using dried macaroni
and pipe cleaners.
(gasps excitedly)
Huh, now to get sent to detention.
That's where I'll meet
my future bank-robbing crew.
(all gasping)
Ha! How do you like them marbles?
Bart, we have a place for kids like you.
Bring it on.
(choir humming
"I'm Shipping Up to Boston")
BART: Kids singing?
(humming continues)
What the hell?
Like you, these kids are gifted
with exceptional energy.
Which they've channeled into a cappella.
♪ I'm shipping up to Boston ♪
♪ Whoa! ♪
(softly)
Departed.
These are the bad kids?
There's not a Wahlberg in the bunch.
I've never felt more like I fit in.
People think Boston's
all Southies and hooligans.
But it's really teachers, Ph.D. students,
doctors, innovators, philanthropists.
It's like living in a giant classroom.
And every day is a new test.
(groaning)
(thunder claps)
Theater?
Colleges?
Culture?
Oh, Pauly,
if you could have known that
Boston was gonna turn out so wussy,
you never would have warned anybody.
Listen, my brother, and you shall see,
this is a town not for you, but for me.
(screaming)
Hey, but what about Grampa?
He lives a thousand miles away.
Great point.
Nobody tell him where we went.
Bart, you haven't touched your clambake.
What's wrong?
This place is all P.C. brainiacs
and Subaru owners
wearing fleece vests.
It's nothing at all
like The Departed.
Oh, honey, I know it's a big change.
But someday you'll understand
that providing our family
with a better life...
Something I've never been able to do.
...is the most important thing
in the world.
We've been given a third ball.
Let's not throw it away.
(groans)
Same to you.
No one likes feeling out of place.
That's how I felt back in Springfield.
But I sucked it up for eight years.
Now it's your turn.
(grunts)
(gasps)
Yes! Finally.
A Southie crew pulling a job.
I finally took that
spin class with Miranda.
I was sweatin' so friggin' hard.
Hey, try this pressed juice, kid.
Ginger, cayenne...
wicked cleanse, pal.
Come on. Donny, Tommy,
these solar laptops for Rwandans
ain't gonna donate themselves.
It's time for me to ship out of Boston.
What a gorgeous day.
I hope it never ends.
So don't I.
You know, guys, I've picked out
the perfect Boston activity
to help celebrate our move.
-(marching band playing)
-Ooh, a parade.
Not just any parade.
HOMER:
The Boston Americans?
CROWD (chanting):
Bonk! Bonk! Bonk!
It's a state holiday because the league
overturned the coach's suspension
for using magnets
to affect the coin toss.
Pretty cool way to celebrate
our new hometown.
Right, Dad?
(forced) As a Bostonian,
I definitely support my team.
Hey, Bonk! Can we get a picture?
Hell to the derrr, little bro!
(grunting)
Come on, Homer, put on the hat.
I can support my hometown team
without putting on a hat.
Hats go on your head!
If you're gonna live in Boston,
you got to wear the hat.
(winces)
Okay.
(grunting, blowing)
You did this on purpose.
My future is at stake.
So don't is mine.
(struggling)
It's... just... a... hat.
You can do it, Homie.
Think of the candlepins.
This is our extra ball!
A... better... life.
(yells)
(all gasping)
(quacking)
Derrr?!
Stupid cheaters!
You cheat,
you flip out
when people say you cheat,
and everybody knows
you're nothing but a big bunch
of cheaters!
(Moe chuckling)
You made us leave that lovely city
rather than just put on a stupid hat.
It wasn't even fitted.
(sighs)
I just couldn't wear the hat.
Well, I'm still mad at you.
I never even got to experience
one of those Boston winters
everyone raves about.
Come on, baby,
we could never escape our problems
by moving somewhere else.
Our problems are who we are,
not where we are.
Well... maybe.
The traffic was pretty annoying.
Not to mention the unspoken racism.
It wasn't that unspoken.
At least someone in this family
is happy about where they came from.
Oh, don't worry, Lisa.
You'll get back to Boston someday.
What are you talking about?
I never left.
I'm in Boston now.
Welcome home, Lisa.
Class is about to start.
(classical music playing)
Eh.
(choir humming
"I'm Shipping Up to Boston")
♪ I'm shipping up to Boston ♪
♪ Shipping up, shipping up ♪
♪ Shipping up to Boston, whoa ♪
♪ I'm shipping up to Boston ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Shipping up to Boston ♪
♪ Whoa! ♪
Departed!
Subtitled by E. Jaeger