-(beatboxing)
-CHOIR: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-(tires screech)
-(grunts)
ALL: Huh?
D'oh!
(groans) No parking spots?
Lousy butt-kissers, coming in before noon,
eating donuts that are rightfully mine.
Oh, oh, oh! D'oh!
Stupid Smart Car.
(tires screech)
D'oh! Spot-hogging S.U.V.
D'oh! Inconvenient sinkhole.
(tires screech)
D'oh! Mandatory credit.
D'oh! "Developed by"?
What does that even mean?
(gasps) It's empty!
Homer, no! That's Burns' spot.
How could you miss that sign?
Oof. The last guy that parked there
is now a...
(quietly) speed bump.
(muffled) Slow down!
Guys, be cool.
Burns'll never know.
He's on vacation this week
with his weirdo hunting buddies.
Fellow members of the Order of
the Knights of Saint Caucasian,
we've got a lot of things to kill today,
so release the sedated quail.
(gun clicks)
How am I supposed to hunt it
if it can move?
Try it now, Davy Crockett!
Damn... you... surface... tension...
Wait a minute.
If I can park in Mr. Burns' space,
I can live his whole life!
Quickly now, before I think it through!
(chuckling)
♪ Mr. Big Stuff ♪
♪ Who do you think you are? ♪
♪ You're never gonna get my love ♪
♪ Now because you wear ♪
♪ All those fancy clothes ♪
-♪ Oh, yeah ♪
-♪ And have a big fine car ♪
♪ Oh, yes, you do now ♪
♪ Do you think I can afford... ♪
(German accent)
Come on along, and sing our Tiki song.
(Latino accent)
And everyone will take their turns.
(Jamaican accent)
To celebrate a man who's great.
The wiki-wakka liki-lakka magic Mr. Burns!
♪ The wiki-wakka liki-lakka Mr. Burns ♪
♪ The wiki-wakka liki-lakka Mr. Burns... ♪
♪ Mr. Big Stuff ♪
♪ Who do you think you are? ♪
♪ You're never gonna get my love... ♪
(quietly) Simpson lines up his hitty stick
and gets ready to clobber
the dimpled round-o.
He's calling the signals.
(yelling) Omaha! 35!
-Hut! Hut!
-Simpson!
(shrieks)
Incoming!
(yelling)
There's a lightbulb out on level P-2!
Oh, good Lord.
The trapdoor is under renovation.
It's not safe!
(grunting)
-Mm-hmm.
-HOMER: Mosaic!
-(screams)
-Congratulations. You're halfway down.
-(electric crackle)
-(grunting)
What the...
(sighs)
(screams) Ow!
I'm drowning in cement!
-Uh, it's actually concrete.
-Whoo-hoo!
Of which cement is an ingredient.
(yells) No!
(rhythmic yelling)
Oh...
-(Marge hums)
-Hmm?
MARGE: Perfect.
(chuckles)
Marge, you've thought of everything.
Except for one nagging detail.
Did I ever tell you about the time
I was in a big cast?
It was the Shelbyville Players
production of Pippin.
-Don't worry, Homie.
-GRAMPA: I went from player
to ticket taker in one performance!
There's two ways of...
-(seagulls chirping)
-(tide rolling)
You are in my seat.
ALL: Fight! Fight! Fight!
Asthma, glasses, asthma!
(grunts)
(cheering, yelling)
Oh. There's too much violence
in rearview mirrors these days.
Hey, boy, want to sign
your old man's cast?
No problemo.
(marker squeaks)
-What does it say?
-Don't worry about it.
-What did you write?
-Sorry.
That's between me
and everyone who sees it.
-I need to know!
-Hmm.
Begins with "F" and ends in "C-K."
Why you little!
(grunting, groaning)
(chuckles)
-Tell me!
-Never!
(grunting)
(moans)
(quickly) D'oh! D'oh! D'oh! D'oh! D'oh!
Whoo-hoo!
D'oh! D'oh! D'oh! D'oh! D'oh! D'oh! D'oh!
D'oh! Whoo-hoo!
(slowing down)
D'oh! D'oh! D'oh! D'oh! D'oh! D'oh! D'oh!
D'oh... Whoo-hoo!
MARGE: Thanks, partner.
We've balled up all the 13-gauge alpaca.
Now maybe there's something fun we can do?
Sure is. A puzzle.
"Foggy Day in Berlin."
5,000 pieces.
Hmm...
(German accent)
Homer, complete the puzzle!
-I'm a married man!
-Fine.
If you need me,
I'll be in your schpankenbank.
FEMALE SINGER: ♪ We'll meet again ♪
Marge, I don't think
we should do this puzzle.
I know. You can't pick up the pieces.
That's why I've devised a grid system.
Huh? I'll hold up a piece,
and you call out the number
and letter of
the corresponding grid square.
Uh, I don't know. Q 15?
Sweetie, it's a side piece.
Q 15's in the middle.
Right. Q 15 is in the middle.
Nothing more fun than rules.
I'll make some tea to help you think.
Oh, I hate being immobile and numb.
If only I was free to move.
(moans) If only.
(excited chatter)
It's never pleasant to see
this kind of activity, Lisa.
Particularly on a cell phone
that is so much nicer
than the one I own.
-(cranking)
-(grumbles)
All the fighting seems to start
with who sits where on the bus.
Um, Lisa,
you seem to have a handle
on the bus problem.
Why don't you tackle it?
But don't think I won't help.
I'm providing you with a sash.
Skinner!
You are asking a six-year-old girl
to fix this school's problems.
-I'm eight.
-Oh, carry on.
(bird caws)
What do you mean,
there's a legal issue with my trapdoor?
And, uh, as you explain,
please take two steps back.
The old trapdoor was perfectly legal.
It was grandfathered in
under the Reagan-era code.
But once you start renovating it,
it has to brought up to modern standards.
Mm. And it has to be handicap accessible.
A wheelchair would never
fall through the current opening.
(chuckling) Oh! But that's not a problem!
-I refuse to hire the handicapped.
-That's another issue.
But for now, we have left ourselves open
to a lawsuit by Homer Simpson.
Fine. Smithers,
go see this Simpson character
and trick him into signing
a waiver of liability.
I'll discuss things with the foreman.
(yelling) Enrique, mas grande la puerta!
(Homer moans)
Look, Homie! We got three pieces together.
That's a good day's work!
Why don't we do one of Maggie's puzzles?
Cow goes in the cow-shaped hole, boom.
Next case.
Hmm, I thought the one good thing
about you hurting yourself
was that we could spend
more time together.
-You did?
-Didn't you?
Oh, yeah, sure, of course.
Only a fool would admit otherwise.
-Mm....
-(doorbell rings)
-(sighs)
Mr. Smithers! Come in, come in.
(chuckling)
Oh! Well, there's our tangle-foot!
-Already on the mend.
-Yeah, right.
They say it'll be three months
before I can scratch my ass.
Six before I can really go at it.
Listen, I-I don't want
to take up your time.
I just need Homer's signature
on a couple of things.
-First, a get-well card to himself.
-(Homer moans)
And what else does he need to sign?
Oh, a... (coughing)
...waiver of liability.
I know, I know.
There are solid reasons to sue.
But do you really want to fill your life
with parasitic attorneys
with get-rich-quick schemes?
Schemes? Rich? Quick?
Parasitic? Whoo-hoo!
How could I have forgotten
to sue Mr. Burns?
That's how you get rich in America.
Sue S. A! Sue S. A!
Oh, Lord.
Finally, a chance to use this.
It was designed ironically,
but I would die for it.
Are you home during the day
because you were injured at work,
school, museum, church,
Iraq, elevator plummet,
uneven sidewalk,
hit by foul ball, hit by fair ball,
or Iditarod viewing party?
The first one! The first one you said!
Call me, Maxwell Flinch,
at 555-555-5555.
Five, five, five...
Wait, what was the number
after the first three fives,
but before the last six fives?
Uh, Simpson, before you do anything rash,
Mr. Burns wanted you to enjoy
this get-well cake.
-What's that writing on top?
-Oh!
It's just, uh, strawberry boilerplate
absolving us of liability.
Now just bite here, here, here,
nibble here, lick here.
Uh, your wife needs to eat this cupcake.
Sir, you cannot bribe me with cake.
Because I just ate several pies.
Hello, Mr. Smithers.
I see you haven't given up.
(sighs) Just enjoy the cake.
As long as you don't eat it
in front of a notary public, you're fine.
I'm a notary public.
You gave your ink pad to Maggie.
(moans)
-I'll, um, I'll walk out with you.
-Don't go yet.
You guys can help me brainstorm
a pattern for my new quilt.
Marge, I mean this in the nicest way--
your idea of fun makes me
want to blow my brains out.
(murmurs disappointedly)
Oh, Razzmatazz is perfect, Marge.
It's-it's uh-- it's red,
-but not, uh, too red.
-You're right!
Why don't you stick around and we'll
discuss stitching patterns over tea?
I'd like that.
And I'll take the cake back to the home
and share it with the seniors.
-Typical.
-I'll keep Dad company.
-Thank you, Bart.
-GRAMPA: (moaning) Oh, I dropped it.
Hey, wha-what did you put down my back?
Could be a tarantula,
could just be some yarn.
-I'll be at Milhouse's.
-(whining fearfully)
(sighs)
What the hell?
Oh, it's such a pleasure
to pour tea for someone
and not have to help him chew it.
We've made our choices.
And the world doesn't understand them,
but we do.
-Oh!
-Ew...
-Oh...
-Aw...
You know, Marge,
somehow I feel that more than anyone,
you understand those horrible words,
"What do you see in him?"
I never said this, but did you ever think
we cling to these guys
because we're afraid to admit
we were wrong?
Do you really think that?
Well, I've tried to use it constructively.
(Marge groans)
I try to have the serenity
to accept the things
I cannot change and the courage
to change the things I can.
HOMER: That's what they said to me
at that Alcoholics Unanimous meeting!
(groans)
LISA: Attention, bus riders!
My new seating plan avoids conflict
through the use of
complex social algorithms.
It teams up compatible seatmates
and places Milhouse with no one.
Yet somehow, I'm still a little scared.
Otto, why are you sitting in back?
Waiting for my assignment, chief.
-The driver's seat. You're the driver.
-Still me?
(scoffs) New management, same mistakes.
It's so quiet. I've never been
able to hear my music before.
(rock music plays over headphones)
Ooh, it sucks.
LISA: (thinking)
This is just the beginning.
Soon I'll have control over
every aspect of their lives.
And then I'll make them achieve
their un-dreamt dreams.
Sherri next to Terri.
Jimbo next to Dolph.
No one next to Milhouse.
Ralph next to his invisible friend.
Kearney next to Nelson.
Martin next to Wendell.
Cosine next to Database.
(gasps)
My first PG-13 fantasy.
Since we haven't been able
to get a settlement,
we'll have to start preparing you
for your deposition.
Caroline here will stand in
for the opposing attorney.
Good afternoon, Mr. Burns.
Release the hounds.
Uh, sir, you should try to project
a friendlier demeanor.
Release the hounds.
Please.
Seriously, sir, it would really be wise
not to mention the hounds.
Oh, that's like telling Three-Finger Brown
he can't play for the Brooklyn Tip-Tops.
(groans)
Waylon, now I can see
why so many women in movies
have gay friends.
Like Princess Leia and C-3PO.
Listen, I made this for you.
(gasps) Oh, my God.
No one ever gives me a gift. Thank you.
No one ever tells me "thank you."
I think you see my true self.
The one I never pay attention to at all.
(thinking) Oh, my God. I want to kiss him.
(thinking)
Oh, my God. She wants to kiss me.
-I'm a married woman.
-She would look good with a mustache.
(cell phone vibrating)
(chiming)
Uh, I've got to go.
Thank God I've got
a husband with benefits.
-Come here, you.
-Okay, but... (exclaims)
Mmm... Smithers.
(Homer thinking) Wait a sec.
Marge is getting her emotional needs
fulfilled by another man,
and now she needs me for nothing but sex.
I'm the luckiest husband in the world!
You haven't gotten that
stupid signature yet?
No. And I'm not sure I want to.
You defy me?
Smithers, pour me a glass of water.
Now squeeze my chest.
(coughs)
Now, either get that signature
or you're in charge of restarting
our plant at Chernobyl.
-That was us?
-That doesn't leave this room.
Well, brother,
prepare to enjoy another day of calm,
peaceful behavior on the school bus.
I got to warn you, a lot of kids
are pretty unhappy
with the required seating.
(chuckles)
Well, they'll be happy
when I also organize cafeteria seating,
who's picked for teams,
and I've divided the playground
into swingers and pushers.
That's insane.
You just bought yourself
a year of pushing.
LISA: (thinking)
Order. Order. Maintain order.
Tunnel.
♪ ♪
(gasps)
Whee!
♪ ♪
This message couldn't be clearer.
The children need more sauce
on their spaghetti.
-Also, their spelling is atrocious.
-(tires screech)
Well, at least I have me photos.
(screams)
(laughter)
I thought I had made things better.
Lisa, the bus is supposed to be crazy.
It's the brief respite
between the twin nightmares
of home and school.
The one thing a know-it-all doesn't know
is that everyone hates a know-it-all.
Did we, uh, lose anyone?
Just the police chief's son.
(beeping)
I bit a rat.
(clears throat)
Marge, this is the last time
I'm coming by.
Oh. Well, that's fine.
I mean, I do have my knitting to get to.
♪ Mm-hmm ♪
I'm going to a living hell
followed by a certain death.
Here's a picture to remember me by.
Taken by my grandma from her deathbed.
(sniffles) The last thing she saw.
Mmm. Mmm. Mmm.
-(groans)
-What's wrong, honey?
Oh, I don't feel like
I have anyone to talk to.
I appreciate that, and I'd like to talk.
I'm just so drained after all the time
I spend with the kids.
-BART: What time?
-I took you to that colonial village.
That was a pub at the airport.
I had an ale. You sat on a barrel.
That makes it colonial.
Homer, I'm sorry, you have to understand.
Without Waylon to talk to,
I feel completely alone.
I totally get it.
-One question-- Who's Waylon?
-Smithers.
Totally get it.
Oh, my wife really needs something
and to get it I may have to forego
my settlement.
Homer, you fell down a trapdoor
into a cement mixer.
Don't you think I deserve
something for that?
I'm just trying to do what's right.
Then why did you file a lawsuit?
I really think you should
change the venue, sir.
You can't win a case in this town.
Oh, are they still mad
about me eating the town panda?
Get over it.
-(blows nose)
-Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I'm willing to sign
anything you want on one condition.
Fine. What's your condition?
-You have to keep Mr. Smithers here.
-I see.
And are you fool enough to believe
a man's handshake means anything?
-I am.
-Well, put 'er there.
Homer, no!
Why doesn't anyone
ever think of the lawyer?
Aw, if I do a slip 'n' fall
on the courthouse steps,
-would that help?
-(sniffs) It might.
See you Thursday.
And I'll see you Thursday night.
Oh. (chuckles)
And I'll see you early Friday morning.
-Mm-hmm.
Oh, these slippery stairs.
(exclaims)
-(gasps) Homie!
-Marge, no!
(both grunting)
(honks)
Marge, I know Smithers
was good at talking to you.
-And I want to talk to you, too.
-Oh.
Just don't expect me to be great at first.
Oh, honey,
no one's great their first time.
It's like baking.
Uh, okay, well, uh...
I like you.
And I adore you.
You sacrificed yourself for my happiness.
There is nothing that makes a woman
feel more cherished and secure.
Thank you, my darling.
(whispers) Marge, this is going great.
GRAMPA: Now don't you worry,
I made you both soup.
Ooh-hoo, it's pipin' hot.
Two hours in the microwave.
(exclaims)
Who knows what the "D.C." stands for
in Washington, D.C.?
Anyone? Anyone?
Mustn't be a know-it-all.
Never again. Not worth it.
D.C. Anyone?
-Daddy's kitchen?
-(grumbles)
Not quite. Anyone else?
No? Okay.
Children, "D.C." stands for
"District of the Capitol."
No it doesn't!
The answer is "District of Columbia."
And, Miss Hoover,
I don't want to be a smarty pants,
but the previous answer was Texas.
Before that, 1848.
Before that, Seward's Folly.
And your dentist appointment
is not tomorrow, it's the day after.
Thank you.
♪ The wiki-wakka liki-lakka Mr. Burns ♪
♪ The wiki-wakka liki-lakka... ♪
Subtitled by A. Vandelay