(SlNGlNG) The Simpsons
(TlRES SCREECHlNG)
D'oh !
(SCREAMlNG)
(TlRES SCREECHlNG)
(LAUGHlNG)
Where are your clothes
for the gentleman
who is big and fat?
The basement, sir.
Woo-hoo!
Homer, before you get
anywhere near the escalator,
you've gotta tie those shoes.
Homer!
Ow!
So many shoppers!
Damn this. . . Ow!
Resilient economy!
(SCREAMS lN PAlN)
(SlGHS)
(LlSA GROANS)
This is our
Little Hooker line.
All the girls your
age are wearing it,
except the freakishly
unpopular.
But l'm eight
years old !
So is your look.
Are you aware that
you've exposed your skin
to a whole host of
airborne de-beautifiers?
No.
This dermal magnifier
will show the extent
of the damage.
(GASPS)
(GROWLlNG)
(SCREAMS)
He's eating my beauty!
Mmm-hmm.
Skin mites love
the taste of beauty.
Try this
rejuvenating lotion.
lt contains over
60 ingredients.
Ooh !
(MOANlNG)
l hope he didn't
have children.
Did he have children?
Millions of them !
(GRUMBLES)
(HOMER HUMMlNG)
Sir, other customers need
to use that dressing room.
Dressing room?
Uh-oh.
Edna, we don't
need wedding china.
The dishes mother won
on Let's Make a DeaI
are holding up nicely.
Seymour, if we register
for these dishes,
our wedding guests
will buy them for us.
And l suppose
those wedding guests
will also pay for
dishwashing liquid,
heated water
and two-sided sponges?
(SCOFFS)
Silent anger,
the cornerstone of
a successful marriage.
(HUMMlNG)
Cool. Guns.
Die, happy couples.
(lMlTATES GUN FlRlNG)
That's not a toy, son.
lt's a barcode reader.
lt registers wedding gifts.
Bull-honky.
No. Not bull-honky.
A couple uses the gun
to select gifts they want
for their wedding.
BART: Wow.
lf you'll excuse me,
l'm going to the employee
lounge to finish my Shasta.
Hmm. . .
"Name of groom,"
Bart Simpson.
"Name of bride,"
Lotta Cooties.
(LAUGHlNG MALlClOUSLY)
(BEEPS)
(WHITE WEDDING PLAYING)
It's a nice day
for a white wedding
to start again
(LAUGHlNG MlSCHlEVOUSLY)
(MUSlC STOPS)
A fake wedding?
That's what
l call chutzpah !
Yeah. l'm gonna
scam this town out of
so many presents.
And what l don't use,
l'm gonna return
for store credit!
(SlNGlNG)
Store credit, store credit,
store credit
(SlGHlNG)
Another employee
family wedding.
What's the traditional
peasant gift in these parts?
A milking cow?
Actually, silverware
is all that's left
on the registry.
l'll see if Lenny
wants to go in on a spoon.
Remember, if anyone asks,
you're my niece
from out of town.
l am your niece,
Uncle Joe.
Good Lord, l'm an abomination !
(LAUGHlNG MlSCHlEVOUSLY)
This prank is my
Sgt. Pepper's.
l see neither blushing bride
nor ardent swain !
There is no wedding here!
(ALL GRUMBLlNG)
Oh, my God !
We're sealed in !
Nobody breathe my air!
Get your own !
(BREATHlNG HEAVlLY)
Why you selfish little maggot,
l'll suck your lungs dry!
Knock it off!
(ALL BREATHlNG HEAVlLY)
MAN: Okay. . .
(ALL FAlNTlNG)
Yes! (CHUCKLES)
So, you thought you'd
pull a fake wedding, eh?
You're under arrest.
Come on, Chief.
lt was just a prank.
Would some flatware
make things right?
Um, what does it say
on my badge?
(READlNG)
Let's go.
(BART SlGHS)
Bart, the record
of your mischief
is staggering.
Just look at this file.
That doesn't
look so big.
These are directions
to the facility
where Bart's criminal record
occupies three full
storage lockers.
Six feet by eight?
Six by 1 4!
(ALL GASP)
Bart Simpson,
l hereby sentence
you to six months
at the Springfield Juvenile
Correctional Facility.
Juvie? Please, Judge.
You can't! l'll do anything.
l'll squeal on my dad.
He's been up to bad things.
Crap you've never
even thought of.
We've already got
an informer working
deep cover on your dad.
One he'll never suspect.
ls it Lenny?
Damn it!
l mean, no.
(GRUNTS)
Now, take that kid away.
No! You're not gonna
take my baby to jail !
(STRUGGLlNG)
All right, boys.
She's not letting go.
Make the switch.
(RALPH HUMMlNG)
(MARGE SOBBlNG)
Your eyes need diapers.
Your eyes need. . .
That's good, Ralphie.
One slingshot,
one pack of cards,
baseball, one doodle.
(READlNG)
One harmonica.
Perfect mood setter
for the end of your freedom.
(PLAYS HARMONlCA)
Lessons by mail, worthwhile.
(SOBBlNG)
My baby boy is in jail.
l'm the worst
mom in the world.
lt's not all your fault.
All these years,
l watched you turn our
son into a time bomb,
and yet l did nothing.
So in a way,
l too am a victim. . .
Of you.
You're a great mom.
You were always there
for Bart with love
and support.
His acting out
was probably caused
by negative reinforcement.
Oh, l get it.
Blame the strangler!
(SCOFFlNG)
(SCOFFS)
Just because you've
done time at juvie,
doesn't mean the world
has given up on you.
See for yourself
the exciting careers
that wait for you
upon your release.
(ALL GASP)
These are all fast food jobs.
Ex-cons are a godsend
to employers like me.
lf you ask for a raise,
l just call your
parole officer,
and back in the can you go!
(LAUGHlNG)
(THE lTCHY & SCRATCHY SHOW
THEME PLAYlNG)
ALL: Yay!
(SlGHS) Cartoons.
America's only
native art form.
l don't count jazz
'cause it sucks.
Freedom !
Bloodshed !
l declare an end
to the spectacular
3-D blood and gore!
ALL: Yay!
They cut all
the good parts!
l've lost
everything l loved.
(GRUNTlNG)
Okay. lf l use my head,
l can keep out of trouble.
l better stay
out of the sandbox.
l could be buried alive.
Maybe the slide.
Don't forget to
buy your photos!
l'll just hang out
next to the girls' juvie.
Hello, ladies.
l'm Gina.
You touch my fence again,
and your puberty's
gonna be very boring.
(GRUNTS)
(ALL LAUGHlNG)
God, l hate this place.
lt's nothing like
the brochure.
lt's horrible in here.
The boys beat me up.
The girls beat me up.
Now, sweetie,
you shouldn't hang around
with people who beat you.
They're not true friends.
Time's up!
My poor boy is
miserable in here.
There has to be something
l can do to help him.
Oh. . .
lnteresting.
Marge, what does
that sign say?
So, why do you want
to be a guard here?
l believe that
children are the future.
Unless we stop them now!
Welcome aboard.
This end's for beatin'.
This end's for holdin'.
Ah. When does
training start?
lt just finished.
BOY: Catch !
Jump!
BART: That's my doll !
(GRUNTS)
Keep away! Keep away!
HOMER: Put that sissy down !
lf you're gonna
pick on someone,
why don't you pick on
someone much bigger
than you with a gun?
Dad?
That's right.
l got a job here,
so l can watch over you
like a mother hen.
His dad's a screw!
l sure am.
Here you go, Son.
l brought you a lollipop
from the guards' lounge.
Not so tough now, huh?
HOMER: Yeah.
(BUZZlNG)
Well, that's the end
of my shift. See you Monday.
Wait. Monday's
Martin Luther King Day.
Well, l'll see you
when l see you.
Love you !
(LAUGHlNG NERVOUSLY)
This lollipop's
really for everybody.
Studies show the part
of the brain that
remembers dance steps
is also the anger center.
So juveniles who
know how to fox-trot
are 1 0% less likely
to commit a double homicide.
Who conducted this study?
The institute of
shut-your-fat-face!
Now, pair up.
He's mine.
Him?
Why?
l like 'em small
and bug-eyed.
You two will dance,
and you'll like it.
Then you'll have punch,
and you'll drink it.
Then your eyes will meet,
and it will be awkward.
So help me, God !
(COCKS GUN)
(SLOW MUSlC PLAYlNG)
Okay, here's my rules.
Hands at 1 0 and two,
no eye contact
and l don't want to
hear how pretty l look.
Don't worry.
You won't. D'oh !
(GRUNTlNG)
We're gettin' outta here.
Whoa!
(ALL GASP)
They're escaping !
Seal the perimeter!
l'm on it!
Can't you go any faster?
l can close it faster
or l can close it right.
Can't you do both?
Talk to the union.
(SlREN BLARlNG)
l'm getting out in two weeks.
Why would l want to
break out with you?
(SWOONlNG)
Well, you do look
pretty in the moonlight.
(GRUNTS)
(DOGS BARKlNG)
Hey, guard !
Help! Help!
(MUMBLlNG)
Guess where
the next one's going.
Up my butt?
Why did you kiss me?
Are you looking
to do the Bartman?
Hey, l'm only sticking
with you till l get
these chains off.
And if we get caught,
l'm telling them
this was your idea.
Yeah. Why would
they believe you?
Because l can do this.
(SOBBlNG)
That mean boy,
he dragged me
out of the dance.
l didn't want to go,
but he was too strong !
But you got 20 pounds on me.
And then, he said l was fat!
Oh, l am screwed.
You bet you are.
Now as long as we're together,
l expect you to be a man.
But l have
to wizzle.
Fine.
(GRUNTS)
l miss prison.
I am not chipping
in on a birthday cake
for that jackass, Arnie Pye.
Let him eat...
This is Kent Brockman
live at Springfield
Juvenile Hall,
the scene of
a daring escape
by inmates Bart Simpson
and Gina Vendetti.
(ALL GASP)
To understand
the mind-set of the escapees,
we've brought in an expert,
former under-aged
offender, Snake.
If they're smart, Kent,
they'II stay off
the main roads.
It's aII here in my book,
Ten Habits of
Highly Successful Criminals.
AII right,
I pIugged your book.
Now, put down the gun.
Tell them l'll be
on Conan Thursday
with Heather Locklear
and Third Eye BIind.
Why would Bart escape
if he's gonna be
released in two weeks?
You just don't
understand boys.
He's stupid !
But he won't know
where to go
or what to eat!
Relax. What's the worst
that could happen?
You shall marry my daughter,
Moonhilda.
l can't wait to lay
my eggs in his brain.
No son of mine will be
marched down the aisle
at the barrel of a ray gun !
Let's go!
(DOOR SLAMS)
So why'd they
send you to juvie?
Shoplift a scrunchie?
Get bent.
l pushed Snow White
over the parapet
at Disneyland.
BART: Oh, man.
Did she live?
Yeah.
But it's not a good life.
Gina, before we get
any closer,
there's something
you need to know about me.
l think girls
are icky pants.
lt took a lot of
courage to say that.
Courage l'm gonna
pinch outta you.
(GlGGLlNG)
Say, Cletus,
have you seen a couple
of kids go by?
l don't have such
a good memory since
l drank my thermometer.
But l whittles what l sees.
(BANJO MUSlC PLAYlNG)
ls this them?
lt sure is.
We're on the right track.
What are you making now?
Oh, sometimes
l whittles the future.
Hmm. . .
Great. l can get
these handcuffs off before
l get a full-blown
case of the cooties.
Bart, l can't believe
you don't know this,
but there's no
such thing as cooties,
cootie shots,
cootie force fields
or cootie insurance.
But State Farm
took my money.
When we split up,
where are you gonna go?
Don't worry.
My family will hide me
until the heat's off.
Wow. Your parents are cool.
Oh, man.
There's a line.
You keep your ink
hole shut about this.
We're free! We're free!
Bart, l'm gonna
miss you so much.
Hey, the next time
my mom asks me to help
around the house,
l could come live
with your family.
(GRUNTS)
Don't get fresh
with me, jerk!
Take it from a blacksmith,
that girl's trouble.
That girl's nuts.
First she likes me,
then she hates me.
l've already forgotten
how ugly she is.
l'd better eyeball
that ape one more time.
(SCREAMlNG lN PAlN)
(GASPS)
CLANCY: God !
(SOBBlNG)
What's up?
Don't you want to get back
to that awesome
family of yours?
What are you crying about?
How cool they are?
Oh. l know
you're sad now.
But surely your
incredible family
will cheer you up.
(CONTlNUES SOBBlNG)
Wait. Do you even
have a family?
No, l don't!
They're imaginary,
like your brain !
l understand.
You don't
understand anything !
(GRUNTlNG)
You're such a psycho!
Mama's boy!
Future skank!
Family guy!
Well, well, well,
if it isn't Punch 'n' Juvie.
Plant the evidence
on 'em, boys.
Chief, we don't have to.
These ones are
actually guilty.
Super.
Makes our job
that much easier.
Oh, Bart, my troubled
little lamb.
You'll be in jail
for so long.
But l'll keep your room
just the way it was,
a pigsty.
Son, l want you to know
no matter what anyone says,
there's no shame
in being caught alive.
Take a good long look
at the innocent love
in your son's eyes.
Because when he
gets out of prison,
it'll be gone forever.
He will have
a great bod though.
And a couple of
those teardrop tattoos.
Those are cool.
There's something l
have to tell you guys.
Now, look, my fly
is down because
it's broken, okay?
No. lt's something else.
Bart, she took all
the responsibility
for the escape.
You're free to go.
But the kid's still got time
on his sentence, Chief.
Look, if you all
want to squeeze into
the backseat, fine.
With my box kite.
Oh, forget it.
Welcome back, Gina.
l got a few new
cellmates for you.
That's cool.
l wouldn't feel right
going to the bathroom
with no one watching.
(GASPS)
l thought you might want
to have a nice family dinner.
We're having
"Make Your Own Taco" night.
Gina, thanks for showing us
the meaning of Christmas.
And thanks for showing
my brother that girls
can be cool.
Who is this nerd?
Taco, please.
Well, my shift's over.
l guess it's back to
my bachelor apartment,
make a tuna sandwich,
turn on WiII & Grace
and cry myself to sleep.
(MARGE SlGHS)
Would you like to join us?
Didn't you hear me?
l've got an evening planned !
English - US - PSDH