CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
WIGGUM: Yeah, I know
Ralphie's birthday is coming up.
Of course
I'm gonna get him a present.
I'm at the...
the toy store right now.
Let's see, present for Ralph,
present for Ralph.
Ooh, what do we have here?
Boy, Ralph would kill himself
with this in two seconds.
And somehow it'd be my fault.
Mm!
This money has been sitting here
since 1998,
not doing anybody any good.
I want to get Ralphie
something nice.
Yeah, a few thousand should do.
Hm-mm.
(whistling a tune)
Uh, you heard me
whistling there, right?
That indicates innocence.
Uh, proclaiming your innocence
indicates guilt.
Oh, yeah?
Well, what does this mean?
♪ Skiddily bop and bah! ♪
(whoops)
(engine revving, tires squealing)
Okay, so at a Ralph party,
always get to the cake before...
Too late.
(both gasp)
BART: That's the best damn tree house
I've ever seen!
(heavenly music plays)
Fine.
I'll rub my eyes the other way.
(inspiring orchestral fanfare plays)
D'oh!
(lively chatter, laughter)
Whee!
Whee...!
Whoa!
The September issue!
(gentle classical music plays)
Ooh! Free wood!
(Homer whoops)
(groans)
Oh.
My tree house sucks.
Haw haw!
(singsongy)
You have class envy!
(slurring)
Nelson, honey,
I told you to stop sayin'
"haw haw."
Give me a dollar and I'll stop.
I don't got a dollar.
Haw haw!
(hums happily)
Do you want to practice
your speech on me?
(chuckles)
No need, honey.
Same speech I give every year.
The opening joke about
Lenny's grandma always kills.
You can't joke about her.
They just put her on life support.
What?! No! She's the linchpin!
It's okay, it's okay.
Everyone is terrified
of public speaking.
But just in case,
I'll defrost a failure ham.
(dramatic musical stinger)
You don't have faith in me!
I have savers.
If I get heckled, I'll say,
"Get a half-life!"
I'm sure that'll be funny to them.
Mm! (kisses)
(whimpers)
Calm down, Homer.
Just leave your body.
Oh, no!
What the hell is this?!
(humming happily)
(startled grunt)
Ooh, throwing away
your "No Girls" sign?
Is it time for you to have
"the talk" with your dad?
Because he's gonna have
to read a few things first.
No. I'm tearing it down.
Ralph has a cool tree house,
and mine sucks.
Well, Bart, your father built it,
and he did the very best he could.
(grunting)
I did my job.
Now it's your turn, tree.
Get growing.
I'll tell you what,
why don't I spruce it up for you. Huh?
But you're an inside grown-up.
Moms can't build tree houses.
You realize that saying that
is gonna make this mom
work her keister off
to make you the best darn
tree house you ever saw!
Sounds good.
(screams)
Don't worry.
You forget, most of that's hair.
BURNS:
(chuckles) So I said,
"Get a half-life!"
(laughter)
(laughs)
Funny and handsome.
And I hear he's loaded.
(chuckles)
Yes.
Now, to end this perfect day
on the perfect note,
Mr. Homer Simpson.
(footsteps echoing)
(footsteps echoing louder)
(man coughs)
You're gonna do great, Homer.
You're gonna kill.
You're gonna-- Oh, where did
all these people come from?!
-(gunshot)
-Aah!
Uh, uh...
Webster's Dictionary defines...
a speech
as a... series of words that...
-(murmuring)
-elo... quently...
I've never seen anyone
bomb like that.
Yeah.
I really feel badly for the guy.
-Boo!
(crowd booing)
(whimpering, shuddering)
I'm a failure.
Shall I release the hounds, sir?
Mm, the therapy hounds.
Oh, oh, I feel a little better.
Now release the real hounds.
(dogs barking, snarling)
(screaming)
It's a pretty good seminar this year.
Dad, what's wrong?
Did your speech go badly?
How do you know
something's wrong?
You're drinking from a can of corn.
Hmm? Eh.
Aw, Dad,
do you know Barbra Streisand
once forgot the words to a song
and didn't perform in public again
for nearly three decades?
Yeah, but she still
had James Brolin to cuddle.
So, on a scale
of ten to ten, how'd you do?
Um...
(water dripping)
♪ Drip drop, you flop ♪
♪ Drip drop, you flop,
drip drop, you flop, ♪
-♪ Drip drop, you flop ♪
-♪ Fail, fail, fail ♪
-♪ Drip drop, you flop... ♪
-♪ Fail, fail... ♪
What the hell is your problem, idiot?!
-(kettle whistling)
-(Homer gasping)
I don't know!
(sobbing)
(whimpers)
I know what will cheer you up.
We'll go to the comedy club downtown.
Downtown?
With all those desperate addicts?
Oh, the city cleaned them up
and made them comics.
Cool!
Homie, you're gonna chuckle
your blues away.
This is the best kind of comedy.
-No writers.
-Amen to that, Marge.
And I appreciate this,
but I really resent
the two-drink minimum!
You always drink more
than two drinks.
But no one makes me.
Three Long Island iced teas, please.
Okay, we're gonna perform
a little improv.
First we need a location.
Uh, 40.7 degrees north latitude,
74 degrees west longitude.
Ah, yes, New York City.
Now we need a relationship
for me and Cathy here.
Loveless marriage!
(laughs)
Okay, I heard loveless marriage.
These guys are pros.
All they did was ask
for two premises.
That's two more
than you've asked for.
(sighs)
Oh, boy.
All right, all we need now
is an object.
Anyone.
(quietly)
Fear of public speaking.
Sorry, didn't hear that.
Oh... fear of public speaking.
Maybe he has trouble
talking in the dark.
Hey, Jerry, bring up number seven.
(shrieks)
No! Jerry, no!
Aah! No! Aah!
Jerry, stop it! No!
Stop... Aah!
Oh, no! Oh-ho-ho! Aah! Oh!
Okay, okay, okay, um...
fear of public speaking.
Well, that's not really an object,
but we'll make it work.
New York City, loveless marriage,
fear of public speaking.
They've pulled back the bow;
now let the arrow take flight.
You know,
I'm gonna move over a seat.
We now take you to an apartment
on 68th and Columbus Avenue.
(trembling)
Oh... eek...
aah... aah... ooh...
What? What?
Cathy, what's wrong?
I-I... I-I...
I... ah-ah-ah... ah...
Aw, for heaven's sakes, Cathy,
when we got married,
you used to speak for hours.
But since we moved
to New York City, nothing!
-(crowd laughing)
-Wow. It all magically fits.
Come on, Cathy, say something!
Anything!
(Italian accent)
Fuggedaboutit!
(laughter, applause)
And scene!
I said "fear of public speaking."
Yes, you did. Very nice.
Return to your seat immediately.
Wow. Wow.
These guys do everything I can't.
Maybe they can teach me.
I don't know
that they're interested in that.
$500 for the first eight classes.
That's kind of expensive.
Couldn't people just form
their own groups for free?
And scene.
Uh, uh...
excuse me, is this the, uh,
improv class?
Yes, and... come in.
Sit anywhere?
Yes, and... be quiet.
HOMER:
This is it.
I feel my mind exploding
with premises.
♪ ♪
So many ideas,
but how do I turn them
into comedy?
♪ Oh, kiss me ♪
♪ Beneath the milky twilight... ♪
(chuckling)
Homer, could-could you
stay with us, please?
I don't know how.
The secret is to lose yourself
and become, say,
a suicidal auctioneer.
I could not possibly imagine
what such a person would say.
Well, just remember,
it's-it's not you.
Don't you get it?
The secret to life
has been right in front of you
all along:
Don't be yourself!
Uh, uh, okay.
What am I bid for this noose?
Do hear $100?
No?
Going... going...
(chokes)
(laughter)
That's great! Really took
my mind off my sick grandmother.
-(phone chimes)
-Oh.
Looks like the hospital
left a message.
-(voice breaking) Gotta go.
-HOMER: See ya!
(laughs)
It made me laugh.
-So, then you pay me?
-No, never!
And if you open your own school,
we'll break your legs!
You want to give him
the one we can never crack?
Queen of Norway buying a car.
(high-pitched)
Oh, dear! I can't a-fjord it!
A star is born.
(grunting)
Excuse me.
I'm from the city.
Are you aware that you live
in a historical tree house
preservation district?
♪ ♪
May I see your permits?
I don't have permits.
-(screams)
-Don't worry.
D-Don't worry.
I'll take care of it.
(grunting)
I've got to hand it to you, Dad.
You went
from fear of public speaking
to starting your own improv troupe.
Improv is exciting, but totally safe.
Like driving a helicopter on the ground.
Um, that's not safe.
Don't deny the premise.
That's anti-improv.
Note for new character,
"Auntie Improv."
(high-pitched)
May I hear a suggestion?
People, don't freak out,
but the improv critic
from the Springfield Shopper
is in the audience.
(gasps)
Steve Thurlson?
No, Thurlson is their improv reporter.
Grant Hood is their improv critic.
Then who's Jennifer Whitehead?
Oh, she writes improv think pieces.
You know, trends, big picture stuff.
Who does the top ten list
at end-of-year "Best of Improv" issue?
They each write their own.
-(all murmuring assent)
-Oh, yeah.
I forgot about that.
That's true.
Huh!
(piano riff playing)
(crowd cheers)
Hi, everybody.
We are "Premises, Premises."
Yes, it says on Google
that there are 5,012 improv groups
with that name.
LENNY:
Take it, Homer.
(nervously)
Uh, okay, I need a location.
Uh, Jackson Square in New Orleans.
And a type of person
that might be there.
Someone with confidence.
Mm, I...
(Cajun accent)
I ga-ron-tee it!
(laughter, cheering)
So, Tuesday
is the tree house warming.
Nelson's gonna show us his mom's bra.
(gasps)
That's the thing that boobs touch.
Whoa, automatic blinds.
Yeah, I think my mom put those in.
No need to thank her.
She's just doing her job.
(grumbles)
The Keebler Elves are real!
Pass the gravy, Bart.
Yo.
Thank you.
Geez, who ordered the crab?
(gasps)
There's crab?
There's no crab.
There's no "thank yous,"
no appreciation.
Nothing.
Uh, who was that directed at?
Bart!
Whew!
Pass the gravy, please.
(phone chimes)
(gasps)
Dad! Dad!
The Springfield Fringe Festival
just invited us to perform!
Huh?
What's a "Fringe Festival"?
My guess would be
it's a three-day series of performances
by alternative comedy and music acts,
including, but not limited to,
improv, stand-up, light circus work
and ironic burlesque.
We're gonna be on
the main stage on closing night!
This is going in my log.
Yay!
(chuckles)
More crab for me.
MARGE:
There's no crab!
Mm!
(humming happily)
(grunts, slurps)
Mmm!
(Marge grunting)
Aw, Marge,
don't take it to heart.
Kids are ungrateful;
that's their job.
You can cheer up watching me
at the Fringe Festival.
Good for you.
The main stage, closing night,
all eyes on you.
Wh-Wh-Wh-What...
what are you saying?
Oh, she's making me
nervous again.
But now I'm a trained
comedy amateur.
No one can get in my head.
MARGE:
Marge Simpson,
you don't want to accidentally
undermine him like last time.
Oh, thank God he doesn't know
what I'm thinking.
I know exactly what she's thinking.
That if I mess this up,
I'll be worse off than ever.
He does know.
She knows I know!
(Homer and Marge scream)
-Homer?
-(muffled) Aw, what?
I slept on it,
and I'm madder than ever.
Go get Bart.
Oh, my God, Marge,
you woke up with
morning-would-be-mad.
Okay,
I'll put this in your new language.
Location: Bart's room.
Action: bring him here.
Can I get a character, please?
Fine. Um...
A near-sighted Frankenstein.
Okay.
(growling)
Bride! Bride!
I do not look like
the Bride of Frankenstein.
Don't deny premise.
(growls)
(knocking on door)
(grunts)
BART:
Mom, can I come in?
You like your eggs
a little runny don't you?
-What?
-And your toast set at four,
with a little bit of butter?
Yeah!
Hash browns might be a little burnt.
I like 'em however you make 'em,
sweetie.
I just wanted to say
I'm sorry.
We all forget just how many
wonderful things you do.
Oh...
(gasps)
(voice breaking)
Y-You're making me cry.
-(sobs)
-And best of all,
you're as hot
as the day I met you.
(sobs)
Thank you!
That apology speech you wrote
worked like a charm, Pop.
Your mother can't resist
an apology
that comes
straight from the heart.
Of this box.
Oh, dear God,
this is not a Renaissance Faire, is it?
Uh, that's in two weeks,
Henry the Weight Problem. Ha!
Gee, I don't know if I belong here
with all this talent.
(goofy voice)
Hey, Reverend.
Why didn't the dinosaurs
make it on Noah's Ark?
(normal voice)
Ooh, I give up.
(goofy voice)
Because they didn't exist.
(laughter)
(carnival music plays)
Dad, this festival
encourages experimentation.
Even failure.
Oh, what if I don't fail?
Desperate times
call for desperate measures.
I am getting a helium balloon.
That makes anyone funny.
(high helium voice)
Be right back!
(Homer retching)
Homer, are you okay?
You look exactly like
Barbara Streisand did in 1967.
I can't think of anything funny.
Homer, Homer, relax,
you're a riot.
Remember how funny you was when
you was the confident Cajun?
Look, just let me
feed you the prompt.
Wait, you mean cheat at improv?
What would Del Close say?
He would say, "Do like Moe says,
and shut the hell up."
Who's Del Close?
Only the author of the best book
I intend to read someday.
Homer, the cemeteries
are filled with people
who didn't cheat at improv.
Hmm.
Okay, let's go over what you're
gonna call out one more time.
Uh, ethnicity: Cajun.
Location: back alley.
Good, good.
The back alley Cajun bit.
LISA: (high helium voice)
Dad!
Are you cheating
by planting suggestions?
-Maybe.
-(gasps)
(normal voice)
Have you learned nothing
from owning an unread copy
of Truth in Comedy?
It's either that or quit the show.
You can't let your troupe down.
They need your space work,
your strong choices
and scene-building skills.
Hey, lay off your dad, huh?
Everything that's
supposedly spontaneous
has already been planned, okay?
Reality shows, uh,
lip-sync singing, even...
(dramatic voice)
award shows.
No!
Yes.
That's why the losers don't show up.
B-B-But they have scheduling conflicts.
Yeah, right.
Dave Franco has a scheduling conflict.
No, no, I've heard enough.
I refuse to use
performance enhancing "sugs."
-(murmuring)
-It's Homer Simpson.
Homer Simpson's here.
(crowd continues murmuring excitedly)
Okay, everyone, I'm Homer Simpson,
and I need an occupation.
Cadaver salesman?
Drive-thru cashier.
Uh, frog gigger.
Finger kisser! Mwah!
Nurse.
You'll have to be more specific.
I need a nurse!
Back alley Cajun!
Mm-hmm!
Ah...
A father I can look up to.
Oh. Um, uh...
I hear... drive-thru cashier!
BOTH:
You wha...?!
Hello, welcome
to "Down-and-Out Burger."
Would you like fries with that?
-(laughter)
-A thousand?
Sure thing, Mr. Brando.
By the way, this is 1992.
(Homer chuckles, crowd laughing)
And now we're gonna do
something a little special.
Our father is gonna improv
live answers to questions
from the TV audience.
It only took us 27 years to do
what they could do in 1954.
Homer, time to bomb.
Hello! I've gathered you here
because I have
an important announcement.
This is the last episode
of The Simpsons.
It's been a good run--
Ah, just kidding!
The Simpsons will never end!
But I do have bad news.
If you're seeing this,
something has gone
horribly, horribly wrong.
Or you're watching
the international version.
In either case,
I have three minutes to fill.
And I can think of no better way
to fill that time
than to throw my hat into the ring
for U.S. President.
I have no previous experience,
no endorsements,
and no idea
when the election is.
That makes me
the most qualified.
By far.
I can beat Trump and Clinton
and Sanders.
Stupid Sanders.
I will make America great again.
Then not so great.
I will keep you on your toes.
I will not run for a second term.
I will walk.
I will drill, baby, drill,
until I find
the river of chocolate
that lies beneath
Hershey, Pennsylvania.
I will not only leave Gitmo open,
I will open Gitmo's tavern.
I believe that no one,
whatever his or her gender,
should have to use
the bathroom after I do.
I am a winner!
If the superdelegates oppose me,
I will destroy them with kryptonite.
I plan to win on the first,
second, and third ballots.
Maybe take a breather
on the fourth,
and come back strong
on the fifth.
And I'll get rid of
the boring Olympic events.
Like all of them.
I will increase American exports,
starting with my two stupid
sister-in-laws.
Uh...
sister-in-laws...?
Let's just call them
"American Uglies."
Soon to be "Canadian Sevens."
I would also like to apologize
for the horrible thing
I just said about Canada.
And so, I withdraw.
I throw my endorsement
to Jeb Bush,
and I trust it's not too late.
In conclusion,
God bless America,
and God bless Springfield,
in the beautiful state of--
Oh, wait.
I'm afraid my time is up.
-(crowd murmuring)
-Shh!
Subtitled by Jimmy Boots