CHOIR: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(Willie grunts)
D'oh!
(grunts)
(all scream)
Oh, my God, Morty,
what did you do?
-You killed the Simpsons, Morty!
-Oh, my God, no!
-No, I-I-I-I didn't mean to!
-Oh, no, no!
God, look at the baby one!
Oh, my God, Morty!
You killed
the entire Simpsons, Morty!
They're a beloved
(belches) family, Morty!
They're-they're-they're-they're
a national treasure.
-And you killed them.
-I-I-I-I'm just a kid!
I'm just a kid!
I don't want to go to jail!
Relax, Morty, calm down.
We'll take care of it.
Okay, I want you to take
that vial of Simpsons' goo
and this picture
to this address.
They'll make us new Simpsons--
you understand me, Morty?
-Me?! W-W-What are you gonna do?
-Morty,
I got to clean this place up
before somebody comes
snooping around.
You know how many characters there are
in The Simpsons, Morty?
There's, like, a billion
chara... (belches) ...aracters.
They did an episode where
George Bush was their neighbor.
Right, can't argue with that.
(spits)
(speaking in native tongue)
(roaring)
Hi-diddly-ho, neighbor!
Looks like you got
a spaceship in your...
Who are you?
♪ ♪
Rick, I'm back!
Wake up! Wake up!
Geez, it's about time, Morty.
Give me those.
(grunting, moaning)
(belching)
Huh, wow.
Hey, Morty, a little tip.
(belches)
Don't clean DNA vials
with your spit!
Let's go.
I'm driving this time.
Aw, no more guest animators,
man!
Okay, children.
I think it's safe now
to put on your math T-shirts.
Wait here.
(grunts)
Nerd!
Model U.N., and step on it!
Ha-ha!
(laughing)
Very good.
That is really... Oh!
Dog in box.
Genius.
(laughing)
All right, let's meet our two teams
of Mathletes, shall we?
First, the Springfield
Elementary Action Fractions!
They rhyme and they...
(groans)
And, uh, from the right side
of the tracks,
the Waverly Hills Elementary
No Equals.
They're spoiled and rich.
Yo! What did the right angle
say to the wider angle?
Well, not knowing these fellows,
I-I couldn't say.
You're obtuse!
(all laughing)
(groans)
Now, let's welcome our celebrity guests,
former winners of this very contest
and current high-flying--
yes, you heard me--
I said high-flying, high flying--
tech entrepreneurs!
Gary, Doug and Benjamin,
who invented Whereditgo.
That's an app that finds
the other apps on your phone.
Enables you to glayvin
with your friends' mobile hoyvin.
One year ago,
we were dateless nerds
living in our mothers' basements.
Now the basement we live in
is in a giant mansion.
-Yeah!
And we own some kind of sports team.
(laughs)
All right,
calm down, just calm down.
Now, here to support
these fine student scholars
is the man who loves math...
Math?!
I thought you said "meth"!
Drug reference!
Uh, seriously,
what am I here for?
-Nobody told you?
-They send a limo, I get in.
It takes me somewhere.
Then I watch the news later
to see what I did.
(crowd cheers and applauds)
What a nightmare.
That's fair enough.
Boo-hayvin!
The teams have created
introductory videos about themselves.
Let's watch them,
shall we, with our eyes?
NARRATOR: Springfield Elementary
was originally designed
as a storage facility for salt pork.
At some later point,
it was turned into a school.
CHALMERS:
Chalmskinn.
On hot days, pork grease
still comes out of the walls.
Oh, quit your whining.
FRINK:
And now, Waverly Hills.
Hi, I'm movie genius
Michael Bay.
I used to be all like, "Math?
Who needs that noise,
am I right?"
But I wasn't right.
The Waverly Hills math team
made me realize
that quadratic equations
are hotter
than a million Megan Foxes.
Math on!
Yo, Waverly Hills!
You guys rock!
Like my friend The Rock!
I know his real first name!
It's Dwayne!
I win Hollywood!
Celebrate now,
you stuck-up snobs.
(cheering)
But our plucky little school
is going to surprise you.
We will surprise you all!
-(cheering)
-Well, Lisa,
we didn't score a single point.
That was surprising.
(crying)
Oh, you'll get them
next time, honey.
No! No, we won't!
That school is so rich!
Every kid has a laptop!
Her crying is sadder
than a child actor
"Where are they now?" story.
LISA:
It's true.
As graduates
of Springfield Elementary,
we want to give back.
We're going to buy
every student a tablet computer
and upgrade your entire school
with the latest
cloud-based technology.
Here's a check.
Take this check.
NARRATOR:
The first black president...
is decades away
from being a reality.
Come back with my fall semester!
We don't need filmstrips like
Life in These 48 States anymore,
because our school is going all digital!
-(grunts)
-WILLIE: Ow, damn it!
The teachers union won't stand for this.
It means less work for you.
I didn't know
it was possible to do less work.
How intriguing.
♪ He said
I've been to the year 3000 ♪
-♪ Not much has changed ♪
-♪ But they lived underwater ♪
-♪ Underwater ♪
♪ And your great-great-great
granddaughter ♪
♪ Is pretty fine ♪
♪ I took a trip to the year 3000 ♪
♪ This song had gone
multiplatinum ♪
♪ Everybody bought
our seventh album... ♪
And if we're ever invaded,
just click this.
♪ I took a trip to the year 3000 ♪
♪ This song had gone multiplatinum ♪
♪ Everybody bought our seventh album ♪
Oh, it's wonderful.
We can finally afford
attractive teachers.
(groans)
I was the only one here
who understood osmosis.
Spare me, uggo.
(groans)
Willie, since all our books
have been digitized,
we have no need
for the paper versions-- burn these.
Wouldn't it be easier
just to toss them out?
Nonsense!
We now have this state-of-the-art
-digital book burner.
-Hmm.
(laughs)
Listen to her hum.
What's that?!
Well, we didn't want to leave you
out of the digital revolution.
Willie, meet your new supervisor.
Aw, I have to take orders
from a machine?
Oh, it can't speak.
But should it ever learn, yes.
("Star Spangled Banner" playing)
(groans)
Will there ever be a technology
that teaches stupid children
how to ding a dang triangle?!
This school has spent the last 50 years
mired in the 1960s.
Let us spend the next 50
mired in now!
(singsongy)
Bo-ron!
And with this ring,
we unite these ancient
warring clans,
who frolic unclothed,
even in winter,
and bring peace to Decapita!
(screams)
Pay cable is awesome!
Who knew they had nipples
in castle times?
You're not supposed to be able
to get outside our network!
You shouldn't have made
your password "password."
Well, it was the name
of the street I grew up on.
Password Drive!
(crackling and buzzing)
Seymour,
you plugged the servers in
with surge protectors, didn't you?
Oh, yes, power strips.
You fool.
Surge protectors
are always power strips.
But not vice versa!
(screaming)
Was that us?
No, sir.
(chuckles)
I like it when it's not us.
(clock ticking)
Let's see.
Roman numerals.
Photosynthesis.
Uh, Robert E. Lee.
Miss Hoover, are you teaching
or are you just saying
anything that comes
into your head?
Miss Hoover,
please report to the main office.
You just did that in your hand!
Ralph Wiggum, put your head down.
You're the mouth-hand!
All right, class.
We don't have computers,
and we don't have keyboards.
But that doesn't mean
we can't practice our typing.
Now, put your index fingers
on marshmallows F and J, and...
tap-tap-tap.
Tap-tap-tap.
Tap-tap...
Nelson, stop that!
This is my dinner.
I'm eating steak.
Mmm! Mmm!
Needs sauce.
Great news, children.
I found an educational movie
I can play on my phone.
Crowd in--
it's kind of a little phone.
NARRATOR:
Mathematics! Agriculture!
Are there two more exciting words?
Since the time of the Romans,
they used scythes
to kill each other.
The ancient farmer needed tools
to measure his land.
Ten stick knots right.
Five left.
Hmm.
(humming a tune)
Oh, come to mock ol' Willie,
have you?
"Ooh, Willie has to work
in the hot sun all day.
Willie's best friend
is a stick and a string."
I'm not here to mock you.
"Ooh, Willie doesn't know
when someone's being sincere!"
I'm just here to hang out.
What's that device
you're using?
My rummlie scob.
Nothing exciting.
Just a measuring stick dating
back to the ancient druids.
Oh!
Could you tell me how it works?
Each knot marks the length
of a sheep's bladder.
A play field
is 75 stomachs by 52 kidneys.
That's 163 square haggises.
Move over, metric system!
I'm learning the gastric system!
Clever.
Uh, good news, sir,
I have assembled
a page on "the piglims"
at "Rhymouth Pock."
Yes, well,
that's the best we can hope for.
Uh, apply the transparent tape.
Principal Skin-ner!
Willie has showed me
that losing our technology
doesn't have to be
the end of our learning.
We can turn our school
into a Waldorf school.
You mean like the hotel?
Nope!
In elementary school,
Waldorf education focuses
on hands-on activity
and creative play.
In secondary education...
Ah, not our problem.
After sixth grade,
it's good-bye and good luck.
-(both chuckling)
-Yes, yes, it is.
Well, it sounds good,
but I have one more question.
Is it based on the book
where you find the guy in the hat?
Where's Waldo?
That's not even the name.
I'm surprised you guys didn't think
it was based on the salad.
BOTH:
There's a Waldorf salad?
(groans)
Behold--
Waldorf education in action!
We're getting our hands dirty
and learning by doing.
So I have to make 360 sloppy joes,
but I only have one pound
of hamburger meat.
How many cubic feet
of Styrofoam peanuts should I add?
Assuming four peanuts per joe,
37 cubic feet.
Well, you're a smart little fatso.
It says here that students
don't have to raise their hands.
They should just ask every question
that comes to their mind.
Oh. Why are pine needles pointy?
And, um-um-um, what's the difference
between an asteroid and a meteor?
And, mm... ooh-ooh!
Can you shrug anything
other than your shoulders?
(sighs)
Does anyone else
have any questions?
Um, if Mommy's purse
didn't belong in the microwave,
why did it fit?
We won't need computers,
we won't need books.
I learned not to drink
out of the crick.
You mean this isn't
crick water?
My daddy raised me
and all my 11 dead siblings
on crick water!
Huh, everyone wears a hat.
Sun hats in the summer,
wool hats in the winter.
Ooh, look at this.
Weekly Friday night parents' meetings.
Oh... Wait.
There might be a safety hatch.
Does the apostrophe come before
or after the "S" on "parents"?
After, which means both parents.
(groaning)
Well, I'm not wearing a hat.
People might think I'm bald.
(Homer grunting)
Before we share announcements
and see the results
of grade three's
dance study
of willows and drooping trees,
we greet the day with a school song.
Now I have to sing a song?!
Why did those idiots mix up
power strips and surge protectors?
♪ Every single living creature ♪
♪ Every cat and every flea ♪
♪ All things with a facial feature ♪
♪ Have the right to smile at me ♪
♪ Every family is a unit ♪
♪ Sometimes yelling,
sometimes mad ♪
♪ Divorced or gay or even foster ♪
♪ Even Billy with three dads ♪
HOMER:
I feel like Beethoven
when Charles Grodin
finally accepted him as his dog.
This school is so great now.
Kids learn by doing.
If it's so great,
why aren't you helping
your kids do their homework?
Bart's here doing it right now.
No, no, no!
Not two-thirds, one-half!
Now that's one-third each.
Now you're learning!
(laughs)
Enjoy.
One earthworm...
Gah!
Two halves.
ALL:
Wow!
Willie! Willie!
They want you to coach
our school math team!
I'll have to check
with my supervisor.
(dings twice)
Good to go!
So, if Willie gets paid
three cents per square foot
for seeding, and if the field
is 2,500 square feet,
what is Willie getting?
I'd say "screwed."
(groans)
You're right!
You! Chalmers!
Aah!
-Uh-oh.
-(tires screech)
Come back here,
you Willie-chiseling cheat!
(grunting)
(tires screeching)
(horn honking)
Hey, who threw that egg
at the most efficient
45-degree angle?
It was me, sir.
Kids,
meet your new math team captain.
It's about time.
But I'm the captain.
Not anymore.
I can't see.
Welcome to the long-anticipated rematch
between Waverly Hills and Springfield.
(crowd cheering)
(grunting)
Um, can you tell me
which college I should go to?
(stammers)
It's not a sorting hat!
Please!
Early applications are due next week!
All right.
Uh, Miami of Ohio.
(groans)
Okay.
Our first question is a toss-up.
"What is the least common multiple
of six, eight and 16?"
-48!
-Is correct!
(all gasp)
Whoa!
No one said there'd be math!
We said there'd be nothing but math!
And you're the math team captain!
I thought
I wouldn't have to do anything.
You know,
like an Italian cruise ship captain.
You're lucky that captain's not here
right now to answer your insult!
He'd crash a ship
right into your house!
Aah!
("Pi" by Kate Bush playing)
♪ Oh, he love, he love, he love ♪
♪ He does love his numbers ♪
♪ And they run, they run ♪
♪ They run him in a great big circle ♪
♪ In a circle of infinity ♪
ESPN isn't covering this.
D'oh!
♪ Three point one, four ♪
♪ One, five, nine ♪
♪ Two, six, five, three, five ♪
♪ Eight, nine, seven, nine ♪
♪ Three, two ♪
And so,
with the score knotted at 29-all,
it comes down to one last question.
Drawing three straight lines,
construct nine non-overlapping--
that's non-overlapping,
not overlapping,
but non-overlapping--
triangles.
HOMER:
Huh? Ooh.
(chuckles)
I have the answer!
(all gasp)
As someone whose dad's hair
is made of Ms, it's child's play.
HOMER: Oh, not this again.
Whoo-hoo! I'm a solution!
The Action Fractions win!
You guys might be richer
and better looking,
but we won a contest
to even the series!
Mm, that'll look great
in our trophy case.
Willie, build a trophy case.
Aye, sir.
But you know what we should
really thank for our success?
Lower standards!
ALL:
Aye.
You're wonderful, Willie.
You and the ancient
Scottish scientist
that invented the rummlie scob.
Well, the truth is,
it wasn't invented for science.
Really?
Then what for?
Oh, it was used
for hanging sheep stealers!
The wee knots
kept them alive longer
to make the punishment
more cruel.
(shudders) Maybe I don't want
to know these things.
Can you say something
nice about Scotland?
Well,
sometimes the fog comes in
and covers everything terrible.
Very atmospheric.
Oh.
♪ ♪
(gulping)
Shh!
Subtitled by Jimmy Boots