♪ The Simpsons ♪
(chalk screeches)
(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(tires screeching)
(horn honks)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
(alarm ringing)
Oh, no. I can't see.
I'm blind. Blind!
Ha ha!
April fool's.
Hee... hee...
Aah!
Ha ha! April fool's.
I been keeping
that carton of milk
next to the furnace
for six weeks. Sucker!
You're going down, Homer.
I'm gonna fool you.
You talk better than you fool.
I'll fool you up real nice.
You couldn't fool your mother
on the foolingest day
of your life
if you had an electrified
fooling machine.
Pee-yew.
(groans)
Ah, what noble visionary
thought up April Fool's day?
Like Halloween and Christmas,
April Fool's day
traces its origins
to pagan ritual.
God bless those pagans.
April first used to be
the pagan new year.
ALL (chanting):
Blood for Baal! Blood for Baal!
Blood for Baal!
LISA: The Christians
changed their calendar
and ridiculed those who didn't.
Happy New Year!
Heigh-ho, pagans.
New year's was three months ago,
but here's a present any-who.
It's ram's blood
for your godless ceremony.
(laughing)
April Fool's.
(snickering)
(growls)
ALL (chanting):
Now who's laughing?!
And that's the story
of April Fool's day.
Dad, I was
telling the story.
Oh, right.
Thar she blows.
The catch of the day.
-Arr.
-Arrgh. Arr.
Arrgh.
Arr.
Why, ye mutinous dogs.
From this day,
I be requiring hairnets.
Arr... argh... arr...
I've got to fool him
before the day is out.
But how?
He must have a weakness.
Ah, beer.
My one weakness.
My Achilles heel,
if you will.
Beer!
Beer is the cheese.
But how to use it...
Whoo! It's a good thing
that beer wasn't
shaken up any more
or I'd have looked
quite the fool--
An April fool, as it were.
(chuckles)
(evil laugh)
Hey, kid, that's for
customers only.
Did you know
there's a guy outside
handing out
free Stridex pads?
Wow! I'm in
pizza-face paradise.
Moron.
Ay! No es bueno!
So thirsty.
Eh! What are you
going to do?
ANNOUNCER:
The following
is a public service
announcement.
Excessive alcohol consumption
can cause liver damage
and cancer of the rectum.
Mmm... beer...
April f--
That sounded
like an explosion
at the old Simpson place.
Forget it--
That's two blocks away.
Looks like there's beer
coming out of the chimney.
I am proceeding on foot.
Call in a code eight.
We need pretzels.
Repeat, pretzels.
(panting)
Mrs. Simpson, I'm afraid
your husband is dead.
(gasps)
(chuckling)
April fool's.
He's very much alive.
Although I'm afraid
he may never walk again.
(all gasping)
♪ Row, row, row your boat ♪
♪ Gently down the stream... ♪
-Homie!
-Marge!
Homer has many,
many horrible problems.
These shadows are brain lesions
resulting from
numerous blows to the head.
(grunts)
(snoring)
Ah...
♪♪ ("Psycho" theme)
Ah!
And his brain waves are
disturbingly erratic.
You are wired into
the rest of your family.
You have the ability
to shock them
and they have
the ability to shock--
Just testing.
Whoa!
Ah!
Bart, how could you
shock your little sister?
My finger slipped.
Ah!
So did mine.
-Ay!
-Ah!
Bart, Lisa, stop that.
BOTH: Ah!
-Bart!
-Whoa!
DR. MONROE:
No, no, no.
No, wait a minute.
Wait, wait.
Folks, folks,
if I could--
This is not the way
to get healthy!
(Simpsons clamoring)
Mrs. Simpson,
can you think of anything
to account for all this?
I have no idea.
Unless it was that time
he kept falling down the cliff.
I won't jump anymore.
I promise.
Oh, thank God,
thank God, thank God.
-I love you, Dad.
-I love you, too, son.
You know, boy,
I don't think
I've ever felt this close
to you as I do right-- Huh?
Huh? What? Huh?
Ah!
D-ah!
CROWD: Ooh!
I'm gonna make it.
I'm gonna make it!
This is the greatest thrill
of my life.
I'm king of the world!
Woo-hoo! Woo-hoo!
I--
(screaming)
Ooh! Ow! Ow!
Oh! Yee! Yow! Oh!
Oh! D'oh! Ooh!
Oh! Oh!
(panting)
Yow!
Ow! Ow!
Ow!
(siren wailing)
Ah!
Ooh! Ow! Ow!
(grunting)
D'oh! D'oh! Ooh!
(panting)
Ow!
Hmm...
that still wouldn't explain
what I'm seeing here.
You look familiar.
-Have we met before?
-DOCTOR: Uh...
Clear.
Doctor, he's gone.
This is the part
of the job I hate.
(gasps)
You're a veterinarian?
That's right.
And for an extra $20,
I'll give Homer a tick bath
and then spay him.
-Here you go, Doc.
-Bart!
Shop around.
You can't beat that price.
You guys must have been
pretty worried about me.
Hey, we know
you're tough, Dad.
Remember that time
you got lost in the forest?
This is a trap.
It's gonna catch us
our dinner. C'mon, boy.
Shh! Just watch.
Ooh...
A-ha! Got him.
(distant thud)
Okay, okay,
this time, I'll just go
into the bushes over there
make a lot of noise,
and flush out a rabbit.
When he comes out,
you step on him.
Right, Dad.
(animals chittering)
Ah! Get them off me!
Get them off me!
(grunting)
It's true-- You have
good coping skills.
Your burgers are
getting cold, guys--
Holy moley.
Ah!
Oh!
Huh?
And there's one
Itchy and Scratchy cartoon
I don't think
we'll ever forget.
Ah!
Why did you
bring that up?
It was an amusing episode...
of our lives.
Thanks for coming
to visit me, Moe.
I brought you
a little present.
No... no...
beer bring pain.
I can't stand
to see him like this.
Ah... ah...
(muffled groaning)
(loud yell)
He really needs a girlfriend.
Oh, Marge, what if I wind up
as some vegetable
watching TV on the couch?
My important work
will never be completed.
Society's loss, I suppose,
but our marriage has been
through hard times
and we always pull through.
♪♪ ("Love Lifts Us Up
Where We Belong")
Huh? Huh? Huh?
Marge!
What a lovely surprise.
You're here to see
me, right?
Of course.
(cheering, applause)
Hey!
Way to go, Homer.
Way to go!
Hey, what'll
I tell the boss?
Tell him I'm going
to the backseat of my car
with the woman I love,
and I won't be back
for ten minutes.
(cheering, applause)
You can do it, Homer.
Stand up.
I can't.
He just won't budge.
I've tried everything.
Nothing can reach him.
Mmm...
(echoing)
chocolate.
(barking)
(yapping)
Wow, chocolate, half price.
Chocolate...
Bah! Bah!
Bah!
Can't breathe...
sweet chocolate...
cutting off air...
(gagging)
Mmm...
nuts.
(Homer gagging)
(swallowing)
Oh, yeah.
Poor Homer.
This world was never meant
for one as beautiful as you.
(gagging)
Ah! Kill it!
Kill it!
Grandpa, please,
he's in a coma.
Coma?
Why, I go in and out
of comas all the--
French toast, please.
Is a coma painful?
Oh, heck no.
You relive long-lost summers,
kiss girls from high school.
It's like one of those TV shows
where they show a bunch of clips
from old episodes.
Yeah, well, anyway,
I wonder
what he's thinking now.
(relaxing music plays)
This man is costing
my health plan $5,000 a day.
I demand that he die
with dignity.
Now, look,
I'm the doctor here.
Well, I demand
a second opinion.
Hi, everybody!
ALL: Hi, Dr. Nick!
(yelps)
Oh, dear.
I see no signs of life.
Just to be safe,
we'd better pull the plug.
Yoink.
Mr. Burns, how can you be
so coldhearted?
You have no idea, woman, what
that man's put me through.
HOMER: Uh, Mr. Burns,
I need to borrow
some money.
Please, do go on.
HOMER: I know
you're a good man
and I have a dog
that's very sick.
Oh, please, continue.
I thought maybe you--
Oh.
Well, thanks for your time.
I have an unorthodox solution--
A fantastic voyage,
if you will.
Three scientists,
one a beautiful woman,
will be shrunk
to microscopic size.
They will then rendezvous
in Mr. Simpson's lower colon.
ALL: Ew!
Well, we have had a little
trouble finding volunteers.
I wish I'd gotten to know
you better, Dad,
but there were times
when we really connected.
Hi, Dad.
Want me to cut out
this infernal racket?
Oh, let me
hear you play.
Why?
Does a father have to explain?
Let's just share
your gift, okay?
♪♪ (blues)
Oh...
(sobbing)
(wailing)
♪♪ ("When the Saints
Go Marching In")
Huh?
Yeah, that's more like it.
Oh-ho! Woo!
♪ Oh, I want to be
in that rumba ♪
♪ When the saints go
over there ♪
♪ Oh, over there ♪
♪ Oh, over there... ♪
I wrote this for you, Dad.
♪♪ (blues)
Dad, I'm so sorry.
I know I haven't been
a perfect kid.
-(rumbling)
-(gasps)
Why, you little--
♪♪ ("Raiders of
the Lost Ark" theme)
What the-- D'oh!
(horn honks)
(Bart snickering)
(primitive jabbering)
I know that I got you mad
once in a while.
(repeatedly yelling "D'oh!")
And sometimes,
I got into trouble.
(rattling)
Bart, you can't go
on like this.
I know.
(coughs)
But you always
looked out for me.
MARGE: Homer,
it's really coming down.
Could you check on the boys?
(thunderclap)
They're fine.
And no matter
what happens
I'll never forget
the advice you gave me.
Now come on, you're gonna
learn how to shave.
And finally, the little spot
under your nose.
Next, we take some
toilet paper
tear off some teensy
little squares
and stick one there,
and there,
and any place
you're bleeding.
There, and there.
Don't worry.
The blood will hold it
right on your face.
Now some after shave.
Ooh! Ah! Eeh!
(screams)
(groans)
Ah! You son of a--!
And that's how we shave.
Dad, it's all my fault.
I shook up that can of beer.
It was just
an April fool's joke.
(beeping)
(growling)
Why, you little--!
Homie, you're all right!
We're a family again!
(Homer growling,
Bart gagging)
This calls
for a celebration.
We're all going
to Hawaii.
(all gasping)
Gotcha!
It's April fool's
for two more minutes.
Dad, it's May 16th.
You were in that coma
for seven weeks.
Uh-huh.
(laughing)
You lost five percent
of your brain.
Me lose brain? Uh-oh.
(laughing)
Why I laugh?
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.