♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
D'oh!
-Ahh!
-(tires screech)
(fax machine beeping)
Aw, all these new
superheroes suck.
None of them
can hold a candle
to Radioactive Man.
The only decent new one
is Radiation Dude.
Naw, he's just a cheap imitation
of Radioactive Man.
Explain.
The similarities
are subtle but many.
For example, Radioactive Man
has his famous catchphrase
"Up and atom!"
with "atom" spelled a-t-o-m
in a delicious pun.
Go on.
While Radiation Dude
has a similar
but lamer catchphrase,
"Up and let's go."
So you kids fancy
yourselves experts, eh?
Well, between us,
we've read all 814 issues
of Radioactive Man.
Yeah, and we both
have the special
limited edition issue
where he and fallout boy
get killed on every page!
Well, I suppose you know then
that Hollywood is planning
a feature film
about Radioactive Man.
(gasping)
I have got
to do something
about that air
conditioner suction.
Who's going to play
Radioactive Man?
I will tell you
in exactly seven minutes.
Okay, here we are.
"Alt-dot-nerd-dot-obsessive.
"Need know star
RM pic."
I don't see why
Rainier Wolfcastle
should be the star.
I think we should
bring back Dirk Richter.
Kids will want to see
the original Radioactive Man.
I keep telling you--
He's 73 years old,
and he's dead.
Granted, but--
Besides, we want to stay
as far away
from the campy '70s
version as possible.
Billowing backpacks,
Radioactive Man!
It's the worst villain
of them all!
The Scoutmaster!
I see him, Fallout Boy.
(a la Paul Lynde)
Go get them, scouts.
Don't be afraid to use
your nails, boys.
(laughing)
♪♪ (rock)
(shudders)
So, where could we
shoot this picture?
We need a city that has
a nuclear reactor and a gorge,
and can guarantee us
the full corporation
of city officials.
I'll check Variety.
Wow!
Look at that ad!
All right,
this place must be hot.
They don't need a big ad
or even correct spelling.
I agree
with that logic.
Get me two plane tickets
to the state
that Springfield is in.
All right, we have
$30 million to spend.
We'll blow up our dams,
destroy forests, anything.
If there's a species of animal
that's causing you problems,
nosing around your camera,
we'll have it wiped out!
Look, we just want
to make movies,
not kill things.
Right.
We understand.
SKINNER (on PA): Students,
I have an announcement.
One of your favorite comic
book heroes, Radio Man--
Radioactive Man,
stupid!
Strange, I shouldn't have
been able to hear that.
Anyway, a Hollywood studio
has decided to film
the Radioactive Man movie
here in Springfield.
(all cheering)
And they will be holding
auditions
to find a local youngster
to play Fallout Boy.
(all gasping)
Oh, and the air conditioner
will be fixed this afternoon.
(all munching)
Look behind you,
Radioactive Man!
The sun is exploding again!
Bart, why are you
talking like that?
Yeah, and who the hell
are you talking to?
Marge, do you have
other men in this house?
Radioactive men?
I'm practicing
my Fallout Boy dialogue.
If I get this role,
I could finally come to terms
with this funny little muddle
called Bart.
Everyone is talking about
Radioactive Man
y'all.
Wow! You mean,
you were one
of the original
Little Rascals?
Yeah.
Which one were you?
The ugly one?
Were you the ugly one?
No. I was the tough kid,
Smelly.
My shtick was looking into
an exhaust pipe
and getting a face
full of soot.
Nobody could do that
better than me.
Of course, it was kind of
hard to think of reasons
for me to look in that
exhaust pipe every time
but, you know,
we had good writers.
William Faulkner
could write an exhaust pipe gag
that would really
make you think.
If you were such
a big shot,
why aren't you
still making movies?
Moe?
Oh, no.
My favorite aggie.
Huh?
(car engine starts up)
You stole my bit!
That's my bit!
Ooh, ooh,
you stole my bit!
Cut!
Oh, my God!
He's killed
the original Alfalfa!
Yeah. Luckily, Alfalfa
was an orphan
owned by the studio.
-ALL: Oh, I see.
-Yeah, that makes sense.
With wealthy Hollywood
people on the way
local merchants
can be forgiven
for raising their prices
a little.
Watch out,
Radioactive Man!
(all rehearsing line)
Watch... out...
Radioactive Man.
-Watch out!
-(gasping)
Radioactive Man!
(cheering)
Totally awesome.
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you.
It's all in the delivery.
Now is the winter
of our discontent.
Oh, no! Run!
Wow!
(cheering)
Mom... Don't make
me do this.
I don't want to be
an actor.
Nonsense.
You're going to be great.
Now take off those glasses
so they can see
your beautiful eyes.
(monotone)
"At last the world is safe,
eh, Fallout Boy?"
-"Watch ou--"
-Next.
Ha ha!
Hey, that hurts.
No wonder no one came
to my birthday party.
"At last the world is safe,
eh, Fallout Boy?"
What's for lunch
tomorrow?
-Next.
-Chicken necks?
We're never going to find--
Wait a minute.
That child has the exact
qualities we're looking for!
He's perfect!
What is his name?!
I don't know. He just came along
with one of the others.
He didn't
sign up officially.
Oh, forget him then.
It wouldn't be fair
to the other children
who filled out their
application forms in full.
Next!
"At last the world is safe,
eh, Fallout Boy?"
Watch out, Radioactive Man!
Brilliant reading. Again.
Fantastic! One more time.
Watch out, Radioactive Man!
Congratulations, Bart Simpson!
You're our new
Fallout Boy!
That's what
I'd be saying to you
if you weren't
an inch too short.
Next.
I've got to grow
an inch by tomorrow
or I won't get that part.
Pull, you mighty stallions!
Pull! Show me no mercy.
Oh!
(alarm clock ringing)
Oh, I only grew
half an inch.
I'm still too short.
Growing half an inch in one day
is still pretty good, Bart.
Yeah, that's how fast
Grampa's shrinking.
Oh, I'm as tall
as I ever was.
Is there any way
I can look taller
without actually
being taller?
Good news,
gentlemen.
I've grown that extra
inch you wanted,
plus several feet more.
We've found our new Fallout Boy!
-(gasps)
-And he's right over there.
Huh?
Ladies and gentlemen,
meet America's new Fallout Boy.
(cheering)
Out of the way.
Milhouse, baby!
Lionel Hutz, your
new agent, bodyguard,
unauthorized biographer
and drug dealer...
keeper-awayer.
(screaming)
Leave me alone!
Mom! Dad!
Make them stop!
What is all this stuff?
We've heard
you've become a star.
We decided we better start
living in the fast lane.
What if I'm not a success?
How will you pay
for all this?
I'm sorry,
I can't hear you, son.
I'm wearing a jacuzzi suit.
(groans)
Oh! I just missed out
on the greatest opportunity
of my entire life.
George Burns was right.
Show business is
a hideous bitch goddess.
Cheer up, Bart.
Milhouse is still going
to need a true friend.
Someone to tell him he's great,
someone to rub lotion on him
someone he can hurl
whiskey bottles at
when he's feeling low.
You're right, Lis.
I can suck up to him
like the religious people
suck up to God.
(banging)
Guess what, kids?
They're gonna pay us
$50 a day
to film some
of the movie here.
We'll run that cable
through here.
Careful, now.
Hey...
Didn't you direct
"Unnatural Discretion"?
Well... yes, I did.
Hoo-wee!
Whoo! Oh!
You know, I never
walk out of a movie
but yech!
(clearing throat)
I've got an idea,
Mr. Simpson--
Why don't you get something
to eat from our food truck?
(distant panting)
Mr. Simpson?
You've got to give me
the part of "Krispy the Klown."
I'm sorry.
You're wrong for the part.
But look at my range.
I'm sorry. "Krispy the Klown"
has been cast
but I will hire you
for "Angry the Clown,"
"Silly Sailor,"
and "Dr. Clowneous."
I won't let you down.
Well, I might let you down
on "Silly Sailor."
Up and atom.
Up and at them.
Up and atom!
Up and at them!
Better.
Hi, Milhouse.
Hey, I want you to know
that I'm glad at least
one of us got the part.
Milhouse!
I didn't do it.
I wished him well.
I wished him well!
(screams)
The stupid dummy wasn't
supposed to explode yet.
(sighing)
There's the real Milhouse.
(tires screeching)
(gasping)
Milhouse!
Hey! You're not Milhouse.
No, I'm just Milhouse
when he gets hurt.
(groans)
Okay, let's get
the real Milhouse over here
under the X-ray truck.
Hi, Bart.
Hey, cool, Milhouse.
You get to be crushed
by a truck.
It sounds like more fun
than it really is.
Hey! I think I'm lying
on a broken bottle.
Beautiful! Use it.
Okay, Fallout Boy
origin scene-- Take one.
Action!
(sizzling)
(grunting)
Up and at them.
Thanks for the help,
mysterious stranger.
Say, I think those X-rays
gave me super powers.
DIRECTOR: And, cut!
That was perfect.
Let's do it again.
Uh, these aren't
real x-rays, are they?
Good question!
We'll check into that.
Okay, X-ray machine
to full power
and... Action!
(sizzling)
Uh, sir, why don't you
just use real cows?
Cows don't look
like cows on film.
You got to use
horses.
What do you do
if you want something
that looks
like a horse?
Usually we just tape a
bunch of cats together.
You guys work
on the movie?
You saying
we're not working?
Oh, I always wanted
to be a teamster.
So lazy and surly.
Mind if I relax
next to you?
(yawning)
Mm-hm. Mm-hm.
Oh, here he comes.
What is it now,
Quimby?
Nothing, nothing, only
the city has just passed
another tax
on puffy directing pants.
But I don't wear
puffy pants.
I meant a tax on
not wearing puffy pants.
-Oy!
-I'm sorry.
Wow! You really got it
made now, Milhouse.
This is living.
Is it, Bart?
Is it really?
Yeah.
Ever since I became
a movie star
I've been miserable.
I had to get up
at 5:00 a.m. just for makeup.
I like the way the blush
brings out my cheekbones
but it's not worth it.
And making movies
is so horribly repetitive.
I've said "Jiminy jillikers"
so many times
the words have lost
all meaning.
We've got to do the "Jiminy jillikers"
scene again, Milhouse.
(growling)
But we already did it.
It took seven hours,
but we did it.
It's done.
Yes, but we've got to do it
from different angles
again and again
and again
and again and again.
(screaming)
Yeah...
(sighing)
I can't believe Silly Sailor
beat us both up
and imprisoned us
in his floating aqua world.
Jiminy jillikers!
Tut-tut, now.
There's no need
for profanity, Fallout Boy.
Everyone in town has been
gouging us silly
but it's worth it.
It's all up there
on the screen.
Yes. That Milhouse
is going to be big.
Gabby Hayes big!
Okay, listen up, everybody.
This is the hardest,
most expensive scene in the movie,
and we only get one shot at it,
so we have to do it right.
Fallout Boy will untie
Radioactive Man
and pull him to safety
moments before he's hit
with a 40-foot wall
of sulfuric acid
that will horribly burn
everything in it's path.
Now, that's real acid, so
I want to see goggles, people.
Real acid?
Okay, roll film...
tip the acid vats...
and action!
(grunting)
Only Fallout Boy
can save me now.
Where's Fallout Boy?
(gasps)
Fallout Boy!
Uh-oh.
My eyes!
The goggles do nothing!
(crashing)
Ah, ooh! Ah!
Where in the hell is Milhouse?
That one shot cost us
a million dollars.
KRUSTY:
Where's the producer?
I want to talk
about this coffee.
Milhouse!
-Milhouse!
Thanks to modern
editing techniques,
we can use existing footage
to complete the film
without Milhouse.
Watch.
It looks like we're
in trouble, Fallout Boy.
Jiminy jillikers,
Radioactive Man.
We'll have to
fight our way out.
Are you ready?
Yes.
(grunting and groaning)
Seamless, huh?
-You're fired.
-And with good cause.
(sniffing)
(growling)
Go!
Okay. We can all
stop worrying now.
These dogs never fail.
But... will they
just find Milhouse
or will they find him
and kill him?
Well, they'll-- When they
find him, they'll, um...
(mumbling)
Uh, excuse me.
You didn't answer me.
You just trailed off.
Yeah.
Yeah, I did kind of
trail off there, didn't I?
I know Milhouse.
I'll just check
all his old haunts.
Have you seen Milhouse?
No. Now, go away.
We're racing
for the title
of the champion
of the universe.
All right.
Yo, Dr. S., have
you seen Milhouse today?
No.
Okay. Thanks.
Wait. Did you know
that there's a
direct correlation
between the decline
of Spirograph
and the rise in
gang activity?
-Think about it.
-I will.
No, you won't.
The only place left
is the tree house.
Aha!
Stay away from me, Bart.
I mean it.
I'm not going back.
I'm not cut out
to be a star.
But, Milhouse,
being a star
is every patriotic
American's dream.
Not mine.
It's a sham, Bart.
You get up on that movie screen
pretending to be a hero
but you're not.
The real heroes are out there,
toiling day and night
on more important things.
Television.
No. Curing heart disease
and wiping out world hunger.
But, Milhouse, they
haven't cured anything.
Heart disease and world hunger
are still rampant.
Those do-gooders are all
a bunch of pitiful losers,
every last one of them.
You want results,
you have to go
to the Schwarzeneggers,
the Stallones,
and to a lesser extent,
the Van Dammes.
BOTH: Mickey Rooney!
Hi, Milhouse.
The studio sent me
to talk to you
being a former child star myself
and the number-one
box office draw
from 1939 through 1940.
Wow, spanning two decades.
How'd you find us?
They tapped your
tree house phone.
(radio signal beeping)
Milhouse, listen, you
can't quit this movie.
I've seen your work.
It's good,
very, very good.
Van Johnson good.
I know I'm good.
Movie stardom
is just so hollow.
Hollow?!
The only thing in
show business that's hollow
is the music industry.
Come on, Milhouse.
You have to do this,
if not for yourself
then for the movie-going public
and for the foreign markets
that are more important
than ever nowadays,
and finally,
for me, the Mickster.
No.
All right. I tried.
Fortunately, we have
a perfectly good
Fallout Boy right here.
Jiminy jillikers.
We're shutting
down production.
Yeah. Well, we only
have $1,000 left, anyway.
Uh, there's a $1,000
leaving-town tax.
MICKEY: Well, I hope
you're all satisfied.
You bankrupted a bunch
of naive movie folks.
Folks from Hollywood,
where values are different.
They weren't thinking
about the money.
They just wanted
to tell a story,
a story about
a radioactive man
and you slick small-towners
took them for all
they were worth.
(whimpers)
Should we give them
some of their money back?
No.
Hurry, Mr. Rooney.
We've got
a disenchanted little girl
in a Jell-O pudding commercial.
I could play that.
So, Milhouse, it
must be a little tough
giving up all
that glamour
and coming back
to school, huh?
Quiet. Maybe I
can get my citizenship.
(cheering)
We know you don't have
any more money left
but that doesn't matter.
Just take whatever you need
from our boutiques
until you can get back
on your feet.
Thank God we're back
in Hollywood
where people treat
each other right.
♪ Lean on me ♪
♪ When you're not strong ♪
♪ And I'll be your friend ♪
♪ I'll help you carry on ♪
♪ For it won't be long ♪
♪ Till I'm gonna need... ♪
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.