(theme music playing)
CHORUS:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
(screams)
Homer Simpson! You stand accused
of eating half the population
of the Planet of the Doughnuts.
DOUGHNUTS: Yeah!
(clamoring)
As Homer's defense attorney,
I feel we should be merci--
-(chomping)
-Hey!
-Did you just take a bite out of me?
-Um, maybe.
I sentence you to death!
(growling) Um! Homer!
-(swallowing, chewing)
-(snoring)
-LARRY: Homer! Wake up!
-(grunting)
It's time for our coffee break.
Hmm? Yeah. I earned it.
Mm, doughnuts. (slobbering)
Wow, there's only one doughnut left.
Yeah, ya drooled all over it, ya-
Gentlemen, there's only one solution.
We place this last doughnut
in the reactor core
exposing it to radiation,
thereby making it big!
Yeah, it worked on my hand!
Oh, wait. It's this hand. Whoa!
(humming, throbbing)
Uh, sir, we found the problem.
Some idiot threw this in the reactor core.
-Success!
-You did this?
-How could you be so irresponsible?
-l-It's my first day.
Since I've never seen you before,
maybe it is your first day.
-Very well. Carry on.
-Uh, sir, that's Homer Simpson.
And he's been working here for 10 years.
Oh, really! Why did you
think you could lie to me?
-It's my first day.
-(chuckling) Well, why didn't you sa--
Oh, whoo! You're fired!
Oh, fired. I can't believe it.
-(TV clicks on)
-MAN: Next, on Exploitation Theater--
Blacula, followed by Blackenstein...
and the Blunchblack of Blotre Blame.
-Whoo! Funky.
-But first, this word.
MALE NARRATOR: Daybreak-- Djakarta.
The proud men and women
of the navy are fighting for freedom.
But you're in Lubbock, Texas,
hosing the stains off a monument.
You're in the Naval Reserve,
America's 17th line of defense...
between the Mississippi National Guard
and the League of Women Voters.
After basic training, you'll only have
to work one weekend a month.
And most of that time,
you're drunk off your ass.
You know, Lisa,
I've taken a lot from this country.
Maybe it's time I gave something back.
Are you thinking of
joining the Naval Reserve?
-Would you be proud of me?
-Yeah, sort of.
Then I'll do it!
Just fill out this form,
and you're on your way to the Reserve.
There's a question that's crossed out.
Well, due to a recent
Presidential order...
we're not allowed to ask
that particular question.
Oh, I think I can make it out.
"Are you a homosex--"
Oh, for God's sake, don't answer that.
I could go to jail.
-But I'm not a ho--
-(singsong)
(continues singsong) I am not listening!
Nice fella. I wonder if he's gay.
Homey, I really don't think
this navy thing is a good idea.
-What if you get called into combat?
-Not to worry, honey.
We live in a highly technological age
where fighting a war
is as simple as turning off a light.
(clapping)
We don't have a Clapper.
(speaking loud) Sorry,
I can't hear you, Marge. I'm clapping.
(clapping continues)
HOMER: Nighty-night.
Well, guys, I won't
be seeing ya for a while.
-Where are you goin'?
-I've joined the Naval Reserve.
Well, I'm not gonna let
anything happen to my best friend.
I'm joining too!
Well, I'm not gonna let anything happen
to my two best customers.
I'm joining too!
And although my religion
strictly forbids military service--
What the hey! I'm in too!
Gee, thanks, guys.
This is just like The Deer Hunter.
The Deer Hunter? Uh, huh-That reminds me.
(rapid footsteps)
(speaking in native language)
I'm sorry, guys.
We're shutting down for a while. Sorry.
-See you in a week!
-Good luck, Dad.
Although I'm morally opposed
to the military-industrial complex
of which you are now a part.
Aw, that's sweet, honey.
I'll bring you back a hat.
Hey, Homer. Bring me back a torpedo.
-No!
-But Flanders got his kids torpedoes!
Oh, he did, did he? I'll show him!
I'll bring you a weapon
of unimaginable destructive power!
-Homer!
-But only if you're good.
Even if you're not.
(kissing sound)
(band playing)
All right, you thumb-sucking worms...
let's get one thing straight,
your mamas ain't here to help you.
-Mine is!
-(belches)
(razors buzzing)
No way, man. My hair is who I am!
Ow, I'm a freak!
-What the--
-(suggestive moaning)
Tuck in that shirt.
Shine those shoes, mister.
-Oh, for the love of--
-Uh, a seagull took my sailor hat.
All right, Simpson.
I don't like you, and you don't like me.
-I like you.
-Um, all right.
You like me, but I don't like you.
Maybe you would like me
if you got to know me.
What are you, a comedian?
(chuckles) Well, I'm no Margaret Cho
but I do a pretty fair Columbo impression.
(imitating Peter Falk as
Columbo) Uh, one more thi--
(coughs) one-- (clears throat)
(as himself) I should get
a glass of water.
(growls)
There. The perfect sheepshank.
Very nice, Simpson. But next time,
tie the other end to the ship!
-(people screaming)
-No!
(Quick March playing)
Congratulations, sailors.
You're all in the Naval Reserve.
ALL: Yea!
(speaking With French accent)
Congratulations! You are all pastry chefs!
-Yea!
-(with German accent) Congratulations.
You are all World War I
historical re-creationists.
-GRADUATES: Yea!
-MEN ON PODIUM: Uh-oh.
Hey, Bart. Check out my new earring.
Pretty cool, huh?
Milhouse, my mom wears earrings.
-Do you think she's cool?
-No!
I think she's hot!
Sorry. It just slipped out.
(chattering, chattering stops)
Hey, look! Milhouse has an earring!
(chanting) Milhouse! Milhouse! Milhouse!
Hey, if you want cool, check this out.
♪ Everybody, if you can,
do the Bartman ♪
♪ Shake your body turn it out
if you can, can ♪
♪ Do the Bartman ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
That is so 1991.
Young man, the school dress code...
specifically forbids
the wearing of earrings...
unless you're of Gypsy extraction.
-Well, I'm a Gypsy.
-(chuckles) Oh, really? Prove it.
Well-- (imitating Dracula)
"I 'vant' to suck your blood!"
Nuh-uh. That's a vampire.
But, uh, they're also covered.
Carry on.
Request permission to come aboard.
Permission granted. (giggles)
-(imitating bugle call) Marge!
-Whoa!
I lost this eye in Haiti.
I was drinking a mai tai...
and I forgot to take
the little parasol out.
Ah, that's not a war story!
I'll tell ya a war story!
I was on P.T. 109 with John F. Kennedy.
I was the first to discover
his terrible secret.
(in German)
(In English) He's a Nazi! Get 'im!
(orchestra playing)
And another thing,
when people come up to me
and say,"Hey, little buddy."
And hit me over the head with a hat?
That's not funny. That hurts!
(laughing)
-Stop laughing at me!
-You know, Marge?
Joining the Reserves
was the best thing I ever did.
I feel good about myself,
I'm helping my country...
and later, I'm gonna get
Gilligan's autograph.
I'm so proud of you, Homie.
Then I'll whomp him
with my hat! (laughing)
-Can I help you?
-I'd like to get my ear pierced.
Well, better make it quick, kiddo.
In five minutes, this place is
becoming a Starbucks.
Hello, everybody! Sparkle, sparkle.
-Bart!
-An earring. How rebellious.
In a conformist sort of way.
What on earth possessed you
to get an earring?
-Milhouse has one.
-If Milhouse jumped off a cliff--
Milhouse jumped off a cliff? I'm there.
Get back here, boy.
You're a disgrace to this family
-and its proud Naval tradition.
-Well, I'm keeping this earring
and you can't stop me!
Oh. I always thought Lisa would be
the one to get her ears pierced.
-Can I?
-No!
Time to reap the benefits of being cool.
-(gasps)
-(chattering)
I don't believe this.
Everyone's got an earring.
My neck hurts, and my ear hurts.
I have two owies.
Next weekend, we're having
our annual war games.
Now, Simpson, because of
your many years as a nuclear technician...
-we're putting you on a nuclear sub.
-"Nuc-u-lar"!
It's pronounced, "nuc-u-lar."
-Oh, whatever.
-"Nuc-u-lar."
(chattering)
-Be careful, Dad.
-Oh, Lisa. It's just war games.
It's not like a game could hurt me.
Damn you, "Rock 'Em Sock 'Em Robots."
Can't we all just get along?
Are you sure you'll be OK?
We have orders not to fire
on anybody but Greenpeace.
(smooching sound)
Well, I guess that's everyone.
-Except Earring Boy.
-Come on, Dad.
Didn't you ever do anything wild
when you were a kid?
Well, when I was 10, I got my ear pierced.
But this is completely different!
Fine. Take it.
Attention on deck!
Captain Tennille wishes to address you.
(clears throat)
I'm a man of few words.
Any questions?
Uh, is the poop deck
really what I think it is?
(laughing) I like the cut of your jib.
-What's a jib?
-(laughs) Promote that man.
The navy has a fine sense of tradition.
Whenever an American vessel leaves port...
the crew sings this ancient sea chanty--
A'one, a'two, a'three-
-A 'four--
-('70s Pop Tune plays)
(tune continues)
(vocals end)
(instrumental music playing)
(music ends)
-(motor revving)
-(whale singing)
(singing continues)
Ya hear that? The whales are hungry.
-(imitating whale)
-Homer, join us.
(imitating whale) Thank you.
Tell me, young man.
What do you want out of life?
-I want peas.
-(chuckles) We all want peace!
But it's always just out of reach.
-Oh! Uh-huh.
-So, what's the best way to get peace?
-With a knife!
-Exactly!
Not with the olive branch,
but the bayonet.
(chuckling) Oh, Simpson!
You're like the son I never had.
And you're like the father I never visit.
Sir! I was running a diagnostic
and there was an obstruction
in torpedo tube number one.
I'll take care of it. (sipping)
(groans) What the hell. Simpson!
-While I'm gone, you're in command.
-Me?
-Him?
-Yes.
Maybe it's the salt water in my veins...
or the nitrogen bubbles in my brain...
but I've taken a real shine to you.
Seaman, open that torpedo tube.
You'll never get a response
talking to my son like that.
-You gotta poke 'im with a stick.
-(moaning)
I don't want to go
to school today! (snores)
Oh, for God's sake!
Contraband!
Whoo, comfy.
Homer, we got an enemy sub,
closing in fast.
-What do we do?
-I don't know.
Fifteen seconds to collision.
We need a decision.
Hmm. What would
the captain say in my spot?
-Don't fire the torpedoes!
-Fire the torpedoes!
(Captain groaning)
-We've been hit by an officer!
-If they're gonna fire on us...
we'll respond in kind!
Fire! Not me, a torpedo!
-(rapid beeping)
-We're losing power!
-(engines slowing)
-We're losing backup power!
We're down to mood lighter here.
(instrumental, Bossa Nova)
-(engines come back on)
-(music stops)
All right, all right.
Mellow out, everybody.
The captain will know what to do.
You just shot the captain
out of the torpedo tube.
-HOMER:D'oh!
-That means you're in charge, Homer.
-I am?
-(sighs) Those were the orders.
Very well, then. I'm a captain.
Mr. Moe, steady as she goes.
Aye, aye, ya big dummy.
(sighs) What a dummy.
Damage report, Mr. Moe.
Sonar, out. Navigation, out.
-Radio, out.
-Enough of what's out. What's in?
Ice-blended mocha drinks
and David Schwimmer.
Yes, he is handsome
in an ugly sort of way.
Captain, how are we supposed
to get home with no equipment?
Don't worry. I've been working on it.
Mm, yes! Uh-huh.
Carry the two--
All right. I can't waste any more time.
People's lives are depending on me.
-Mr. Sulu, make a left!
-Aye, aye, Captain.
Setting course for Rigel Seven.
I mean home. (chuckles)
HOMER: That's it. Left. Left.
Steady as she goes--
On second thought, go right.
-(metal clanging)
-HOMER: D'oh!
Well, sir, "Treason Season"
started early this year...
as a nuclear sub was hijacked
by local man Homer Simpson.
Oh, my God!
I told him that photo
would come back to haunt him.
Could Homer Simpson be a Communist?
His father spoke out on his behalf.
My Homer is not a Communist.
He may be a liar, a pig,
an idiot, a Communist,
but he is not a porn star!
It's over there.
The Soviet Union will be pleased to offer
amnesty to your wayward "wessel."
The Soviet Union?
I thought you guys broke up.
(laughing) Yes! That's
what we wanted you to think!
(laughing evilly)
(chorus, Russian)
-(screaming)
-(growling)
Must crush Capitalism. (growling)
PRINCIPAL SKINNER:
Children, I'll be frank.
In the event of nuclear war,
we can only save our best and brightest.
Therefore, space in the fallout
shelter will be Reserved for...
Lisa Simpson, Martin Prince,
our championship kickball team...
and Sherri, but not Terri.
Ha-ha!
Captain, the renegade sub
is directly below us.
Drop the depth charges. We'll either
destroy it, or force it to surface.
Oh, my God! We're all gonna die!
-(intercom sounding)
-Y'ello?
Mayday! Mayday! The engine room
has sprung a leak.
It's filling up with
a clear, nonalcoholic liquid.
-You mean, water?
-Yeah, that's it.
We got a pinhole leak
and there's no way to plug it.
I guess that's it. Ladies and gentlemen...
we're in a tough spot,
and I don't know if we're gonna get out.
Please remain calm,
and think of your loved ones.
(baby talking) Oh, Mr. Snookums.
Oh, I "wuv" you so-
What are you looking at?
Hey, this stupid machine took my money!
(kissing sound) Don't ever change.
-Sparkle, sparkle.
-Bart!
-Pinole leak!
-Dad? The earring could plug the hole.
I'll plug your hole!
I mean, eureka!
(cheering)
-You saved us, Homer.
-Mr. Moe? Prepare to surface.
-You wanna stop calling me Mr. Moe?
-No.
Attention, Homer Simpson. You have
10 seconds to explain your actions...
-before we open fire!
-Uh, it's my first day!
-(all laughing)
-(speaking Spanish)
-(laughing)
-(speaking Chinese)
-Quack, quack, quack.
(chittering)
Seaman Simpson, your actions
have given the Navy
a black eye from which
it may never recover.
I would throw the book at you, but I've
been indicted in the Tailhook scandal.
-Good-bye.
-I, too, would punish you
but I'm under indictment for accepting
bribes from military contractors.
Um, I torpedoed a Carnival Cruise ship.
Impersonating the first lady.
-I think you're off the hook.
-Whoo-hoo!
A dishonorable discharge.
That's the best we could have hoped for.
You can't spell "dishonorable"
without "honorable."
I think you're a hero, Dad.
Well, I couldn't have
done it without Bart.
Boy, I guess I was wrong about
that earring. It saved us all.
Then can I get a tattoo that
says, "Bite me"?
You never know when
it might come in handy.
-I don't think so, son.
-A king cobra?
-HOMER: No.
-BART: Weapons-grade plutonium?
-HOMER: Ask your mother.
-BART: Knockout drops?
-HOMER: No.
-BART: Ninja death stars?
HOMER: Maybe for Christmas.
(theme music played by a marching band)
-(murmuring)
-Shh!
Captioned by
Visual Data Media Services