(theme music playing)
CHORUS: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
(screams)
-(Globetrotters theme)
-(whistle)
What? Uh-oh.
Here comes the evening rush.
Clear out, fellas.
(mice squeaking)
(whistle blowing)
(all talking at once)
What a day.
Serious drinking.
-Evening, Moe.
-(toilet flushing)
Morning, Moe.
Yeah, all right,
listen up, guys.
The Springfield police
have told me
that 91% of all
traffic accidents
are caused by you six guys.
-All right!
-All right.
I knew we could do it!
Yeah, I know, I know.
But the bad news is we got to start
having designated drivers.
(all grumbling)
Are you kidding me?
We'll choose the same way
they pick the Pope.
Everybody reach in
and draw a pickled egg.
Whoever gets the black egg
stays sober tonight.
Whew.
No!
You got the black one.
(laughing and shouting)
(men shouting)
Hey, everybody
I'm Peter Pantsless!
(laughing)
I can't take this much longer.
I got to have a beer.
(drum machine playing)
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
Oh, no.
Oh, no. Not tonight.
Not tonight!
Are you ready to get duffed?
(cheering)
Hey, it's Duffman--
The guy in the costume
that creates awareness of Duff.
Duffman wants to party down
with the man who sent in
10,000 Duff labels
to bring me here today.
I've got a bottomless mug
of new Duff extra cold for...
Barney Gumbel!
ALL: Chug! Chug! Chug!
I can't.
I'm the designated driver.
(music stops)
Yeah, that's swell.
Duff wholeheartedly supports
the designated driver program.
Now, who wants to party?
(crowd cheering)
♪ Hey, yada, yada,
yada, macarena ♪
♪ Hey, macarena! ♪
Please, I'm trying to drive.
Hey, let's go to
the girls' college.
No, the Playboy Mansion.
Playboy Mansion!
Shut up!
It's my car,
and I say we're going
to the Lost City of Gold.
Oh, that's just drunk talk--
Sweet, beautiful drunk talk.
Good night, Barney.
Don't forget to bring back
my car back tomorrow.
Just slide it under the door.
Yes. (clicks tongue)
Tomorrow.
(tires squealing)
Face it, Homer.
The car is gone.
-HOMER: Ohh!
-Barney ain't never coming back.
MAN: Here we are, Mr. Gumbel.
Uh?
Thanks for the lift.
Barney, where's my car?
Well, all I remember
about the last two months
Is giving a guest lecture
at Villanova--
Or maybe
it was a street corner.
So you lost my car, eh?
Well, that's just great.
I ought to punch you
in the nose
but I have to pick up
my kids at school.
-(wheels squeaking)
-(Homer grumbling)
Homer, I don't want
you driving around
in a car you built yourself.
Marge, you can stand
there finding fault
or you can knit me
some seat belts.
Sorry, sorry.
Dad, you got a letter from
the City of New York.
(scoffs) Throw it away.
Nothing good has ever come out
of New York City.
"Dear motorist, your vehicle
is illegally parked
in a borough of Manhattan."
My vehicle.
"If you do not remedy
this malparkage within 72 hours,
your car will be thrown
into the East River
at your expense."
Oh!
I don't want to go
to New York City.
-Why not?
-New York is a hellhole
and you know how I feel
about hellholes.
Dad, you can't judge a place
you've never been to.
Yeah, that's what
people do in Russia.
(groans)
It's time I told you
about a chapter of my life
I'd hoped
would be closed forever.
I was on my way
to the Harrisburg coat outlet
to buy an irregular coat
but it required a stopover
in New York City.
(piano playing
"The Entertainer")
All I had to do was
walk a few blocks
from the Port Authority
Bus Terminal
to my train at Penn Station.
(speaking inaudibly)
Anyhow, I must have looked
at somebody the wrong way
because the next thing I knew
I was running for my life.
And that's when the C.H.U.D.s
came at me.
Oh, Homer,
of course, you'll have
a bad impression of New York
if you only focus
on the pimps and the C.H.U.D.s.
Oh, I'd love to see New York.
We could all go
with the bus company's special
supersitter fare.
Nine bucks? This one's on me.
Great. We're all
going to New York.
(mumbling)
Lousy Bart and his money...
All right, New York,
I'm coming back.
But you're not getting this.
Dad, our baby pictures
were in there.
Don't you start.
MARGE: Wake up, everyone.
We're almost there.
(yawns)
(yawning)
That took too long.
How come we had to transfer
in Atlanta twice?
I just think we should have
paid the extra $1.50
and gotten
a bus with restrooms.
(yawns)
Hey. Marge,
I can't feel my legs.
I can't feel my legs!
Homer!
Homer, those legs belong
to the man behind you.
(chuckles) Hi.
(gasps)
We're here!
Wow.
I feel like such a nobody.
It's wall-to-wall landmarks--
The Williamsburg Bridge,
Fourth Avenue,
Governor's Island.
Look. It's ZZ Top.
You guys rock!
Eh. Maybe a little.
Now remember, criminals prey
on small-town folk like us.
So if anyone asks,
we're sophisticated
millionaires from the Ozarks.
Homer, you're scaring
the children.
Good. I don't want
to spend one extra second
in this urban death maze.
You wait here at
the bus station while I get the car.
The bus station is just
one of the sights we came to see.
We'll meet you
in Central Park at 5:00.
Oh, all right,
but not a minute later,
'cause once the sun goes down,
all the weirdos turn crazy.
I'm on to you!
"Your vehicle
is illegally parked at...
One World Trade Plaza."
Hmm.
Whoo.
Aah!
Aaaah!
Oh!
MARGE: Wow.
Governor's Island looks
so insignificant from up here.
Hey, immigrants! Beat it!
Country's full!
OK, folks, you heard the lady.
Back into the hold.
We'll try Canada.
(disappointed moans)
(speaking native language)
Stupid city.
What the hell is this thing?
(groaning)
C-come off!
Come... off.
All right, you.
(angry muttering)
Ow.
MAN (shouting): Hey!
When you're done with that,
I got something up here
you can bite on!
Hey! Why don't you be polite
you stinking pus bag!
Pal, you got to call that
number right on the boot!
Sorry about that guy.
They stick all the jerks
in Tower One!
That's it!
I'm coming over there!
Yeah, why don't
you come over here!
(both arguing)
Shut up, the both of yous!
WOMAN: Thank you for calling
the Parking Violations Bureau.
To plead not guilty,
press one, now.
Thank you.
Your plea has been...
MAN: Rejected.
WOMAN: You will be assessed
the full fine plus a small...
MAN: Large lateness penalty.
WOMAN:
Please wait by your vehicle
between 9:00 a.m. and 5:00 p.m.
-for parking officer Steve...
-MAN: Grabowski.
(dial tone)
They expect me to sit here
from 9:00 to 5:00?
That's... How many hours?
Ten, 11... Denominator.
Oh! Where's Lisa
when you need her?
Here's a better idea.
You give me your address,
and I'll write to you.
Uh, OK.
Just send it to...
Jesus, care of the Pentagon.
I'm so glad we took the subway.
"Laser wart removal"?
Wow. The future is here.
Hey, where's Bart?
(coins rattling)
Ladies and gentlemen,
I'm sorry to disturb
your pleasant ride.
but unlike yourselves,
I was born without taste buds.
Let me demonstrate.
(groaning)
Ew. I'm in over my head here.
Thank you for your time.
Ah...
Come on. Pick up the pace.
Hey, I'm not a bum.
Thanks, but I don't need...
OK, if you insist, but...
Spare change, lady?
Lousy cheapskate.
So hungry.
Can't leave car.
Getting closer.
Closer.
Almost...
there.
(snapping)
Ow!
MAN: Fresh Khlav Kalash!
Get your Khlav Kalash!
Hey, could you go
across the street
and get me a slice of pizza?
No pizza, only Khlav Kalash.
Oh, shoot.
All right, all right.
Give me one bowl.
No bowl. Stick. Stick.
Aaah! Geez!
That's just awful.
Mmm.
Now, what do you have
to wash that awful taste
out of my mouth?
Mountain dew or crab juice.
Blech! Ew! Geez!
I'll take a crab juice.
(belches)
Uh-oh.
Uh... You got
a men's room in there?
Only Khlav Kalash.
Men's room in tower.
Tower. Observation deck.
(whimpering)
But I can't leave my car
until the parking guy gets here.
Oh, why did I drink
all that crab juice?
Mmm.
(whistling)
Don't even think about it, pal.
Are we still in Little Italy?
Actually, I think
we're in Chinatown now.
Only in New York.
Mom, are those rabbits dead?
No. No, Lisa.
They're just... Sleeping...
Upside down and inside out.
Bart.
No fireworks. Put that back.
You're the boss.
Oh, no!
Chinese firedrill!
Serious this time.
(whimpering)
Come on, boot guy.
Oh. Flushing Meadows.
(celestial chorus)
(toilets flushing)
Oh, I can't take it anymore.
All right, I'll only be gone
for a second.
Frontsies, backsies,
I'm with them.
V.I.P Coming through.
Very important person.
They gave me frontsies.
(elevator bell dings)
(gasps)
How frightfully rude.
I certainly hope someone
stabs him in the eye.
(elevator dings)
Gah!
(pained moan)
(zipping)
(lift bell dings twice)
(loud groan of relief)
Oh, yes.
(gasps)
D'ohh!
D-ohh!
(panting)
What?
"Failure to wait by vehicle..."
$250?
You... Oh!
(angry muttering)
Oh, no.
It's getting dark.
Well, that's it.
I'm getting out of
this town alive if it kills me.
(engine revving)
(boot clanging)
(tires screeching)
(laughing)
Ow!
Look at
all those beautiful shoes.
I know they're made
from animals, but wow.
Mmm, If only I didn't already
have a pair of shoes.
Speaking of shoes,
I don't care about shoes.
I'll meet you ladies
back here in half an hour.
OK, Dad.
Stay where
I can see you, honey.
(gasps)
MAD Magazine?
(moaning)
(breathes sharply)
Excuse me.
Is this MAD Magazine?
No, it's Mademoiselle.
We're buying our sign
on the installment plan.
Seriously though,
my name is Bart Simpson.
My father has a subscription.
I'd like
the grand tour, please.
Listen, kid, you probably think
lots of crazy stuff
goes on in there,
but this is just
a place of business.
Oh... OK.
Get me Kaputnik and Fonebone.
I want to see their drawings
For "The New Kids
on The Blecch."
And where's my fushlugginer
pastrami sandwiches?
Wow.
I will never wash
these eyes again.
(grunts)
(horns honking)
Get off the road,
you freakin' maniac!
Yeah, you jackass!
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
♪ Everything is beautiful ♪
♪ In its own way... ♪
(deep growl)
LISA: " Kickin' it --
A musical journey
through the Betty Ford Center."
You know, when I was a girl,
I always dreamed of being
in a Broadway audience.
How do you find the defendant?
♪ He's guilty of mayhem ♪
♪ Exposure indecent ♪
♪ Freaked out behavior ♪
♪ Both chronic and recent ♪
♪ Drinking and driving
narcotics possession ♪
♪ And that's just page one
of his ten-page confession ♪
♪ I should put you away ♪
♪ Where you can't
kill or maim us ♪
♪ But this is L.A. ♪
♪ And you're rich and famous ♪
(Broadway show tune intro)
♪ I'm checkin' in ♪
♪ He's checkin' in ♪
♪ Checkin', checkin' in ♪
♪ No more pills or alcohol ♪
♪ No more pot or Demerol ♪
♪ No more stinkin' fun at all ♪
♪ I'm checkin' in ♪
♪ He's checkin' in ♪
♪ No more looking
pale and thin ♪
♪ No more bugs
beneath your skin ♪
♪ Hey, that's just my aspirin ♪
♪ Chuck it out ♪
♪ You're checkin' in ♪
When I grow up, I want to be
in the Betty Ford Center.
You better start saving now.
-It's very expensive.
-Shh.
They're strapping down
Liza Minnelli.
HOMER:
Oh, it's gonna be dark soon.
I'll never make it out of here
with this rotten boot on my car.
(tires screeching)
A-ha. I've got it.
Brain,
how can I ever thank you?
Just don't bump me on your way
out of the car.
Sorry.
-Just a minute!
-(horns honking)
Everything's under control.
Yes, I'd be upset, too.
Hey! Hey!
Hey!
What?
The boss says you're fired.
I'll get him.
(chuckling)
So long, Mr. Boot.
C-c-come on.
C-c-come on!
Die! Die!
Homer one--
New York nothing.
(clanking)
D'ohh!
Thanks for your patience.
-(gunshot)
-Aah!
What a perfect way
to end our day in New York.
Mm. I hope your father had
as much fun as we did.
(growls)
-(horn honking)
-(screaming)
(horn honking)
My God!
That maniac is heading
straight for us!
Go, Secretariat! Go!
-Ow!
-Hey, it's Dad. Right on time.
We're getting out of here.
Now jump in, Marge.
Trust me, throw the kids.
-No time for the baby.
-We're not jumping, Homer.
-(tires screeching)
-(horse whinnies)
Come on, let's go.
Everyone into the car now.
Tell your friends
to ask for Jimmy.
LISA: What a magical city.
Can we come back
next year, Dad?
We'll see, honey.
We'll see.
("New York, New York" playing)
♪ Start spreading the news ♪
♪ I'm leaving today ♪
♪ I want to be a part of it ♪
♪ In old New York ♪
♪ If I can make it there ♪
♪ I'll make it anywhere ♪
♪ Come on, come through ♪
♪ New York ♪
-(murmuring)
-Shh!
Captioned by
Visual Data Media Services