CHOIR: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(excited chattering)
Our journey begins
65 million years ago
when amazing creatures
took their first steps.
It's so cute that
all these children
are excited to see
their favorite dinosaurs.
(roaring)
(screaming)
(screeching)
These aren't dinosaurs!
Dinosaurs sing!
(grunts)
I want to go back in Mommy!
(roaring)
(panicked screaming)
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
I paid $800 for five minutes!
NARRATOR: The dinosaurs ruled
the Earth for millions of years,
until a massive asteroid
collided with the Earth,
bringing their reign to an end.
(crackling)
(groaning)
HOMER: Ex-tinct!
NARRATOR: So remember,
take good care of the Earth,
or we could suffer the same fate
as the dinosaurs.
Ooh, kids,
did you hear that lesson?
How is that the lesson?
The point of the dinosaurs is,
no matter what we do,
an asteroid's gonna wipe us out,
so we should party hard
and wreck the place!
Yeah! Why should the asteroid
have all the fun!
(grunts)
What? They've got a point.
(grunting)
BOTH: Gift shop!
All right, you can each have one toy.
Lisa has a big toy. No fair.
-That means I get two small toys.
-No fair.
-This isn't big, it's medium!
-No fair!
Then I get four small toys,
and Lisa gets one medium
and one small.
What?!
He gets four and I only get two?
-No fair!
-All right, that's it!
Forget it! No toys for anyone!
-Okay, Maggie gets a toy.
-BOTH: No fair!
Choke on fossil poop!
(screams)
Hey, I know you.
(gasps)
Wait! Wait! Come back!
Dad, follow that dinosaur!
I've waited my whole life
to hear that.
(Homer panting)
Triceratops head coming through!
Stegosaurus back plates,
used for either defense or control of
body temperature, coming through!
(panting)
So tired. Go on without me.
(groans)
(sighs)
(Homer snoring)
You're T.R. Francis!
You wrote the Angelica Button books.
They're my favorite fantasy novels.
Um, yes, it's me,
the creator of
your beloved magical world,
full of whimsy and, uh... chapters.
Now, off you go.
Bye-bye, now.
But why are you working
at a dinosaur show?
And why did you
run away from me?
And how did Angelica
get a new wand
after Baron Mortdeath burned
the Wandwood Forest? And...
Look, you seem like a smart kid,
so here's the truth.
T.R. Francis isn't real.
(laughs)
Of course you're real.
Everybody knows
you got the idea for this series
after an explosion
at a crumpet factory
knocked you off
a double-decker bus.
How could that be made up?
I'm just an actress
they use for the jacket photo.
That inspirational life story
is pure fiction.
Oh, I hate to break it to you,
but all the books you kids love
are conceived
in executive boardrooms.
The plots are based
on market research,
and the pages are churned out
by a room full of
pill-popping lit majors
desperate for work.
Publishers rake in the cash,
and unsuspecting kids
get ten books a year
by their favorite "author."
(gasps) Everything I believed
about "young adult" literature is a lie!
(sobbing)
HOMER: It's not against the law
to sleep in a Tyrannosaurus head.
Sir, you're inside an Allosaurus.
HOMER: I demand to speak
to my paleontologist!
Can I have my allowance early?
I need to buy some
carbon-offset credits
so I can burn
all my Angelica Button books.
Oh, honey,
I'm sorry your book lady
turned out to be a dinosaur.
But you liked the stories
when you read them.
So what does it matter?
Doesn't it bother you
that Betty Crocker
is an invention of '20s-era ad men?
I know you're hurting,
but that's no reason
to lash out at me.
Can you believe publishers
would lie to their readers
just to make an easy million bucks?
A million bucks?!
Every book on
the "young adult" charts
is written by five idiots
who just want
to take advantage of kids.
(gasps)
I know five idiots!
And they just cash their checks
and get away with it every time.
It's the perfect crime.
As long as you don't mind
betraying the trust
of vulnerable young minds.
The perfect crime, eh?
♪♪
(video game weapon blasting)
Whatever the job is,
I'm not interested.
A million bucks has changed
stupider minds than yours.
I like the beat,
play me the tune.
-We're taking down kids who read.
-Chapter-book crowd?
That's a juicy peach.
But what's the cream?
I'm putting together
a tween-lit gang-write.
-Tween-lit gang-write?
-Tween-lit gang-write.
But this Babar needs a Zephyr.
-A Zephyr?
-You're the Zephyr.
This better not turn
out like Kansas City.
It won't be like Kansas City.
♪♪
Come on, Skinner,
you're the best kid-man in the business.
You've read their notes,
searched their lockers--
-you know how tweens think.
-Oh, no, thanks, gentlemen.
I've got a nice, quiet life here
and I mean to keep it that way.
Your friends are looking
at my bloomers!
-Wash 'em again!
-(groans)
With your share of the money,
you could get
your own studio apartment.
The refrigerator could have
my magnets on it.
I'm in.
Come on, beautiful,
I can't do the job without you.
So, what do you say...
D'oh! Ow.
Our crew needs you, Bouvier.
You've read enough fantasy novels
to choke a hippogriff.
Mm. It's true.
I'm fluent in every imaginary language,
from Dothraki to Parseltongue.
(speaking Parseltongue)
I wouldn't join one
of your harebrained schemes
for all the Japanese
girlfriend pillows in Kyoto!
We're not here for you,
we're here for Lenny.
Sorry, guys.
I just adopted a capuchin monkey,
and I can't leave it alone
during the bonding phase.
Wait, wait, wait, I want in!
What does your crew need,
a safecracker?
A-A wheel man?
The caper is writing
a kids' fantasy novel.
Well, I, uh, I don't like to brag
about it, but I did publish
five modestly successful
children's books.
Hmm?
All we need now
is a computer guy.
-Do you have a computer?
-(coughs) Uh, yes.
-You're in.
-In what?
I keep going over the job
from every angle,
but I can't shake the feeling
that we're missing something.
Relax.
With the team we put together,
our book'll fly off the shelves,
and we'll be sipping Mai Tais
on a beach in Shelbyville.
You're group-writing a book?
But the only reason anyone
would ever do that is...
(gasps) profit!
Like no one ever writes
for money, Lisa.
I don't see your boyfriend William
Shakespeare missing too many meals.
I'll show you!
I'll write a book myself!
A personal story
my readers will connect with.
Wait, you're gonna be all the guys?
How would that work?
(frustrated groan)
This is how real writers do it.
I'll just bang out 2,000 words,
and then I'll stop--
even if I'm on fire.
I got to pace myself.
(chuckles)
Chapter one.
Wait. I can't start
without music to inspire me.
Why is Bach next to Muddy Waters?
That's my problem--
I got to get these CDs organized.
(classical music playing)
There. Finished.
Now, if I win just
two more games of online Boggle,
I'll be ready to start writing.
Spot, stop, sop, top-tops,
pot-pots, opt-opts...
Post!
♪♪
Okay, we've cased
a lot of tween books.
What's their M.O.?
The heroes are all orphans.
And they're set in a place
kids relate to--
say... a school--
but it's actually magic.
And the protagonist always discovers
that he is supernatural.
Okay, our book will be about
an orphan who goes
to a magical school
where he discovers
he's... a vampire!
Vampires...
-like these?
-HOMER: Huh?
-Or those?
-Huh?
-Or these guys?
-Huh?!
(frustrated groans)
So many vampires!
With the fangs and the capes
and the medals--
nobody knows how they earned them.
Hey, this job's falling apart.
Everyone head for a different airport,
and we meet in Rio in a year
with new faces.
(two gunshots)
No one's going anywhere.
Okay, the vampire genre
is sucked out.
All we got to do is find
a new monster to be our hero.
-KIDS: (scream) A troll!
-Hey, I ain't a troll.
Look, I bleed red, just like you.
The first part is always green,
but it turns red.
A troll! That's it!
Our book could be
about an orphan troll!
Trolls live under bridges--
the school should be under a bridge.
The Brooklyn Bridge!
And the cool kids are elves.
The cheerleaders are pixies.
The stoners are...
gargoyles!
And they play a complicated sport
which makes no sense
called Fuzzlepitch!
-Oh, yeah, yeah, that's good!
-(chuckles) We've cracked it.
We're gonna be rich!
Pardon me, but are you
scheming to coauthor
a successful series
of children's fantasy novels?
Okay, Stonehenge, let's see
how good you are at eavesdropping
without a throat!
Don't kill him!
That's Neil Gaiman.
I don't care if he's the guy
who wrote Sandman Volume One:
Preludes and Nocturnes--
no one spies on us!
Perhaps someone of
my experience
would be a valuable addition
to your... crew.
The king of fantasy books
on our fantasy book-writing team?
Okay, Gaiman, you're in.
Your job is to get lunch.
And lose the British accent.
(with American accent)
Cheeseburgers, French fries.
I'm all over that, pal.
Sitting in a coffee shop.
I couldn't feel more like a real writer.
(sighs)
Oh, I better set up my Wi-Fi,
in case I need to do some research.
But if I'm gonna use
their free Internet,
I really should buy something.
God, I love being a writer!
♪♪
"And so,
Lucinda placed the fifth shard
in the stained-glass window,
which now clearly read,
'Your parents are alive.'
Gregor turned to his twin sister,
and they both understood,
their journey was just beginning."
The end.
(applause)
-(cries)
-It's good.
Weekly Reader
Star Selection good.
I just hope we put in enough
steampunk, whatever that is.
Who wants to see
my cover mock-up?!
(whirring)
"The Troll Twins of
Underbridge Academy."
I'm so proud of us.
Oh, you didn't write any of it.
That tuna didn't salad itself.
(muttering)
(gasps) I've got it!
A mermaid falls in love
with a boy on land.
I'm a genius!
(yells)
Writing is the hardest thing ever!
-(whirring)
-Huh?
Hope you don't mind us printing
our book in your room, Lis.
Yeah, only your professional-strength
output tray
can handle the weight of our manuscript.
Correction. Finished manuscript.
-Whoo-hoo!
-(Lisa groans)
♪♪
Trolls in a magical prep school
under the Brooklyn Bridge?
-Interesting.
-GROUP: Whoo!
This is a really good book.
We know. We wrote it.
I laminated the lunch menus
and put them in a binder.
But we have a problem here.
Where's your fake author?
-Fake author?
-Fake author!
If you don't have a made-up author
with an inspirational tale,
you don't have a book.
Where's your Franklin W. Dixon?
Where's your T.R. Francis?
Where's your Stephen King?
Stupid, stupid, stupid!
We forgot to create a fake author!
That was Gaiman's job.
Let's acid melt him in a bathtub!
Okay, stay frosty.
All we need to do is find some sap
to pretend to be the writer of our book.
So hit the floor and find
some pathetic wanna-be author.
♪♪
Coming to the book fair
sure was a great idea.
'Cause you can't write if you don't know
what the competition's up to.
(wry laugh)
A dog wrote a best-seller?!
(yells)
All I've done is procrastinate!
Ah, who am I kidding?
There will never be a book
with my name on it.
Or your name could be
on a book in ten minutes.
Do I have to do any writing?
-No.
-I'm in.
♪♪
Ah, a preteen prodigy.
I like the hook.
What's the phony backstory?
I was raised in a traveling circus.
My mother was a lady ringmaster,
and my father was a lion barber.
I wrote my first story
with clown lipstick
on a flattened popcorn box.
It was featured in The New Yorker's
"Best Forty Under Four" issue.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Is R.L. Stine here,
'cause you just gave me Goosebumps?
(laughter)
Oh, good one, boss.
Congratulations.
You just sold your book
for a million dollars.
-♪♪
-(cash register rings)
Gentlemen, to The Troll Twins
of Underbridge Academy.
(whooping)
So, does this square us
for Kansas City?
Square as Golden Books, Pop.
What happened to me?
In one vulnerable moment,
I became the thing I hated most--
a literary fraud.
But Lis, when this book comes out,
you'll be beloved.
Not just by Milhouses.
You'll get attention from Jacksons,
Xanders, even Aidens.
Aw, I've always wanted an Aiden.
(door creaks open)
Here it is, an advance copy.
PATTY: "The Vampire Twins
of Transylvania Prep"?!
Where's the trolls?
The trolls are now vampires,
the Brooklyn Bridge
is now a castle,
and Fuzzlepitch is now Bloodball.
Oh, weak! Weak and lame!
How could the publishers
change our book?
If they had been in charge
of the Sistine Chapel,
the whole thing would be vampires,
instead of the pope's
private naked dude mural.
Look, we market-tested the book,
and it really got dinged
on the whole trolls thing.
I mean dinged.
So we made some changes.
Don't feel bad.
Before we got our hands on Twilight,
it was about a girl
who fell in love with a golem.
But teenagers weren't going
to spend their allowances
to join Team Schmul.
But the trolls were the best part!
Do the characters still say
trolly instead of cool?
-No.
-Oh, that is so untrolly!
Hey, if you don't want your words
changed, write a screenplay.
We own your book,
so why don't you go and cry
into your million-dollar check?
-(dial tone)
-How could they do this to our book?
It was the singular vision
of seven people.
-No way!
-What you're feeling is called
pride of authorship.
You thought you only cared
about money,
but you actually care more about
what you've created together.
British Fonzie is right.
Our story is actually
more important than money.
I was gonna buy the apartment
next door and fill it with dolls,
but now that just sounds stupid.
They can't do this to us.
We've got to fight back!
-Yeah, let's get 'em!
-He's right.
We got to fight...
Rule number one of book heists--
never fall in love with the book.
We queer the deal,
we lose the money.
Bart, remember the 1,000-year war
between the trolls and the ogres?
-Yeah?
-Now it's a dance contest
at the vampire prom.
(gasps)
Let's steal back our book.
(brakes screech)
♪♪
Somewhere in that building
is a computer
with their sucky version
of our masterpiece.
The book prints at midnight,
so if we swap in the original version,
they'll print the wrong book--
our book.
And before the publishers
can do anything about it,
The Troll Twins of
Underbridge Academy
will be in every bookstore
in America!
This is the Fuzzlepitch Finals,
and tonight,
we drink from the Wazzle Cup!
Hello.
I'm the pizza delivery man.
-We didn't order a pizza.
-No, of course you didn't.
The establishment I work for
delivers pizzas to everyone,
and then gives
the customer the option
of accepting or refusing delivery.
That's a terrible business strategy.
-No, no, it's quite sound.
-Okay, fine.
-Where's the pizza?
-Pizza?
♪♪
The central computer's through here.
All we have to do
is upload our file and...
-Good evening, gentlemen.
-Kansas City.
(sighs) Kansas City.
So, you thought
you would un-ruin your book.
If it's any consolation,
you never had a chance.
Whoo-hoo! All right!
Someone in your gang
tipped me off to your little caper.
A traitor?
(all grunt suspiciously)
I bet it's the Earl of Marmalade
over here.
(whimpers)
No, guys. It was me.
-(all gasp)
-It can't be!
-It's always a dame.
-But why?
Because a little girl
wants her dream to come true.
LISA:
My name is finally on a book!
And they're letting me
write the sequel!
A hard deadline is just the kick
in the pants I need to focus
and get some serious writing done.
Now to enter the password
and to authorize final publication.
My favorite theme
of a wall calendar.
Lisa, would you care
to do the honors?
I'm sorry.
(whirring)
Oh, by the way,
the audio book
is only available... abridged.
Abridged! (cackling)
Well, we may have lost,
but we gave the bad guy a laugh.
That's something.
Our book! The real one!
-Yes!
-Wonderful words!
No need to thank me, boys.
Hey, you wouldn't say that
unless there was a need to thank you.
You could never have printed
your version of the book
without the publisher's password,
so I pretended to betray you.
Then after he typed the password,
I secretly switched the flash drives.
You switched the drives?
I got the idea
from every movie ever made.
And the best part is,
my face is still on the back flap.
(gasps) Gaiman!
Poor Lisa.
Did it never occur to her
that there might be
three flash drives?
I've heisted my way
to the best-seller list once again.
And the most brilliant part is,
I don't even know how to read.
♪♪
(laughs)
Gaiman, I've been waiting
to do this for a long time.
(yells)
Congratulations, partner.
We did it.
Hey, Neil, how come
you watched me drink mine,
-but you didn't drink yours?
-It's simple, Moe.
I don't like the taste... of poison.
Ah... crap.
(theme music playing)
Shh!
Subtitled by A. Vandelay