The Simpsons
D'oh!
I love Chinatown,
although I wish they'd stop
picking on Tibet Town.
Ooh, it must be
Chinese New Year.
People buy them
when they're small and cute.
Then they flush them
down the toilet.
Uh, yeah.
I'll have the shark butt
with butt sauce.
Bart!
Excellent choice, sir.
How is the Feast
of Twelve Delights
with Triple Happiness Sauce?
Very disappointing.
Then I'll have the
sweet and sour rice.
Oh, very good.
Would you like that
with the fragrant bee
bellies or the cat noses?
Neither, thank you.
Is there any way
we can enhance
your dining experience
by hurting an animal?
No!
Fortune cookies!
And now to read my fortune.
"Geese can be troublesome. "
What the hell is that
supposed to mean?
Oh. Fortune means
geese cause problems.
Well, I knew that
before I came in here.
A guy outside told me that.
"Every house
has a bathroom. "
Oh, these fortunes
are terrible.
Is there a problem?
These fortunes
are terrible.
They're supposed to
predict stuff
and ease you through
times of doubt
and sickness.
Well,
with all due respect, sir,
I suppose
you could come up
with better fortune?
Easy.
Well?
"You will be aroused
by a shampoo commercial. "
That's not bad.
Come with me.
It's terrible!
What am I doing here?
I should be in
New York writing riddles
on Popsicle sticks!
Then I'd be
making a difference.
They ruined my best fortune.
I wrote, "Let a frown
be your umbrella. "
They change it to "smile. "
A frown is a much better
umbrella than a smile!
This gentleman here
can write better fortunes
than all of you
put together.
Show them.
Okay, let's see...
"The price of stamps
will climb ever higher. "
Very profound.
He's like a young me!
Please!
Yung Mee was a hack
compared to this guy!
You're hired.
Let's see.
"You will invent
a humorous toilet lid. "
"You will find true
love on Flag Day. "
"Your store is
being robbed, Apu. "
Are you getting
all this, Lisa?
I don't know.
"You are a real winner. "
That fortune
really nailed me,
and my winning ways.
"You will take
a short sea voyage. "
Yarr! I'll enjoy that.
$14 and 10, 11, 12 cents.
There you go.
You know, sir,
tipping is customary.
Ooh! Me sorry!
Me no speaky Chiny!
General Gao,
you're a bloodthirsty fool,
but your chicken
is delectable.
This cookie feels heavy,
as if there's
some paper inside.
Nice job, sir.
That was my thumb.
There seems to be
some sort of communiqué!
It's your fortune, sir.
Capital!
"You will find true
love on Flag Day. "
Why, it's Flag Day today.
True love at last!
Well, it's just
you and me here, sir.
No time for jokes,
Smithers.
Come along.
We're going womanizing.
Oh, goody.
So I foreclosed
on her mortgage
and took her cats.
Oh, Monty.
It's such a delight
to talk to you.
I've gone five minutes
without saying,
"Well, I never!"
Excellent.
Let me fetch you
another Thomas Collins.
Damn that Pennybags!
Between him and
Scrooge McDuck,
all the best ankle is taken!
Perhaps there're
some girls in here.
Great heavens!
It's one of those nude
female fire stations!
I'd always be second place
to some kitten stuck
in a tree.
Let's go, Smithers.
Smithers?
That fortune
promised me true love.
This has been
the worst Flag Day ever.
That constable
is ticketing my car!
I told you we should've
parked next to the curb.
Now, see here, Flatfoot!
My goodness.
You're beautiful.
Oh, thanks,
but I still gotta
give you the ticket.
Of course you do.
You can lift my
wiper any day.
Is it still Flag Day?
For 12 more seconds, sir.
Miss,
would you submit to a wooing
by a gentleman caller?
Oh, I'm sorry,
but you're really not my...
Well, okay.
O frabjous day!
She said yes!
He'll pick you up at 7:00.
Wear a petticoat.
Petticoat?
Here's a place
that rents them.
It's about time
Mr. Burns found a woman.
I can't stand to
see a man single.
Some people enjoy
being alone, Mom.
No. Everyone should
be paired up.
It wasn't meant to be.
I've gotta be honest, Monty.
I've never dated anyone
who knew Calvin Coolidge.
Well, I've never dated
anyone with their
original hair and teeth.
You're a nice guy, Monty.
You're always laughing
and tenting your fingers.
I like that.
Excellent.
And you're so upbeat.
You think everything's
excellent.
I really feel safe with you.
It's like going out
with my brother.
Yes!
It's going great!
So, what are you into?
"Into"?
Yeah.
Like, what's a fun day
for 104-year-old?
Oh, I enjoy all the
popular youth trends
like piloting motor coaches
and collecting dog waste.
So,
what shall we do tomorrow?
Go grousing?
Or if you'd
rather stay home,
you could sing
while I accompany
you on the clavichord.
Actually, Monty, I...
I've got some wonderful
stereopticon images
of the Crimean War.
Look, I had
a lot of fun today,
but I don't think
we're right for each other.
The age difference
is just too...
Balderdash!
It's not important
how old you are on parchment.
It's how old you
feel in the humors.
I'm sorry, Monty...
Stop that dog!
It has my gum!
Look. There's one of
my young chums now.
You there!
Yes, Mr. Burns?
Tell my young sweetheart here
of our youthful exploits.
Uh...
Play along, chubsy.
There's a pie in it for you.
Oh! Yeah.
Monty's a wild man!
Yeah!
Whoa!
He ran his own casino,
stole the Loch Ness monster,
got shot by a baby,
and blotted out the sun!
Wow. That was you?
So, shall I pick you
up at 8:00?
Well...
Come on.
He's a total player.
Okay.
Stop kicking my door.
Well done, young man.
Your youthful trendiness
will come in handy
throughout the
courting process,
because these days,
you...
Where did you get
that pie?
Windowsill.
New underpants?
Homer, what are you up to?
Burns wants me to
come along on his date
to show him where
hip young people go.
Well, don't look too hip.
You don't want that
girl falling for you.
You're right!
These would stop
Joan Collins herself!
Drat!
I wish that song were longer.
I've got to admit,
you can really shake it.
Yes.
That's totally voluntary.
So, you guys come
here all the time?
Constantly.
When we're not
being kicked out
for our rowdy
youthful behavior,
eh, pally?
Yep. No one's rowdier
or more youthful than
Old Man Burns!
You mean Young Man Burns.
Put my hand on her knee.
Yes, Mr. Burns.
I said her.
And I said knee.
Oh! Sorry.
I'm going to make
such love to you
that you'll forget all
about Rudolph Valentino.
Turn left here.
No problem.
Mmm.
All right, you're dismissed.
I'll take it from here.
But Mr. Burns,
you're exhausted.
Yes. But I have
a little secret.
I've obtained a rare
powerful aphrodisiac.
It was made from the
pockets of the pocket fox,
an animal that only existed
for three weeks in
the 16th century.
See you tomorrow night,
Simpson!
Huh?
Homie, that was amazing!
I hope the kids
didn't hear us.
Wow.
Burns looks happy today.
Watch me take advantage
of his good mood.
Mr. Burns?
Can I have a raise?
Clean out your desk.
You're gone.
Well, I had a good run.
If I counted
all of the things I've got
You might really think
I had a lot
But I won't be satisfied
if I don't have you
Living in a castle
like a king
Wouldn't be much fun
without my queen
And I'd probably
throw it all away
if I don't have you
Once again, my dear,
you've beaten two
strapping young bucks!
Excellent.
Did you hear that?
That "excellent"
was excellent.
Can I have some ice cream?
I finished my pizza.
In time, in time.
I need to speak
with you in private.
Back in a moment, my dear.
We have to...
Expel some urine!
You're going to
ask her to marry you?
Isn't it wonderful?
I'm head over heels
in love!
Are you sure you
want to do this so fast?
Yes. My biological
clock is ticking.
I could be dead again soon.
Wait, my dear.
I think you'll find
that red ball
more "engaging. "
Hmm?
Monty, it's beautiful.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Gloria,
say you'll marry me.
Oh, Montgomery.
Of course I'll marry you.
Spectacular!
Now we must celebrate.
I'll get some Champagne-iola!
This is the happiest day
of my life.
Nothing could spoil it.
Absolutely nothing.
Okay, gun. Check.
Dollar-sign bag, check.
Power bar, check.
All right! Let's rob this...
Bowling alley?
Okay, whatever.
All right!
Totally... Gloria?
Snake?
I thought you
were in prison.
I was. I told the guard
that I was going out for
a pack of cigarettes.
Then I totally stabbed him.
You're looking good, baby.
Why did we ever break up?
You pushed me out
of a moving car.
The cops were chasing us.
I needed to lighten the load.
And, um, protect you.
Ha, ha.
Come on, baby.
We can talk more
at my hideout.
No! I'm engaged now!
My ring!
Let go of her,
or I'll scream!
Callooh! Callay!
We're in luck!
They had a magnum
at the shoe counter.
Now for...
Gloria?
Her ring.
Well, she's run off!
With Simpson.
Well, this is my house.
Uh-uh.
Jeez,
I just wanted to escape.
Gloria, you better
tell your boyfriend
to be a good little hostage.
He's not my boyfriend.
Mr. Burns is.
Homer just comes
along on our dates
and carries us
to the bedroom.
You're dating that
old trilobite? Gross!
We're in love, Snake.
Don't say that, baby.
I'm gonna win you back
if I have to pistol-whip
this guy all night.
Pistol-whip?
Ooh.
Mmm.
Pistol Whip.
Local authorities
are confident
the killer bees
are just curious
and won't bother us
if we don't bother them.
On a serious note,
two local residents
have been missing for
the last 20 minutes.
We take you now live
to Barney's Bowlarama
and the last man
who saw them,
C. Montgomery Burns.
I don't understand.
She was my
young sexy fiancée.
He was my
sexually-virile best friend,
and they just drove off
in my Bugatti Sexarossa.
How could this
ever have happened?
Well, according to
our audience insta-poll,
46% say you're too old,
and 37% say she's a skank.
Almost there.
Wow. Who do you have to kill
to get a place like this?
I think his name
was Gustafson.
Ow!
Let me guess.
Now you're gonna start
working him over
with the brass knuckles.
You are so predictable.
You know what
would be surprising?
A foot massage.
Shut up.
D'oh!
Beating a man
to a bloody pulp
isn't going to impress me.
It used to.
What if I beat him harder?
Wow, you so don't get it.
Has the ship sailed
on my foot massage
suggestion?
Don't worry, Mr. Burns.
We'll track down Simpson
with your vehicle's
anti-theft system.
Car gone! Car gone!
Yeah, we know that.
Where has it gone to?
Car gone!
Car gone! Car gone!
Chief? This yokel
says he saw Simpson
driving down near Hickton.
Uh-huh.
My peepers don't lie.
That's nice work, Lou.
Lock him up.
Huh?
Hey! Hey, I want that lawyer
what wears the cowboy hat.
Release the girl, Simpson!
I think I can
take him out, Chief.
That's a sweet shot.
He's tied to a chair.
That means Dad's
not a kidnapper,
he's a hostage!
Get off my lawn, coppers,
or I'll totally
turn the sprinklers on!
Come on, Snake.
You don't want to
soak all these people.
We're in minute two
of this standoff.
What's the situation, Chief?
Well, we have an officer
sneaking around the house,
Kent,
so unless they have
a television in there
or can hear my
loud talking...
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Well, I guess that
answers that, doesn't it?
I swear I can change, Gloria.
I'm taking classes
in computer fraud.
That's what
you said about the
telemarketing scams.
But you didn't stick with it.
I don't like
bothering people at home.
Good fire.
Keep burning.
Almost there.
Just a little more.
Wait!
But Gloria is still inside!
Save her!
It's too dangerous!
But I got a sister
you might like.
She's completely hairless,
like those cats.
I don't care if she's
Miss Hairless America!
I'm spoken for.
Now step aside.
I'll save Gloria myself.
You? No offense,
but you're a decrepit
monkey skeleton.
Perhaps.
But this monkey skeleton
is in love!
Oh.
Who am I kidding?
I'm just a feeble old man.
Gloria!
He did it!
He saved her!
Well, the important thing
is they're both safe.
I know you've been
through a lot, ma'am,
but we need you
to stand in front
of the burning house and say,
"Channel 6 is
hot, hot, hot!"
Wow, Mr. Burns.
How did you do that?
Never forget, Homer.
There's no muscle stronger
than the human heart.
What about the wiener?
A guy on TV lifted
a can of paint with his.
Yes.
Monty, you saved me!
And to think
I was once in love
with that dirty lowlife
with his arrogant smirk,
gutter mouth,
tough-guy attitude,
macho tattoos,
hair that can't be tamed,
prison-sculpted body...
Uh-oh.
I'm sorry, Monty.
Oh, Snake!
Don't ever change.
Yeah, but... But you...
I don't get it, Simpson.
I'm a "bad boy. "
Oh, I know.
I'm absolutely evil.
You're preaching
to the choir, man.
What do I have to do?
Grow a devil beard?
Devil beard?
You know,
the little goatee thing.
You mean a Vandyke?
No, a Vandyke has
a moustache, doesn't it?
I think it can.
Are you talking
about a soul patch?
No! Wait.
Maybe.
English - US - PSDH