♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
(yowls)
Ah, spring break in Hong Kong.
Custom-made suits
at slave labor prices.
Good Lord!
They've got this all wrong.
(keypad beeping)
Yes, this is Principal
Seymour Skinner.
How can I help you,
Principal?
I'm afraid there's
some problems with my tickets.
I asked for a center seat,
not an aisle seat.
I specifically requested not
to have the kosher meal.
And I booked the flight leaving
Saturday morning, not Friday morning.
Okay, I've gone ahead
and made those changes,
and with the one-day
advance purchase price,
it's just an extra $7,830.
G.M. Chrysler!
I can't afford that.
(sighs) But I can't close
the school a day early
just to suit my vacation.
Or can I?
Think, Seymour, think.
"Go to Work
With your Parents Day"?
SKINNER (on P.A.): Yes, "Go to Work
With your Parents Day."
Tomorrow,
you will learn by doing
and apply your knowledge
of fractions and gym
to real-world situations.
♪ ...Itchy
and Scratchy Show! ♪
I still don't understand
why you get to stay home
and watch Mom work.
Because I've always
been an advocate
of women in the workplace,
Lis.
I can't help it if Mom's
workplace contains our TV.
I'm honored, Bart.
And Lisa, you'll have a fine
time at the plant with Dad.
You've been interested
in nuclear power for years.
I've signed numerous petitions
to shut down that plant.
-Well, there you go.
-Mom, you're blocking the TV.
If you need something to do,
you can fill out my form. Here.
"Parent's occupation.
"Please note.
Homemaker is not allowed
"as it is not real work.
That's why you don't
get paid for it." Aw.
Bart can take my place
at the plant.
But he so wanted to see
women in the workplace.
Well, how about Aunt Patty
and Aunt Selma at the D.M.V.?
-(gasping)
-Of course, of course.
I would never ever
have thought of that.
(chuckles)
Some days, we don't let
the line move at all.
We call those weekdays.
-(laughing)
-Oh, good one.
Oh. Well, at least,
I'm not stuck
at the cracker factory
like Milhouse.
Wow!
-Ever wonder how crackers get salted?
-Have I!
-Wow!
-Crackers ho!
I never knew cracker production
could be so exciting.
Where do they make
those crackers
with the peanut butter
already inside?
Ah, put this on
and come with me, son.
Whoo!
Doughnut?
No, thanks.
Do you have any fruit?
This has purple
stuff inside.
Purple is a fruit.
Uh... Oh, this a map
of nuclear sites
around the country.
As a safety inspector,
I'm responsible for changing
most of these light bulbs.
Why are there so many
burnt-out ones?
'Cause they won't hire
an assistant.
Martin, here's ten dollars
to invest in the futures market.
Soy! Soy! Soy!
ALL:
(bell ringing)
Martin, you're up
one million dollars.
Yes!
(buzzer sounds)
And now, you've lost
all but $600.
You got greedy, Martin.
I'm sorry.
I guess watching me
isn't any more exciting
than being me.
Maybe we can make
your job more fun.
What are those?
I don't know.
Well, what if we used
our imaginations?
Houston, we have a problem.
Homer 13 is spinning
out of control.
I'm going after him.
(both laughing)
Boy, this is a lot more fun
with a second person.
Okay, one more step.
I've just got to go
laminate your license.
You'll get it in
two or three weeks.
Hot damn!
No more sitting
in the dirt at the drive-in.
Bart, I left the driver's
license-making machine on.
Turn it off.
25 years old?
You're not
25 years old.
This I.D. Is completely fake.
Yes, you're right,
Milhouse.
It is a fake.
Which makes it
a fake I.D.
A fake I.D.? Cool!
And it's our ticket to the best
spring break of our lives.
One adult
and two children, please.
I can think of at least
two things wrong with that title.
Twenty-five?
Whoa, I 'm sorry, Mr. S.
But, you know,
I gotta check everybody.
What, are you kidding?
I take it as a compliment.
Three beers, please.
Hey, join the party.
(belches)
Spring break!
Yeah!
Well, when are we
going to get rowdy?
Maybe when we find something
decent to do with this I.D.
We could go rent
a carpet shampooer.
(mechanical barking)
Greetings, chums.
Were your days at work
as profitable as mine?
I just had a sinful
shopping spree at Wee World.
Well, we're having the best
spring break of our lives,
and we don't need you
around nerding it up.
That job is taken.
But surely,
I and my $600
could play some small part
in your vacation fun.
Yeah, right.
Like there's any way
to get some kicks
with a big wad of cash
and a license to drive--
MILHOUSE:
Wow!
(barking)
Oh, boy, Flipsy!
You and I are going
on a road trip.
(cries out)
-(tires screech)
-(electric window operating)
(barking continues)
NELSON:
Ha-ha.
Gentlemen, for our road trip,
I have taken the liberty
of preparing an air-tight
and utterly plausible alibi
for use on our parents.
I've been selected
to represent the school
at the National Grammar Rodeo
at...
the Sheraton Hotel in Canada.
I've been selected
to represent the school
at the National Grammar Rodeo
at the Sheraton Hotel in Canada.
I'm going away for a week.
See ya!
Eh!
The National Grammar Rodeo?
I wish I were going.
Oh, wait, wait! I mean...
I wish I was going.
-Is that right, Bart?
-(mumbles) I dunno.
It's not fair. I'm the best
student in school.
How come I never heard
about this competition?
Maybe because you are,
as we say in Latin,
a dorkus malorkus.
That's not Latin.
Mom, Bart 's faking it.
Oh, honey,
you've had your glory.
Now it's Bart 's turn.
Hmm.
(rock intro to "Radar Love")
♪ I been driving all night,
my hand's wet on the wheel ♪
♪ There's a voice in my head
that drives my heel ♪
♪ It's my baby calling
Says, I need you here ♪
(radio tuning back and forth)
Oh, oh, oh, wait,
oh, yeah, I wanted that...
Oh, wait, oh, oh.
Ow!
Bart! Nelson hit me.
He sure did.
(gasps)
A cup holder!
Bart, we gotta stop
and get a cup.
Uh, Bart?
Cruise control, my good man.
Everybody all set back here?
Nelson, good to see you.
Martin, always a pleasure.
(kids screaming)
Oh... Diablo Canyon 2.
Why can't you be more like
Diablo Canyon 1?
(sighs)
(phone ringing)
Hello.
Oh, Homie! Hello.
I can't remember the last time
you called me from...
Oh. You want to speak to Lisa.
Hi, Lisa.
How is your spring break going?
I'm learning about owls.
Oh, owls, eh?
So you probably wouldn't want
to spend another day
at work with me...
Sure, I would.
I can learn about owls
this summer at bird camp.
(grunting)
(gasps)
We've arrived in the vast
cornfields of Canada.
How much farther
to the grammar rodeo?
Grammar rodeo!
We're going to
a grammar rodeo?
We're not going
to a grammar rodeo.
That was just
an alibi, Milton.
-Martin.
-Fellows?
-OTHERS: What?
Where are we going?
Well, I realize it's trite,
but we could tour
the bridges of Madison County.
Hey, who has better
vacation ideas than Triple-A?
According to the publisher
of this triple-a guidebook--
no one.
I've always wanted
to see Macon, Georgia.
Wait, how about a fair?
Not just a county fair.
Not just a Europe fair,
but a world's fair.
The world's fair
in Knoxville, Tennessee.
Keep reading.
The Hungarians have built
a giant, motorized Rubik's cube,
and the fair's symbol
is the Sunsphere
which sits atop a 266-foot-tall
steel shaft.
-What's inside?
-An information desk.
ALL: Cool.
So, it's a choice between
Disney World and Knoxville.
ALL (chanting):
Knoxville! Knoxville! Knoxville!
I concur.
(tires screeching)
You made it!
Did you have any trouble
getting past
the security guards?
Security guards?
-Great! You want to get some lunch?
-Sure.
The way I figure it,
if candy stays
in the machine
for more than a year,
it's up for grabs.
(groaning)
Why do you need me?
Well, it's a two-man operation,
and you're the only
man here I trust. Ready?
Ready.
-Whoo-hoo!
Simpson! What in God's
name are you--
Zagnut bar, Mr. Smithers?
Razzles? Skittles?
Whatchamacallit? Twizzlers?
They all have hilarious names
and are delicious.
Well, I am partial
to Jolly Ranchers. Mmm.
Good work, Simpson.
Simpsons.
Boy, Lisa, with you here,
this hardly seems like work at all.
I don't know how I'm
going to make it
through my night shift
without you.
-We can have a slumber party.
-Oh, that'd be great.
Sleeping bags on the floor,
a roaring fire--
It'll be like the time they kicked me out
of the sporting goods store.
(kids yelling, laughing)
If you kids can't keep
your hands to yourself,
I'm going to turn
this car around,
and there'll be no
Cape Canaveral for anybody!
That's it!
Back to Winnipeg!
Bart, can we stop
for ice cream?
Yes.
Bart, can we weigh the car
at that weigh station?
Yeah.
Bart, can we pick up
that hitchhiker?
I don't see why not.
Bart, can we stop
for ice cream?
Yes.
Well, I didn't think
I was rehabilitated,
but I guess they needed
the extra bed.
(sighs)
With Bart gone,
and now you and your father,
I'm not going to have
anyone to--
Thanks, Mom. Bye.
...talk to.
-What is this place?
-Branson, Missouri.
My dad says it's like Vegas
if it were run by Ned Flanders.
Andy Williams!
Oh, we don't need
to stop here.
-Yes, we do!
-Ugh!
ANDY WILLIAMS:
♪ ...my huckleberry friend ♪
♪ Moon river ♪
♪ And me ♪
(cheers, applause)
(whistles)
Wow!
I didn't think he was
going to do "Moon River,"
but then, bam,
second encore.
Okay, time
for truth or dare.
-You go first.
-Eh... truth.
Ask me anything.
Who do you love most--
me, Bart, or Maggie?
D'oh! All right, dare.
Okay, why don't you...
Hello, I'd like to speak
with a Mr. Snotball.
First name Ura.
Ura Snotball?
What? How dare you!
If I find out who this is,
I'll staple a flag to your butt
and mail you to Iran!
-Okay, your turn.
-Mmm... truth.
Uh... do you have
a crush on anyone?
Dad.
I won't tell anybody.
Dad, you tell everybody
everything.
Even Moe knew when I
threw up on the dentist.
Moe thinks he knows
a lot more than Moe knows.
Well, just give me
another chance,
and I'll prove
I can keep your secret.
Okay.
I like...
Langdon Alger.
I have no idea who that is.
Nobody does.
(giggling)
He's very quiet
and enjoys puzzles,
but that still doesn't mean
you can tell anyone.
I've already forgotten his name.
It was Larsen something, right?
(giggling)
Thanks, Dad.
Oh, this has been
the best spring break ever.
And with my patented seminar,
you will learn
how to corner the real estate
market through hypnosis.
Why waste your hypnotic powers
on neighbors and co-workers
when...
I can't take this anymore.
(sighs)
(coughing)
(coughing louder)
(groaning)
(crying)
Aw, there, there...
oh, Maggie, there...
We're on the home stretch.
Next stop--
the Knoxville World's Fair
and its fabulous Sunsphere.
Hurry up.
We've only got four days
to spend at the...
"Wod... fir"?
(metallic clatter)
Uh... excuse me.
Is this the World's Fair
visitor's center?
It used to be,
back in 1982.
You're 14 years too late.
But there's another world's fair
coming soon, right?
Before Friday?
What about the Sunsphere?
You mean the Wigsphere.
You're welcome to go up there
if you want to see
16,000 boxes of unsold wigs.
Now, you gentlemen gonna buy
some wigs or ain't ya?
I guess fate was against us.
It's really nobody's fault,
right?
Uh, right?
Well, we've still got a car
and a wad of cash.
Uh, no, we don't.
I must have spent our last $10
on this Al Gore doll.
You are hearing me talk.
I hate this place!
We've got no car.
We've got no money.
And no one knows we're here.
TOGETHER:
We're stranded!
-(crying)
-But on the plus side,
I knocked over the Sunsphere.
NELSON:
Ha-ha!
This never would have happened
if we'd gone to Macon, Georgia.
I'm just saying, is all.
Fellows, I think perhaps
the time has come
to call our parents.
No! They'd kill us.
Look, we got here on our own,
so we can survive here
on our own.
All we need is money, food,
and a way to get home.
Follow me.
Everybody, remember, we're
parked under the Sunsphere.
Hey! I need those to see!
Ah, these lenses are perfect.
Now I can re-bottom
those antique coke bottles.
-300...
-Hey, come back!
400, 500, 600...
Ow! Oh!
500, 400, 300,
200, 100, zero.
Come on!
This train goes
right through Springfield.
(all groaning)
(phone ringing)
Well, of course, I'll accept.
Bart! I've missed you so mu--
You want to speak to Lisa?
So, how's the National
Grammar Rodeo, Bart?
Lisa, I really need your help,
so I 'm gonna let you in on a secret.
There's no such thing.
I knew it! I knew it!
Because why would they have
our national grammar rodeo
in another nation?
Oh, Bart, you're going
to be in so much trouble.
I'm in trouble already.
Here's what happened.
So you've got to think of a way
I can come home for free.
Hmm... you could travel for free
if you were a stewardess.
Well, how badly
do you want to get home?
All right, all right,
how about a courier?
They travel for free too.
No, that's a terrier.
They're dogs.
Well, you sure don't look 25
but your un-laminated
out-of-state driver's license
is proof enough for me.
Here's your first assignment.
(speaking Chinese)
What the--
(snoring)
Can we call our parents yet,
Bart?
(phone ringing)
BART (on phone):
Lisa, this isn't working.
I've got to courier something
to Springfield.
And it's got to be big enough
to fit Milhouse, Martin,
and Nelson inside.
Bart, that will cost a fortune.
Simpson, how'd you like
to escort 500 Big Macs
to Marlon Brando's island?
Oh, I can't take
much more of this.
I'm counting on you, Lis.
-(dejectedly) Whee.
-What's wrong, honey?
There's something
troubling me, Dad.
But I don't think I can tell you
because it's a secret.
Well, you don't have to tell me,
but I thought we trusted
each other with our secrets now.
I mean, I haven't told a soul
about your new boyfriend.
Langdon Alger?
I don't like him anymore.
Okay, but you gotta promise
you won't get mad
or tell anyone,
especially Bart.
I promise.
Bart rented a car
with a phony driver's license
and drove Milhouse, Nelson,
and Martin to a wig outlet in Knoxville
and the car got crushed,
and they're out of money
and they can't get home,
and Bart 's working as a courier
and just came back
from Hong Kong.
Yes, that's a real pickle.
Would you excuse me
for a moment?
(muffled yelling)
All right, I have thought
this through.
I will send Bart
the money to fly home,
then I will murder him.
No, no! Then he'll know I told!
Dad, you said I could trust you.
(sighs)
Okay, we'll work this out
together.
First things first.
Where is Knoxville?
It's in Tennessee, right next to
the Oak Ridge nuclear facility,
birthplace of
the atomic bomb.
Well, maybe we could
order something from Oak Ridge.
And Bart could
be the courier!
Yello, Oak Ridge?
This is Springfield Nuclear.
We need to order a, uh...
T-437
safety command console.
Springfield, my computer
shows your t-437
is fully operational.
Uh, I suggest you--
Oh, my God!
Oh, God, no!
This can't be happening!
This... you're operating
without a T-437, Springfield!
Ah, sweet mother of mercy!
I mean... I mean, my God!
And have it sent to the Springfield
nuclear power plant
care of Homer J.
No, don't use your real name
or Bart will know!
Forget the name
Homer Simpson.
Have it sent care of
Langdon Alger.
MILHOUSE (muffled voice): Bart! Hey,
we really could use another air hole.
Shh! They'll know
you're in there.
(chuckling)
But I don't think
I'd go back again next year.
It's getting too commercial.
They've forgotten it's supposed
to be about the grammar.
(phone ringing)
Hello.
Oh, hello,
Principal Skinner.
No, Bart has never
been to Hong Kong.
Good night.
(phone ringing)
Hello.
Tennessee state police?
No, my son's car was not
crushed in Knoxville.
I don't know where
to begin telling you
what's wrong with that.
(phone ringing)
Hello.
No, Bart is not
available tomorrow
to deliver a human kidney
to Amsterdam.
(snickering)
Homer, are you
laughing at me?
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.