The Simpsons
D'oh!
Hey.
Want a chocolate?
Hold it right there,
Forrest Plump!
This town has laws
against impersonating
movie characters.
Oh, behave!
"Luke, I am your father. "
"Shagadellic. "
What are you doing
here anyway?
Waiting for my wife.
She has a surprise
for me.
Hey, hey, hey.
I didn't ask for
your life story.
Did you say life story?
Things started out great.
I ate what my mother ate.
And my mother loved chili.
Then suddenly...
Let go! Let go!
Wow. Tell me some more.
Don't you have
criminals to catch?
Hey, I'm working on it. We...
We got an undercover guy
who's infiltrating the mob.
Oh, there he is now.
Hey, Pete! Pete!
They fixed the
Coke machine!
Now where were we?
My father and I
were never
really close.
"Jack and Jill
went up the hill and...
"Jill came tumbling after.
The end. " Good night.
Is that the same Jack from
Jack And The Beanstalk?
You know, Son,
I believe it is.
And Jack Sprat,
is that him, too?
Say, how about
a little NyQuil?
All gone. Hmm.
I never found
true happiness
until I met Marge.
Excuse me.
Is this Room 106?
Hey, who's that?
I... I don't know.
Why do birds
suddenly appear
Every time you are near?
Just like me
they long to be
Hi. Would you
like to go...
She's mine!
We'd do
everything together.
Ooh!
Wow. A '50s
nostalgia cafe.
Well, well, well!
I have never seen such
reckless disregard for a
wife's well-being in my life.
You just won yourselves
a motorcycle!
Whoo-hoo!
And life just
gets more exciting.
Marge, can we trade?
I don't trust these guys.
We've gotta get home
before someone sees us.
You know, all
this danger is kind
of a turn... Okay.
Then came the day
that changes every
couple forever.
The day we got
our elephant.
While I wait for my family,
I'll tell you about the time
my baby shot my boss.
Hey, that's great,
but I gotta get going.
Whoa! There's a whole
'nother row of
these bad boys!
Keep talking.
It's time for
your surprise, Dad.
Yeah. Hop in, Homer.
Ah. The family car.
We've been through
a lot together.
Get off the road,
you freaking maniac!
Yeah, you jackass!
Homer, maybe
I should drive.
What? I can see fine.
That had
nothing to do
with the bucket.
Homer, you genius!
Geronimo!
Huh?
Now before we get there,
you have to put
this blindfold on.
All my
other senses
are getting sharper.
Bart, you had
pizza for lunch.
Lisa, you're
extremely depressed.
As if.
Hey, Homer,
do you remember
this voice?
Kathleen Turner!
No! It's me, Krusty!
And you're
at the Springfield
Friars Club
where tonight
we're roasting you,
Homer Simpson!
Are the proceeds
going to charity?
Hell, no!
Whoo-hoo!
We're all here tonight
for one reason.
To keep Homer
away from the buffet!
Excellent.
That was at
my expense!
What kind of
a roast is this?
Now I'd like to read some
telegrams from people
who couldn't make it.
First we have Mark Spitz.
Who's Mark Spitz?
What's a telegram?
Oh, forget it!
I gotta get to the hot wings
before the Comic Book Guy.
"You know, Lisa.
They say father
knows best. "
"That's true, Bart. "
Excellent.
But seriously, we've
had a lot of fun with
our dad over the years.
Joy to the world,
the Lord is come!
Let earth receive her King
Let every...
Season's greetings.
Peace out.
Silent night
Holy night
All is calm
All is bright
Oh,
that hurts!
Will you take us
to Mount Splashmore?
No.
Will you take us
to Mount Splashmore?
No.
Will you take us
to Mount Splashmore?
No.
Will you take us
to Mount Splashmore?
No.
Will you take us
to Mount Splashmore?
No.
Will you take us
to Mount Splashmore?
No.
Will you take us
to Mount Splashmore?
No!
Will you take us
to Mount Splashmore?
No.
Will you take us
to Mount Splashmore?
No.
Will you take us
to Mount Splashmore?
No!
Will you take us
to Mount Splashmore?
No!
Will you take us
to Mount Splashmore?
No!
Will you take us
to Mount Splashmore?
No!
Will you take us
to Mount Splashmore?
No!
If I take you,
will you two shut up
and quit bugging me?
Yeah. Well...
Of course.
Will you take us
to Mount Splashmore?
Yes!
Thanks, Dad.
Isn't this that cartoon
that causes seizures?
Bart, what are you doing?
Hey, what the...
All right.
A lot of people think
our dad's behavior
has screwed us up.
And it has.
But it's all worth it
just to hear him sing.
Shaving
my shoulders
I'm getting it
all shaved off
Max Power, he's the man
whose name
you'd love to touch
But you mustn't touch
His name sounds
good in your ear
But when you say it,
you mustn't fear
'Cause his name can
be said by anyone
Max Power!
I like pizza,
I like bagels
I like hot dogs
with mustard and beer
I get the picture.
I'll eat eggplant
I could even
eat a baby deer
Who's that baby
deer on the lawn...
Enough already!
Dancing away my hunger pangs
Moving my feet so
my stomach won't hurt
I'm kinda like Jesus,
but not in a sacrilegious way
And now our next speaker
is Mr. Warmth himself,
C. Montgomery Burns!
I stand here to expose
the criminal ineptitude
of Homer J. Simpson.
Again and again he's
brought this town to the
brink of annihilation.
Why are you laughing?
His bungling has
shortened your lives and
mutated your children!
Just look at all of
his catastrophic
nincompoopery.
Poop.
Get ready,
everybody.
He's about to do
something stupid.
Well, I'm sorry
to disappoint
you gentlemen,
but you seem to have me
confused with a character
in a fictional show.
Now if you'll excuse me,
my fondue is just about...
Get out of my way!
Fire, fire,
fire, fire...
Here comes one
of our fellows now.
I think I won,
Mr. Burns.
Now here's a couple
that's been dating.
Carbon dating!
Grampa Simpson
and Agnes Skinner!
Sweet Toledo!
What's keeping
that dress on?
The collective will
of everyone
in this room!
Excellent.
You fruits wouldn't know
what to do with me!
I first met Homer in 1927
in a bar in Brooklyn.
Little did I know
he would soon become
Mrs. Joe DiMaggio and...
Roll the clips!
Uh-oh.
Okay, don't panic.
Remember what
the instructor said.
If you ever get into trouble,
all you need to do is...
Feels like I'm wearing
nothing at all.
Nothing at all.
Stupid sexy Flanders!
Ow! My legs!
This is the worst
pain ever!
Single.
How's he doing?
I don't know.
I think Dad might
be a little heavy
for parasailing.
Faster, Marge! Faster!
The snapping turtles
are massing!
Heads up!
Coming through!
Look out!
Hey, volleyball!
Can I play later?
Hi, Apu.
Oh, dear! You have
ruined my work,
you flying fat man!
Hey!
Step on it, Mom!
Dad's signaling that
he wants to go higher!
Higher.
Bye-bye, fishies!
Higher! Higher!
I'm soaring!
Soaring majestically,
like a candy wrapper
caught in an updraft.
Higher, Marge! Higher!
It won't go any...
Higher, I say!
I want to soar higher
than any man has
ever soared!
I want to look
down on the clouds
with contempt!
I want to sneer
at God's creation
and spit on his...
Uh-oh.
Lower! Lower!
There goes my turn.
Hey, Abe,
you want to hook up
after the show?
Yeah!
To a suicide machine!
Now everyone knows
Homer loves his family.
I'm sick of your lies!
Secrets and lies!
It's always
secrets and lies!
Homer, these people
are professional roasters.
Don't give them fodder.
Secrets and lies!
Now let's welcome
Springfield's original
God couple,
Reverend Lovejoy
and Ned Flanders!
Thank you so much.
The Camptown ladies
sing this song
Homer Simpson's
breath is strong
Hey, hey!
Now hold on there.
The nice people
want to hear
the real words.
But, Ned,
I was singing
the real words.
Oh, let's just
take it from the top.
The Camptown ladies
sing this song
The Camptown racetrack's
five miles long
That's better.
Homer's breath smells bad...
Oh, those are
not the words!
Silence!
Cease all quips
and comebacks!
Look! You weren't
in dress rehearsal,
so you're not in the show!
This can't be good
for my pacemaker.
What are you doing here?
Our planet
has been observing
your puny species
since your planet
was created 5,000
years ago by God.
In the name
of the Father, the Son,
and the Holy Ghost.
And now humanity
must be judged!
The fate of your planet
rests on one human being,
Homer Simpson!
Why him?
Because he is the fat,
selfish epitome
of modern man!
Hey, he stole my bit!
Now we shall probe you
to see if you are worthy.
Yep! Word for word.
Okay, let's see
what we've got.
It has to be
on Channel 3.
Yes, yes.
Oh, yeah.
That's a fine-looking...
D'oh!
Okay, no big deal.
Stupid Lisa!
You gotta build fast.
Cement drying!
All right, let's see.
English side ruined!
Must use
French instructions!
Le grill!
What the hell is that?
Come on, fit, you!
Yeah. That's one
fine-looking
barbecue pit.
Why doesn't mine
look like that?
Why? Why must life
be so hard?
Why must I fail
in every attempt
at masonry?
How's your father's
project coming along?
I think he's almost done.
Yeah. He's done.
Why you little...
Better or worse?
Worse!
Much better!
Lisa, no!
Your hands are too weak!
Ow!
I'll mace you good!
Your species
is brutish
and primitive!
Do you have anything
to say before we
obliterate your planet?
Wait! What about
Maggie's memories?
Surely the innocent
soul of a child
will redeem mankind!
Sure,
let's give it a shot.
Oh, there's my
sweet little Maggie.
Oh, Maggie.
You're a Simpson again.
You know, Maggie.
The sooner kids talk,
the sooner they talk back.
I hope you
never say a word.
Daddy.
It worked, Mom!
Maggie's memories have
shown them humanity's
inner goodness!
These are not tears!
We are vomiting
from our eyes!
Your baby's treacle
has only intensified
our loathing!
Wait! Look at the screen!
The baby continues
to reminisce.
Elton John!
That's my name.
Well, not really.
Stephen Hawking!
Hi. I'm Ron Howard.
Billy Baldwin!
I'm Alec Baldwin.
Wait a minute.
Xena can't fly.
I told you,
I'm not Xena.
I'm Lucy Lawless.
Oh.
Wow, Joe Namath!
That's right.
My car broke down
in front of your house.
Yo, dudes! Awesome show!
It's *NSYNC!
Word!
This child thinks of
nothing but trendy
Hollywood celebrities.
We can learn much
from this innocent one.
Like Justin Timberlake's
home phone number.
So I guess you
can't destroy Earth,
since so many of
your favorite celebrities
live and work here.
We will not
destroy the Earth!
On one condition.
You name it.
I can't believe
we're going to the
People's Choice Awards!
And tomorrow,
the Daytime Emmys.
Oh, it's Burt Reynolds
and Michael Jeter!
Could an Evening Shade
reunion be in the works?
There's Shannen
Doherty. Didn't you
have a thing with her?
Don't go there.
Ullman shorts, Christmas show
Marge's fling, Homer's bro
Bart in well, Flanders fails
Whacking snakes, monorail
Mr. Plow, Homer space
Sideshow Bob steps on rakes
Lisa's future, Selma's hubby
Marge not proud, Homer chubby
Homer worries Bart is gay
Poochie, U2, NRA
Hippies, Vegas, and Japan
Octuplets and Bart's boy band
Marge murmurs, Maude croaks
Lisa Buddhist, Homer tokes
Maggie blows Burns away
What else do I have to say?
They'll never
stop the Simpsons
Have no fears
We've got stories
for years
Like Marge becomes a robot
Maybe Moe gets a cell phone
Has Bart ever owned a bear?
Or how about a crazy wedding
where something happens and...
Sorry for the clip show
Have no fears
We've got stories
for years
ENGLISH - US - PSDH