Day-oh!
D'oh!
Come on, out of my way!
Where was this traffic
when I was driving to church?
Homie, calm down.
We're not going to miss
the San Castellaneta Festival.
I love San Castellaneta.
Delicious food,
wonderful people.
It's just like being in Italy.
But with streets that are
wide enough I can fit in them.
And I love the rides
that are dangerous
because they're 100 years old.
Hold on, kids. Here we go.
I beat out a mule
and an ox for this job.
The secret is
not to ask for benefits.
Give me pizza,
give me pasta
Give me lots of cannoli
I'll drink sambuca
till I puke-a
Then I'll finish
with spumoni
Drink until my legs
are Jell-O
Cheap red wine
and limoncello...
You want us to bring you
anything back
from the festival, Tone?
No. It's all carbs.
I don't want people
to think I'm fat.
But your name is Fat Tony.
It blends.
I can't believe
you're not going,
after I flew out
your uncle from Sicily.
- Idiota!
- That icy glare
is why I left the old country.
Tightlips, you do a poor job
of reading my moods.
But you're the only one I trust.
Go. Enjoy your festival
while I sit here
bonding with my uncle.
Do you want to go
to the festival, zio?
I came to this country
for the Burning Man.
Before I die,
I want to see a naked
crunchy chick riding a bicycle.
Everybody has a treat...
- Opa!
- That's Greek, Chief.
Hey, Lou, when's the festival
for Saint Know-It-All?
- I believe it's October the...
- There isn't one!
Nobody likes a know-it-all.
Idiot.
Hey, we got a-zeppole,
we got a-braciole,
capicola, scungilli,
and I don't know
what the hell-a this is.
Can you make it all
in one thing and fry it?
I saw-a you coming.
This place
looks interesting.
Dad, no,
that's an actual church.
Welcome, everyone,
to this festival
that does not celebrate
Christopher Columbus.
Repeat, not Columbus.
As we stand here at the corner
of Niña and Pinta
and Santa Maria,
let us welcome
your master of cere-spumonies,
Aquaman himself,
Jason Morororora.
It is an honor
to be here on land today
to recount the inspiring story
of this great saint.
- Aquaman.
- Sign my left boob.
Aquaman is not here
for the signing of boobs.
That's a separate event at
the Marriott. Conference room C.
In 250 A. D.,
Brother Ignatius Castellaneta
refused to recant
his Christian faith.
And so the Romans
chopped off his head,
they chopped off his arms,
they chopped off his legs,
and they chopped off his toes.
They shot him with arrows
made of frozen snakes
and they pulled out his eyes
and replaced them
with chocolate-covered
pistachios.
But still,
Ignatius refused to recant.
So they boiled his bones
in sparkling cherry wine.
So that's why
the thrice-martyred saint
is remembered with spumoni,
the chocolate pistachio
cherry ice cream treat.
Not good.
Yes, thank you, Super-Fish.
And now, let us show
our deep reverence for Jesus
by festooning his statue
with dollar bills.
Pin a dollar on Jesus, Homer.
He doesn't need money.
I hear his father's loaded.
Hey, where's my wallet?
Yeah, my wallet's gone too.
- My purse!
- My belt!
My clutch!
We are the victims
of a pocket-picking pandemic.
Do something, Wet Panther!
Peter Piper picked
a peck of pocket wallets?
How many paupers did
Peter's pocket picking produce?
I'm afraid no pants are
safe from this Dockers stalker,
this chino bandito,
this trouser browser.
But Chief Wiggum vows he will
solve this pickle of a puzzle.
Oh, I solved it, all right.
Thief of polite.
I said it first!
Wiggum, I hate to interrupt
this important police work...
Police. That's it.
Thief of police.
Hey! I need that to switch
to Access Hollywood.
You need a lot more than that.
I'm Lenora Carter,
special investigator
from the attorney general's
office,
and I'm taking over this case.
Look, ma'am,
you seem nice, but no one
comes into my precinct
and tells me what to do.
- Shut up and listen.
- Yes, ma'am.
You are the worst police officer
I've ever had the pleasure
of humiliating
in front of his men.
You are so fat,
you're good cop and bad cop.
Your drug-sniffing dog
is in rehab.
Okay, it's for sex addiction.
You there,
Riggs and Murtaugh.
It's time to do
some real police work.
I see, fine. No, go ahead.
I'll go work out my feelings
on the gun range.
We don't have a gun range!
We'll trap the pickpocket by
planting a wallet with a tracer
in a rear end so huge,
no criminal could miss it.
- We need to find the biggest ass in town.
- Hello.
Could you direct me to the
Office of Park Bench Removal?
Yeah, just take a seat, sir.
Thank you, I have my own.
I'm not letting
my husband risk his life.
I admit it, I'm scared.
Ma'am, this is a matter
of public urgency.
Your husband's rear end
is bigger than the both of us.
With your kids' permission,
we can watch
your father's butt
crack this case wide open.
Wide open.
Homer, we're placing this
tracking device in your wallet.
Then you just have to put that
sweet seat meat on the street.
Now let me pull your wallet up
so it's just peeking
over the pocket.
Allow me.
Pick a card. Any card.
Thank God that thing
is on our side.
I don't think
you're ready for this
'Cause my body's too
bootylicious for you, babe...
I don't think you're ready
for this jelly
I don't think
you're ready for this
'Cause my body's too
bootylicious for you, babe
Baby, can you handle this?
We've got our target.
What are you doing here?
I admit it,
I couldn't stay away.
I was following you.
Also, I was driving around
to put Ralphie to sleep.
That kid will not go down.
I'm a lotto ball.
You lose again, Daddy.
We're going in.
Except you.
You work with two guys
all your life
and you think you know 'em.
Betrayed by Lou
and the other guy.
What is his name again?
I want to say Greg.
You know, Uncle, guests, like
fish, stink after three days.
I told you once,
I told you a thousand times,
I'm not leaving
until my wife forgives me.
- She's dead.
- You always take her side!
Cops?
What are you doing here?
This is a setup.
What are these things?
I was told this was an
Asian fusion pop-up restaurant,
but I see no Asian nor fusion.
Marion "Fat Tony" D'Amico,
you're under arrest
for heading a pickpocket ring.
But I've never seen
these wallets before.
The room is spinning.
So this is what it feels like
to be innocent.
And this is how it feels
to be irrelevant.
Daddy's an elephant.
No, I'm not
an elephant, Ralphie,
and please
don't you forget it.
The Wolf of Wallet Street?
Reputed mobster Fat Tony D'Amico
is at last behind bars.
My wife.
My goomar.
My teacup pig.
What's wrong, Chief?
Marge, you ever felt like
life has passed you by,
there's no point?
Oh, you're just having
a rough patch.
It happens to all men
in their 50s.
I'm 38, Marge.
Chief, do you know
why I love my husband?
For that most romantic
of reasons, inertia.
I love him because
he's not afraid to fail.
He has boundless unjustified
confidence, and you should too.
Really? You think so?
Boy, suddenly,
I see a break in the clouds.
I will not let you down, Marge.
Marge, can I get
a ride to the station?
Ralphie will stay
with the car.
Dear Lord, who sees all,
the jabronis and the mamalukes,
you know I am innocent.
In your mercy and by your grace,
help me kneecap
the rat Judas who set me up.
Amen.
Almighty God,
I'm not a praying man.
For me, getting down on my knees
is often a one-way trip.
I know I made a deal
with the devil to be chief,
but please just ignore that
and help me out, will ya?
Dear Lord, please bring back
plastic straws.
The paper ones
get soggy so fast.
I brought the mob lawyer
right away
like you asked, boss.
They wouldn't even let me
put my pants on.
I was barely able
to grab my rate clock.
Al diavolo rate clock.
Get me out of here.
- And I mean fast.
- Patience. Patience.
Okay, what have they got you on?
Murder one?
Murder two?
Pickpocketing!
Quit talking slow!
All right.
Actually, I'm innocent.
Innocent?! Innocent?!
A judge wouldn't believe you
for a second.
I've got nothing
to work with here.
What would you even plead?
You really did it this time.
I didn't do it.
- You want me to whack him, boss?
- No! Just usher him out.
Got it. I'll usher him out.
I mean show him the door.
Right.
I'll show him the door.
Whatever you think I want you
to do, just do the opposite!
The one crime I would
never commit is pickpocketing.
He seems sincere.
I am sincere.
When I was a boy,
my father, Fatso Antonio,
needed a heart transplant.
On its way to the hospital,
that heart was pickpocketed.
My father died
the way no made man should die:
of natural causes.
Oh, my God.
I discovered a clue.
I found an electric toothbrush.
Well, he'll sleep good tonight.
I can tell he's innocent,
with a certainty
you can only develop
putting hundreds
of innocent people in jail.
DNA technology
has not been my friend.
Lights out!
Why do you "psst" me?
I'm not going anywhere.
I think you're innocent.
But you're gonna
have to convince me
to ignore
your entire past history.
I was not born a rich man.
Where I grew up, there was
one way out, your fists.
Or the many scholarships
available
to young Italian-American
students.
But the forms
required information,
and I ain't no snitch.
All right,
I'm losing my confidence.
You did it, didn't you?
I swear on this former priest
that I didn't do it.
He's not guilty.
- And I know guilty.
- And I can prove it.
- Well, go ahead.
- I said I can prove it.
I didn't say I would.
Well, why wouldn't you?
Because what I was actually
doing at the time is something
a mob boss cannot do
and let people know.
If you help me, I swear an oath
we'll find the guy
that framed you.
All right, I will show you
what I was doing
when the heist went down.
It's so embarrassing,
it has to be true.
Give me your phone.
This is what I do
every day at that time,
the time of the crime.
As you will see,
I walk into my private space,
I gargle,
and then, God help me,
I...
Good times and bum times
I've seen them all
and, my dear
I'm still here
Plush velvet sometimes
Sometimes just
pretzels and beer
But I'm here...
Now you know. When I'm alone,
I sing show tunes.
You didn't steal those wallets.
You stole my heart.
Leave it on.
Ten years a mob boss,
hits and whacks
Bought judges and mayors,
and never paid tax...
Okay, that's enough.
Definitely enough.
We're gonna get you out, today.
Appreciate the offer, Chief,
but prison has changed me.
Now I'm thinking I should
just give up, serve out my term,
then sit in the warm sun
outside the butcher shop.
Isn't that what you always did?
Yeah, but every few hours,
someone would whisper
something into my ear,
then I had to decide
whether to nod or shrug.
It was very stressful.
The agita.
I thought you wanted
to get the guy who put you here.
I do.
Well, we will,
if you will wear a wire.
I'm sorry, but on principle,
that is something I cannot do.
Let me repeat,
something I cannot do.
Now, remember the phrase
to call for help.
- What phrase?
- Remember the phrase.
I will. What phrase is it?
Remember the phrase.
I would if you would
tell me what it is.
The phrase is
remember the phrase.
That is the dumbest thing
I've ever heard.
Just remember,
your life depends on us.
Oh, and please, no profanity.
I play these for the missus
when we're...
we're getting in the mood.
A toast to Fat Tony,
a man like a Botticelli nude.
Fat, old and easy to frame, huh?
Hello, fellas.
Fat Tony. I was just saying
how much we missed you.
Huh, guys?
- Oh, yeah, sure.
- Yeah, we said that.
Quiet! I don't want
to hear anybody
but Frankie the Squealer.
What do, what do you want
to hear from me?
The name of the man
who framed you? I would never.
I didn't say Johnny Tightlips.
I would never say
Johnny Tightlips.
Ladies and gentlemen,
our new boss, Johnny Tightlips.
So, it was you, Johnny.
- What? Hey!
- You!
After all your
passive-aggressive replies
and bitter looks,
I never would've guessed.
You mistook my taciturn nature
for fealty.
But it was simply
that I didn't feel comfortable
in social situations.
Then I saw this commercial
where a sad cloud
goes on a date with the sun.
So I talked to my doctor
about Paxil,
and it gave me the confidence
to betray you.
This is my crew now.
Ain't that right, Jimmy Kissass?
You was always my favorite.
What about you, Sonny Go-along?
I'm good if everyone else is.
- Willie Whatever?
- Whatever.
And you,
Joey Can't-Read-the-Room?
You're nuts! Ain't none of us
gonna go along with this!
Yeah, see, that's,
you didn't, that's not...
Just a small town girl...
I'm surprised Maggie isn't here.
Lonely world
She took the midnight train
Going anywhere...
Mmm, this pasta's delicious.
I'm gonna find out
what the sauce is.
Remember the phrase.
Remember what phrase?
Oh, right.
Ooh, sauce.
I'm hit!
Right in the heart...
of your ass.
Someone's got to suck out
the bullet.
Wiggum, damn it, this is
what you were born to do.
Don't stop...
There he is.
We thought we were gonna lose
you for a minute there, champ.
You have the chief here
to thank.
His quick suction
may have saved your life.
Thank you.
Well, Wiggum, I have to say,
when I first met you,
I thought you were
totally incompetent.
And?
And?! And?! And?!
I believe in you, Chief.
And, yeah, that's enough.
The three of us,
we are not that different.
Whoa! Hey, whoa!
What's this guy talking about?
We are cicciobomba,
who like to sit in the sun
and enjoy a nice prosciutto.
Cicciobomba, prosciutto.
You guys make garbage
sound good.
We call garbage spazzatura.
Mmm, garbage.
Garbage.