Homer, the results of your
physical are very concerning.
- You're 80 pounds overweight.
- I wore my socks on the scale.
And your cholesterol
is sky‐high.
Go big or go home.
Oh, and your testosterone
is just a little bit low.
Testosterone?
That's what fuels
my punching and yelling.
And my undeserved confidence.
Now I'll never be an
NFL quarterback/international superspy.
Don't worry, low T is very
common amongst men your age.
It can be treated
with a prescription drug
called Vicodude.
- Pill me up.
- But before I give you the drug,
I just need you to watch
this short informational video.
There's an ad first?
If I had more testosterone,
I'd kill you.
A single truck can't possibly be
best in its class
in torque, towing and payload.
Think again, Professor Killjoy.
Man up with the Road Monster
Triple‐XL 550.
The Triple‐XL 550
delivers ultimate tow,
ultimate payload
and ultimate torque.
The Triple‐XL 550.
It's what a man drives.
Dr. Hibbert, you're a genius.
That truck
is exactly what I need.
No, what you need is medication.
Wrong again, Professor Killjoy.
See you next year.
Not if this chart is right.
Peonies are such
interesting flowers.
They need less water, but...
Look what the doctor
made me get.
You know it, baby.
The engine growls
just like that.
And don't worry, it has
maximum torque for its class
and the highest possible
ranking from J.D. Power.
What about his associates?
Oh, you know they're on board.
Look at me.
I'm a payload.
This truck is an offense to
everything I hold dear, and...
Oh, but it comes with a family
subscription to Slapify,
the music streaming service.
I don't know what that is,
but I'm great for having it.
Whoa, and check out
the picture on the back‐up cam.
It even has infrared.
Okay, Slapify,
let's see if your algorithm
can predict my taste.
Good luck.
Age, eight. Gender, female.
How did you hear about truck.
Oh, it already has suggestions.
A little trendy,
not for me.
Okay, but still
pretty mainstream.
Good taste is a curse,
but I'm sure a great song
is just a click away.
If you hate everything,
you might like this.
Quilloughby?
Never heard of him.
Quilloughby and his British
bandmates, the Snuffs,
dominated the '80s indie scene
with their brand
of literate, sardonic...
Ooh, sardonic.
Music that focused
on Quilloughby's obsessions,
especially his
militant vegetarianism.
The flesh that you cover
with cheese
Is proof
of your moral disease
It's death for no reason
And death for no reason
Is hamburger homicide
Yes.
Quilloughby's music
is so smart and dour and jangly
and no one has seen him in
30 years, he's a famous recluse.
And his commitment to
animal rights is so inspiring.
I just had
the most amazing idea.
Lisa doesn't like it
when other people talk.
Attention, Elementarians.
Inspired by
my new favorite musician,
whom I'm sure
you've never heard of,
today is the first
Mushroom Monday.
So dig in to these
all‐vegan mushroom tacos.
Mushrooms?
Those are chairs for toads.
Don't you see? The flesh
that you cover with cheese
is proof of your moral disease.
Just give them a chance.
So delicious.
Three kinds of ground mushrooms,
portobello, shiitake...
Don't forget the yummy
little pieces of bacon.
You said these were vegan.
But they are.
Vegetables plus bacon.
Vegon. Am I wrong?
I ate meat.
This taco had a mom.
Everyone at my school is a jerk.
Why are they so mean? Why?
Is the problem me?
The problem is never you.
It's those sour‐breathed
know‐nothing sheep
who graze the blighted meadows
of your so‐called school.
Okay, it was probably
just a bacon hallucination.
Quilloughby isn't actually
in my room.
I'm traumatized by eating meat.
You must stop
talking to yourself.
People will think
you've gone mad.
You're not real the real
Quilloughby. You're imaginary.
I've gone crazy.
Master of the obvious
Ensconced in her dreadful
red frock
I don't want to be crazy.
Not this kind of crazy.
Just get out of here.
Hey, Lis, what you pointing at?
Some bacon you want to eat?
I've got a pig nose.
Want to eat me?
Bart, slowly,
almost imperceptibly,
your friends
are growing tired of you.
What? What? I'm the drumstick
of this chicken bucket.
They're not getting tired of me.
Of course we're not, Bart.
Wait, what was that look?
What look?
You guys are not
getting tired of me.
No, no, I was just yawning
because I stayed up late,
thinking about your pranks.
Still so fresh.
Quilloughby, you completely
ruined my brother
with just one sentence.
Thank you.
Oh, there's nothing
more tiresome than gratitude.
I think I'm gonna like
hallucinating you.
Here's a gift. Put this
on your faded Army jacket.
Oh, my God.
You think I'm cool enough
to wear a faded Army jacket.
Keep in mind, I'm merely a product
of your fractured psyche.
Oh, shut up, don't ruin it.
Hey, Homer, ever so slowly,
your friends
are growing tired of you.
With this much testosterone?
No way, baby.
Take me
for a ride in your truck.
Trucks aren't for driving.
They're for doing
kick‐ass truck stuff.
Have you actually done
any truck stuff?
Put it on.
But I don't want this.
You're welcome!
For an imaginary friend,
you were really keen
to get out of the house.
That small woman
was such a bore.
Maggie's a baby,
and she was sleeping.
Even she knows it.
This place reminds me
of my own hometown.
It's dismal and nothing good
will ever come from it.
Well, almost nothing.
Get out your tickers and tape,
here comes the prat parade.
Facial hair is not
a substitute for personality.
Two times zero is still zero.
Bit early
for the apricot brandy,
is it not, Vicar?
Quilloughby,
is there anyone you do like?
Yeah, well, let me
tell you something, Lisa.
Every day I try to smile
But can't help but frown
Every day I draw my bath
And pray I will drown
I step out my door
and I take a deep breath
Turn back inside
and pray for my death
'Cause everyone is horrid
Except me and possibly you
Possibly me
Oh, everyone is horrid
And my dear,
I fear you are too
Lisa Simpson.
Those measures were supposed
to be pianissimo,
but instead they were sforzando
and scherzando.
Well, would you care to share your
private tee‐hees with the class?
I was just thinking,
every day you wave that wand,
and yet nothing magical
ever happens.
You're a smart‐mouthed
little sass pants.
And you're a sad little man
whose best days never happened.
I'm not sad, I'm happy.
And 5'8" is a very nice height
for a fella.
Very nice.
Lisa, I enjoyed that.
And I enjoy nothing.
Mr. and Mrs. Simpson,
I called you in here
because Lisa's behavior has
become wry, sardonic, and yes,
poetically world‐weary.
I know what's going on.
Lisa's become infatuated
with this snobby, judgy,
British crooner from the '80s.
You're right to worry.
With the popularity of
the Slapify streaming service,
I'm seeing more children
becoming lost
in the music of the past.
Oh, here she comes
Watch out, boy,
she'll chew you up
Oh, here she comes
She's a man‐eater!
Well, we take this
very seriously.
My husband and I are
going to have
a heart‐to‐heart
with our daughter tonight.
Isn't that right, Homer?
You don't tow me!
I tow you!
Stop resisting!
Surrender to my mighty torque!
Never!
What has gotten into you?
You used to be
such a happy little girl.
When?
Okay, but never like this...
with the sour attitude,
and the black booties.
You've become a crab...
no, a pill!
Lisa, darling,
please silence the din.
That's it!
I'm cancelling
your music subscription.
Jiggly... and bloop.
Shocking.
How can Mom take away
the only place
I can hear your music?
Maybe not the only place.
Apparently, this is happening.
Oh, my God.
I can see you.
I mean, the real you.
Well, you're in for
a treat, my dear.
My live shows are, quote,
like a three‐hour dance party
in a freshly‐dug grave.
David Fricke,
Rolling Stone magazine, 1987.
Oh, but Marge will never
let me go.
And even if she would,
I don't have enough money.
Those tickets cost,
like, five Lego sets.
Look in your pocket, Lisa.
My dad's credit card.
Did you steal this?
Did I?
A little of both.
It's complicated.
Sometimes I identify
as imaginary,
but sometimes I can do this.
Ow, the zipper!
What?
I'm a little stressed out.
Making sandwiches
calms my nerves.
Ooh, sandwiches!
Lisa is sullen, dressing weird,
obsessed with English music...
Our eight‐year‐old has
turned into a teenager.
Well, from now on, I'm going to
pay very close attention to her.
Marge, little girls are a lot
like all‐wheel anti‐lock brakes
when road conditions
are unpredictable...
We're talking about
your daughter, not a vehicle.
Well, both do have maximum
torque for their class.
Will you shut up
about the damn truck?
But the truck is who I am.
It's a perfect fit for my manly,
off‐road lifestyle.
Oh, really?
You hate the outdoors.
You've never been camping.
You've never hauled
or towed anything,
or shown any interest
in hauling or towing.
And please, tell me the meaning
of the word torque.
The smoke hole where
the truck's farts come out?
Torque is
the tendency of a force
to rotate the body to which
it is applied. Like this!
Homer J. Simpson,
you are not a truck guy!
Now, I'm going to deal with
an actual problem,
our daughter's
pre‐pre‐teen rebellion.
Lisa's gone!
I'm going to my first music
festival with my best friend!
Best imaginary friend.
Right. I guess
I didn't need to buy
two VIP passes then.
Sorry, Dad!
Oh, the pain of laughter...
Our daughter is by herself
at an outdoor
music whoop‐de‐doo!
And she's using
my stolen credit card.
What?
Hey...
No...
This combines my two
least favorite things...
other people's music,
and other people.
Yeah, but we're going to see
the real you perform.
Ooh, do you think you'll play
Labour Action
at the Biscuit Factory
or Simon Has a Birthmark?
How dreadfully predictable...
but the nippers must suckle.
Oh, these bands are all rubbish,
and this sun is too sunny.
Quilloughby, this festival
is our dream.
Stop being such a, such a...
Such a pill?
Sorry, Marge.
Hey, I'm just trying
to have a fun day.
Oh, a fun day.
Why don't we all just
have fizzy drinks
and rainbow lollipops?
Happy, happy, happy.
Vacuous animals waiting
for the slaughter.
Well, it's a good thing
Dad got this truck.
- Oh, my God.
- You see, Marge?
- I never want to hear another word...
- Bart gets it.
- About this truck.
- The truck is awesome.
- It makes me so mad!
- You don't get it...
- And you never will!
- Truck this, truck that.
- Truck, truck, truck, truck...
- I wish I was married to Bart!
You never stop whining!
The term is whinging.
Conspicuous eye roll.
I used to think
you just hated bad art
and cruelty to animals
and people who wear
baseball hats,
but it turns out
you hate everything!
But, Lisa,
I thought that was our bond.
Coming now to the main stage...
performing for the first time
in over 30 years...
Quilloughby and the Snuffs.
This is it...
The real you!
Oh, dear God, no!
I look like bloody Churchill!
Shut your gobs, you wankers!
Woo‐hoo! Wankers!
Can't you see this show
is just a cash grab?
I'm only here
because I lost my fortune
suing people for saying things
about me
that were completely true.
Is this what I turned into?
I'm greedy, I'm hateful,
and my face looks like
a syphilitic moon.
Well, it's not your fault
you got old.
Sting is old.
Old Sting's bloody gorgeous,
and he knows it.
You can jeer while
I enjoy this pastrami on rye.
But you're vegan!
I was,
until I found out veganism
was invented by foreigners,
of whom there are far too many
on this planet!
That's right,
I hate the foreign!
Coming to this country
and taking our jobs!
Sleeping with our men!
But you're a foreigner!
And you took the job
of sad, washed‐up rock star.
No! You turned your back
on veganism.
And you're also a huge racist.
Because everything is horrid
except meat,
so slag off to you!
Lisa, dear, don't let him
happen to you.
Try not to sneer at everything.
And listen to others,
at least a bit.
Perhaps one out of five times,
but I can't tell you
which times.
Thanks, Quilloughby.
You're the best imaginary friend
a complicated eight‐year‐old
could ever ask for.
But I think we both know
it's time for you to go.
I'm going to miss you,
you bloody wanker.
Okay, okay, okay,
I'm going to play a few songs
off my new album.
It's entitled
Refugees? Again?
Stupid millennial traffic.
And this is just in,
a full‐scale riot has broken out
at the Bummershoot Festival.
But Lisa's in there!
Who will save her?
Did someone call
for a truck guy?
Misplaced anger!
Somebody save me!
Torque, don't fail me now.
Truck, truck, hooray!
Truck, truck, hooray...
Homer. Homer. Homer, wake up.
He fell asleep while driving?
No, we got stuck in traffic
and ran out of gas,
so Dad ate a garbage bag
full of Mom's PB&Js
and passed out.
Thanks for walking over
and getting me.
Me and Trucky saved the day.
Sure you did, Homer.
Testosterone...
I don't know what came
over me, Mom.
I was sullen, moody,
thought everybody except me
was an idiot...
Wait, is that what
being a teenager is like?
Well, sometimes, sweetie.
Were you ever like that?
Blue mascara is who I am, Mom!
You're just jealous because
you can't pull off hot pants.
For your information,
I was going
to break up with Homer.
But if you hate him,
he must be great.
Honey, whatever phases
you go through,
I'll always be waiting for you
on the other side
of the slammed door.