(squeals)
(exclaiming)
(school bell ringing)
(Barney belches)
(whistle blows)
(yells)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
D'oh!
(tires screeching)
(grunts)
(electrical buzzing)
- (Homer grunts)
- MARGE: D'oh! Stupid fuse.
♪ The Simpsons 25x12 ♪
Diggs
Original Air Date on March 9, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
Mmm!
Maggie?
Maggie!
Mmm!
(honking)
(groans, growls)
(grunts)
(honking)
(growling)
Hmm...
Maggie?
- Maggie!
- Hmm.
Hey!
Maggie!
And it's for all these
reasons and more
that the Kingdom of Moab is the
least interesting in the Bible.
Amen.
Amen! We're done!
Allow me to introduce
our guest speaker
- (Homer groans) - from the
ill-advised mission in Indonesia,
the Reverend Kartawijaya.
(Bart groans)
- I know how you feel, young man.
- Huh?
The children in my village
are just like you.
One boy, named Sumadi,
never comes to church.
He is always tying the
monkeys' tails together
and yelling, "Tiger is gone,"
when, in fact, tiger is there.
- Hmm!
- Unfortunately, Sumadi is sick now.
What?! Su-Sumadi
has a problem?
Sumadi and others
equally doe-eyed...
need urgent medical
treatment.
After all, we are all
just children of Allah.
I mean God. Sorry.
Recent convert.
Poor Sumadi.
Born in such a
terrible country.
- Now, wait a minute.
- But good news.
To help him, we will now
have a second collection.
(congregation groans)
Wasn't our sympathetic
nodding enough?
Mom, can I have
some money?
I'm sorry, honey.
I'm all out.
I spent all I had lighting that
candle for Great Aunt Betty.
I hope that wasn't somebody's
Aunt Betty or something.
Dad, please?
For Sumadi?
Sorry, son, I only have 20s.
And if God needs money,
why doesn't he just
write another Bible?
The first one sold
pretty well.
Does anyone remember when it was
considered rude to talk in church?
Pipe down, Ned.
Please?
All right, son, but you
have to pay me back.
(sighs)
Life is good.
- Do you have my money?
- What?
- How could I?
Right, right, too soon.
- Do you have my money?
- (groans)
Seriously, do you
have my money?
Where's my money?
Huh?
(slurping)
Where's my money?
Where's... my...
mon... ey?
It's been a rough
patch, man.
Hope you got something
to cheer me up.
Well, there is one fun fact I've been
saving for an emergency situation.
Did you know there really
was a Duncan Hines?
Where's my money? Do you have
my money? Where is it?
You know, if you had the
money, I'm right here.
Do you have the money?
Money-money-money-money-mon...
Homer, quit
badgering the boy.
Pressure's how you make your
beloved diamonds, Marge.
I don't have any diamonds.
Quit pressuring me!
Money, money.
I need money!
Would you eat
anything for money?
I guess.
Who are you?
School play. Damn Yankees.
Children of the playground!
I will eat anything
for money!
Except money!
I'll give you a quarter
if you eat my gum.
I'll give you another
if you eat mine.
Here's some
orthodontic wax!
(lisps):
And some cinnamon!
Saint-John's-wort!
And here's something that'll make
you forget about the other stuff.
Ay caramba.
(blubbers)
So, what else you got?
All right, Simpson.
20 big ones says you're not
messed-up enough to eat... this.
(laughs)
(whimpers)
(gasps)
No, Bart, no!
Do it, and you'll always be known
as the kid who ate the dead frog.
(Homer's voice): Where's my money?
Get my money!
Money-money-money-money-money!
(disgusted exclaiming)
(slurps, kids exclaim)
Easiest money I ever...
(beeping)
Son, by rights, I should be
playing banjo at your funeral.
That frog was filled to the gills with
formaldehyde, a highly toxic poison.
(chuckles)
- Here's your money, Dad.
- What?
Did you owe me some money?
And, Homer, here's
your bill for $4,000.
D'oh!
Where's my money? You got my money?
Where's my money?
(chuckles)
Seriously, where's
my money?
Ew! It's the kid who
ate the dead frog!
Herbivore!
That's someone
who eats plants.
I named the frog Herb.
Even you won't
sit with me?
Bart, if you sit here,
I'll be the boy
who sat next to the boy
who ate the frog.
And I'm already the boy
who shared a comb with a boy
who threw up on the boy who wet
his pants at the winter carnival.
P.S. I would've given
you the money.
(groans)
(tires screech)
(school bell rings)
(tires squeal)
What's the matter,
frog in your throat?
You're the ones that
paid me to eat it.
All we hear is:
Ribbit, ribbit!
(bird shrieks)
(exclaiming)
You said this was a
simple bullying job!
Diggs and Freedom
at your service.
Diggs is short for Digby.
Thanks. I'm the kid
that ate the frog.
Oh, so you're the reason I had to
dissect a Muppet in biology today.
Thanks for the help, man.
Oh, you're welcome.
At least for me.
There's no way to say
what the bird thinks.
Or even if he
thinks, really.
Wait, wait, wait!
Who the hell are you?
I transferred here
a few months ago.
To this school?
On purpose?
Even after Springfield Montessori
opened across the street?
(gentle classical music plays)
That place is
really in your face.
I like the lack
of attention.
(quietly):
Especially in here.
(door creaks softly)
This school has a falconry club?
No way.
I resuscitated it.
I'm president, secretary
treasurer and faculty advisor.
That took a lot of
fancy paperwork.
But it was worth it
to be left alone.
Can I join?
Hmm. I'll have to
check with Freedom.
(loud clink)
Habemus Papam!
We have a poop!
It's white. You're in.
Looks like the falconry
club's back from the dead.
Can the Esperanto
Society be far behind?
(chuckles):
I mean...
Cu la Esperanto-Societo
esti multe malantau?
(sighs)
Two languages, and somehow
no one will talk to you.
Gi estas vera.
- Mi tre soleca.
- Loser.
The first thing to learn about falcons
is how beautiful they are in flight.
(screeches)
♪ ♪
Don't fret. He'll be back.
There's my Sky Gramma!
(mumbles)
Bart's usually first in line for
Taco Night, but now he's muy tarde.
(quiet gasp) Oh, is it all
right to say "tarde"?
Mmm, hey, you've said it twice,
Marge... you're in pretty deep.
- Homer!
- Ten-minutes rules!
Lisa!
(muffled):
What? A rule's a rule.
There he is!
(gasps)
Ah, he is just riding
that thermal!
You were right about
watching him fly.
I thought you'd get it. Seat
backs and tray tables, Bart.
We're coming in
for a landing.
(screeches)
Wow, you don't know how
impressive that is
to a boy whose dad can't
even get the dog to sit.
Sit. Sit.
Sit...
Sit!
(yells):
I don't know what that is,
but it's not sitting!
Where could Bart be?
I saw him heading across
the field after school
with a kid a little bit older
and undoubtedly wiser.
Oh, I know what
that means!
There comes a time when a
boy sneaks his first beer.
Finally! I was beginning
to think that kid was a...
(quietly):
Teetotaler.
Bart Simpson,
at your service.
More like "at your
six-pack," am I right?
(laughs)
It's okay if you need
to take a little nap.
Why would I want a nap?
Because you're so drunk you
can barely keep it together.
I wasn't drinking. I was
learning that nature
isn't a complete
waste of space.
That doesn't
sound like you.
But it does sound
like the kind of lie
you'd make up after the
first time you got blitzed.
I met this kid. A little
older, kind of strange.
I don't think other
people get him.
But I just want to hang out
with him all the time.
(gasps)
It's even better
than I thought.
You've found
your Moe Szyslak!
In just a few short years, you'll
be getting your version of baked
on your version of pot listening
to your version of Journey.
(laughs)
Wha...? What's he doing?
(Freedom cries)
Now, when he lands, you'll feed him so
he has positive associations with you.
(squawks)
Don't worry, he's only bitten
off one of my fingers.
- (gasps)
- (laughs)
Just goofing on you. This
is the finger he bit off.
If he starts to carry you
off, slip out of the glove.
Now tell him to fly.
Fly! Fly!
Come on, man!
Do the wing thing!
(Freedom squawking)
I did it! He did it!
We did it!
Yes, Bart, that is how you
conjugate the verb "to do."
Well done.
♪ Come Saturday morning ♪
D'oh!
♪ I'm going away
with my friend ♪
♪ We'll Saturday spend ♪
♪ Till the end of the day... ♪
- Hey! Bring back my bling.
♪ Just I and my friend ♪
♪ We'll travel for miles ♪
♪ In our Saturday smiles ♪
Give that back! All I got
is a hole in my face!
(nasally):
Uncle Krusty's back.
(Freedom cries)
Whoa! Did you teach
him to do that?
(laughs)
Nobody could
communicate that.
Except maybe Gerard
Manley Hopkins.
"I caught this morning
morning's minion
"Kingdom of daylight's dauphin,
"Dapple-dawn-drawn
Falcon, in his riding
"Of the rolling level underneath
him steady air, and striding
High there, how he rung upon
the rein of a wimpling wing."
Wow!
(frog croaks)
I've already eaten.
Hey, you want to see
something really cool?
Is a falcon's training
leash called a creance?
Yes!
(grunts)
Say something so I'll
know you're not hurt.
- I'm really hurt.
- Phew!
Bartholomew!
Good to see you, old sport.
Where's Freedom?
Well, my dad said don't bring
home any more dogs, cats,
turtles or snakes, but he never said
anything about predatory birds.
(muffled squawk)
(fans cheering)
Okay, in your terms,
points are like mice...
(screeches)
Don't interrupt. I just thought it would
be nice if we shared an interest.
(Freedom screeches)
GRAMPA:
Ooh...
You Korean girls know
what a soldier likes.
(squawks)
Fine! But the game is much more
enjoyable if you understand it.
Look, the Eagles
and the Falcons.
Tell me you're not
interested in that.
(Freedom screeches)
(groans)
I could fly, too, if I didn't
have a wife and three kids!
Hey, you've had
a lot of visitors.
No, I signed them myself.
They're people I would've
liked to come visit.
Ay, caramba!
Listen, what happened
in that tree?
Um, you want the truth?
Of course you do.
You're like Diogenes.
But with slingshot
in place of lamp.
I wanted to fly.
I know it sounds a
little crazy now,
but I suddenly thought
maybe we can all fly,
but somehow we've
forgotten that we can.
You don't still
think that, do you?
Hey, I'm not flying anywhere
with this broken wing.
Bart, here's another
doctor that would like
a few words with
this young man.
This hospital has
another doctor?
So they're transferring him
to another hospital.
Well, I hope he gets out soon
and takes his bird back.
I don't care for how
it circles the cat.
(cat meowing)
He's just riding the
thermals from Dad's butt.
At least someone in this
family is using them.
I never heard of this new hospital,
so I looked it up and printed it out.
Ooh!
Can I visit him tomorrow?
(sighs)
I don't know, Bart.
This is one of those Arkham
Asylum-type hospitals.
Diggs isn't cuckoo!
Uh, listen, boy.
Maybe you should spend more
time with your old best friend.
- You know, Dweebler.
- Milhouse abandoned me.
So, why can't I go there?
Bart, if this is
what I think it is,
it's not a place we should
ever, ever take a little boy.
Then why is Diggs there?
Because it's his
home forever.
You know, Bart,
just because Diggs
is a little different
doesn't mean
he's not a good person.
What would you know about
friends like Diggs?
- I have about eight of them.
- So, how do we fix him?
Oh, Bart.
Diggs's problems don't
have easy fixes.
What kind of cheer-up
talk is this?
Well, sometimes it helps to
know people feel for you.
(chuckles)
Want a hug?
You hug the bedpost.
Then I hug the bedpost.
That way we never
hug each other.
♪ Come Saturday morning ♪
♪ I'm going away... ♪
Hey, Simpson.
I heard bird boy
got a new cage.
One with rubber bars.
Yeah, and a rubber perch!
- Yeah, yeah, and a...
- I get it. It sucks.
- Really sucks.
- Rubber birdfeeder.
Making fun of the
mentally ill...
real classy.
- But you guys were...
- We were what, Captain Sensitive?
The rumors of my bonkertude
have been greatly exaggerated.
DSM-5 indicates
paranoid schizophrenia,
but that work is mired
in controversy.
- Mired.
- I knew you'd escape!
Were you carried out
by a flock of falcons?
I got a one-day pass.
Were falcons
involved in any way?
I obtained the pass to enter the
Springfield Falconry Contest,
which is what Freedom and I were
training for when we first met you.
Oh, great.
Before anything else,
let me just get closer
to the door and say,
"How crazy are you?"
I'm fine. My meds won't
wear off till tonight.
Then I'll have Freedom
tear you to shreds.
No offense, but when a crazy guy
pretends to be crazy, it's not funny.
You're discounting
all talk radio.
Excellent.
COMIC BOOK GUY:
Fly, my pet, fly!
Yes!
(falcon cries)
- Yes, now back to Papa.
Yes.
Why am I not surprised
the only sport you do
is one where a bird
brings you food?
Um, a falcon's greatest joy
is to serve its master.
(squawks) Fatso!
Once again, I must point out
that you are not a parrot.
Fatso, fatso!
Pees in the shower!
- (squawks)
- Shut up.
- What are you doing?
- We're up next.
When Freedom hits the air, you
and I open all the cages.
Um... with our minds?
No. With this rope.
I'm a messed-up kid.
I'm not Magneto.
ANNOUNCER:
Diggs and Freedom.
(all squawking)
"In his ecstasy. Then
off, off forth on swing!"
Where's my bird going?
Wherever he wants.
He's free now.
If you see the stork what
brings us babies, kill it!
Now, Bart, I'm afraid one-day
passes don't last forever.
And I'm probably not going to get
another one for quite a while.
Wait!
Wh-When will I see you?
You can't quit
the falconry club!
It's all yours, Mr. President.
Well, I guess some delicate
birds are safer in a cage.
I had thought of it as
a therapeutic milieu,
but now "cage" is stuck
in my head, so thanks.
And thanks for
being my friend.
Bart, when I
pushed you away,
I was really pushing away
the thought of losing you.
How long did it take
you to think that up?
Two hours with the therapist.
- I'll take that.
- She came in on a Saturday.
Missed her kid's
karate demonstration.
- He was going up a belt.
- Enough!
Mom, you didn't
cook the falcon?
Of course not.
It's just duck.
- Aw.
(munching loudly)
Pass the peas, please.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
Shh!