D'oh!
Okily dokily.
Aw, our own home.
All right. Takeout Chinese.
Everyone can have
their favorite thing.
Bart, General Tso's chicken.
For Lisa, Pacifist Tso's tofu.
For Maggie, Kung Pao Cheerios.
And, Homer,
I've got your favorite...
Favorite? That's my favorite.
MSG.
Ah, needs salt.
Y'ello.
Ahoy-hoy, Simpson.
I have four seats to tonight's
basketball joust,
and you were
at the top of my list.
So, what do you say?
Thank you, Mr. Burns.
Oh, boy, courtside seats.
I feel like
Billy Crystal's doctor.
Who was it?
You'll never believe it.
We just got...
Homer, wait.
You don't want to go with them.
Why not? They're my family.
Sweetie, I know that
you're talking to your brain.
Why don't you just do
whatever your heart tells you?
Not that guy.
I'm numb.
Chest pains!
Just go to the game
with your friends.
Brain, you're the greatest.
Is there anything
I can do for you?
Yeah, you could read a book
once in a while.
D'oh!
Carl, I got courtside seats!
Lenny, I got courtside seats!
Barney, I got courtside seats!
I'm in.
Who's on trial?
You guys got courtside seats?
I'd love to go.
Just let me lock up
the good liquor.
Sorry, we only have
four tickets.
Me, Lenny, Carl and Barney.
You really don't want me?
I thought we was friends.
Yeah, we did too.
Then we realized
you were serving us beer
that's mostly suds.
Also, your chicken wings
weren't chicken.
Hey, meat's meat.
Although none of it was meat.
Look, hey, where we going
with this?
You're not invited, Moe.
Hey, wha...?
Not invited, not invited.
Who's on trial?
I am truly alone
in this world.
No, you're not.
Thanks,
Anti-Suicide Keychain.
You're welcome.
I care about you...
Moe Szyslak...
very much.
Moe, about last night...
Yeah, on the house, fellas.
And I got new cocktail napkins
that ain't just
unpaid parking tickets.
See? Yeah, huh?
How about that?
Why you being so nice to us
after we rejected you?
Well, maybe the problem
wasn't youse, maybe it was mees.
So, I'se, uh,
sprucing up the bar,
trying to make things nice,
you know, like they used to be.
Hey! It's the Pin Pals,
our old bowling team!
Those were great times.
Them were the best times.
Closer than brothers,
we was, says I.
Then Apu had his octopuses,
and suddenly he didn't have time
to bowl with his buddies
five nights a week.
But as I said, great times.
Guys, I think we should
reform the Pin Pals,
but this time with me,
Lenny, Carl and Moe!
Oh, guys, I would love to!
But I can't bowl no more.
I got beer-pull tunnel syndrome.
Another, please.
It's a little short.
I guess you'll have to ask
Barney to bowl with ya's.
- Do they have beer?
- Yes.
To bowling!
I get knocked down
But I get up again
You're never
gonna keep me down...
Moe, this is for you.
- What do you say?
- Coach? Terrific!
I love screaming at people
who are trying their best.
To Moe!
What are you doing?
Don't drink that.
You're in training.
The boys are back in town
Boys are back in town...
A lot of music in this episode.
The boys are back in town
Boys are back in town
The boys are back
The boys are back in town
Boys are back in town
I said the boys
are back in town
The boys are back in town...
Okay, sidekicks,
back in our shadows.
Hallelujah
We made it, boys.
Going to the state finals
in Capital City!
Sorry, that's where we store
our extra balls.
Quick! Rest his head!
All right, the state finals.
If we win this, the next
tournament is on ESPN8.
All right, guys,
don't be yokels.
Just act like
you seen it all before.
Holy crap!
It says we're on lane 17.
Wow! Topiary lane numbers.
I'll bet they're plastic.
Yep, they are,
but don't tell management.
So I guess we're playing
you guys, huh?
Best two out of three.
I'm Reynolds.
We're high-frequency traders.
I was the model for
The Wolf of Wall Street.
I was the model
for American Psycho.
I was a model for toe fungus
in a Dr. Scholl's commercial.
- And I was...
- I'll give you $100 to stop talking.
Deal!
Hey, and here's a hundred
for you for looking at me
like I am the most
amazing thing you ever saw.
I think I'm giving you
a $500 look.
Well, here's $400,
and screw you.
Wow. I finally found
my path in life, socio.
Hey, Harold, buddy.
You know, I was wondering...
Excuse me.
Why cheeseburgers?
The cheese holds it together
in flight. Duh.
I mean, why do you throw them
at good people?
Question time is over.
Really hope that social worker
pays better
by the time you grow up.
Social worker.
Hey.
This little dingus gets it.
All right, little man.
From now on,
we're gonna call you McDingus.
You're treating me like dirt!
I belong!
I'm wearing a new hat!
I'm gonna show you
that the one thing in the world
that you're a little bit
good at, I'm better.
Okey-doke.
Damn it!
All right, now, listen to me.
These stuffed suits
don't stand a chance
against us working joes.
- Because we got...
- Moxie?
- No.
- Grit?
Nah, we're pretty grit-less.
Well, what have we got?
My stepdad is Lebanese.
We are a damn rainbow!
Yeah!
We win. We win!
The first out of three!
I haven't been this confident
since I saw La La Land
win Best Picture
and turned off my TV.
Good win, you guys.
Lunch is on us.
Wow! Is that a Visa
double diamond card?
Yep. Doesn't have to be
inserted or swiped.
It just knows.
It can sense that you're poor.
Once again they substitute
rhino for narwhal.
It's like they think
we won't notice.
Thanks for lunch.
And now you'll be
eating crow for dessert.
Side note...
I have actually eaten crow.
It is not bad.
Tastes like seagull.
Chang-stein, I bet you
that I can break down
this loser right here
in, oh, 15 seconds.
Moe, I would like to ask you
about your last birthday.
Why?
What have you heard?
Did you have a party?
No, sir.
- Cake?
- No.
Ah, man, it looks like
he's tearing Moe a new one.
Well, most of his old ones
are pretty bad,
so that could be a good thing.
So, did you leave your house?
No.
Any phone calls?
- Yes.
- Meant for you?
No!
I pretended to be someone
who was interested
in carpet cleaning.
That's time, and he is
definitely crying, so you win.
Bart, you don't want
to be with these guys.
They're monsters.
Hey, their 401Ks
are monsters.
Do you even know
what a 401K is?
I assume it's a gun.
Yeah, well, I may not have much,
but I got some things
that matter, huh?
My bar, my friends,
my good name.
Hear! Hear!
All right, well, if you believe
in your friends so much,
how about we make
a little wager on the match?
- Oh, can I bet on youse to win?
- No.
Careful, Moe.
I got a bad feeling about this.
Just leave us be, huh?
All right, how about this?
If we win the next two games,
your bar is ours,
and you have to change
your good name.
I got a bad feeling.
Bad feeling, bad feeling...
But if I win, I want something
I can share with my friends.
Something only a rich guy
like you can give us.
Let's do this.
Look at me, Moe Szyslak,
shaking hands with a guy
wearing a shirt worth more than
I'll earn in my entire life.
It feels like
I'm shaking hands with a squid.
No, the squid has
a much firmer grip.
Hey, Pin Gals.
Wha...?
Hey, hey, hey, we ain't afraid
of no bowling shirts.
They're not shirts,
it's compression wear,
which increases blood flow
to our arms
and decreases wind resistance.
Oh, yeah!
They know two-handed bowling.
Hey, we been hustled!
Huh, if you can't trust
hedge fund guys,
who can you trust?
Nice toss.
Nobody likes suck-ups.
All right? Cheeseburger.
I want to help you
stand up to them.
But they're traders.
All we know is
how to collect information.
Everyone has a weak spot.
We will aggregate
their emotional responses
and run a regression
through the data.
Thanks for dumbing it
down for us.
Polish your balls?
Man, this alley does everything.
Oh, I don't work for the alley.
No, indeed.
Bart?
Hey, Mom, I got
a question for you.
- Am I too young to start drinking vodka?
- Yes.
Wish you would've told
me that an hour ago.
Here's a little
don't tell Homer money.
If you love money
with all your heart,
the money will never
love you back.
Will having no money
make me happy?
No.
Does Bill Gates love his wife?
Melinda? Of course he does.
They started a foundation
that does wonderful things.
- With money, right?
- Yes.
So, money's the answer
for everything.
Have a C-note, sweetheart.
She gets it.
Whew, they really
kicked our butts.
I'm gonna lose
my bar and my name.
No Moe, no tavern, nothing.
I'm gonna jump into
that empty elevator shaft!
Moe, no!
I just... I can't win.
Oh, yeah, now we're
getting somewhere.
All right, we've come
to that time...
the time where I give
that inspirational speech
I've been keeping in my pocket.
You have given
this lonely little man
a reason to get up
every single day,
and that is why
I love youse, Marge.
I mean Pin Pals,
Pin Pals.
And we got a secret weapon.
This guy is sober.
I am, because of the love
of your sister.
Now, just so you know,
that was,
that was a catfish thing, right?
What's a catfish thing?
I'll explain it to you
after the match.
Just don't drink.
You know how
Miriam hates it.
You know, you sister looks
just like Jennifer Lawrence.
And all her pictures say
Getty Images.
Yeah, that's a problem
with your computer.
Just stay sober, huh?
Hey, have you ever tasted
liquid gold?
You realize that was
a thousand-dollar swallow.
Return to me.
Yeah
Oh, what do you want?
Fair warning,
we have combed through
all the emotional data on you
to find your soft targets.
What the hell
are you talking about?
You'll see, in just 15 seconds.
Reynolds,
artificial intelligence
is just three months away
from taking your job.
Without my job,
I'm just a douche.
You don't know
that the other two
are sleeping with your wife.
I thought you were, but you?!
You're all about your BMW,
but you couldn't afford
the sport package.
And I win, just like
all good people always win.
- McDingus.
- Yes, Father?
Throw this at your sister.
You won't do it, Bart.
Why not?
It's you and it's me,
and it wastes food.
You won't do it
because, deep down,
there's something weird
that connects us.
You're crazy.
Neither of us admits it,
but it's there.
I hold myself out to you.
Go on, make my face
the home of the Whopper.
I can't do it.
You do like me. You do!
And we'll always keep this
burger as a symbol of our fr...
May I wax your alley?
Will you get out of here?!
All right, this is it, the
tenth frame, the final frame.
The frame where you start
looking for your regular shoes.
All right, Barney,
just do your thing. No pressure.
Here's a picture of my sister
in the movie
Silver Linings Playbook.
Take a look.
Hey, you guys liquored him up!
Don't worry, Moe, I can still
win the spelling bee.
Recidivism.
R...
Because of
this idiot, Homer,
we need three strikes from you.
I just want to know what
it's like to be a winner, huh?
Just one time.
What about that
Women in Film award?
No, I stole that.
Okay, Moe, for you, I'll do it.
We're gonna win. I'm not gonna
have to start over again!
Because starting over,
what would that even mean?
That could be my reality.
Oh, my God,
I got to lose this match.
Homer, no!
- Give me the ball!
- I need it to bowl!
I don't want to win!
You're the worst coach ever!
Just give me the damn ball!
What's wrong, Moe?
- Yeah, we won.
- Nothing. I just got to go back
to the worst thing
in the world, huh?
Being me.
The guy you wouldn't even invite
to a basketball game.
Wha...
Did somebody say wait?
- No.
- Well, I wouldn't come back now
if you begged me.
- Wait!
- Yeah?
Just making a point.
Surprise!
You guys are my friends.
- That's right.
- We sure are.
And we're gonna have
a big party!
Right after we get back
from the basketball game.
Salt to the earth there.
All right, guys,
since we won the championship,
those hedge fund do-rags
have to deliver
an experience for me and my pals
that only they can bring.
When does it start?
Right about... now.
Welcome to how I always feel.