♪ The Simpsons ♪
(chalk screeches)
(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(tires screeching)
(horn honks)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
(growling)
SMITHERS: It's
a breakthrough product, sir,
scientifically formulated
to rinse clean with
no oily deposits.
Hot dog.
And it's mild enough
to use every day.
Isn't life grand?
What's wrong, sir?
Did I get some in your eyes?
The shampoo specifically said,
"no more tears."
A lovely promise
but one beyond the powers
of a mere shampoo.
sir, I feel there's something
you're not telling me.
Perhaps you'd feel
more comfortable
talking to
Snappy the Alligator.
Maybe.
Hello, Mr. Burns.
Snappy, you know it's hard
to imagine
but I was once a barefoot boy
with cheek of tan.
I dreamed
of grand slam home runs
and wiping out nations
with the stroke of a pen.
There's still time for
all those things, sir.
Is there?
Controlled nuclear fission is
a demanding mistress, Snappy.
So you feel resentful
towards the plant?
Yes! Yes, exactly!
You know, maybe it's time
I sold the old girl.
(gasps)
(humming)
Mmm!... hmm?!
D'oh!
Ohh, what do they want?
Maybe a nap
will boost my spirits.
I'll get that whale song
cassette you like, sir.
Oh, it's not fair!
(crying)
I know how you feel,
Simpson.
I've never seen Mr. Burns
so depressed.
I know people think because
he's rich and powerful and cruel
he doesn't have feelings
like other men, but he does.
And you know what?
I bet he wouldn't sell
the plant for $100 million.
Ooh, that's a lot of money.
D'oh!
Uh... Mr. Smithers,
do you have change
for a dollar?
Good, good--
try to eat something.
(ringing)
Homer Simpson here.
Homer, it's your stockbroker.
Your stock in the power plant
just went up for
the first time in ten years.
I own stock?
Yes, all the employees got some
in exchange for waiving
certain constitutional rights.
So, how much did it go up?
Wait a minute,
let's not do that yet.
The book says we have
to make a little small talk
before you get down to business.
-Everybody alive?
-Yeah.
-Like any sports?
-Sure.
-Ever go dancing?
-Not anymore.
-We should get together sometime.
-That'd be great.
Ah, there, now we
trust each other.
Well... how are you?
(hacking)
Near death.
I'm renewing my notary license
on a weekly basis.
Uh-huh, so what's
my stock up to?
Let me punch that up
on the computer.
Uh... 25¢ a share.
What should I do?
Let me put it this way--
you'll get $25 if you sell now.
Sell! Sell! Sell!
Whoo-hoo!
Twenty-five dollars!
Ooh!
Mmm... hot wax.
Ooh.. hammer.
♪ Fight, fight, fight ♪
♪ The Itchy & Scratchy Show! ♪
(humming)
(screaming)
Mmm.
(laughing)
Bart, Bart, turn to
the financial channel.
Aunt Patty says our stock
is skyrocketing.
Unconfirmed takeover rumors
have pushed Burns Worldwide
from 1/8 to 52
and a quarter.
(gasping)
Your father's stock
is worth $5,200!
Wow! 5,200 smackers!
Oooh!
Ahhh...
(laughing)
Hey, Homer.
Want a Duff?
No, I'd like a bottle
of Henry K. Duff's
Private Reserve.
(gasping)
Are you sure?
'Cause once I open the bottle,
there's no refund.
For your information
I just made a cool $25
playing the market.
Buy low, sell high--
that's my motto.
I may just quit my job
at the power plant
and become a full-time
stock market guy.
Have a Duff, boys!
(German accent)
Oh, thank you.
My English is not perfect,
but I have to tell you
your beer
is like swill to us.
Do I have that right?
I'm saying that only a swine
would drink this beer.
Ja, but thank you, anyway.
Hey, you guys aren't
from around here, are you?
Nein.
We are from Germany.
He is from the east;
I am from the west.
I had a big company,
and he had a big company.
Now we have
a very big company.
We are interested in
buying the power plant.
Do you think your owner
would ever sell it?
Well, I happen to know
that he won't sell it
for less than
$100,000,000.
A hundred million?
Ein, zwei, drei,
vier, funf...
Oh, don't worry.
We'll still have enough left
to buy the Cleveland Browns.
It's the miracle
we've been waiting for.
What are we gonna
spend it on?
Homer's probably buying some
magic beans with it right now.
We'll have
a savings account.
We've never had one.
Kids, I think everything is
going to be okay from now on.
Hey, hey!
Oh, Homer!
You heard?
We heard.
Isn't it wonderful?
We have some great plans
for that money.
Well, I'm afraid I had
some great plans too.
What do you mean?
I spent it on beer.
Surprise, surprise.
You spent $5,200 on beer?!
$5,200?
What are you talking about?
What?
(screams)
I sold it all for 25 bucks!
-(grunts)
-Oww!
Come on, everybody.
It makes you feel better.
Hey, Homer.
Did you buy this car
with your stock money?
Sure did, and
the great thing about it
is everybody got rich.
For once, all us working
stiffs got a break.
(moans)
Wait till you see Lenny.
He just got back from
the plastic surgeon.
Sheesh, Lenny, looks like you
got the works.
It started out as an eye tuck,
but the stock kept goin' up.
Hey, come here.
Mr. Burns is on TV.
-Mr. Burns?
-Here, Mr. Burns.
Over here. Mr. Burns?
Mr. Burns, we've heard that
a German consortium
has offered to
purchase the plant.
Any comments?
You'll see the Statue of Liberty
wearing lederhosen
before you see Germans
running my plant!
Well then, sir,
why are you meeting with them?
So I can look Uncle Fritz
square in the monocle
and say, "nein!"
(speaking German)
You never cease
to amaze me, sir.
Hmm?
Hmm...
Whoo-hoo!
Whoo-hoo! Whoo-hoo!
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
(clears throat)
I grudgingly accept.
♪♪ (polka)
Now, don't worry.
I think that you'll find
these two gentlemen
are as
American as apple pie.
Hans and Fritz--
Why, that's just
John and Frank.
Ich bin ein
Springfielder.
They'll bring
their own people in.
This ain't good.
We could all
lose our jobs.
Look at all those
worried faces...
except for Lenny.
He looks great.
This is the worst day
of my life.
Those lousy Germans
can't fire me.
I'm the only one who knows
how to unjam the rod
bottom dissociator.
Well, they can't fire me.
I'm the only one certified
to run the gaseous contaminant
particulate fire.
They can't fire me.
BOTH: Why?
'Cause...
MAN: Guten morgen.
I am Horst.
The new owners have elected
me to speak with you
because I am
the most nonthreatening.
Perhaps I remind you of
the lovable Sergeant Schultz
on "Hogan's Heroes."
-Oh, yeah.
-Yeah, he does.
What is the best way
to an efficient plant?
-I don't know.
-Well, uh...
Search me.
Happy workers who feel secure
at their jobs--
So let's get to know
each other better.
Do we have any
alcoholics among us?
-Uh... me.
-Right here.
I'm drunk right now.
You'll be given
a six-week treatment
at our drying-out facility
in Hawaii,
after which
you'll return at full pay.
-Oh, great!
-Great.
Hey, maybe I'll marry
Elizabeth Taylor.
Lucky drunks.
Also, we cannot uber-emphasize
the importance
of employee safety.
We plan to have
some frank discussions
with your safety inspector.
Yeah, sock it
to 'em, Horst!
Psst. Hey, Homer.
Aren't you
the safety inspector?
D'oh!
Mm-hmm-hmm...
Mm-hmm...
That's one big check.
You look sharp today, sir.
You looken sharpen todayen,
mein herr.
You looken sharpen
todayen, mein herr.
That was
a gutsy decision, sir.
BURNS: Smithers,
come here. I want you.
I wanted to give you something
to remember me by,
and I know you've always had
your eye on this photo
of Elvis and me.
He was so good
to his mother, sir.
Yes, but I couldn't understand
a word that man said.
(with Elvis drawl)
"Mr. Burns...
(mumbling) ...hound dog."
Stop it.
You're killing me, sir.
Oh, sir, what will
you do next?
First, I'll get that new hip
I've been hankering for.
Then, who knows?
Beekeeping, boxing,
bocce ball...
The world is my oyster,
Smithers.
Farewell.
Lisa, your father
needs your help.
Do you know anything
about Germany?
Well, it's a country
in Europe.
Good, good. I'm learning.
One of the economic powers
of the world.
Because we send them money?
(laughing)
No.
Because they're efficient
and punctual,
with a strong work ethic.
D'oh!
Oh, woe is me.
Homie, come to bed.
Oh, Marge, I'm gonna be
fired, I know it.
Don't worry.
Whatever happens,
we'll pay the bills somehow.
Marge, it's not the money.
My job is my identity.
If I'm not
a safety whatchama-jigger,
I'm nothing.
Well, if you can't sleep,
why don't you do
something constructive?
Ooh... Battlestar Galactica!
(groaning)
Fit, damn you! Fit!
(grunting)
There.
(snoring)
Yo, Homer, you got
to get ready for work.
Uh-huh. What?
What am I gonna--
(gasps)
Hey, you!
Stop being... so unsafe!
Smitty... safen up.
Homer, could we have
a word with you?
No.
I must have phrased
that badly.
My English is--
How you say? Inelegant.
I meant to say may we have
a brief, friendly chat?
-No.
-Once again, I have failed.
"We request
the pleasure of your company
for a free exchange of ideas."
No!
You've been safety inspector
for two years.
What initiatives have you
spearheaded in that time?
Uh... all of them?
I see.
Then you must have
some good ideas
for the future as well.
I sure do!
Such as?
Well, uh...
I wish the candy machine
wasn't so picky about taking
beat-up dollar bills...
because...
a lot of workers
really like candy.
We understand, Homer.
After all, we are from
the land of chocolate.
HOMER: Mmm...
the land of chocolate!
♪♪ (upbeat)
(barks)
(yipping)
Wow... chocolate, half-price!
♪ La la la-la-la-la-la ♪
Mr. Simpson?
♪ La-la-la-la-la ♪
-Mr. Simpson?
-Huh?
Oh, I'm sorry.
We were talking
about chocolate?
That was ten minutes ago.
I think I did
pretty good in there.
Yeah, you know
those Germans aren't so bad.
Sure, they've made mistakes
in the past,
but that's why pencils
have erasers.
HORST (on PA):
Attention, workers.
We have completed
our evaluation of the plant.
We regret to announce
the following layoffs
which I will read
in alphabetical order.
Simpson, Homer.
That is all.
(disappointed meow)
Ay, caramba!
Now Bart, Lisa did
a wonderful job
on my hair,
and we saved $40
for the family.
We all have to pull together
till your father
gets a new job.
I made a
new bar of soap
by squeezing all our
little soap slivers together.
MARGE: That's very clever.
And today, instead of
buying comic books,
I just read them
and left them in the store.
(groans)
You shouldn't do that.
My jump rope broke but
I just tied it back together.
That's good, Lisa.
I didn't take
a bath today
and I may not take
one tomorrow.
I want you to take baths,
Bart.
Lousy German know-it-alls.
Who are they
to say I'm not safe?
Oh, what's the matter
with this thing?
No problems here.
That's right,
Burnsie.
Keep your wrist
supple.
Throw it,
don't aim it.
(grunting)
(laughing)
This is my park.
Get out!
It was worth it.
This place has really gone
to hell, Mr. Burns.
It's obscene what they did
to your office.
Listen Smithers,
you caught me at a bad time
but my folk guitar class
has been canceled for tonight.
Would you like to get
together for a drink?
Would I?!
I got to go.
See you at 6:00.
(bell dings)
You're going down,
my friend.
Yes, sir, Mr. Burns.
That shouldn't be.
Ach du lieber!
Raccoons!
That's right.
Gather the nectar,
my little drones
and make the honey--
honey for your children.
Fools!
(maniacal laughter)
Ready for
that drink, sir?
Just a second, Smithers.
Let me introduce you
to the gang.
That's Buzz, that's Honey,
and you see
that queen over there?
Her name is Smithers.
That's very flattering,
sir, but we should go.
Several bees
are stinging me.
(phone rings)
Moe's Tavern.
Moe speaking.
Uh, yes, I'm looking for
a Mrs. O'Problem,
first name: Bea.
Uh, just a minute, I'll check.
Uh... Bea O'Problem?
Bea O'Problem?
Come on, guys.
Do I have
a B.O. Problem here?
You sure do.
(laughing)
Oh! It's you, isn't it?
(Bart laughing)
Listen you!
When I get a hold of you
I'm gonna use your head
for a bucket
and paint my house
with your brains.
(laughing)
Bart, I want you
to go down
to Moe's Tavern.
I need you to bring
your father home.
(gulp)
(snoring)
Excuse me.
I'm looking for--
Wait a minute.
I know that voice.
If it isn't
little Bart Simpson!
I haven't seen you in years.
That's right.
That's my pop.
Oh, little Bart,
we hear all about
your monkeyshines.
Bet you get into
all kinds of trouble
he don't even know about.
Am I right? Huh?
Am I right?
Well, I make
some crank phone calls.
Aw, ha-ha, that's great!
Ha-ha-ha!
Hey, would you sing
that old song
you used to sing for me?
Moe, for you, anything.
BURNS:
Look! A blue-collar bar.
Oh, Smithers,
let's go slumming.
♪ Every teddy bear
who's been good ♪
♪ Is sure of
a treat today ♪
♪ There's lots of
marvelous things to eat ♪
♪ And wonderful games
to play ♪
♪ Beneath the trees
where nobody sees ♪
♪ They'll hide and seek
as long as they please ♪
♪ Today's the day ♪
♪ The teddy bears
have their picnic ♪
(cheering)
BARNEY: Encore!
He's a pip,
this one is.
Ah, the mirthless laugh
of the damned.
Hold your nose, Smithers.
We're going in.
(cheering)
Watch me blend in.
Barkeep,
some cheap domestic beer
for me and my buddy here.
I'm not your buddy,
you greedy, old reptile.
Smithers, who is
this saucy fellow?
Homer Simpson, sir.
Sector sieben gruber--
I mean, sector 7-G.
Recently terminated.
That's right.
I lost my job
so that you could have
another $100 million!
Let me ask you something.
Does your money cheer you up
when you're feeling blue?
-Yes.
-Okay. Bad example.
So let me ask you this:
Does your money ever hug you
when you come home at night?
Why, no.
And does it ever say
"I love you"?
No, it doesn't.
(singsongy)
Nobody loves you.
You're old and you're ugly.
-Way to go, Homer!
-Nobody loves you!
Good heavens, Smithers.
They're not afraid
of me anymore.
BART: Hey, Mr. Burns.
Did you get
the letter I sent?
Letter? I don't recall
any letter--
That's because I
forgot to stamp it!
-Ew!
-(loud laughter)
Ah, that kid slays me.
That was no accident.
Let's get out of here.
♪ Na na nah nah ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey ♪
♪ Good-bye ♪
What good is money
if you can't inspire terror
in your fellow man?
I've got to get
my plant back.
(screams)
Gott in Himmel!
Who'd have thought
a nuclear plant
could be
such a death trap?
It will cost
another 100 million
just to bring it
up to code.
Please sell me my plant back.
I'll pay anything.
Isn't this
a happy coincidence!
You are desperate to buy,
and we are desperate to sell.
Desperate, eh?
Advantage: Burns.
This is my offer.
I think you'll find
it's most unfair,
but those are the breaks.
But, Mr. Burns, this is
half of what we paid you.
That's my final offer.
Take it or leave it.
All right, Mr. Burns,
you win,
but beware-- we Germans
aren't all smiles und sunshine.
(sarcastic)
Ooh, the Germans are mad at me.
I'm so scared.
Ooh, the Germans!
Uh-oh, the Ger--
-Stop it.
-Stop that.
Don't let the Germans
come after me.
Please stop the 'pretending
you are scared' game.
No, they're so
big and strong--
Stop it, Mr. Burns.
Protect me
from the Germans!
Burns! Stop it!
(children playing)
Get out!
This is my office now!
You too!
This is a place of business
not a pee-wee flop house.
(crying)
Your orders, sir.
Restore my office,
cancel all repairs,
and rehire that chap
who sassed me in the bar.
Homer Simpson? But why?
Smithers, I keep
my friends close
and my enemies even closer.
He'll slowly regain
his confidence
as the months and years
drift by,
blissfully unaware
that the sword of Damocles is
dangling just above his head.
And then, one day
when he least expects it...
(grunts)
Whoo-hoo!
I got my job back!
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.