The Simpsons
D'oh!
My brain!
Welcome to Career Day.
Here to tell to
you about his job
is Bart's friend's dad,
Kirk Van Houten.
How many of you children
have gone out to your car
and found a flyer
on the windshield?
Are you the guy
that puts them there?
No. I'm his assistant.
But one time he was sick
and he let me do it.
I totally screwed it up.
That's it.
I see. Well, we still
have 56 minutes left.
Any questions?
Do you know Mom's
getting re-married?
What? But she...
I think we
should probably talk
about that later, Son.
No. You might as well
talk about it now.
That was one
lousy Career Day.
If we can't get
better speakers,
we'll have to go
back to teaching.
And I can't stare
at those lifeless
fisheyes anymore!
As head of the
Student Activities Committee,
I have an idea.
I was wondering what
she was doing here.
The speakers are poor
because we're letting
just anybody do it.
Groundskeeper Willie,
Groundskeeper Willie's
enemy, Seamus.
Yes. Seamus.
Ninety minutes of watching
a man drink in a bathtub.
Well, I think we should
try the Springfield
Speakers Bureau.
Good idea.
Seamus,
we won't need you
to speak anymore.
What?
This is your doing, Willie!
I'll turn your groin
to pudding!
You speak like a poet,
but you punch like one,
too!
You bastard!
Wow. Walter Mondale,
Marvin Hamlisch,
Mark Fuhrman.
The former president
of Procter & Gamble!
We have a special this month.
Mr. Blackwell debates Mr. T.
Oh, please.
I've seen nicer chains
on a set of snow tires.
I pity the fool who
derives self-esteem
from mocking other
people's clothes.
I hate myself.
Ooh! Here's a
wonderful speaker,
Geoff Jenkins!
Who?
He created a cartoon
called Danger Dog.
It's popular with
kids and adults.
Yes. Fine. He'll do.
Anything to end this
unstructured conversation.
And in a gutless act
of political correctness,
Pizza Day will
now be known as
Italian-American
Sauce Bread Day.
Now that's sensitivity.
Right, Giuseppe?
Giuseppe is such
a happy monkey.
And now,
today's guest speaker,
the creator of Danger Dog,
Geoff Jenkins!
Geoff! Geoff! Geoff!
Thanks, kids.
Next month we'll be
airing the Danger Dog
Easter Special.
Would anyone like to
see a sneak preview?
Yeah!
Danger Dog,
Neuterville needs you!
I hope this is important.
I've got a hot date tonight.
With Sarah Jessica Barker.
Nice.
Anyway, your archenemy,
Molly Ringworm,
has threatened to destroy
the city with her puke ray.
The mayor's barf is
worse than his bite.
Le mot juste.
If you freeze the frame,
you can see that
the chunks of barf
are actually pictures
of our animators
and their friends.
Are there any questions?
Here! Right here! Hello!
Yes, you.
What state does
Danger Dog live in?
Michigan. Next.
Why does Danger Dog
mean more to me than
school or church?
Because those things suck.
I have
a question, Mr. Jenkins.
Could you tell us
about all the hard work
and buckling down
that you put
into every cartoon?
Are you kidding?
This is the easiest job
in the world.
I spend most of my time
eating candy and going
to R-rated movies.
Wow. Cool.
Wow.
Well, then,
tell the children how hard
you studied in school
to get
where you are today.
Studied?
Kids, all I ever did was
sit in class and doodle.
Like this one.
It's what your principal
would look like as a woman.
Fire, children!
Hurry outside!
There's no time to let
today's lecture sink in!
Why'd you do that?
I won't stand by
while you're
glamorizing sass.
Now those youngsters
will throw their lives away,
drawing things
that never were.
I'm coming up with
my own cartoon character.
He's called Danger Cat.
Mine's called Trouble Dog.
I'm called Ralph.
Mine is Danger Dude.
But he's a dog.
Oh, yeah.
Well,
I'm my own toughest critic,
but I think it's genius.
Now, to sell it
for millions.
This comic strip is
lame and derivative.
I'll be
the judge of that!
Oh...
Stan Lee?
Creator of Marvel Comics?
Greetings, true believers.
My heart is pounding
like Thor's hammer
on Dr. Doom's
titanium-infused faceplate!
Hey, aren't you
the guy who was
stalking Lynda Carter?
The term is "courting. "
The restraining order
says, "No, no. "
But her eyes say,
"Yes, yes. "
Let's see what
you've got, son.
My Spidey sense
is tingling.
It's that good?
Did I say "Spidey"?
I meant stinky. 'Nuff said.
What did I do wrong?
I don't know.
Try everything.
Now hold on, Comic Book Guy.
This boy's still
finding his voice.
So, you're saying
I should keep trying?
Absolutely.
And if you fail,
you can always open
a comic book store.
Stan Lee insulted me.
But in Bizarro World,
that means he likes me.
I just need
one great idea.
Batman!
It's been done.
Green Lantern. No.
I like Little Dot.
Could you rip that off?
I mean,
who's gonna know?
I'd know, Mom!
That little girl
sure loved dots.
Hmm. All I need is
one classic character.
Stupid lawn chair!
Come on! Unfold, you...
Ow!
D'oh!
Hey!
This'll teach
that stupid chair!
I'm on fire!
I hope
no one's drawing this!
Hey, always drawing
your old man, huh?
You must think
I'm the greatest
dad in the world.
Lousy minor setback!
This world sucks!
Don't you hate carpet
stores that charge extra
for the under padding?
I hate them so much!
Tonight,
When Dinosaurs Get Drunk...
Mmm!
Oh, I've been there, man.
...has been canceled.
Instead we bring you
The Boring World
of Niels Bohr.
My ice cream sandwich!
Then where the hell's
the remote?
Why do people
keep moving it?
Stupid...
This is perfect.
A couple of stink lines
around his butt,
and I'm done.
Angry Dad rocks!
"Argh! I'm angry. "
That's like something
my dads would say.
Simpson, you've created
a timeless comic character.
Thanks, guys.
Will you sign
Martin's cast?
What cast? Ow!
I won't be swimming
this summer.
Bart, this is just Dad.
It's a composite character.
Your dad, my dad,
a little of Maggie's dad.
No. It's just Dad.
Maybe Angry Dad
needs a sidekick,
Know-It-All Sister!
Can she have a pony?
And the last line
in the scene?
Your penciling
is sub-Ziggy
and the main character
is off-model
in every frame.
However,
I deem this rack-worthy.
Wow, I made it!
My week-long dream
has come true!
Hold it, son.
Wouldn't you rather have
an exciting action figure?
But only Batman
fits in my Batmobile.
Are you nuts?
The Thing fits in
there perfectly.
Look.
He's fitting right now.
Stan Lee came back?
Stan Lee never left.
And I'm starting to
think that his mind
is no longer in
mint condition.
You broke my Batmobile!
Broke?
Or made it better?
Now I can't stand
in line anymore.
Bart Simpson,
creative genius?
What's it to you?
I'm from the Internet.
We'd like to
turn Angry Dad into
an animated series.
Wow! Angry Dad,
an Internet cartoon!
I'll be in cyberspace next to
the Nabisco Cookie Web site!
Hey, Soul Patch,
you cut the line!
Here's my card.
Whoa!
This is people working?
This is great.
Hey, Bart. Care for
a children's cappuccino?
What up, man?
This is my manager/sister,
Lisa.
What up?
Everyone here
loves Angry Dad.
It's just what
we've been looking for.
So, what do you
want to do with it?
Bart, I'm not a woman
and I can't have babies.
But I can
give life to animated
Internet cartoons.
Let me show you one
of our hottest shows,
Bin Laden in a Blender.
Well, it delivers
what it promises.
Now, Bart,
we can't pay you a salary.
But we can give you stock.
How is your
company gonna make money?
Do you have a business model?
How many shares of
stock will it take to
end this conversation?
Two million.
It is done.
Now, let's watch
another of our
great cartoons,
Lou Rawls, Secret Agent.
You'll never find
that microfilm of mine
Bart, meet the voice
of Angry Dad.
Okay. Let's hear it.
Well, I was thinking
of something like,
"I'm a big fat idiot!"
Wow! I think
we have our Angry Dad.
Woo-hoo!
When do I get paid?
In 2012.
D'oh!
Now, we just add color.
In five minutes, it'll be
on the World Wide Web.
I can't wait that long.
To pass the time,
help yourself to
some more stock.
That's funny!
There's only one way
my show can compete
with this.
Book that animal
that always chomps
on my groin.
Susan Anton?
No, the lemur!
Oh, what a day.
Maybe the headlines
will cheer me up.
That's opinion, not news!
That guy's hilarious.
I especially like
his white shirt
and blue pants.
Wait a second.
Angry Dad is me.
Yeah.
Didn't you know? You've been
world-famous for an hour now.
You're the Internet's
number one
non-porno site.
Which makes you
ten-trillionth overall.
What kind of a monster
would humiliate me like this?
This has been
a Bart-toon presentation.
In association with
Ay Carumba Entertainment.
Why that little...
Stupid Bart-toon.
Bart-toon, that's clever.
I'm gonna kill him.
Look,
it's Internet buffoon,
Angry Dad.
Let's send him into
one of his trademark fits.
Hey, come on!
Make your eyes explode.
Stop it!
The more you rock,
the angrier I get!
You heard the freak.
Leave me alone!
Look at me.
I'm Angry Dad!
This job sure is easy.
Now, to press this button.
Not again!
Angry Dad, you're fired.
Die, monster!
Homer, what are you doing?
We're just rehearsing
The Motion Picture.
How'd you like to be played
by John Goodman?
That's so obvious.
It should be Gary Oldman.
Dad, I'm no fan
of Bart's cartoon,
but you have a real
problem with anger.
I'm just passionate.
Like all us Greeks.
No, you're angry.
Look, you're punching
the cat right now.
I am...
Oh, my gosh,
you're right!
I'm a rage-aholic.
I just can't live
without rage-ahol!
Congratulations, Dad.
The first step
is admitting it.
Is it also the last step?
No. The last step
is quitting.
Very well.
I'm not gonna be Angry Dad
for one day longer!
I'm giving up
anger forever!
If you ask me,
you should give
up fatty foods.
I said anger!
Did it again.
Where the hell is that
soothing music coming from?
Homer, what's going on?
I gave up anger forever.
From now on,
I'm into candles,
soft music,
and horse tranquilizers.
Nothing can make
me mad out here.
Paperboy!
Milkman!
Piano lady!
Must suppress rage.
Huh?
Come on,
Angry Dad, get angry!
Don't make me do a clip show!
Hello there,
Flan-diddily-danders.
Hey, Homer.
I've been singing
your praises all day.
Marge said we could
have choir practice
in your house tonight.
Here's a preview.
God said to Noah
build yourself an arky-arky
Animals came on by
onesies and twosies-twosies
Elephants and
kangaroosies-roosies
This little trap
is gonna make
my dad angrier
than he's ever been.
In the meantime,
I got to tell
those Internet guys
to hold tight.
Can I come, too?
Good idea.
You can speak
nerd to them.
I'm not a nerd, Bart.
Nerds are smart.
Oh, my God!
What happened?
They went belly up
like all the other
Internet companies.
Looks like
the bubble burst.
Bubbles can burst?
Yeah, but it's a golden age
for the repo business.
One that shall never end.
Bart, it's over.
Ow!
What do you mean,
"It's over"?
We're bankrupt.
The stock is at zero.
But I have
52 million shares.
What's 52 million times zero?
And don't tell me it's zero!
Bart, it's not about
how much stock you have.
It's about how
much copper wire
you can get out of
the building with!
Looks like you can't
retire by age 12.
Yeah. But at least now
that my show's canceled,
I don't need material.
So there's no need
to lure my dad into
the trap I set for him.
The trap!
They call me
mellow yellow, quite rightly
This fellow never bellows,
quite rightly
Mmm.
This looks suspicious.
But delicious!
Cacti!
Dirty diapers on strings!
Time to put this
ordeal behind me.
Homer mad!
Thank God his
pants stayed on.
Homer mad! Homer smash!
Get revenge on world!
Look!
It's the Incredible Hulk!
He can't be the Hulk!
I'm the Hulk!
Please.
You couldn't even
change into Bill Bixby.
Come on, damn it!
Change!
Forget it.
I really did it once.
Yes, yes. I just wish
you had the power
to leave my store.
You almost
had it there.
Bart, your prank cost
$10 million in damages!
I know. I'm sorry.
Sorry for what?
Saving your father's life?
What?
It's true.
You see, these boils
on Homer's neck
are pent up rage.
If Bart's trap
hadn't set Homer off,
the anger would've
overwhelmed Homer's system.
You mean I shouldn't
punish Bart at all?
Why, if anything,
he should punish you.
Huh?
Okay.
Well, Son,
I want to show you
how grateful I am.
Let's go fishing.
Who knew that anger
was saving my life?
Say it, don't spray it.
You're trying
to get me angry!
Thank you.
You're not welcome.
D'oh!
I love you, boy.
Ha-ha! You love a boy!
Stop it now!
If you love me so much,
why don't you marry me?
That's a good one.
English - US - PSDH