CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screeching)
D’oh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
This is
so exciting,
watching a movie
outside with the whole town.
Yes, thank you for
talking to all of us
like we just tuned in.
Ooh, a fat man falls--
real original.
(groans)
Dad, there aren’t
any places left to sit.
(frantic whimpering)
(grunts)
There’s a spot.
MILHOUSE:
Hurry, Dad!
We got to get
that space!
♪♪
-Hey!
-Sorry.
-Aah...
-Oy!
-(groans)
-Oh!
We’re not
gonna make it.
Yes, we are.
(giggling)
(Homer giggles)
Oh!
Tonight’s G-rated gem is
a silent film
from my favorite year--
yester.
While you’re watching this
quiet riot,
I’ll be slipping these religious
pamphlets
on your windshields.
Start her up, boys.
(playing melodramatic music)
Hey, can you
fix the sound?!
And the color!
And show it
in a regular theater?
♪♪
NELSON:
Ha hah!
This movie
isn’t silent.
I can hear
it sucking.
All the snacks we stole
are "heart-smart"
What the hell is
a radish anyway?
It’s like an apple
did it with an onion.
Dude, shut up and huck.
(grunting)
(both yelling)
Uh-uh!
Radishes!
(all groaning)
I demand entertainment!
Yeah, show the movie!
Come on,
let’s go!
This is our chance.
We’ve been carrying
these home movies
around for years,
just waiting
for a moment like this.
Calm down, everybody.
Here’s a movie of us.
(crowd booing)
Wow, even I ain’t
hoping for porn.
("The Aquarium"
by Camille Saint-Saens plays)
Ooh, this is one of our
trips to Barnacle Bay.
We used to rent a beach house
there every summer.
♪♪
I was so happy on that island.
I never seen Marge want to go
somewhere so badly.
I’m gonna take her back there
by burning that home movie
on to a DVD.
I’ve never seen Marge like a DVD
about a place so much.
I’m gonna make her dream
come true
by downloading that movie
on to her Ipod.
Marge, I’m sorry
I couldn’t figure out
how to get that movie
on to your Ipod.
So I’m taking the family
on a surprise vacation
to Barnacle Bay!
BOTH:
Ta-da!
Aw.
(gasps):
Where’s Maggie?
-Ta-da!
We left plenty of food
so you won’t starve.
Oh, thank you.
I was talking
to the cat.
(ship’s horn sounds)
It’s the famous
Barnacle Bay fog.
There’s even
a poem about it.
"Oh, cotton candy
in gossamer light,
Thy soft gray kiss
upon my cheek..."
(sniffs)
It smells like heinie!
(coughing and gagging)
(gasps)
My childhood paradise--
It’s a dump.
♪♪
Ugh! This is the most disgusting
place we’ve ever gone.
What about Brazil?
After Brazil.
Oh, this was my favorite
seahorse.
I called him,
Mr. Funny-Good-Feeling.
(gasps)
Oh, God, someone carved
swastikas on your eyes.
Oh, Marge, I’m sure
it was just some guy
filled with hate.
Oh, my God!
Tourists.
We haven’t seen their
kind in years.
Dip your berries?
Powder your jellies?
You could
caramel my arm.
(Italian accent):
I make it nice
and sticky, eh?
(sizzles)
(screams)
I didn’t say stop.
Mmm!
(grunting greedily)
Homer, that’s
too much sugar.
It’s not sugar.
It’s caramel.
(sucking and moaning)
Excuse me, skipper.
This island used
to be a paradise.
What happened?
(scoffs)... I bet it was
Bill Clinton’s fault.
No. No, it was
long before him.
Slick Willie wiggles
out of another one.
(groans)
This island has been
on hard times since...
well, since
the yum-yum fish disappeared.
Yum-yum fish?
Oh, yum-yum fish are
all we used to eat here.
They’re the most delicious
fish in the ocean.
Better than cod?
Much better.
Whoa, baby.
We brought them in
by the boatload,
day and night.
Then one day they,
well, they were gone.
Maybe you just
overfished them?
Maybe they
under-spawned.
Maybe you killed them all.
Maybe the fish
killed themselves.
Maybe you should be
ashamed of yourself!
Maybe you should
marry Milhouse.
(gasps)
Yeah, that’s right,
I know about Milhouse.
(Marge sighs)
I guess, in the end, nothing’s
as good as you remember.
(stairs squeak)
Oh, I can’t stand to see
your mother unhappy.
But this town could be great
for your mother again,
and I know three people
who can make it happen.
(grunting and groaning)
Nice brushwork, Emily.
Nathaniel, you could learn
a lot from her.
Mr. Simpson, we’d do anything
to help a stranger
who claimed a vacation here
30 years ago.
And make a little
meth money on the side.
(stuporous laughter)
(singsong voice):
Oh, Marge!
We have a surprise!
Come to the window...
and look down at the street!
(gasping)
Homer, you made an effort.
("The Daring Young Man on
the Flying Trapeze" plays)
Homer, this is wonderful.
Where are the kids?
Oh, they’re getting
a little exercise.
(grunting, groaning)
MARGE:
Can I go again?
HOMER:
All night long, baby.
(groaning)
What a great day.
It’s not over yet.
(fireworks whistle and pop)
(all gasping)
Hee-hee-hee!
Blue pinwheel, red pinwheel...
big white ball.
Wait for the "ah."
CROWD:
Ah!
A green spinner
to build suspense
and then the big finale.
The ka-pow boom!
Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom,
pow, pow, pow, pow, pow,
ba-boom!
Ka-powi.
(sizzling)
(shrieks)
(screaming)
(fireworks whistle)
Oh, so, forming
an angry mob, eh?
Who we going after?
Oh, hey!
Well, at least
they left your underwear on.
That was nice of them.
I think the hook
is touching my brain.
(speaking gibberish)
...package, board baby,
bortal, bortal, bortal.
My husband meant no harm.
There must be some way
he can pay for what he did.
He’s good
at opening jars.
I say let him fish it off.
These waters are so barren,
by the time he pays the debt,
he’ll be as old
and as queer as I am.
Queer strange,
or queer gay?
Oh, a touch of both.
(maniacal cackling)
Ooh... (kissing sounds)
Homer, I want you
to meet my crew.
This is
my first mate, Billy.
And this is Fausto.
Yeah, he just plays
with that knife
all day and night.
It’s my thing.
Great, now I need a new thing.
How many yum-yum fish
did we get?
(sighing):
None.
Just a few slarg fish.
Ew, it tastes terrible.
You don’t eat it.
Its oil is used
to polish
stripper poles.
Ugh, finally, something
even I wouldn’t eat.
Well, maybe a little more.
Terrible.
(thunder crashing)
Here you go.
Beer battered shrimp.
Wait, this is bait.
Homer, I told you to
beer batter the shrimp
and bait the hooks.
Did you do
the opposite?
Uh, I thought today
was Opposite Day.
By the way,
you’re very ugly.
(loud whisper):
It’s Opposite Day.
Hey, Captain, we should not
go out and check the hooks.
It’s not Opposite Day.
So that means...
it is Opposite Day.
CAPTAIN:
It’s not Opposite Day!
(boat creaking)
The yum-yum fish--
they’re back.
We’re going to be rich.
And it’s all thanks
to you, Homer.
Or should I say...
Chief Fish Clubber Homer.
I don’t know what to say.
Let your club
do the talking.
(Etta James singing):
♪ At last ♪
♪ My love has come along ♪
♪ My lonely days are over... ♪
Ooh, an institute.
DIORAMA VOICE:
Press button to see what
global warming will do
in the next three years.
Three years
is a long ways away.
MAN:
Oh, my God--
a perfect storm.
My husband is out there.
I won’t lie to you.
It’s the most powerful storm
I’ve ever seen,
and I’ve seen three storms.
(gasping)
Captain, I don’t like
the look of the western sky.
Let us head back.
I’m sure our TiVo’s are
groaning with great shows.
We’re not leaving while
there’s still fish
to be air-drowned.
Are you sure,
Captain?
The barometer don’t lie.
All right, now listen,
if a storm were coming,
my trick knee would
be acting up.
Hey... hey... hey... hey.
Dear God.
Oh, Homie, I’m so worried.
But if I concentrate,
our love is so strong,
I know I can hear your thoughts.
HOMER:
Dear Marge, how are you?
I am fine.
The waves here are way bigger
than the ones at home.
And the saltwater is rising.
What’s next, pepper water?
Ha-ha. Love ya. Homer Simpson.
Oh...!
(grunts)
This old barge
can’t take much more!
Take out the life raft!
Bart, what the hell
are you doing in there?
Dad, I couldn’t stay
with Mom and Lisa
while you were
out here.
Aw, son.
There were going to go
to the folk art museum,
then they were going
to paint crab shells.
Not crush them, paint them!
You did the right
thing, boy.
(all agree)
Ugh!
What is it, Moe?
I just had this
awful feeling
that, uh, Homer’s
in terrible trouble.
Ooh, that’s funny.
I just had a feeling
that some guy I don’t know
named Fausto
is in trouble.
Come on.
We got to go
help Homer.
And Fausto!
(thunder crashing)
Whoa, whoa, it’s really
coming down out there.
We could run
to the car.
Yeah, but then we’d have
to stand there
while we get
the doors unlocked.
Don’t you have
one of them keys
that beeps
the doors open?
Yeah, but still.
(all screaming)
Watch me drive
a golf ball off the bow.
(grunts)
Yeah!
Shi...
...pwreck!
(yelling)
We’re still gonna make it,
aren’t we, Dad?
Uh, sure we will, son.
Right, Captain?
Absolutely, Bart.
The sea wouldn’t dare
take the life
of an apple-cheeked young lad
like yourself.
(loud whisper):
Should I hit him
with a shovel
to spare him the pain
of drowning?
(loud whisper):
Not yet.
What’s the code word?
(both gasp)
Oh, Mother Sea,
giver of fish,
taker of boats,
toilet to the world,
the Greeks call you "Poseidon,"
the Romans... "Aquaman."
Look into thy starfish heart
and protect our souls
so we might live
to go tubing on thee again.
Do you think your mother
will every remarry?
BART:
In about two seconds.
Why, you little...!
(gasping, grunting sounds)
Just see if I die!
(belling tolling)
Bart was on the boat?
(sobbing)
We’ll never know how that brave
crew spent their final moments.
Maybe a boiler blew up,
sheared their faces clean off.
All we do know is they’re
in heaven now,
hanging their lines off a cloud
and fishing for airplanes.
HOMER:
The hell we are!
Homer!
Bart!
Portuguese Fausto!
Yi-yo-yu!
How did you make it?
Well, handsome here
was in big trouble...
...when suddenly...
(gasps)
Oh, my God, it’s beautiful!
Welcome, Homer
to our watery realm.
Wait a minute.
How am I breathing?
You’re not.
Then when all seemed lost...
(coughing)
Aw! Lot of garbage
fish today.
I can’t go back
to living on the
surface world!
I can’t!
Then they brought us home.
So that’s our story.
Oh, wait. We were attacked
by a giant whale.
He turned out
to be pretty cool.
Come on, boys.
Let’s grab our nets
and go fish us some yum-yums.
(all cheer)
Wait!
Haven’t you learned
a lesson here?
Overfishing and greed
have brought this town
nothing but wrack and ruin.
(murmuring)
Repent! Repent,
before it’s too late!
I always wanted to do that
in a New England church.
Little she-nag
has a point.
Got to be some way
we can make money
without depleting
our precious oceans.
(saws buzzing loudly)
Nicely done, Lis.
Instead of killing
living things,
they’re just
killing trees.
MAN:
Step aside, please.
These logs have to go
to Larry Flynt’s paper mill,
where they’ll be made
into Hustler and Barely Legal
magazines.
This is not what
I wanted at all.
(chainsaws buzzing)
(gasping)
("The Aquarium"
by Camille Saint-Saens plays)
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Shh!
Enhanced by Fotokem