♪ The Simpsons ♪
(chalk screeches)
(bell ringing)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
Ugh!
(chattering)
They say the pancakes here
stink.
Thank you,
Agnes.
Let's begin.
I'm happy to report
that our shares
in Dynaflux Unimatics
are up a delicious
seven and three-quarters.
This means our investment
club portfolio
has nearly doubled
in value.
(murmuring)
I suggest
we pump our profits
into some new
high-risk ventures.
Oh! Oh!
How about Oklasoft?
It's Oklahoma's fastest-growing
software company.
Um, cushions?
Everybody likes
to sit on cushions.
Children are
so fat today.
Isn't there some way
we could make money off that?
There's a franchise fair
this weekend.
Why don't we buy
a business?
(murmuring)
I never thought of that.
I'm not wild about
these high-risk ventures.
They sound
a little risky.
Oh, Marge.
You are such
a wet blanket.
If we'd listened
to you,
we wouldn't have sponsored
that Mexican wrestler.
Yet she still gets to share
in all the profits.
-Mm-hmm.
-Is that fair?
I guess I'm just
not comfortable
with the whole idea
of "investing."
Face it.
You can't keep up
with the go-go '90s.
Well, Marge...
You're about as popular
as rug burn. (chuckles)
All in favor
of expelling Marge
from the Investorettes...
ALL: Aye!
All right, Helen.
If I'm not wanted,
I'll leave.
You'll get your pancakes
in the mail.
MARGE:
And then they gave me back
my $500 investment
and kicked me
out of the club.
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait.
Back up a bit now.
When are the pancakes
coming in the mail?
Well, maybe it's all
for the best.
What do you need
to make money for anyway?
As long as I have
my earning power,
this family's got nothing
to worry about.
Oww!
Oh, call work and tell them
I won't be in tomorrow.
Mom, this is no time
to be conservative.
Let's roll
the dice here.
It would be nice
to beat those women
at their own game.
Maybe I should
look into a franchise.
Greetings, humans. I am Investo the Robot
from the planet Opportuniac.
My superior brain advises you
to enter the franchise fair.
Well, we're trying to,
but you're blocking our way.
Danger! Danger!
Don't forget to pick up
pamphlets.
I'll handle this.
(sizzling)
(clunking, beeping)
(whistling)
Help, help, help.
Security code 30.
MAN: Well, that's the miracle
of the franchise.
You get all the equipment
and know-how you need,
plus a familiar brand name
people trust.
You'll be on a rocket ride
to the moon.
And while you're there,
would you pick up some
of that nice green moon money
for me-- Royce McCutcheon?
No deal,
McCutcheon.
That moon money
is mine.
Now, folks, I don't want
to alarm you,
but scientists say
40% of America's pictures
are hanging crooked.
ALL: No! No!
Yeah, it's true,
and I hear you asking,
"Well, who's going to straighten out
all these artistic abominations?"
Your friends? A neighbor?
Those fat cats in Washington?
(chuckling)
Good luck. Hey, you know,
maybe no one will notice.
Maybe the problem
will just fix itself.
Now, you're the one
who's being naive.
Okay, fair enough.
But you sound like
you're ready to become
your own boss
in the exciting world
of frame-nudging.
Yes, for a minimal
franchise fee
you'll receive a pair
of straightening gloves,
a canister of wall lubricant,
and a booklet of the most
commonly asked questions
you will hear,
including "Who are you?"
And "What are you doing here?"
Hmm, I don't want
to own my own business.
I don't know why I came here
in the first place.
Hello, Helen.
Marge.
Edna.
Uh...
Oh, my name is Agnes,
and you know it's Agnes.
It means lamb--
Lamb of God.
I'm sorry,
Agnes.
Marge.
♪ Do the hustle ♪
Did you know
that disco record sales
were up 400%
for the year ending 1976?
If these trends continue...
Aay!
Uh, your fish
are dead.
Yeah, I know.
I can't get them
out of there.
Hmm, pita.
Well, I don't know
about food
from the Middle East.
Isn't that whole area
a little iffy?
(laughs)
Hey, I'm no geographer.
You and I, why don't we
call it pocket bread, huh?
What's tahini?
Flavor sauce.
And falafel?
Crunch patties.
So, we'd be
selling foreign...
Specialty foods.
Here, try a Ben Franklin.
Mmm, that is good.
What's in it?
Tabbouleh
and rezmi-kabob.
Uh, that's our chef,
Christopher.
(ranting in foreign language)
I could see eating this.
I really could,
and I am not kidding.
(murmuring excitedly)
Look at them!
They've jumped
on the one franchise
I might possibly
have considered
thinking about
becoming interested in.
Hmm.
I'm not cut out
for the world of business.
Ooh, you sound like me.
Well, the old me,
which was, ironically,
the young me.
I was once like you were,
young lady--
like all these people--
lost in a sea
of flashy gimmicks
and empty promises.
Then God tossed me
a life preserver,
a tasty golden brown
life preserver.
Here. Try a pretzel.
Mmm!
That's not bad.
It's not only not bad;
it's knot bread.
"Knot bread"--
You get it?
Huh? Ha-ha? You see?
I do!
(both laughing)
"Knot bread."
(bugle plays fanfare)
Let's hear it
for the newest members
of the Fleet-A-Pita
franchise!
♪ I'm feeling good
from my head to my shoes... ♪
Maude... Helen...
Agnes... Luanne...
Edna... Bart...
Whoo!
We're number one!
We're number one.
Hey, what's going on?
Wait, wait. Hey.
Your franchise...
How much?
-$500.
-I'll take it!
Congratulations,
and welcome
to the dynamic world
of mobile pretzel
retailing.
When can I start?
What's my territory?
Eh, territory...
Well, let me tell you:
Wherever a young mother
is ignorant
of what to feed her baby,
you'll be there.
Wherever nacho penetration
is less than total,
you'll be there.
Wherever a Bavarian is not
quite full, you will be there.
Don't forget fat people.
They can't stop eating.
Hey! Pretzels!
Oh. Hello.
I'm Frank Ormand.
And if you're watching me,
that means
you've got pretzel fever,
and not the kind that attacked
my intestinal lining
some years back.
(laughing)
So let's get your franchise
up and running.
Start by setting up an office
in your basement or garage.
An automatic garage door opener
makes you feel
like you're working
in a futuristic wonderworld.
Next: Blanket your community
with flyers.
A phony ticker-tape parade
will help you
avoid littering laws.
(cheering)
Welcome back, space girl.
(sobbing)
Now you're ready
to make pretzels.
Open your bag of ingredients...
Ugh.
Check for millipedes.
Eww.
Hmm...
Hmm, hmm, hmm.
(exclaims)
(honking)
Hey, what's all that
commotion outside?
Why, it's one of those
pretzel wagons
the movie stars are
always talking about.
(gasping)
Here? At our plant?
That's right, Lenny.
Let's all give in
to deliciousness
the pretzel wagon way.
ALL: Yay!
-Yeah.
-That's pretzeltastic.
Let's go. Yeah.
Homer's right.
Oh, yeah.
Wow, Mom,
look at all those customers.
Hairnets, everyone.
Welcome to Pretzel Wagon.
May I take your order?
Uh, let's see.
I'll have... One--
Hey, hurry up.
I want to get
my pretzel.
One pretzel.
Thank you.
Uh, let's see, um...
I will have
one of your, uh...
Come on, come on,
while we're young.
(honking)
♪ Don't stop thinking
about tomorrow... ♪
Wow, check out that van.
It looks like it doesn't
even need our business.
Hey, let's go.
♪ It'll be
better than before ♪
♪ Yesterday's gone ♪
Excuse me.
I had this spot first.
Sorry, dear.
Just business. Ha!
Well, I guess Macy's
and Gimbels learned
to live side by side.
Gimbels is gone,
Marge, long gone.
You're Gimbels.
Very well.
There must be dozens
of great locations in this town.
Don't you worry about me.
Hey, slow down.
I wants to talk to you.
Give us 300 pretzels.
You see? A little persistence
and patience paid off.
That'll be $300.
Hey, I don't think so.
I got me 300 coupons.
(Marge grumbles)
I should have said,
"Limit: One per customer."
Should've, but didn't,
so hand them over.
Hey, kids, we're eating
dinner tonight.
Come on, Tiffany,
Heather, Cody, Dylan,
Dermot, Jordan, Taylor,
Brittany, Wesley, Rumer,
Scout, Cassidy, Zoe,
Chloe, Max, Hunter, Kendall
Caitlin, Noah, Sascha, Morgan,
Kyra, Ian, Lauren
Q-bert, Phil.
(groans)
"Hang in there, baby."
You said it, kitty.
"Copyright 1968"?
Hmm, determined or not,
that cat must be long dead.
That's kind of a downer.
They're good pretzels,
Mom,
but you got to think big.
Find a major public event
and set up shop there.
Here you go.
Free Pretzel Wagon pretzels
for everyone.
One bite
and you'll be hooked.
-Thank you.
-Gracias.
That means
"Thank you," Marge.
MAN (on P.A.): Ladies and gentlemen,
a winner has been chosen
for today's giveaway.
And the 1997
Pontiac Astrowagon
goes to the fan sitting
in seat number 0001:
-C. Montgomery Burns.
-(gasps)
-(scattered booing)
-Yay! Yay!
MAN 2: And the fans do not
like this one bit.
MAN: And here
come the pretzels.
No. No, don't do that.
You're supposed
to be tasting them.
MAN 2: Hall-of-famer Whitey Ford
now on the field
pleading with the crowd
for some kind of sanity.
MAN: Uh-oh, and a barrage
of pretzels now
knocking Whitey unconscious.
Wow, this is, uh...
This is a black day
for baseball.
Oh, cheer up, Mom.
You can't buy publicity
like that.
Thousands and thousands
of people saw your pretzels
injuring Whitey Ford.
You could call them
Whitey-Whackers.
I was wrong to have a dream--
Wrong as usual.
I mean, if you're nothing
special, why kid yourself?
Oh, Mom, no.
Listen to your mother,
kids.
Aim low.
Aim so low no one will
even care if you succeed.
Dinner's in the oven.
If you want some butter,
it's under my face.
Marge needs help, and God knows
I'm not the man to provide it,
but I know who can.
Ah, it looks likes
Mr. Pretzel-man
is doing pretty well
for himself.
I'm here to see
Mr. Ormand.
Of course.
Right this way.
(organ playing)
Oh, I guess I should speak
to the executor of his estate.
He's right over there.
They were in the same car.
You're my last hope.
I've never reached out
to you before,
but my wife
is in her hour of need.
Your help could make
all the difference in the world.
FAT TONY: Okay.
See, boss?
I told you that ad
in the church bulletin
would pay off.
(phone ringing)
Hello?
No.
Pretzel Wagon's no longer...
300 pretzels?
Wait. Wait.
Let me get this down.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
Meat Packer's Union Hall,
Batavia, New York.
I'll send them right out.
Homer.
Homie, wake up.
Wake up,
I'm back in business.
I had a feeling things
would work out for you, honey.
Hey, what are you doing?
This is a pretzel town,
pretty boy.
(jazz music plays)
Are you sure the children
will get enough nutrition
from these pretzels?
Yes, I am sure.
Sure as sure can be.
Oh, my God,
what happened to your fingers?
MAN WHISPERING:
Boating accident.
I believe it was
a "boking" accident.
I have to go now.
I don't understand
why they won't unload
our falafel fixings.
Ship's impounded,
ma'am.
Yeah. We found
a couple of barnacles
on the hull.
That and, uh,
the deck was, uh, wet.
That's crazy.
And what are those men
doing under my van?
MAN:
Let's get out of here!
Look, lady, if I was you,
I would just leap
into the air
as I'm preparing to do.
Here you go, Homer.
Thanks, Moe.
Ah, Homer, you know
your money's no good here.
Hey, wait a minute.
This is real money!
Yeah.
My wife is raking it in.
(bell rings)
(whistling)
(clears throat)
Greetings, Homer.
Hey, Fat Tony.
You still with the mafia?
Uh, yes, I am.
Thank you for asking.
Now, Homer,
as you no doubt recall,
you were done
a favor by our--
how shall I say--
mafia crime syndicate.
Oh, yeah.
Now the time has come
for you to do us a favor.
You mean the mob
only did me a favor
to get something
in return?
Oh, Fat Tony...
I will say good day
to you, sir.
Okay, I will go.
Hey, wait a minute.
Well, here I am,
11905 Dead Weasel Road.
I don't see any apartment
building.
I just...
-(tires squealing)
-(Marge screams)
Hey, what's going on?
Is there a button
or a release for these keys?
Oh. Oh, you have
to push in as you turn.
-Ah.
-Yeah, that's it.
-Who are you?
-We are your business partners,
and as such, we are entitled
to a percentage of your profits.
Something in the area
of 100%.
What are you talking about?
We suggest you have
a conversation
with your husband.
You have 24 hours
to give us our money.
And to show you
we're serious,
you have 12 hours.
-Huh?
-See you at 6 a.m.
Homer, did you
tell the mafia
they could eliminate
my competitors
with savage beatings
and attempted murder?
In those words?
Yes.
It just sickens me.
How could you do this
to someone you love?
How could I not?
I saw you pouring
your heart and soul
into this business
and getting nowhere.
I saw
you desperately trying
to cram one more
salty treat
into America's
already bloated snack hole.
So I did what I could.
I did what any
loving husband would do.
I reached out to some
violent mobsters.
Oh, Homer,
I know you were trying
to shield me from failure
but this is my business,
and the mafia's not getting
one cent of my money.
So what are
we going to do?
We're going to do what
we do every day.
We're going
to make pretzels.
There.
That's the last one.
(pretzel snaps)
(knocking on door)
(both gasp)
I had that dream again.
Oh, thank God,
it's only Grampa.
-(knocking)
-Now what?
-(both gasp)
-Sorry we're late.
Could we have
the money now?
The answer is no.
I'm afraid I must insist.
You see, my wife,
she has been most vocal
on the subject
of the pretzel monies.
"Where's the money?
"When are you going
to get the money?
Why aren't you getting
the money now?"
And so on.
So, please... The money.
You heard her.
She said no.
Legs, Louie, advance on them.
HELEN LOVEJOY:
There they are.
Well, well,
if it isn't Marge Simpson
and her gangland cronies.
Your goon squads certainly
gave you the edge
in the mobile
snack business.
But I'm afraid we've outdone
you once again.
Hiroshi, Yukio.
Perhaps you've heard
of the Yakuza,
the Poison Fists
of the Pacific Rim?
The Japanese mafia.
They'll kill you five times
before you hit the ground.
-All right.
-Go!
(grunting)
Hey!
Take that.
Take this.
Come here,
you little squirt.
Homie, maybe
we should go inside.
But, Marge,
that little guy
hasn't done
anything yet.
Look at him.
He's going to do something
and you know it's going
to be good.
(man kiais loudly)
-(blow lands)
-(body thuds)
-Aw...
-(blows landing)
You must hate me,
Marge.
Every time I try to help,
I just fail miserably.
Oh, I don't hate you
for failing.
I love you for trying.
-(yawning)
-What's going on outside?
Oh, it's just
a mob war.
Go back to sleep,
honey.
Forgiveness, please.
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.