♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell rings)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
Oh, my God.
The Mad Magazine
Special Edition!
They only put out 17
of these a year!
Boy, they're really
socking it
to that Spiro Agnew
guy again.
He must work there
or something.
Let's do the fold-in.
Okay.
"What higher power
do TV evangelists worship?"
I'll say God.
I'll say Jesus.
BOTH:
The all mighty dollar?
You fold it, you bought it.
Ooh! Snappy answers
to stupid questions.
I'm great at these.
Ask me if something
smells funny in here, boy.
Does something smell
funny in here?
I don't think so...
stupid!
(laughs)
Homey, you want pork chops?
No, I want roast beef,
you clod!
(laughs)
Look at this special insert--
"Iron-on Madness!"
(laughing)
"Ban the bath."
"Don't trust anyone over ten."
"Sock it to me!"
(worried groan)
Those magazines create
a dangerous amount of laughter.
"The all ighty
ollar?"
(laughs)
I get it.
Gee, business
stinks tonight.
Where's Barney, Lenny,
and Carl?
Ah, they never come
around anymore
now that they got
their mistresses.
Ah, might as well
close the dump.
I am going to drink
you under the table.
No, I am going to
drink you under the...
-Aw.
(yawning)
Well, you're closing.
It's getting late.
My kids are probably wondering
where their daddy is.
There's got to be
some other place we can go.
Think, Moe, think!
(voice cracking)
Sorry. It's league night.
I couldn't give a lane
to my own mother.
I have no son.
Man, you go through life,
you try to be nice to people,
you struggle
to resist the urge
to punch 'em in the face
and for what?
For some pimply little puke
to treat you like dirt
unless you're on a team!
Well, I'm better than dirt!
Well, most kinds of dirt.
Not that fancy
store-bought dirt.
That stuff's loaded
with nutrients.
I can't compete
with that stuff.
That I cannot bowl wreaks havoc
with my self-esteem as well.
But who am I
to complain?
I'm tired of being
a wannabe league bowler.
I wanna be a league bowler.
(bell dings)
Hey...
We can be a team.
Excuse me, but my team
is ready to bowl!
You're short one person.
Uh... that
long-haired freak's
bowled with us
for years.
Oh I don't care
if it takes me all night.
I'm going to get me
that lobster harmonica.
Come on, lobstie!
Oh!
Oh, okay.
Then I just need
your $500 registration fee.
$500?
No problem.
Would you take
an out-of-state
two-party bad check?
No, I will not pay you
$500 for sex!
Aw, come on, Marge!
You're getting something
in return
and I'm getting a bowling team.
It's win-win!
It's sick! And I don't have that
kind of money to spend on sex.
Maybe you could get
someone with money
to sponsor your team...
like Mr. Burns.
Burns never gives money
to anybody.
Just last week,
I asked him for $1,500.
For what?
Aw, I gotta get the
third degree from you too?!
Tonight's homework
assignment is...
Oh, man.
Is it hot in here!
I better take off my sweater!
"Down...
"with...
...homework?"
(class laughs)
Don't look at it, children.
The shirt makes
a good point.
I'm with the shirt.
Homework rots.
(chanting)
Down with homework!
(coughing)
As I was saying,
my yearly evaluation
couldn't have come
at a better time.
Well, Seymour, I must say,
for once I am impressed.
In fact, I am going
to give this school
a perfect 10.
I'll just write
the zero first.
Now a vertical line
to indicate the one...
STUDENTS:
Down with homework!
Skinner!
Why are there children
walking on my head?!
(gasps)
So... we meet again
"Mad Magazine."
How do you know
it's from Mad?
The year was 1968.
We were on recon
in a steaming Mekong delta.
An overheated private
removed his flak jacket
revealing a t-shirt
with an iron-on
sporting the Mad slogan,
"Up with mini-skirts."
Well, we all had a good laugh
even though I didn't
quite understand it.
But our momentary lapse
of concentration
allowed Charlie
to get the drop on us.
I spent the next three years
in a P.O.W. camp
forced to subsist
on a thin stew
made of fish, vegetables,
prawns, coconut milk,
and four kinds of rice.
I came close to madness
trying to find it here
in the states
but they just can't get
the spices right.
Uh, my punishment?
Hmm? Oh. I'm going to have
to think about that.
Meanwhile,
wear this home.
No!
I need some more ether.
I can still feel the movement
of the emery board.
We're fresh out, sir.
I'll get some more.
Leave the rag.
(sniffs)
Mmm!
Uh, excuse me. Mr. Burns?
Poppin' Fresh!
You glutinous
little doughboy!
Oh, there's something I've
wanted to do to you for years!
(giggles)
(giggling)
Ow!
Mr. Burns...
I, uh, was wondering
if you'd like to sponsor
my bowling team for $500.
Oh, why certainly,
Poppin' Fresh.
I owe my robust physique
to your tubes
of triple-bleached goo.
Whoo-hoo!
Hey, everybody!
If you want to ask Burns
for a favor, now's the time!
He's doped up or dying
or something!
Uh, excuse me.
I'd like
to request $17
for a push-broom
rebristling.
Why, it's that delightful
TV leprechaun!
I'm going to get
your Lucky Charms!
(drill grinding)
MOLEMAN:
Oh, no. My brains.
Hey, nice, quote
"uniforms", end quote.
This just in-- a new addition
to our "Worst-Dressed list":
Those guys!
Forget this.
I am far too fragile
to withstand an evening
of barbs like that.
Aw, come on.
If we quit now
we'll never know how badly
they're going to beat us.
Yeah, you're right.
That's the kind of thing
that would haunt you.
Si!
(laughing)
Buenas noches, señoritas.
What did he say?
Was that about me?
Okay, Otto. Pressure's on.
Don't choke, don't choke,
don't choke, don't...
choke!
Oh, man!
I knew I was going to choke.
Well, that's
a funny-looking strike.
Come on, guys, let's be the team
that supports each other.
(cheering) You can do it, Otto!
You can do it, Otto!
"Help each other out"
That'll be our motto.
You can do it, Otto!
Make this spare,
I give you free Gelato.
Then back to my place,
where I will get you blotto.
Domo aregatto,
Mr. Roboto.
You can do it, Otto!
You can do it...
Guys, I Made the spare. We won.
All right!
Way to go!
We did it!
Those beers are
five dollars apiece.
-Let me set the scene for you, Marge.
-All right.
It's a 7-10 split,
the hardest shot in bowling.
It was all up to me.
Oh!
So I got up all my
courage right away.
My lips started to move
and I came up with the chant
that won the match!
Who knocked down
the pins?
I don't know...
You know, some guy, uh...
Otto, I guess.
Good for him!
Yes, but Marge, you're not--
You're missing the point!
The individual
doesn't matter.
It was a team effort
and I was the one
who came up with
the whole "team" idea!
Me!
I can't believe Otto
picked up a 7-10 split.
He's phenomenal!
-But, but--
-Wow!
Several days ago,
a violent riot erupted
incited by an
inflammatory t-shirt slogan.
No, no, now, don't try to
remember what that slogan was.
To ensure that this frenzied
dance of destruction
is never repeated,
I have decided, starting Monday
all students will be required
to wear uniforms.
ALL:
Uniforms?!!
(Herb Alpert & Tijuana Brass'
"Spanish Flea" playing)
Say hello to our
little genius Martin
who looks even smarter
in this vest
and short pant combination
from Mr. Boy
of Main Street.
Or how about
little Lisa Simpson?
She'll have no reason
to play the blues
in this snappy ensemble
topped off with
a saucy French beret
that seems to
scream, "silence."
All right, pick your size:
"extra-small" or "extra-large."
We've got both.
No pushing now, I-- What?
Oh, I've just been informed
we've run out of "extra-large."
Go, Moe! Go, Moe!
Don't make Homer
shout out "D'oh!"
(cheering)
Woo-hoo!
-(pins clatter)
-(cheering)
All right, Snake,
make us proud.
One, two, three...
(rapidly) four, five, six, seven,
eight, nine, ten. Bye!
Uh... we forfeit.
(cheering)
There it is, boys:
the Championship Trophy.
We will never possess it.
The Holy Rollers have won it
five years in a row.
MOE: They think they're
so high and mighty
just 'cause they never got caught
driving without pants.
(ridiculing laughter)
God-boy couldn't get a strike!
(laughing)
It's me-- Ned.
(screaming)
Mom! My slingshot doesn't
fit in these pockets!
And these shorts leave
nothing to the imagination.
These uniforms suck.
Bart, where do you pick up
words like that?
Yeah, Moe, that team
sure did suck last night.
They just plain sucked!
I've seen teams suck before
but they were the suckiest
bunch of sucks
that ever sucked.
Homer! Watch your mouth!
Got to go. My damn wiener
kids are listening.
We are not wieners!
Then what are you
dressed like that for?
BOTH:
They made us.
"Oh, they made us."
That's loser talk.
You got to start acting
more like me and my team--
the future league champions
of the world.
Nothing's going to stop us now.
Stop everything.
I don't remember
writing a check for bowling.
Sir, that's a check
for your "boweling."
Oh, yes.
That's very important.
Yes, sir. Remember that
month you didn't do it?
Yes. That was unpleasant
for all concerned.
Anyway, back to the checks...
Stop everything!
I don't remember
writing a check for bowling!
Hmm... the memo says
"To my pal, Poppin' Fresh."
Oh, yes... that greedy,
grasping glob of chemicals.
Probably one of your ether-induced
hallucinations, sir.
I'll check
the employee files
to see who
could pull off
such an impersonation.
Hmm, it was either
Pops Freshenmeyer...
or Homer Simpson.
Simpson, eh?
Let's shut down this
bowling scam right now.
Come on, Homer.
Pretend this is baseball
and hit us a Homer!
-Way to go!
-Yeah! Yeah!
-Way to roll it.
-Yes, sir! Oh, yes.
By the way, rhyming "Homer"
with "Homer"--
(making Italian kissing sound)
Look at them, Smithers,
enjoying their embezzlement.
I have a much uglier word
for it, sir:
"misappropriation."
Simpson!
(gasps, man screams)
Listen here...
I want to join
your team.
You want to
join my what?
You wanna "what"
his team?
I've had one of
my unpredictable
changes of heart.
Seeing these
fine young athletes
reveling in the humiliation
of a vanquished foe...
I haven't felt this energized
since my last...
boweling.
Oh, man, he'll blow
our winning streak.
Yeah... call this an unfair
generalization if you must
but old people are
no good at everything.
Look, guys, it's not
that simple-- he's my boss.
I'll tell you what.
I'll give him a shot
and if he stinks
it'll be easier to tell him no.
(grunting and groaning)
(panting)
(muttering)
Welcome aboard.
(softly)
It wasn't any easier.
Ah, these uniforms
are a godsend.
Horseplay
is down 40%.
Youthful exuberance
has been cut in half,
and high spirits
are at an all-time low.
They've even begun
blinking in unison.
I love that sound.
Now, children
while you're having quiet time
I'm going to make sure my desk
is exactly parallel
to the rear wall.
Oh, there's something
I used to do
in this situation.
But... can't... remember.
Ha ho?
Whoa, I can't believe
I got booted off the team
for Mr. Businessman.
(snorts)
I bet I'll get
a little respect
once I get that
Harvard diploma.
Look at that!
All the way to the end
with only one push.
Ah, that's the third game
in a row he cost us, Homer.
Mama mia!
Hoot mon!
Yee haw!
Arr, me maties.
Arr!
Whoo! They begged me
to join their team.
Begged me.
Well, we certainly
got walloped tonight
eh, fellas?
(laughs)
Ow!
Well... ow!
Uh, Mr. Burns, next week
is the big
championship game...
Ah, yes, that silly
championship...
The only "ship" worth a damn
is friendship.
Look, here comes
the friend ship
sailing your way.
Ooh, here.
Let me get that,
friend.
Oops, lost a nail.
Well, that's leprosy
for you.
You're "it."
Now you are the one
who is "it."
Understood.
Well, I've got to hand it
to you, Seymour.
These drab student coverings
have created the perfect
distraction-free environment
thus preparing the children
for permanent positions
in tomorrow's mills
and processing facilities.
Best of all, with less than
a minute to go before I leave
absolutely nothing
has gone wrong.
(thunder rumbling)
Well, it is
starting to rain
but I can hardly be blamed
for that, can I?
(both laughing)
Yes, very good.
Wow, look at all
the colors, man!
Red, green,
yellow, orange.
I remember all of these.
I'm freakin' out!
Hey, something's
coming back to me.
Down with homework.
And down with uniforms.
(cheering)
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
Skinner!
Why aren't these
uniforms colorfast?
I don't understand it.
I got them at the same place
I buy mother's dresses.
Good Lord, Mother's in the park.
Now this, I gotta see.
Aw, Marge, we were so close
to winning the championship.
Now, thanks to Burns,
it's never going to happen.
And I spent so much time
building that trophy case.
Homer, maybe Mr. Burns
will bowl a great game
and you will win
your championship.
So you're saying
we're definitely going to win?
Whoo-hoo!
I won't need this
any more!
(toilet flushing repeatedly)
Marge, someone
broke the toilet.
Don't worry
about nothing, Homer.
I have a feeling
that Mr. Burns
is going to have
a little accident
that might keep him
from bowling
with us tonight.
Heh, heh, heh.
Smithers, I'm afraid
I won't be able
to play tonight.
My old gimpy knee
has gone akimbo again.
Take that!
Ooh... Smithers.
That precision assault
popped it back into place.
Thank you, masked stranger.
D'oh, he's gonna
ruin everything.
All right, that's it, Homer.
Either Burns goes or Moe goes.
Yes, I am afraid that I am
going to have to make
a similar threat
with my name
in place of Moe's name.
So, who's ready
to kick
some Christian
keister?
Oh, uh, Mr. Burns,
as team captain
it's my duty
to inform you that...
Oh, I almost forgot.
I brought you all
a little something.
Aw, would you look at that?
"The Pin Pals."
(gasps)
At last, I finally
have a garment
fine enough to be married in.
I've always been wealthy
but this is the first time
I ever felt rich.
Aww!
Now Homer, you were about
to say something to me?
You're off
the team.
What?
(nervous laughter)
Homer!
He's just ribbing you, Monty.
-Yes!
-Oh-oh-oh, you guys.
(grunt)
Hey-hey-hey!
Hallelujah!
-Hey!
-Hallelujah!
-Oh!
Nice one, Homer.
Thanks.
Okay, the Holy Rollers are ahead
by one pin.
And we only have
one bowler left: Mr. Burns.
(grunts)
Next time, a few steps more
toward center, don't you think?
Goodbye,
trophy.
Whoa! Whatever I got
a hold of, it's big.
(grunting)
Yes!
Excellent!
(plays harmonica note)
Whoo-hoo! We won! We won!
You mean I won.
But we were
a team, sir.
Oh, I'm afraid I've had one
of my trademark
changes of heart.
You see teamwork
will only take you so far
then the truly evolved person
makes that extra grab
for personal glory. Now...
I must discard
my teammates
much like the boxer
must shed roll
after roll
of sweaty, useless,
disgusting flab
before he can win
the title. Ta!
I guess some people
never change.
Or they quickly change
and then quickly change back.
You know what?
We don't need him
or his trophy.
We got each other,
huh?
Yeah, that's right, Moe.
♪ Go, Homer, you're our man ♪
♪ If you can't do it,
no one can! ♪
(burglar alarm blaring)
(screams)
Well, I guess
no one can.
Run, before they're
through feeding!
-(snarling)
-(shouting)
♪♪
Shh.
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.