♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
Ai! Que agonia!
(laughing)
Oh, he wants
that corn so much.
Ai! Dios no me ama.
So good.
Huh? I want to see what's
on the other broadcasts.
Where's the oscillator
on this thing?
-No, Grampa, don't!
-Dad, sit down!
-Gosh darn it!
What does this do?
I'll make my adjustments
here and...
(glass shattering)
(tires screeching)
(together)
Yay! We're getting a new TV!
Let's go to
The Sharper Image.
They've got a TV shaped
like a '50s diner.
No, let's go
to The Nature Company.
They've got a TV
assembled by Hopi Indians.
We can't afford to shop at
any store that has a philosophy.
We just need a TV.
We're going to go
to the outlet mall in Ogdenville.
(moaning)
(gasps) Look at these
low, low prices
on famous brand-name
electronics.
Don't be a sap, Dad.
These are just crappy knock-offs.
(scoffs) I know a genuine
Panaphonics when I see it.
And look, there's
Magnetbox and Sorny.
Listen, I'm not going
to lie to you.
Those are all
superior machines,
but if you like
to watch your TV--
and I mean,
really watch it--
you want the Carnivale.
It features
two-pronged wall plug,
pre-molded
hand-grip well,
durable outer casing
to prevent fall-apart...
Sold. You wrap it up,
I'll start bringing in the pennies.
Honey, I don't think
these clothes are us.
Who are they?
Hey, Brandine
you can wear this shirt to work.
Oh, Cletus, you know I got to wear
the shirt what Dairy Queen give me.
Hey, Mom, there's
something in here.
Ooh.
Oh, it's beautiful.
Can it be a real Chanel?
(gasps)
It is!
90 dollars?
(groans)
But it's marked
down from 2,800.
Oh, you look
so sophisticated.
Just like Mary Hart.
It fits like
a dream too.
But we can't
afford $90
even if it is
a bargain.
It wouldn't be right to
buy something just for me.
If it were a suit we could
all wear, maybe, then...
Come on Mom, you never treat
yourself to anything.
Oh, sure, I do.
I treated myself to a Sanka
not three days ago.
But this is a real find.
Just buy it.
You don't have to
rationalize everything.
(groans)
All right, I will buy it.
It will be good
for the economy.
(easy listening music plays)
(whistles)
You look great.
Really?
You like it?
Oh, I'd love to wear this
someplace special.
Spurlock's Cafeteria,
it is.
Mmm. What about
the symphony or the theater?
Oh, gah, geez.
What's the point
of going out?
We're just going to
wind up back here, anyway.
(groans)
(singing in Italian)
(vacuum starts)
Oh, Mrs. Simpson, you are
looking very prosperous today.
Might I interest you
in some of our impulse items
here by the cash register?
Perhaps a crazy motorized
wiggle pen?
(laughing)
Look at... the craziness.
Attendant, I'd like some gas.
Yes, I'm sorry,
I do not speak English okay.
But you were
just talking to...
Yes, hot dog, hot dog,
yes, sir, no sir, maybe, okay.
Well, I can't pump it myself.
I'm calling triple "A."
I used to be a little
overwhelmed too
but it's not that hard.
I can show you.
Marge? Is that you?
Marge Bouvier,
from high school?
Um... yeah.
Hi. Hi, Evelyn.
How about that.
Marge,
you look wonderful.
And to think I heard
you married Homer Simpson.
I did marry Homer.
Come, you must
show me the pumps.
90% of the time,
if the gas isn't pumping,
this is your problem.
Automotive skills
and fashion sense.
Well, you've come a long way
from the girl I knew
nothing about in high school.
We ran with different crowds.
You had your
debutante balls
and skinny-dipping,
and I had my...
home shoe repair course.
Oh, Marge, you haven't
changed a bit
as far as I know.
Say, why don't you drop by
the country club tomorrow?
Oh, and bring the family.
(antique horn honking)
You there, fill it up
with petroleum distillate
and re-vulcanize my tires,
post haste.
Bart, comb your hair.
Homer, I don't think you should
wear a short-sleeved shirt
with a tie.
Oh, but Sipowicz does it.
If Detective Sipowicz
jumped off a cliff,
would you do that too?
Aw, I wish I was
Sipowicz.
Do I have to go?
That country club is a hotbed
of exclusionist snobs
and status-seeking
social-climbers.
I've told you, I don't like
you using the word "hotbed."
Please, Lisa, we so rarely
get to do things like this.
And everybody, everybody please,
be on your best behavior.
Bart, no grifting.
Ah, raspberries.
Name, please?
Simpson family.
We're not poor.
Well, we're not.
Go on in.
They're expecting you at the clubhouse.
(all gasping)
Wow. Living large.
Oh, my.
I've always dreamed
of coming here.
Everybody, keep smiling
and I know we're going
to fit right in.
(screams)
EVELYN:
Oh, Marge. You made it.
And you wore
that lovely suit.
Kar-rin, Gill-ian, Elyza-beth
Pa-tree-sia,
Rowber-tah, Seuss-in
Meet Marge.
-Hello.
-How you doing?
Pleased to
meet you.
You look like such a
happy bunch... of people.
That's the trouble
with first impressions.
You only get to make one.
(ladies giggling)
Oh.
That reminds me of
a funny apron I saw.
You know Marge, your family
doesn't have to stand
in the alcove.
They're free
to enjoy the club.
(sighing)
Ugh, come on kids,
let's go sit in the car
till your Mom's done
fitting in.
Elyza-beth is right.
Why shout yourself hoarse
at incompetent sales clerks
when you can get nearly
everything mail order?
Um hum, I won't eat
anything
unless it's
shipped overnight
from Vermont or
Washington state.
We order our steaks
through the "New Yorker."
I have a sneaking suspicion that
L.L. Bean and Eddie Bauer
are selling me the same honey.
(ladies tittering)
I get food
through the mail,
but in a different way.
Every month,
"Good Housekeeping"
arrives in my mailbox,
bursting with recipes.
Sometimes, the most
satisfying meal
is the one you
cook yourself.
Hmm.
That's very true, Marge.
One night, Wif and I
came home late,
and we decided not
to wake Iris
and instead,
we microwaved our own soup.
(women chattering)
Of course,
it was a horrible mess,
but Iris didn't mind
cleaning it up.
(ladies tittering)
Why can't my Thurston
be more like Wif?
That Iris is a gem.
MARGE: Didn't everybody have
a wonderful time?
I thought it was so opulent
like the Playboy mansion,
but nonsexual.
That place is weird.
A man in the bathroom
kept handing me towels
till I paid him to stop.
Should have held out
longer, boy.
The rich are different
from you and me.
Yes, they're better.
Socially better,
and if we fit in
we can be better too.
So today, while the rest of you
were out being different,
I did a very good job of
fitting in--
so good that Evelyn
gave us a guest pass.
They might even ask us to join.
Boy, Marge!
You must have really done
a number on those rich suckers.
Don't thank me.
Thank my beautiful
new suit.
Oh, Fritz, you idiot.
I didn't order
a bologna sandwich.
I ordered an abalone sandwich.
I don't know
what Mom's thinking.
This whole country club scene
is so decadent.
All these... spoiled... brats...
and... their... smug
complacent parents.
It just reinforces
the unspoken class... system...
of horses... sitting...
on... their... high... horses.
I'm sorry. I got to go!
Oh. We've got a winning hand.
We can take
the rest of the tricks.
Oh, you better be careful.
The purpose of this game
is to make friends.
You don't make friends
by winning.
Still, there's nothing
more popular
than a gracious winner.
Don't ask me.
I'm just hair.
Your head stopped
18 inches ago.
Hmm...
Queen of hearts.
I believe all the rest
are ours.
Oh, well played.
We could have stopped them
if you had changed
to a different suit.
I thought, perhaps,
changing suits
had gone out of fashion.
Eh, Marge?
(women tittering)
(Marge grumbles)
D'oh!
(moaning)
Mmm.
(chuckling)
You know, Homer,
the traditional way
to cheat in golf
is to lower your score.
That's one way.
I'm P.G.A. Tour
Pro Tom Kite.
How about I give you a
few pointers on your game?
Now, you don't want
to overthink.
Not an issue.
Keep your head down.
Huh?
Pretend there's
no one else here.
(belches)
And just go at your own pace.
Wow, very impressive.
You're a natural,
Mr. Simpson.
Really?
Uh-huh. All you need is
your own set of clubs
and stay the hell
out of my locker.
You can keep the shoes.
Marge, did you know that
Kennedy and Lincoln
had the same handicap?
Homer, please,
I have to alter this suit
so it looks different
for tomorrow.
(yawning)
Just slap some
bumper stickers on it
and come to bed,
will you, Marge?
(snoring)
Love your outfit, Marge.
The vest says,
"let's have lunch"
but the culottes say,
"you're paying."
Why, thank you, Rowber-ta.
LISA:
Mom, look!
I found something
more fun than complaining.
Marge, your family
is fitting in
perfectly here.
If all goes well
at Saturday's ball,
I'd love to sponsor
you for membership.
Oh, that would be
a dream come true.
I'll be there
with bells on.
Bells?
Where exactly
will you be attaching them
to that mangled Chanel suit?
(ladies laughing)
Oh, don't worry, Marge.
Her idea of wit
is nothing more
than an incisive observation
humorously phrased
and delivered
with impeccable timing.
I'm sure you'll be
a smash at the ball,
and I just know you'll have
a lovely new outfit.
(repeated toilet splashes)
Hey, that's some mighty fine
chipping, Homer.
Yeah, can you bank it into
the handicapped stall?
Seat-- down.
(air dryer blowing)
(ball splashes)
Hmm. Who is that lavatory
linksman, Smithers?
Homer Simpson, sir--
One of the fork and spoon
operators from Sector 7G.
Well, he's certainly got
a loose waggle.
Perhaps I've finally
found a golfer
worthy of a match
with Monty Burns, eh?
Oh, his waggle is no match
for yours, sir.
I've never seen
you lose a game
except for that one in '74,
when you let Richard Nixon win.
That was very kind of you, sir.
Oh, he just looked
so forlorn, Smithers
with his, "Oh, I can't
go to prison, Monty.
They'll eat me alive."
Say, I wonder if this
Homer Nixon
is any relation.
Unlikely, sir. They...
They spell and pronounce
their name differently.
Bah. Schedule a game
and I'll ask him myself.
Oh, this game could mean
big things for me, Marge.
If I beat Mr. Burns..
I mean really wallop him bad,
I'm sure to get that big raise
I've been gunning for.
Alright, alright, but if you
win, don't make a scene
and dance around
with your "whoo-hoos," please.
We can't afford
a single slip-up.
They're judging us.
Mwah!
Mom, did you like horses
when you were my age? 'Cause I--
I don't know.
Lisa, tonight is
very important.
Mommy has to alter her suit
so it looks a totally new one.
Mom, do you want to know the 15 reasons
I like horses better than cars?
One, a horse never has to--
I really need to concentrate
on this, Lisa.
Would you mind just..?
You know how a horse
goes like this?
Mom! Like this!
I've already altered
this so many times,
-it's not even possible--
-Whinny! Mom! Mom! Mom!
Mom! Mom! Mom!
Lisa, please!
Hmm.
(gasps)
No.
No, no, no, no!
(cloth rips)
(groaning)
At times like this, I guess
all you can do is laugh.
I need a formal dress
for tonight.
You've come
to the right place.
We've got classy duds
up the ying-yang.
I call this one
"fantasy in maroon."
It's got some
cigarette burns
but we can patch them
up with Nu-Vinyl.
It's a bit peppery for me.
Why don't we put this
in the "maybe" pile?
This was originally
a Halloween costume,
but it found its way
into my regular rotation.
Uh-huh.
Good morning,
Mr. Burns.
Beautiful day to be
outside, isn't it?
Rant on, Simpson,
but your
vainglorious boasting
will only add savor
to my inevitable triumph.
Yes.
Woo-hoo!
D'oh!
Yes. You're
in deep "D'oh" now.
(sandpaper scraping)
Perfect as always, sir.
Right on the green.
Oh, quit cogitating,
Steinmetz,
and use
an open-faced club.
-The sand wedge.
-Mmm.
Open-faced club sand wedge.
You're four strokes
behind, Simpson.
(chuckles)
Oh, a cunning
stratagem, sir.
It's curving right
toward the green,
and it's... there.
He got to the green
in one shot?
How can that old man
hit so...
far?
Now, keep
your head down.
Ignore all distractions.
(yells)
Hmm. Hmm.
Hmm? Miss?
Miss? Do you have
a Chanel suit
or any other
high-quality clothes?
No, ma'am, but we do have
a shipment of slightly burnt
Sears activewear
coming in this afternoon.
Oh, I give up.
What time and
how burnt?
Cripes man, can't you ever
get to the green
in less than two shots?
SMITHERS: Aagh!
(groans)
Smithers, what
are you doing up here?
What are you doing
with this ball?
And all those
other balls?
Ahh, there are
no other balls.
Just these, uh,
reptile eggs.
Ooh, step away.
They're endangered.
These aren't reptile eggs.
You've been cheating.
No matter where
Mr. Burns hit the ball,
you put a fresh one
on the green.
(gasps)
Cheating? For me?
Good Lord, Smithers,
that's patently unnecessary.
I'm one of the world's
finest golfers.
In all the years
you've caddied for me,
I've never lost a...
-Oh.
-So...
♪ You're not
the best golfer here ♪
♪ Wait till I tell
everyone about this ♪
♪ You stink ♪
Homer, Mr. Burns holds
a lot of sway at this club.
If you would keep quiet
about the alleged
decades of cheating,
I'm sure he'd support
your application
for membership tonight.
Bull honkey!
I don't care
about joining
this stupid club.
But does your wife?
Ohh.
(yells)
I knew my kind
wasn't welcome here.
(sighs loudly)
-Ooh.
ALL:
Ahh.
Mom, you are looking fabulous.
Yeah. You look great.
You can do anything
with that sewing machine.
No, I can't.
Come on, let's go.
You mean it's a new dress?
Where did you get it?
The outlet store.
Wow. Two finds in one store.
What are the odds?
-Call it fate, let's go!
-How much did it cost?
-A dollar. Let's go.
-With tax or without?
Without. Let me go.
So with tax,
how much was it?
Why do you always
have to question
everything I do?
You look nice, is all.
MARGE:
Homer, what are you doing?
I'm driving up
to the main building.
They've got
valet parking tonight.
We can't drive this up there.
They'll see the dent.
They'll see the coat hanger antenna.
Stop the car. We're walking.
But Marge, valets.
For once, maybe someone
will call me "sir"
without adding,
"you're making a scene."
I'm going to regale everyone
with my anecdote.
You know, the one I tried
to say on the radio?
Who's going to bleep me
this time?
I'm going to pose
as an Italian count
and get some old lady
to leave me all her money.
I'm going to ask people
if they know
their servants' last names
or, in the case of butlers,
their first.
No! No! No!
Not tonight!
No vulgarity.
No mischief.
No politics.
Just be good.
I'm sorry, Mom.
I'll behave.
I won't say anything controversial.
I just won't say
anything, okay, honey?
You kids
should thank your mother.
Now that she's
a better person,
we can see how
awful we really are.
Come here, Maggie.
Oh, Homie,
I like your
in-your-face humanity.
I like the way
Lisa speaks her mind.
I like Bart's...
I like Bart.
And I like my old green dress.
I didn't have to spend our
savings on this stupid gown.
Our savings?
Don't worry.
I saved the receipt.
We'll have
a $3,300 credit at Chanel.
They have beer
and gum, right?
Come on, let's go.
I wouldn't want
to join any club
that would have
this me as a member.
It's okay.
Those snobs never would have
made us members, anyway.
Well, I wonder
where Marge could be.
She's missing
her own initiation.
I hope she didn't take
my attempt to destroy her
too seriously.
Where's Homer?
Oh, and to think
I spent all afternoon
baking him this cake.
Mmm. Grr...
I pickled the figs myself.
Hey, did you guys
just come from the prom?
Sort of.
But, you know, we realized
we're more comfortable
in a place like this.
Man, you're crazy.
This place is a dump.
Oh man, I'd be anywhere
except this place, that's for sure.
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.