♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
-(vocalizes)
-Quit it, Bart.
Quit it. Quit it.
Quit it! Mom!
Bart's making faces.
Stop that, Bart.
Homer, speak to him.
Blah. Blee. Bleh.
(chuckles) Stupid animals.
Ah, the daily newspaper.
Ooh, the Springfield men's shelter
is giving away 60 soiled mattresses.
Why do you read that "free" column, Homer?
They never have anything good.
(gasps)
Oh, my God!
-What is it?
-"Tramampoline." "Trambapoline."
He said what now?
Please, don't bring home
any more old crutches.
-(car door closes)
-(tires screech)
Oh, no you don't.
That trampoline is mine.
-(panting)
-(bicycle horn)
-(spits) Huh?
-(laughs)
-(bicycle horn)
-(laughing) Yea.
-Hey. That seltzer ain't free.
-(gasps) Krusty!
-That's me.
(goofy laugh)
You here for the trampoline?
Yeah. What's the deal?
Well, I used to do
a lot of tumbling in my act,
but I'm phasing it out
for more dirty limericks.
-There once was a man named Enis--
-I can just haul it away, free?
Yep. It's all yours.
(chortling)
(door slams)
You're a good dog, aren't you, boy?
Aren't ya?
Hi, son.
-Hmm?
-Hi, son.
Wow!
(panting)
I can't believe it.
Whoa. Whoo-hoo!
Dad, this one gesture almost makes up
for years of shaky fathering.
(all whooping)
-HOMER: Hey, look at me.
-BART: Whoa-ho.
-HOMER: Bart, look.
-BART: I will never get tired of this.
LISA: I'm gonna have
my wedding here.
Whoa! Whoa!
I don't know
if this is a good idea.
HOMER: Marge,
it's the perfect exercise.
It'll double the value
of our house,
and it was free-- free!
-Are you sure it's safe?
-Absolutely.
And this is just the beginning.
I've got some big plans.
-♪♪ (calliope)
-(delighted squeals)
-It smells funny in there.
-No, it doesn't.
Whoo.
(laughing)
Whoa.
Yeah-- (grunts)
-(groans)
-Otto, are you okay?
-Yeah. Just pop my shoulder back in.
-(cracks)
Ooh. Thanks, buddy.
Hey, I lost my turn.
Oh! My arm.
Whee! Ow!
I bit my tongue.
Each leap brings us
closer to God.
-Catch me, Lord. Catch me. Wh--
-Ow!
-What have we done to make God angry?
-You did it.
Stop jumping on me.
I'm hurt.
Kids, kids. Once you get hurt,
move aside and let other people jump.
-Homer, this is terrible.
-Okay. Okay. I'll take care of it.
-Hmm?
-(moaning)
(all moaning)
I told you
this was a bad idea.
All right, all right!
I'll get rid of the trampoline.
Hey, Krusty.
I'm bringing back the--
You just keep
right on driving.
(grunts)
There we go.
That's the last I'll see
of Mr. Trampoline.
Yep, it's finally gone.
D'oh!
(grunting)
If this were a cartoon,
the cliff would break off now.
(animal howling)
I'm thirsty.
-(screams)
-(body thuds)
-Checkmate, Mr. Trampoline.
-(whirring)
(yelling)
Oh!
All right. All right.
You win for now,
but someday you'll rust!
Rust, I tell ya!
(hysterical laughter)
Dad. Dad?
You really wanna get rid
of this trampoline?
Uh-huh.
Observe. A bike lock.
(chain rattles,
lock clicks)
Now just turn around
and count to three.
One, two, three.
Uh, better make it five.
-(chain rattles)
-All right. I got me a bed.
DOLPH: Shh! Quiet.
You'll wake up Old Man Simpson.
JIMBO:
Hey, no more trampoline.
DOLPH:
Let's jump on the car instead.
-(metal thudding)
-(boys grunting)
Okay, the trampoline
was a bad idea.
But you know what?
At least I'm out there trying new things.
If it were up to you, all we'd ever do
is work and go to church.
That's not true.
Name one thing you've done in
the past month that was fun.
I can name 10 things.
Um...
-I made Sloppy Joes.
-(scoffs) That's not fun.
Kids, tell me the truth. Am I no fun?
Do I just nag all the time?
-Um.
-Well.
-Uh--
You should've called.
I was very worried.
We're on a tight budget here.
Bart, watch your language.
You are not going to perform
that operation yourself.
(groans)
-See, Marge?
-I didn't realize people saw me that way.
-Are you mad?
-No, I'm fine.
I'm going
to my sisters' now.
-(door slams)
-(car tires squealing)
NED: Careful there, Marge.
You almost nicked me.
Well, your blood pressure
is off the chart.
And I don't like
this urine sample one bit.
You're headed for a nervous breakdown.
You need Brad Goodman.
His infomercial plays
round the clock on Channel 77.
-(applause)
-Thank you, Martha Quinn.
There you have it.
Unrehearsed testimonies
from important celebrities.
She's one of my favorites.
I loved her in the thing I saw her in.
You know, my course can help you
with every personality disorder...
in the "feel bad" rainbow.
Let's look at the rainbow.
What's in there?
Geriatric profanity disorder,
or G.P.D.
And chronic nagging, nagging,
nagging, nagging, nagg--
-Sorry. It does that sometimes.
-Nagging. Nagging.
Mm-mm-mm. What up, Marge?
I'm watching a videotape
that could change our lives.
♪♪
Oh, hi. I'm Troy McClure.
You might remember me from
such self-help videos as...
"Smoke Yourself Thin"
and "Get Confident, Stupid."
Well, now I'm here to tell you about
the only real path to mental health.
That's right. It's the Brad Goodman...
something or other.
-Marge, can I go outside and play?
-Shh.
A few weeks ago, I was a washed-up
actor with a drinking problem.
Then Brad Goodman came along and gave me
this job and a can of fortified wine.
(loud gulp)
Ahh! Sweet liquor eases the pain.
And now I'd like to introduce
the man who will put the "you"...
in "impr-you-vement."
-Brad Goodman.
-Thank you so much, Troy.
And, by the way,
I'm not happy you're still drinking.
But, at least you're down
to one from more than 50.
(applause)
Folks, I'm often asked
about my qualifications.
Well, I may not have a lot of
"credentials" or "training,"
but I'll tell you one thing,
I'm a Ph.D.... in pain.
Now, let me show you
how you can change your life.
Troy, this circle is you.
My God, it's like you've
known me all my life.
(applause)
Doctor, you've solved all my problems.
(gulps)
That video
really opened my eyes.
I can see that I'm just
a passive-aggressive coculprit.
By nagging you when
you do foolish things,
I just enable
your life-script.
And that sends me into
a shame spiral.
Exactly. So from now on, I'm going to
quit nagging and have more fun.
Homer, did you eat
my whole pan of brownies?
Uh-oh. You're in for it
now, Dad.
Marge, I'm feeling
a lot of shame right now.
I'm hearing that
you feel a lot of shame.
And I feel that
you hear my shame.
I'm feeling annoyance
and frustration, but also tolerance.
-I feel validated by that.
-Good. I'm glad we had this talk.
Me too.
(whistles)
-Hmm?
Wow! For free.
Surplus drums of mayonnaise
from Operation Desert Storm.
(gasps) Brad Goodman
is coming to town!
Oh, Marge, you and I are fine now.
Who needs Brad Goodman?
-(clattering)
-(whooping) Yee-haw! Yahoo!
Well, here we are
at the Brad Goodman lecture.
-We know, Dad.
-I just thought I'd remind everybody.
After all, we did agree
to attend a self-help seminar.
What an odd thing to say.
-(applause)
-Thank you.
Okay, folks.
Let me hear what's troubling you.
Don't be shy. Yell it out. Everybody. Go.
-I, uh, can't commit to a relationship.
-I'm too nice.
-I have problems with--
-I'm always interrupting people.
Okay. Okay. Right now, I want each of you
to try something interesting.
There's no trick to it.
It's just a simple trick.
Now, close your eyes for a moment and
really listen to that inner voice inside.
Your inner child.
(quietly)
Listen. What's he saying?
Stay the course, Big Ned.
You're doing super.
-Food goes in here.
-It sure does.
(Italian accent)
Hey, Moe. What'sa matter?
-You no talka with your accent no more.
-Mamma mia.
Principal Skinner,
let's try some rage work.
I want you to pretend this dummy
right here is your mother.
Okay, I'll try.
(chuckles)
Tell this dummy mother
exactly how you feel right now.
I'm annoyed with you, Mother.
Not just annoyed, angry.
I'm a grown man now,
and I can run my own life!
(grunting)
(whispering) Shh-shh. Calm down.
Calm down. Moving. You can sit down now.
We're still going antiquing
on Saturday, right, Mother?
You see, folks?
We're all trying to please someone else.
And as soon as you're not
a human being,
you're a human doing.
-Then what comes next?
-A human going!
-(laughter)
-Bart, be quiet.
Son, that's wonderful.
Come here. Come up here.
What made you
yell out that remark?
I don't know.
You just wanted
to express yourself, yes?
-I do what I feel like.
-That's marvelous.
I couldn't have
put it better myself.
"I do what I feel like."
People, this young man here is
the inner child I've been talking about.
What?
Son, you've never read
any of my books, have you?
-(snorts) Earth to boring guy.
-(laughter)
(laughs) I get that means no, huh?
I'm not so old-fashioned.
Your parents have done a fantastic job.
Mama? Papa? Could you come up here?
-(applause)
-MAN: Yeah!
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
This is really remarkable. Here we have
a man with an obvious eating disorder,
and a woman with a bizarre hairstyle--
I'm sure worn only for shock value.
-(groans)
-And yet,
they've managed to raise
an emotionally healthy son.
-That's fantastic.
-Oh, thank you.
We can all learn a lot
from this young man here.
-This-this--
-Rudiger.
Rudiger. And if we can all
be more like little Rudiger--
-His name is Bart.
-His name isn't important.
What's important here is that this lad
has fully developed ego integrity...
with well-defined boundaries.
(loud snoring)
-(laughter)
-(chuckles) Isn't he--
People, I am excited.
I can sense a change
in the air tonight.
You are all going to
start living. Really living.
(all)
Yea! Living! Living!
-Be like the boy.
-Be like boy! Be like boy!
-Just the ladies.
-Now, the seniors in the back.
-We like Roy! We like Roy!
(chattering)
This is madness. He's just peddling
a bunch of easy answers.
And how.
(laughs)
A new mood is in
the air in Springfield,
as refreshing as
a pre-moistened towelette.
Folks are finally accepting
their feelings
and really communicating
with no holding back.
And this reporter thinks
it's about (beep) time.
Of course, all these
good vibes can be traced
to one feisty little scamp...
who taught us that
if it feels good, do it.
(gurgling)
Lis, today I am a god.
Is that why you're sitting on
an ice cream sandwich?
Ew!
(groans)
Now, instead of
my boring old sermon,
I'm going to take a page
from the book of Bart,
and do something
I've always wanted to do.
Take five, Mrs. Feesh.
♪♪ (ragtime)
-♪♪ (discordant)
-Wait. Wait. I can do this.
-♪♪ (resumes)
-Wait. Wait. Hold on.
(groans)
The wireless was an invention
by Guglielmo Marconi.
Who can tell me
what his first message was?
-Uh--
-I want-a change-a my name-a.
-(laughing)
-Ah, good one, Milhouse.
Anyone else?
The first message by wireless.
-It was--
-Our 10th caller
will receive
tickets to Supertramp.
(laughing)
Oh, jeez.
Everybody's a comedian.
I'm blue. Time for some of my
patented spitting off the overpass.
-Aw, man!
-(all spitting)
(cars honking, crashing)
(groans)
Lis, everyone in town is acting like me.
So why does it suck?
It's simple, Bart.
You've defined yourself as a rebel.
In the absence of a repressive milieu,
your societal niche has been co-opted.
I see.
Ever since that self-help guy
came to town,
you've lost your identity.
You've fallen through
the cracks of our quick-fix,
one-hour photo,
instant-oatmeal society.
-What's the answer?
-Well, this is your chance
to develop a new
and better identity.
May I suggest
good-natured doormat?
Sounds good, sis.
Just tell me what to do.
Springfield will have
its first annual
"Do What You Feel" festival
this Saturday...
whenever you feel like
showing up.
It'll be a welcome change from our
annual "Do As We Say" festival,
started by German settlers
in 1946.
-(ropes creaking)
-If elected mayor...
my first act will be to kill the whole
lot of ya and burn your town to cinders.
-(whispering) Mike's on.
-I know it's on.
Park anywhere. I'm not gonna
lay any rule trip on you today.
♪♪ (calypso)
♪♪ (humming)
I feel like such a free spirit,
and I'm really enjoying
this so-called "iced cream."
Sir, in the spirit of
the festival and everything,
I'd just like to say that--
(clears throat)
-I... love you.
-Hmm?
In those colors!
(nervous chuckle)
Oh, who am I kidding?
The boathouse was the time.
-MAN: My God. They're naked.
-Double your pleasure, Springfield.
I'm sweating.
Let's ride through the car wash.
ALL: Ew.
Arr! This picture will serve me well
on those lonely nights at sea.
This is great. I can
finally look like I want...
and not get hassled
by the man.
APU:
Cowabunga!
Skateboards?
You copycat wannabes.
-Ow!
-Eat my shorts, young man.
Good afternoon and welcome to
the "Do What You Feel" festival.
By the way, this young lady is not
my wife, but I am sleeping with her.
I'm telling you this because
I'm comfortable with my womanizing.
-Yea!
-Arr!
And now to usher in
this new era of feeling good...
here's the, uh,
Godfather of Soul, James Brown.
♪ Ow! I feel good ♪
♪ Huh, I knew that
I would now ♪
(grunts)
♪ I feel good ♪
♪ Good God,
I knew that I would, hah ♪
♪ So good ♪
♪ So good, I got you ♪
(yells)
-(all gasp)
-Hey. Wait a minute. Hold on here.
This bandstand
wasn't double-bolted. Huh.
-I didn't feel like it.
-Hey. I hear you, buddy.
Uh, I don't want to judge
the rightness of your ego orientation,
but my inner critic says
you should've done your job.
Hey, now, Marge.
Let's not "should" this fella to death.
Yeah. Next you'll be laying a guilt-trip
on me for not oiling that Ferris wheel.
-(loud screeching)
-(riders screaming)
(screaming continues)
(various animal noises)
-(screaming)
-(elephant trumpeting)
In the, uh, spirit of the occasion,
I must tell you what I think.
You two screwed up royal.
You know, I really don't feel
like being blamed.
I feel that you should shut up.
You know, you really
irritate me, Skinner.
What with your store-bought haircut
and excellent posture.
Mister, I can't stand
the sound of your voice.
-Oh, really? Come here.
-Oh!
Oh, now, now. There's no need
to resort to violence.
-Aw, sure there is.
-(clamoring)
I knew it.
If only I had nagged more.
God is angry. We've made
a false idol of this Brad Goodman.
No. You must not
blame yourself, Reverend.
You must blame that little boy.
He started it all.
-Get him!
-Eep.
(crowd jeering)
-Here, boy. In here.
-Huh?
Hold on, son.
(engine puttering)
So long, suckers.
Damn. They're very slowly
getting away.
-They're heading for the old mill.
-No, we're not.
Well, let's go to the old mill anyway,
get some cider.
-MAN: That's a good idea.
-Let's get some cider.
Aw, boy. If only Bart had been
a better role model for everyone.
That's not fair.
The lesson here is that...
self-improvement is better left
to people who live in big cities.
No. Self-improvement can be achieved,
but not with a quick fix.
It's a long, arduous journey of
personal and spiritual discovery.
That's what I've been saying.
We're all fine the way we are.
-(TV clicks on)
-Ooh, it's that new show...
about the policeman who solves
crimes in his spare time.
Crank it, Homer.
MAN (on TV): You busted up that
crack house pretty bad, McGonigle.
Did you really have to
break so much furniture?
MCGONIGLE: You tell me, Chief.
You had a pretty good view
from behind your desk.
Ah, McGonigle eases
the pain.
CHIEF: You're off the case,
McGonigle.
MCGONIGLE: You're off
your case, Chief.
CHIEF:
What does that mean exactly?
HOMER: It means he gets results,
you stupid chief!
-LISA:  Dad, sit down.
-HOMER: Oh, I'm sorry.
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.