♪ The Simpsons ♪
-(chalk screeches)
-(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(tires screeching)
(horn honks)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
ANNOUNCER:
It's the...
Hey, hey, it's great to be back
at the Apollo Theater and...
K-K-K?
That's not good.
(giggling nervously)
Oh...
Ow! Now I'd like
to introduce a new feature
never before seen on TV.
Dumb pet tricks.
(laughs)
Oh, boy.
Here's a dog
that's been trained
to catch
this red rubber ball.
(screams)
Somebody shoot it!
These specials get worse
every year.
I'll see
what else is on.
Hey, where's
the remote?
Hello? Hello?
Stupid cordless phone!
I'll try
the old-fashioned model.
Ah, that's better.
-How you doing, Gertie?
-(sizzling)
And now our parody
of "Mad About You"
entitled "Mad About Shoe."
Give me a kiss, baby.
No tongue.
(laughs)
(audience booing)
Oh, you're not going to like
our "NYPD Shoe" sketch.
It's pretty much
the same thing.
Ma, could you
get me some milk?
Can't you get it yourself?
Oh, that's okay.
I'll just go without liquid.
(hacking)
Oh, all right, all right.
-I'll get your milk.
-Thank you.
Does anyone else want anything
while I'm up?
ALL:
No!
Marge, get me a beer.
-Oh...
-Uh, Mom?
What?
Um, there's a hair in my soup.
But I'll just eat around it.
What kind of hair?
Well, it's blue.
Six feet long...
-Ew!
It's my hair.
(gasps)
Excuse me.
Your mother seems really upset
about something.
I'd better go have a talk
with her...
during the commercial.
Now let's hear it
for a great American.
Former president
Gerald Ford.
Thank you, Krusty,
for inviting me.
Well, all the good presidents
turned us down.
Oh, well, I'd like to talk
about a subject
that is very important to me.
The Boy Scouts of America
have molded men
for over 100 years...
What are you--
Uh... um... how's
your wife, Nancy?
-Betty.
-Who cares?
Oh, Marge...
I just had a couple of beers.
(gasps)
Eww!
♪ Give me a head with hair ♪
♪ Long, beautiful hair ♪
♪ Shinin', gleamin',
streamin', flaxen, waxen ♪
-♪ Give me down to there ♪
-♪ Hair ♪
-♪ Shoulder-length, longer ♪
♪ Here, baby... there, Mama ♪
♪ Everywhere, Daddy, Daddy ♪
♪ Hair... ♪
(suggestively) Marge, I was just
watching women's volleyball on ESPN.
Mmm-mmm-mmm.
Come on.
There's no need
for that baba-ma-bushka.
All right, but
don't be shocked.
Oh, there's no way I could--
(screams)
Homie, I'm losing my hair.
Now, sweetie,
don't worry about a thing.
I'll teach you to comb it over
so no one can tell.
Just like my hair.
(sobbing)
Mrs. Simpson,
there's no physical reason
why your hair
should be falling out.
This thing has me buffaloed.
(chuckles)
Phone call, Mrs. Simpson.
Lines one and two.
BART:
Ma, I need a glass of milk.
LISA:
Me too.
(grumbling)
I think the problem
may be stress.
I was just with Dr. Hibbert.
He said I was under
a lot of stress
and should get some help.
Marge, whatever it takes
to make you well, we'll do it.
Well, I was thinking we could
hire a nanny to help me out.
-A nanny?
-But how am I supposed to pay for that?
We'll find a way.
Mom has made
so many sacrifices for us
it's time we gave up
something for her.
I'll stop buying
Malibu Stacie clothing.
And I'll take up smoking
and give that up.
Good for you, son.
Giving up smoking
is one of the hardest things
you'll ever have to do.
Have a dollar.
But he didn't
do anything.
Didn't he, Lisa?
Didn't he?
Hey, wait a minute.
He didn't!
Homie, please.
I never ask for much,
but this is something
I really need.
All right, Marge.
I'll get you your nanny.
And to pay for it,
I'll give up the civil war
re-creation society I love so much.
Well, Homer's out. We got to find
a new General Ambrose Burnside.
And I'm not too crazy
about our Stonewall Jackson.
The South shall come again.
(doorbell ringing)
Hello. I'm Mrs. Pennyfeather.
I understand
you're looking for a nanny.
-Pleased to meet you.
-Wait a minute, Marge.
I saw "Mrs. Doubtfire."
This is a man in drag!
You're phony.
Fakey phoney broad!
Gimme those!
Homer, if you're going
to do this to every applicant,
we're never going
to find one.
Sorry.
Hello. I'm Mrs. Periwinkle.
-(growling)
-(screams)
I'm here about
the nanny job.
I'll keep a watchful eye
on your kids,
and if they get
out of line... pow!
I like him.
Thanks. Where do you
keep the liquor?
I hide a bottle of schnapps
in the baby's crib.
I'm sorry, young man.
You're not
what we're looking for.
You're telling me,
you blue-haired witch.
I heard that!
I guess we're not going
to find anyone.
We have our own suggestions
for the new nanny.
Would you like to hear them?
You have my undivided attention.
(playing "Turkey in the Straw")
(humming)
Well, I'd like to hear
your suggestions.
Maestro, if you please.
(clears throat)
♪ If you wish
to be our sitter ♪
♪ Please be sweet
and never bitter ♪
♪ Help us with math
and book reports ♪
♪ Might I add--
Eat my shorts ♪
-Bart!
-Just cuttin' through the treacle.
♪ If Maggie's fussy,
don't avoid her ♪
♪ Let me get away
with moider ♪
♪ Teach us songs
and magic tricks ♪
♪ Might I add--
no fat chicks ♪
Homer!
♪ The nanny we want
is kindly and sage ♪
♪ And one who will work
for minimum wage ♪
♪ Hurry, nanny,
things are grim ♪
I'll do it!
♪ Anyone but him ♪
Well, that's nice, kids,
but I don't know where
we're going to find
anyone like that.
(coughing)
Whoo-whoo-whoo!
Hello.
I'm Shary Bobbins.
Did you say Mary Pop--
No, I definitely did not.
I'm an original creation
like Rickey Rouse
and Monald Muck.
Now, as your nanny,
I'll do everything
from telling stories
to changing diapers.
Put me down
for one of each.
Now, Miss Bobbins,
if you want this job,
you're going to have
to answer a few questions.
First, do you have
any bad habits?
No. I'm practically perfect
in every way.
Well, so am I.
(gulping loudly)
(belching)
Ah!
(sighs)
Okay. Question two.
Who was your last employer?
Lord and Lady Huffington
of Sussex.
(whispers)
Marge, do we know them?
-No.
-Come on. Isn't he the guy I bowl with?
-The black guy?
-That's Carl.
Oh, yeah! So you worked
for Carl, eh?
I have a question.
Pop quiz, hotshot.
I'm supposed
to be doing my homework,
but you find me upstairs
reading a Playdude.
What do you do?
I make you read every
article in that magazine,
including Norman Mailer's
latest claptrap
about his waning libido.
Ooh. She is tough.
Shary Bobbins, you're just
what we're looking for.
Very well.
Come along, children.
(penny whistle blows)
My, she seems too good
to be true.
I'll say. Her butt waxed
the bannister.
Ooh! I can see myself.
All right, children.
Let's clean up this room.
-Oh, man!
-Do we have to?
Now, now.
I know a little secret
that will make the job
go twice as fast.
(sprightly piano intro)
♪ If there's a task
that must be done ♪
♪ Don't turn your tail
and run ♪
♪ Don't pout, don't sob ♪
♪ Just do a half-assed job ♪
♪ If... you... ♪
♪ Cut every corner,
it is really not so bad ♪
♪ Everybody does it,
even Mom and Dad ♪
(straining)
♪ If nobody sees it,
then nobody gets mad ♪
♪ It's the American way ♪
♪ The policeman on the beat ♪
♪ Needs some time
to rest his feet ♪
♪ Fighting crime
is not my cup of tea ♪
♪ And the clerk
who runs the store ♪
♪ Can charge
a little more ♪
-♪ For meat ♪
-♪ And milk ♪
-♪ From 1984 ♪
♪ If... you... ♪
♪ Cut every corner,
you'll have more time for play ♪
♪ It's the American way ♪
(pacifier squishing)
Hi-diddly-ho,
Shary Bobbins.
Yo, Shary Bobbins.
I picked you some posies,
Shary Bobbins.
Oh, thank you, Nelson.
Aw, jeez.
(oompah musical intro)
(heavy brogue)
♪ I'm a maniac ♪
♪ Maniac, that's for sure ♪
♪ And I'm dancing like
I've never danced before ♪
Aye.
That's the stuff.
(feeble applause)
Yeah. Thank you,
you ungrateful bast...
Shary Bobbins!
Is that you?
-Hello, Willie.
-You know her?
Aye. Shary Bobbins and I
were engaged to be wed
back in the old country.
Then she got her eyesight back.
Suddenly the ugliest man
in Glasgow
wasn't good enough
for her.
It's good to see you, Willie.
That's not what you said
the first time you saw me!
Extra! Extra!
Ripper strikes
in White Chapel!
Boy for sale!
Is this legal, man?
Only here and in Mississippi.
Oh, Shary Bobbins,
this is ever so much fun.
With you, every day
is Guy Fawkes day!
Bah, humbug.
Oh, Mr. Burns,
I think you'll find
all life's problems
just float away
when you're flying a kite.
Balderdash. This is
the silliest load of...
Ooh! Look at it fly!
Whee! Look at me, Smithers!
I feel practically
superduperfragicalicexpiala--
D'oh! Oh!
Ooh. What's this strange
sensation in my chest?
I think your heart's
beating again.
Ooh. That takes me back.
God bless you,
Shary Bobbins.
That Shary Bobbins
is a miracle worker!
The kids love her,
the house is spotless,
and my hair's grown back!
It's so full and thick,
it can support a beach umbrella.
Come to bed, Marge.
Oh! Ooh.
No, no. Leave it in.
(laughs)
He-he-he-he!
It's 8:00, children.
Time for bed.
But we're not sleepy.
Sing us a song,
Shary Bobbins.
Yes, sing us a song!
I've been singing you songs
all day.
I'm not a bloody jukebox!
Oh, all right.
(slow piano intro)
♪ In front of a tavern ♪
♪ Flat on his face ♪
♪ A boozehound
named Barney ♪
♪ Is pleading his case ♪
♪ Buy me a beer ♪
♪ Two bucks a glass ♪
♪ Come on, help me ♪
♪ I'm freezing my ass ♪
♪ Buy me brandy ♪
♪ A snifter of wine ♪
♪ Who am I kidding? ♪
♪ I'll drink turpentine ♪
♪ Move it, ya drunk ♪
♪ Or I'll blast
your rear end ♪
♪ I found two bucks ♪
♪ Then come in, my friend ♪
SHARY:
♪ And so, let us leave ♪
♪ On this heartwarming scene ♪
♪ Can I be a boozehound? ♪
♪ Not till you're 15 ♪
-More kippers, mum?
-Oh, thank you.
Ooh, I can't get enough
of this blood pudding.
The secret ingredient
is blood.
Blood?! Ugh!
I'll just stick to the brain
and kidney pie, thank you.
I believe my work
here is done.
Thank you for everything.
We'll miss you, Shary Bobbins.
You've changed me as well.
I'm no longer the money-driven
workaholic I once was.
I love you all.
Oh! To think I'll never hear
those sweet voices again.
(screaming)
Aw, you... you...
-(gagging)
-You little...
Oh.
(gasps)
Oh. I'll just unpack my things.
I think we got our
umbrellas switched!
Whee! I never felt
so alive!
(snoring)
Little more...
-Too much. Take it back.
-(groans)
MAN (on TV): Welcome back
to "Before They Were Famous."
We all know Rainier Wolfcastle
as the star of the
blockbuster "McBain" movies
but here's his first appearance
in a commercial
in his native Austria.
(to the Oscar Mayer tune):
♪ Mein Bratwurst has a first name ♪
♪ It's F-R-I-T-Z ♪
♪ Mein bratwurst
has a second name ♪
♪ It's S-C-H-N-A-C-K-E-N-
P-F-E-F-F-E-R-H-A-U-S-E-N... ♪
Shary Bobbins!
I want another beer.
-Well, you know, Homer...
-(piano introduction)
♪ If there's a job
that must be done ♪
♪ You'll find
it's much more fun... ♪
You'll find it's even more fun
if you get it for me.
♪ But the beer will taste
more sweet ♪
♪ If you get up off
your seat ♪
Lady, the man asked
for a beer, not a song.
Do-re-mi-fa-so...
Now, let's take a look at a young
Charles Bronson's brief stint
replacing Andy Griffith
in "The Andy Griffith Show."
Where's Otis?
He's not in his cell.
-I shot him.
-Well, that's-- What?
Now I'm going down
to Emmett's Fix-It Shop...
to fix Emmett.
(The Andy Griffith Show
theme playing)
Bart Simpson, this room
is a frightful mess.
I'll get right on it.
Bart, don't you remember?
Cleaning up can be a game.
I got a better game.
It's called
"whipping cupcakes."
♪ The Itchy and
Scratchy Show! ♪
♪ Yes, I'm stuck
in the middle with you ♪
♪ And I'm wonderin'
what it is I should do... ♪
♪ It's so hard to keep
the smile from my face ♪
(Scratchy screaming)
(giggles)
What I'm trying to say
in this cartoon
is that violence is everywhere
in our society, you know.
It's, like, even
in breakfast cereals, man.
(playing "Miserlou")
Lisa, don't sit in front of that telly
like a fly stuck on a toffee.
It's a great big world
out there.
-Been there, done it.
-I know!
We could have a tea party
on the ceiling.
Shh. TV.
Oh, you people
will be the death of me.
(sobbing)
♪ Wasted away again
in Margaritaville... ♪
♪ Searching for my lost
shaker of salt... ♪
Oh, here it is.
Aw, that poor woman.
We've crushed her
gentle spirit.
You people should be
ashamed of yourselves.
Shary, you did
the best you could
but you can't change
this family
and neither can I.
From now on, I'm just going
to sit back and enjoy the ride.
But haven't I taught
you people anything?
-Nope.
-No.
-So you like it this way?
-Indubitably!
♪ Around the house ♪
♪ I never lift a finger ♪
♪ As a husband and father,
I'm sub-par ♪
♪ I'd rather drink a beer ♪
♪ Than win father of the year ♪
♪ I'm happy with things
the way they are ♪
♪ I'm getting used
to never getting noticed ♪
♪ I'm stuck here
till I can steal a car ♪
♪ The house is still a mess ♪
♪ And I'm going bald
from stress ♪
♪ But we're happy
just the way we are! ♪
♪ They're not perfect ♪
♪ But the Lord says
"love thy neighbor" ♪
♪ Shut up, Flanders ♪
♪ Okely-dokely-do ♪
♪ Don't think
it's sour grapes ♪
♪ But you're all
a bunch of apes ♪
♪ And so I must be
leaving you ♪
Good-bye, Shary Bobbins!
Thanks for everything.
So long, Superman.
Do you think
we'll ever see her again?
I'm sure we will, honey.
I'm sure we will.
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.