The bidding stands
at eight million dollars.
Nine million.
Ten million.
11 million!
$15 million.
Joan Miró's The Poetess,
going once, going twice, sold.
To billionaire tech mogul
Megan Matheson.
Don't take that painting,
I love it!
I won't let you take it!
There you have it,
Ms. Matheson,
Joan Miró's The Poetess.
My painting's been stolen.
That's impossible.
It's a mystery so baffling,
only one man can solve it.
Get me Manacek.
Thank goodness you're here,
Mr. Manacek.
You're the best freelance
insurance investigator
in the business.
Oh, well, isn't that
just what we need?
Some smug pretty boy
out to make us cops look stupid.
Ah, Clancy,
you're looking well...
- Fed.
- See?
He put that pause between
those two words deliberately.
Maybe I did, maybe I... didn't.
Well, two can play at that...
pause.
Three people bid
on the stolen painting.
Nuclear magnate Mr. Burns,
venture capitalist
Megan Matheson
and mini golf cheat
Homer Simpson.
They're all suspects.
I don't mind
telling you, Manacek...
I hope you fall flat
on your face.
I hope not.
My mother's rather fond of it.
Damn your wit.
Look, Manacek, I don't
know why you're talking to me.
It's my painting
that was stolen.
Yes, but you insured
a $15 million painting
for $30 million.
For a woman with a head
for numbers, it doesn't add up.
You smug son of a bitch.
I like you, Manacek.
But you should be talking
to the real painting thief.
The man I outbid,
Montgomery Burns.
That's quite a workout
you're getting.
Although, I can think
of a better one.
Sorry, but I'm in
a committed relationship
with the former Miss Denmark.
She's created a breed
of mosquito that cures malaria.
Well, if she invents a cure
for commitment, let me know.
Pull.
Shoot.
Nice shot, Mr. Burns.
You're a natural
in the ancient art of skeet.
Oh, spare me
your flattery, Manacek.
I know why you're here.
You think I stole
that ridiculous painting.
Absurd.
A little clay pigeon told me
that you couldn't stand
being outbid by a woman.
Pull, pull, pull!
Looks like the only thing being
hit around here...
is a nerve.
I'll blast that smile
right off your smug face.
I like you, Manacek.
But it's obvious
who took the painting.
That lunatic who said he'd do
anything to have it.
Homer Simpson.
I... Did you bring that
with you?
It's inflatable.
I got it at Brookstone.
I don't know what help I can be
with your case, Mr. Manacek.
As you can see,
I'm a very busy man.
According to my sources,
Lenny...
you were obsessed
with that painting.
I myself was once obsessed
with a suede sports jacket
with leather pockets.
I would have done anything
to get it.
Even steal a painting.
Me? Obsessed with
some stupid painting?
That's absurd.
- Is it?
- You're right.
I'd do anything
to have that painting.
Lie, kill, steal.
Well, not kill.
But I would steal it,
and then lie about it.
But I didn't steal it.
And I'm not lying.
Believe me, or I'll kill you.
I like you, Manacek.
I'll kill you!
I like you.
Mr. Simpson,
there's more to your story
than you're letting on.
And I'm gonna find out what.
Please don't.
The pizza delivery boys get
better looking all the time.
I'm Homer Simpson's wife.
I love wives. They never
pester you to marry them.
Geez, you've got a lot of lines.
You will too, after I show you
my corduroy sheets.
Mr. Manacek,
my husband is a wreck.
Please, just give me a chance
to convince you he's innocent.
Only if it's over dinner.
Okay.
More Frito pie, Mr. Manacek?
Sure, why not?
If he's not guilty
of stealing that painting,
why is Homer cowering
on the stairs,
eating cereal
straight from the box?
Well, Homer's so quick to panic.
It's his only flaw.
Marge, I need you
to be straight with me.
Okay, I admit it,
he has many flaws.
Thousands. Flaws.
Everywhere, flaws.
Your husband doesn't really seem
like a typical art lover,
but he shows exquisite taste
in the female form.
Hey, Front Pockets,
quit hitting on my mom.
She only loves one stocky man
in tight pants, our dad.
Sorry, I can only solve
impossible crimes
if I'm seducing
an amazing woman.
It's my process.
I'll tell you everything I know
about Homer
for one of those Tiparillos.
No Tiparillos.
- Women.
I like you, Manacek.
So let me clue you in
on the real story
about my dad and that painting.
Homer was chaperoning my class
field trip to the art museum,
and he was not happy about it.
Come on, come on.
Hurry up in there.
Three to a urinal.
No hand washing,
or we'll be late for lunch.
Sheesh, look at
that stupid painting.
What is it even supposed to be?
Art should be of pretty ladies,
hunting dogs with dead rabbits,
Bible crap
and 3-D sidewalk drawings
where it looks like
you could fall in.
I get it.
I... get... it.
Mr. Simpson, some of the kids
went to the gift shop.
We were only supposed
to bring five dollars,
but some brought more.
Wha... Wha... What?
Oh, right. Chaperone.
This is warm beer.
That's an '07 Michelob.
Homer was saving it
for a special occasion.
Yes.
My husband just couldn't stop
thinking about that painting.
Wha...? Honey,
I love a painting.
Oh, what is it of? Grapes?
- No.
- Flowers?
- Peaches?
No.
You sure it's a painting?
I'm positive. I touched it
when no one was looking.
Well, there's nothing wrong
with being an art lover
as long
as it's representational.
It is representational,
isn't it?
Tell me it's representational.
What else about
our marriage is a lie?
Are you really
a licensed DJ?
I took the courses,
but I failed the test!
A blue-collar Joe
suddenly likes modern art?
That story and two bits
will get you a cup of coffee.
What year do you think it is?
Hey, who's the shamus here?
I'm telling you, deep down,
my dad is really sensitive.
Oh, good, you're awake.
You're the only one
I can talk to about... this.
I know that painting.
It's called The Poetess
by Joan Miró.
Why does it bring me such peace?
Why?!
See? Even though
the painting is abstract,
that yellow circle
can represent the sun.
Or Pac-Man at rest.
Dad, you think art sucks.
Snap out of it.
Wow. I mean, wow.
Every time I look at it
from a different angle,
I see something new.
I just want to take a moment
to acknowledge
that for the first time,
you're dragging me
into the museum.
Yeah, it's a topsy-turvy world.
Beach volleyball's bigger
than regular volleyball.
Sorry, pally. Sorry, gally.
But the museum's
closed down for good.
Can we go in and look
at our favorite painting
one last time?
It's called The Poetess.
Oh, it's right there,
inside the crate
that's going
to the auction house,
where a billionaire will buy it
and you'll never see it again.
Oh, and I'll have to
take that too.
Now museum, now you don't.
The Springfield Museum
of Fine Art
is the latest victim
of this city's budget woes.
The storied institution
has closed its doors forever.
Its legendary art collection
will be sold at auction
and its docents
released into the wild.
The closure is being protested
by a coalition
of local art lovers
and homeless bathroom users.
Picasso, Goya,
Cézanne, Dalí,
selling off artwork
would be folly.
We're here, Vermeer,
get used to it!
People, people.
Government is about
making tough choices.
This was not one of them.
Museum attendance was near zero.
We lost thousands
on stolen audio wands.
What do people want with wands?
These wands
are putting the hurt
on these walnuts.
Notice how Edward Hopper's
use of windows
invites the viewer
into the scene
but also keeps them at bay.
But Mayor Quimby,
the Springfield Museum
of Fine Art,
or SMOFA, was a jewel.
SMOFA was the one institution
of genuine culture
our town could be proud of.
Stop saying SMOFA.
It never caught on.
Excuse me, Mayor SMOFA.
I'm not like these brainy
tote bags over here.
I like my crusts stuffed,
my martial arts mixed,
and my movies fully Sandler-ed.
But there's this painting
from that museum,
and when I really look at it,
only one word
explains what I feel.
What is it again?
Transgender.
Transcendent.
Transcendence
doesn't fill potholes
or educate our children.
Did you know we had to lay off
a third of the police force?
That's right. Eddie.
I used to have a gun.
Fine, sell the artwork.
Let's move on
to the next protest.
Too many poke restaurants.
Poke is just okay.
At Water's Edge
by Paul Cézanne,
sold for $65 million.
Yeah! I'm as happy
as Steve Martin.
It's... Oh, God, no.
Our last item is The Poetess
by Joan Miró.
The bidding starts
at five million dollars.
I bid that.
- What are you doing?
- I have a plan to get the painting.
Six million dollars.
I think we can do
better than that.
I need this painting
for my private monkey sanctuary
in Costa Rica.
The monkeys find the colors
quite arousing.
Seven million dollars.
- Eight million.
- Nine million.
Sir, we attempted
to verify your funds
at the First Bank of Moe's.
The man at the phone
threatened to boil our skulls
and make them into...
rat toilets.
It's okay, Dad.
You just really loved
that painting.
The bidding stands
at eight million dollars.
- Nine million.
- Ten million.
11 million.
$15 million.
Joan Miró's The Poetess,
going once, going twice, sold.
To billionaire tech mogul
Megan Matheson.
Don't take that painting,
I love it!
I won't let you take it!
Your story had everything.
A field trip, a dream sequence,
Sideshow Mel...
and it gave your father
the perfect motive
to steal that painting.
A deeper connection
to his daughter.
Well, maybe,
but I'm sure he's innocent.
Mom, Lisa, 1970s horndog,
Dad's run off.
He's on the lam!
You know, once I send
your husband to prison,
you'll be kind of single.
It seems Homer escaped
out this window.
In all my years
as an investigator,
I've never seen a trellis
take such a pounding.
I know it looks bad,
but think
about what we told you.
My husband could never
have stolen that painting.
Thank you, Marge.
I now know exactly
how everything happened.
How do you know that?
I'll be happy to explain...
over breakfast?
You have
a real problem with women.
I know.
I'm seeing a therapist...
tonight at my place.
Oh, get out.
Go, go!
White chocolate...
the loneliest chocolate.
Homer, I know you're in there.
How did you find me?
I knew you'd return
to the scene of the crime
where your inner peace
was stolen.
You can't bring me in.
You're not a cop.
You're not even a regular
insurance investigator.
You're freelance.
You don't get paid
unless you submit an invoice.
Which lets me control
when my corporate year ends.
You're always one step ahead.
I don't like you, Manacek.
Your family's story
of how you fell in love
with that painting
did prove your innocence.
- How?
- By providing one crucial fact.
You're too dumb
to steal anything.
Maybe I did take it.
- Trust me, you didn't.
- I could have.
But I know you didn't.
That's what I'm saying.
- I'm smart.
- You're dumb.
After careful consideration
of facts and evidence
observed only by me,
I can reveal
who stole The Poetess.
Ms. Matheson.
Your last IPO was DOA,
and you needed the cash
to keep your girlfriend
in hybrid mosquito larva.
I've seen it a thousand times.
Impossible!
The armed guards
never let the painting
out of their sight.
But which armed guards?
It was a simple matter
of finding
the guards' identical twins,
then hiring them to rob
their own brothers.
That's the last
impossible mystery
you'll ever solve.
Well done, Mr. Manacek.
Who would have suspected
it was the person none of us
had ever met before?
Yes, it's a shame she went
through all that trouble
to steal a painting...
that had already been stolen...
by you.
Not yet, sir.
I mean, how dare you accuse me
of such a crime?
But the painting
was safely in our vault
until it left the auction house.
But which auction house?
It was a simple matter
of Burns building
an identical auction house
next door to the real one.
The actual painting
never left the vault,
so Burns could steal it
at his leisure.
- Now?
- Yes, sir.
My painting!
Oh, thank goodness
those thieves didn't get you.
It's a shame I punched out
a woman and an old man over...
a gift shop tote bag.
Lisa?
It wasn't my plan to steal it.
That painting
was the first thing
my dad and I
ever had in common.
I couldn't bear
to see him lose it.
It was a simple matter
of switching my canvas tote bag
for the painting
before it was
even auctioned off.
I knew it was wrong,
but isn't it a worse crime
to let some billionaire
hide art away
where guys like my dad
can never fall in love with it?
So, who gets The Poetess now?
Ten million dollars.
Ownership of the painting
reverts back to the city.
But where will we hang it?
We're knocking down
the art museum.
And what are you doing
with the money Springfield got
from selling
all the public's art?
Well, we're building
certain vitally needed
civic improvements.
Everything I love
in one place.
Beer. Hot dog.
Bathroom. Painting. Daughter.
Marge, you're a beautiful woman,
but you're loyal
to your husband.
And I respect that.
But if things were different,
would I have a shot?
You are the most conceited,
chauvinistic, son of a...
I like you, Manacek.