(SlNGlNG) The Simpsons
(TlRES SCREECHlNG)
D'oh !
(SCREAMlNG)
(TlRES SCREECHlNG)
Children, l'm sorry to say
one of your lunches exploded.
Who has the Little Bunny
FooFoo lunchbox?
Um. . . That would be me.
(ALL LAUGHlNG)
lt's not my fault.
l can't afford
a better lunchbox
'cause l'm poor.
(LAUGHlNG)
Shut up!
My mom got too fat
to work at Hooters!
(LAUGHlNG)
They won't even
let her park cars!
Please, children.
Don't be cruel.
Nelson might be poor
but l'm sure he has
the seven dollars
for today's field trip.
Um. . .
Well, actually. . .
(BRAKES SQUEAL)
(CHlLDREN LAUGHlNG)
(SOBBlNG)
Someday. . .
Now, l know
the rest of us are excited
about visiting the Museum
of Television today.
Hey, don't tell us
how to feel !
Bart Simpson, be quiet!
Hey, that wasn't me.
That was. . . Milhouse?
Milhouse? What happened
to my little class coward?
What do you care,
Mrs. Krabappel?
Or should l say
"Mrs. Crab Apple?" Ha-ha!
"Crab Apple?"
l never thought of that.
lt totally works.
Oh, how could
l have been so blind?
(SlNGlNG)
Rollin', rollin', rollin'
Toxic barrel rollin'
They're so hot and gIowin'
We'll die
Smithers,
the board of directors
is coming here today.
l don't want them
to see Snap, Crackle,
and Pop down there.
Sir, there's a big
cardboard box out back
that could keep them amused.
They could make a fort.
No, no.
Just give them each a nickel
and send them to Moe's.
Let them while away
the afternoon
spilling their beer
on gullets and trousers
while drooling
over French postcards.
(GlGGLES)
Hello, l'm lsabel Sanford,
the beIoved Weezy from
The Jeffersons.
At this "museum,"
you won't see a MicheIangeIo,
but you might
see Michael Landon
and BeverIy D'AngeIo.
This blows.
Let's sneak off.
Wander away from the group?
Man, you've been huffing
from the Bart bag.
To old man Burns,
who's paying us to drink
because we're embarrassing.
We suck!
(GROANS)
A lot of that
went in my lungs.
Attention,
American bar devils.
lt's our anniversary.
Free drinks for everyone.
That's great!
l'm honored to drink to Apu
and. . . Apu-lina.
Ah.
You know, Marge and l
have an anniversary
coming up.
l have given
Manjula many gifts
including
a bouquet of flowers,
diamond earrings,
and we're going to see
Paris Hilton in Paris.
Texas. . . On our way
to Paris. . . France.
What did you plan to
get your wife, Homer?
Well, these charity
address labels
that came in the mail.
Milhouse, why are
you acting so crazy?
Did your imaginary friend
try to kill you again?
No. Walter's been cool.
(SlGHS) Bart,
l gotta say something.
And it's not easy.
Well, if it's not easy,
don't do it.
That's how l got where l am.
Then let's just
say l don't care
what people think
of me anymore.
You mean,
up until now you did care?
Then why did you wear
that tutu to school
last week?
What about all the times
l didn't wear a tutu?
Nobody ever brings those up!
Now leave me alone!
MAN: It's the
Paul Lynde, Helen Reddy,
Hudson Brothers
Easter Special,
with guest stars
WiIIie TyIer and Lester,
and Nadia Comaneci.
I'd Iike to hippity-hop
on your baIance beam.
I don't think you understand
the mechanics of
heterosexual sex.
WeII, circIe gets the square.
TV sure has come a long way,
huh, Milhouse?
(MlLHOUSE LAUGHlNG)
Check it out!
l'm riding some guy
named lronside!
Ow, my banana!
Danger, danger.
Door ajar.
The indignity.
The agents got aII my money.
(NElGHlNG)
l'm bored.
Let's go switch the heads
on the Cosby kids.
HOMER: l don't want to
go home. l'm not done
talking to me.
Just get out
this door, rummy, and
you're the city's problem.
lf you make it
through the night,
you're welcome back.
Ah. home sweet home.
Now to watch some TV.
(RAT SQUEAKS)
Oh. . . You poor soul.
You think that
rat is a remote.
Here.
What? Five bucks?
l don't need your "sharity."
(SQUEAKlNG)
l'll dance for my money!
(SlNGlNG DRUNKENLY)
Oh, you poor man.
You think you can dance.
l didn't say stop.
(CONTlNUES SlNGlNG DRUNKENLY)
Bart, there's something
l gotta tell you.
l'm moving.
What?
My mom got a job
in Capitol City.
Capitol City?
You can't move that far.
You're my best friend !
What's your mom making?
l'll match it!
lt's too late, Bart.
My mom's already
transferred her 401 K.
No!
Luann, what are you doing?
Look, Kirk.
l need a fresh start.
Well, couldn't you
get a fresh start
by re-marrying
your old husband?
Kirk, we are going.
Fine. But you
can't take Milhouse.
l have visitation rights.
Yes. And you're also supposed
to pay child support!
Hey, l thought you said
my money was no good.
l said you're no good.
Get in the car, Milhouse.
This isn't over!
l'll fight you
with every lunch
half-hour l get!
Oh ! Speaking of which. . .
(HUMMlNG)
lt's gonna be tough
to be peppy today.
Tell me about it.
(KlRK SlGHS)
(TlRES SQUEAL)
(MARGE GROANS)
Why are your clothes
so dirty?
And why do you
smell like liquor?
Have you been clubbing?
(GASPS)
Homie, they're beautiful.
That Chevron Station
has the most
romantic bouquets.
l feel a swoon
coming on. (GASPS)
Here it is.
l am so wasted.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
We're having
a simultaneous pass out!
Well, at least
they're not fighting.
(lTCHY & SCRATCHY SHOW
THEME PLAYlNG)
Oh ! Mmm-mmm.
Right this way.
What's on the menu?
(SCREAMS)
(SCRATCHY GRUNTlNG)
(SlGHS)
(GROANlNG)
(LAUGHlNG)
Oh, Bart, l'm sure it's hard
to lose your best friend.
You mean Milhouse?
Funny little guy.
Afraid of the dark
and the light.
Now l've got new friends.
Guys who get me.
(DOORBELL RlNGS)
There's one right now.
Who is it? ls it Ralph?
lt is not Ralph.
Hi, Bart. My nose makes
its own bubble gum.
Just get in here!
. . . 1 8, 1 9, 20.
l found you, Bart!
Ralph, we're
playing checkers.
l don't like you, Boy-Mommy!
(GROANS)
Hmm.
Oh, loveless loners
are so lucky.
There's no way l can afford
to give Marge a nice
anniversary present.
Oh. . . You poor man.
You smell worse
than you did last time.
Hmm.
Hey, buddy,
that's nice sign work.
Your penmanship
is clear, yet sad.
Hey, l know you.
We met in a police lineup.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
You know, number two
and number four
are an item now?
You don't have to tell me,
l was number three.
Listen, you have any
pointers for a newbie?
Well, there are
six schools of begging.
Bad musician,
messed up vet, cripple,
fake cripple,
religious zealot,
and crazy guy.
l think you would
do well with
crazy guy.
Coke and Pepsi
are the same thing !
Wake up, people!
(BABBLlNG)
Wow. Now that is good crazy.
(SNlFFS)
(SlGHS)
Oh, no. Oh, no! Oh, no!
HOMER: Hmm?
Oh, yes!
l never thought
l'd have to take a plane
to see Milhouse.
Well, l'm sure
he'll be happy you came.
MAN: (OVER lNTERCOM)
Now departing, No-FriIIs
AirIines FIight 89.
(PEOPLE SCREAMlNG)
Milhouse, Bart's here.
What up, B?
Milhouse? ls that you?
Yeah. l gave my looks
a new flava.
Suck it in !
Uh. . . Maybe later.
(DOORBELL RlNGS)
What up, M-life?
Milhouse, this isn't you.
This is my
only chance to be cool !
Now please,
let me give you a wedgie
in front of these guys.
No way!
Please? l'll be gentle.
Oh, fine.
Wedgie!
(LAUGHlNG)
Milhouse,
you went Cap City on him.
Springfield baby in a diaper,
poked his eye with
a windshield wiper.
Springfield baby!
l'll always love you, Bart.
(CHOKlNG)
(BOTH LAUGHlNG)
(SOBBlNG)
Bart, honey, it's a nice day.
Why don't you play outside?
Outside? That's where
me and Milhouse played.
(SNlFFLlNG)
Hmm.
You know, l think your
sister could use a little
help washing the car.
You'll be like an owl saying,
"Milhouse who?
Milhouse who?"
Hey, Moldilocks.
Mom says l'm supposed
to help you.
Fine. You can confirm
the accuracy of the hose.
(YELLlNG)
(LAUGHlNG)
You wet your pants!
Shut up!
lt's a serious problem !
Lise, you are so dead.
(YELLS)
l'm gonna hit you so hard
l'll kill your whole family.
Bart, you're in my family.
Shut up!
(BOTH LAUGHlNG)
(EXCLAlMS)
Homie, l'd like to know
what you've been
doing after work.
Marge, l'm not
gonna lie to you.
(GRUMBLES)
l also found this
in your drawer.
(CHUCKLES)
All the answers
you need are in here.
Happy anniversary.
(GASPS)
Are these Diamonique?
Nope.
Diamondelle?
Cubic Diamondium?
Nope.
Dioxy-ribo-diamondoid?
Close but no cigar.
Just plain diamonds!
Oh, my God !
We finally have something
to put in the wall safe.
Hostess Twinkies?
l heard if you age
them for 1 0 years,
they turn to liquor.
Kids, go ride bikes
for a while, huh?
Yeah, you heard your mother.
We can't jump this ditch.
Sure we can.
But let me go first.
Everyone knows
you're the future
of this family.
That's not true, Bart.
Mom and Dad value
us equally and. . .
Ah, you're right.
Okay, go ahead.
Geronimo!
(WHlMPERS)
Just forget
everything you know
about gravity.
But l know so much about it.
Just do it!
Geronimo!
(LAUGHlNG)
Look.
We can go inside.
Ooh ! We're like
Howard Carter discovering
the Temple of Tutankhamen.
Or like when l discovered
the school Xerox code. 1 -4-7.
Just saying it
makes my butt feel
warm again.
(GASPS) Arrowheads!
(GASPS) Pictographs!
Bart, this is a Native
American burial mound.
(LAUGHS) Look!
He's picking his nose.
(CHUCKLlNG)
Hey, we shouldn't
tell anyone we were here.
This place should be
our special secret.
Okay. Shake.
(WHlMPERS)
Psych !
There's spiders
in your hair.
That's what you call
commitment to a bit.
(SlNGlNG) Mr. Bo-jangIes
Mr. Bo-jangIes
We're aII Bo-JangIes
Who kiIIed Bo-JangIes?
Maybe it was you
Thank you. Thank you.
Remember, my dog
up and died. Thank you.
You got your wife
the earrings, man.
Why are you still doing this?
l want to get a second house,
closer to work.
He's taking all our business.
We're gonna have
to do something.
We never do anything.
That's why we're bums.
Hey, you're a woman.
And you're
a three-headed devil dog !
Devil dog !
Wanna make out?
No one wants to be alone.
LlSA: "The mound builders
"worshipped turtles,
as well as badgers,
snakes, and other animals."
Thank God
we've come to our senses
and worship a carpenter
who lived 2,000 years ago.
(TELEPHONE RlNGlNG)
Hi, Janey.
Branford Marsalis' car
broke down outside
your house?
And he's just jamming
till Wynton shows up?
(GASPS)
Oh. . .
Um. . .
Some other time maybe.
Today l'm just
hanging out at home.
(DOORBELL RlNGS)
Hey, Bart. l "borrowed"
my uncle's pellet gun.
You want to go shoot Apu?
Oh, that does sound fun.
But not today.
l think l'm just
gonna hang out at home.
Oh, my God.
My brother's my best friend!
Oh, my God!
My sister's my best friend!
Diamonds. l still can't
beIieve he gave me diamonds.
Mirror, mirror on the wall,
who's the baldest
of them all?
One time,
l swung all the way around.
You did not.
Well, l know a guy who did.
Who?
You don't know him.
He lives in Russia.
l can't believe
they're hanging out.
Ha! Maybe she'll be
a good influence on him.
Or maybe he'll corrupt her.
lt won't last.
Brothers and sisters
are natural enemies,
like Englishmen and Scots,
or Welshmen and Scots,
or Japanese and Scots,
or Scots and other Scots.
Damn Scots!
They ruined Scotland !
You Scots sure are
a contentious people.
You just made
an enemy for life!
Listen, Mr. Hobo,
you may not have laundry
to wash, but l do.
Now what do you
want to show me?
There's your husband,
aka Mooch-a-lini,
Drooly McGee,
Corporal Flashback,
etcetera, etcetera.
Homer!
(SCREAMS)
You're panhandling !
l should've known from
that panhandling sign,
plus that ticket
you got for panhandling.
But, Marge,
it was all for you,
to buy you all
the nice things you deserve.
The flowers, the earrings,
the Bob Seger boxed set,
which really only
needed to be one disk,
but the box was nice!
Homer, l don't need
fancy things.
And even if l did,
this is the wrong way
to get them.
And to remind you
of what you've done,
l'm gonna keep these
earrings and wear them at
social occasions.
l don't understand.
Well, then maybe you need
to buy me a broach.
Bart, l cracked
the code of the pictograph.
lt says there's
a curse on the mound.
Of course l don't
believe it. . . (SCREAMS)
Hi, Lisa.
l brought you
the Cap City version
of Monopoly.
Baltic Avenue
is now Wayne Street.
lt's awesome!
Milhouse, l thought your mom
took you away forever.
l got a court order
bringing him back.
The judge said
l was the most
pathetic person
he'd ever seen in court.
Pity custody. Boo-yah !
(VOCALlZlNG)
Repo man.
l'm here to take your pants.
Not in front of my son.
Please!
You're somebody's father?
Yes, okay?
Oh, boy.
Well, l'm glad to be back.
Those Cap City kids
don't think l'm cool anymore.
We were having a sleepover
and a robber came
and wet my bed.
Then he folded
the bed back into the couch
and disappeared
into the night.
l knew you'd blow it.
Now let me show
you that mound.
You told him our secret?
Hey, he's my best friend.
Oh. l see how it is.
Great. Then we're all cool.
(SOBBlNG)
Since he's been back,
Milhouse has had
three bloody noses
and stepped in dog doo.
(CHUCKLES) lt's always
a party with that guy.
Well, it's nice
you have your
best friend back.
You should hang
with us sometime, Lise.
Mmm-hmm.
l think l'll go to bed now.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
(CHUCKLES) Boy,
are you in trouble.
What are you talking about?
When a woman says
nothing's wrong, that means
everything's wrong.
And when a woman says
everything's wrong,
that means
everything's wrong.
And when a woman says
something's not funny,
you'd better not
laugh your ass off.
Hey, Lise,
you want to play
Cap City Monopoly?
Look, just because
Milhouse is gone,
doesn't mean
you have to pretend
to be my friend.
Oh, come on.
l'll roll the dice for you.
Three, four, five, chance.
Pick up a card.
Sheesh.
(LlSA READlNG)
What? Really?
Yep. Pick up another one.
But it's not my turn.
l'm trying to do
something nice, you dink.
Pick up a card.
"Bart will defend you
when other kids
call you a nerd."
No one calls me a nerd.
Trust me,
that is a valuable card.
Pick up another.
"Bart will give back
the Malibu Stacy head
you thought was lost."
Oh, Bart,
that's really sweet.
Just because
l have Milhouse back
doesn't mean l haven't
learned a few things
about being a brother.
l think l'm gonna use
this card right now.
Oh. . . Do l have to?
Mmm-hmm.
(SlGHS)
All right.
This is what sitcoms call
a "schmaltzy ending,"
a sentimental capper
to leave the audience
feeling good.
Usually followed
by a little coda
to cut the treacle.
Granny, l'm gonna shoot me
some Vietcong.
Yeah? Well, l ain't
cooking 'em.
(AUDlENCE LAUGHlNG)
And George Jefferson,
wherever you are,
we love you and want you
to come home.
WeII, we're movin' on up
Movin' on up
To the east side
To a deIuxe apartment
in the sky
Movin' on up
CHORUS: Movin' on up
To the east side
Movin' on up
We finaIIy got
a piece of the pie
Fish don't fry
in the kitchen
Beans don't burn
on the griII
Took a whoIe Iotta tryin'
Just to get up that hiII
Now we're up
in the big Ieagues
Gettin' our turn at bat
As Iong as we Iive,
it's you and me, baby
There ain't nothin'
wrong with that
WeII, we're movin on up
Movin' on up
To the east side
To a deIuxe apartment
in the sky
English - US - PSDH