♪ The Simpsons ♪
-(chalk screeches)
-(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(tires screeching)
(horn honks)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
HOMER:
Mmm. "Hors do-vers."
Homer! You promised.
I promised I wouldn't eat?
Never. You lie.
Homer, please.
We've never thrown a party.
Now we're gonna pay back
all the friends
who have invited us
to their homes.
Never thrown a party?
What about that big bash we had
with all the champagne and musicians
and holy men and everything?
-That was our wedding.
-Oh.
Children, it's time for you
to go to bed.
But Mom, I want to hear
the witty banter of
sophisticated adults.
Yeah, you can't have
any fun in bed.
(chuckles)
Oh, son, when you're older,
you'll know better.
Mmm.
Oh, baby.
Mmm. Yeah.
-(doorbell rings)
-Oh, they're here!
-How does everything look?
-How do I look?
-Do we have enough glasses?
-Do we have enough gag ice cubes?
-Homer, put a record on!
-What are all our friends' names, again?
-MARGE: Children, go!
-(Tom Jones music plays)
-Hi, Homer.
-Please come in.
-You look lovely tonight.
-Marge, you're looking swell.
And the house--
You've done whatever.
Hey, anybody mind
if I serve as bartender?
I have a Ph.D. in Mixology.
(chuckles)
(disdainfully)
College boy.
Hey, Homer, care to try
some of my Flanders
Planter's Punch?
Why not? I paid for it.
Hey, Flanders, next time
why don't you put a little alcohol in it?
Au contraire, Simpson.
It has three shots of rum,
a jigger of bourbon,
and a little dab-a-roo
of Crème de Cassis for flavor.
Really? I do have
a warm sense of well-being,
and I seem to be slurring
my speech.
You're right.
Give me another.
Homer,
go easy on the alc-e-hol.
Remember last year,
at the Winfield's party
when you threw up
in the laundry hamper?
-No.
-(groans)
♪ The look of love is in... ♪
Hey, you're Homer's
sister-in-law, right?
I remember you.
But I don't remember you
being so beautiful.
(belches)
Ow! Hey!
(belching and coughing)
Is that a new kind of mace?
Really painful.
Oh, Dr. Hibbert.
Enjoying the party?
Uh, no, not really.
Someone seems to have slipped
one of those novelty ice cubes
with a fake fly in my drink.
(laughing)
It was me. You fell for it.
Homer, these novelty ice cubes
are often made
from highly toxic chemicals.
Ironically, a real fly would
have been much more sanitary.
You should see the
look on your face. It's priceless.
Hmm.
Bart! Come over here.
-What?
-You little monkey.
-You're a little monkey, aren't you?
-Yes, sir.
Bart, do that thing you do
that's so cute.
-What?
-That thing you know how to do.
-Go to bed.
-Hey, everybody!
-Whoa.
Look! I'm the funniest guy
in the world!
-Oh.
-Oh, Homer, you're the king.
Hmm.
(slurring) I have been wanting
to tell you off for years,
but I never had the nerve.
I don't know you. My wife
and your wife are friends.
We just met
just three hours ago.
You stink!
You and your whole
lousy operation stinks.
I quit!
-Uh, gee, don't-- don't quit.
-All right then.
Could you...
give me a...
handful of peanuts...
-Maude?
-Oh, sure.
-Not those peanuts.
-Oh?
-The ones at the bottom.
-Oh, okay.
(shudders)
(growling)
BARNEY:
Hey, thanks for inviting me.
I had a wonderful time.
I must apologize
for my husband.
If you want him to live
through the night,
I suggest you roll him
onto his stomach.
Thank you, I will,
Dr. Hibbert.
Thanks for coming.
Remember, I said if.
(snoring)
(straining)
I have never been
so embarrassed
in my life.
Why?
What did you do?
-(vacuum whirring)
-(Marge grunting)
Ooh. Ow.
Ooh.
-Marge! Huh?
-(cat shrieks)
-Come here.
-Where are we going?
Shh! I want to make sure
-the kids don't hear.
-("Mexican Hat Dance")
When I was young, I always hated
knowing my parents were fighting.
They're fighting
in the car again.
That music always sends
a chill down my spine.
Homer, do you remember the way you
acted at the party last night?
The way I acted?
So I said, "I must get out
of these wet clothes
-and into a dry martini."
-(group chuckles)
-Well-said, indeed.
-Thank you.
Good Lord, there's a fly
in my drink.
-I put it there.
-You did?
I slipped it into
your glass as a gag.
-Pure hilarity.
-(chuckles) Pure Homer.
I pronounce it to be the most
whimsical joke of the season.
(laughing and clapping)
Hmm.
(groaning)
(Homer panting)
Homer?
I like to think
that I'm a patient,
tolerant woman
and that there was no line
you could cross
that could make me
stop loving you.
But last night,
you didn't just cross that line,
you threw up on it!
I'm sorry, honey.
Can't we just forget it,
and go to church?
I'm going to church alone today.
You're going to stay here
and explain to Bart
-why you scarred him for life.
-No, I didn't!
I... oh, you mean
inside, don't you?
About last night--
you might have noticed Daddy
acting a little strange,
and you probably
don't understand why.
I understand why.
You were wasted.
I admit it. I didn't know
when to say when.
I'm sorry it happened.
I just hope you didn't lose
a lot of respect for me.
Dad, I have as much
respect for you
-as I ever did or ever will.
-Aw...
Now, before I give you all a sneak
preview of next week's sermon,
I have some announcements to make.
We have some new pamphlets
available in our church
news rack,
including "Bible Bafflers,"
"Satan's Boners,"
"Good Grief,"
"More Satan's Boners,"
and for the teens,
"It's Not Cool to Fry in Hell."
Marge? Marge?
(people whispering)
I'm sorry, the Lord and I
can't compete
with the squeaking
of Homer Simpson's shoes.
Why don't we just put everything
on hold until he takes a seat?
-Sorry, Reverend.
-Sit down, Homer.
Mrs. Lovejoy and myself
will be holding
our third annual marriage retreat
next weekend at Catfish Lake.
It's psychological counseling
for couples whose marriages
are hanging by a thread--
(groans)
-...or those just in need of a tune-up.
-Hmm?
Now, if you wish to participate,
please sign up in the lobby
-after the service is over.
-(bell tolling)
Will the Simpsons be attending
our little retreat?
Oh, well, it's very tempting.
Really a wonderful idea.
Marge! What are you doing?
Are you insane?
No! Give it to--
-We'll be there.
-D'oh!
Marriage encounter weekend,
here I come.
Now you want to go?
They're holding it
at Catfish Lake.
They couldn't
call it Catfish Lake
if it didn't have
a catfish in it.
We're going to this retreat to give
our marriage a tune-up and that's all.
-No fishing.
-Oh!
-(doorbell rings)
-That must be the baby-sitter.
-Hello. I'm Mrs. Simpson.
-Simpson...
-(chuckles) Come back for more, eh?
(gasps)
(screaming)
(screaming fades)
(engine starts)
(screaming resumes)
(screaming)
-Hey! What? What?
-Oh my!
Where are we supposed to get
a sitter on such short notice?
Oh dear, if we can't find
a baby-sitter, we can't go.
What a kick in the teeth.
What do you need
a baby-sitter for?
-I'm almost 10 and a half.
-Mom, you wouldn't dare.
Don't take that tone
with me young lady,
or I'll give you a taste
of the back of me hand.
No you don't!
-Grampa?
-Hey! Yow! What?
Grampa, could you do something?
-I can dress myself.
-Oh. Well, I was wondering.
Do you think you could
baby-sit the kids this weekend?
I wouldn't ask,
except I'm desperate.
Oh, sure. Last resort.
Old Grampa, the feeb,
the guy who can't be counted on
for nothing, nohow, dag-nab it.
Everyone's against me.
I'll do it.
Marge, just putting
a few last things in the trunk.
(chuckles)
Now, if Maggie runs a fever,
you call this number.
If she sticks her finger in
an electrical socket, call this number.
And if she drinks pine cleanser,
call this.
Just give the list!
I can read.
Alright, alright.
Good-bye, children,
and behave yourselves.
Mwah!
Call this number if Grampa
falls in the bathtub.
-I heard that.
-ALL: Bye.
Grampa, Mom was in such a hurry,
she forget to give you this.
It's a list of the things
Lisa and I can and can't do.
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
You're allowed to smoke cigars?
HOMER:
Hmm... bait.
Uh-oh. Better get some gas.
Fill 'er up.
I guess I'll go
and stretch my legs.
(bell dinging)
-Where are you headed?
-Catfish Lake.
Oh, after General Sherman,
are you?
Wait a minute.
Who's General Sherman?
He's only the biggest catfish
in these parts.
-Oh, yeah?
-They say he weighs upwards of 500 pounds.
-Whoa. Who says that?
-They do.
HOMER:
Oh.
Yeah, that there is the only known
picture of the general.
Can't see what he is, exactly.
He's freakishly big, though.
Hmm...
Gentlemen, I am going
to catch General Sherman.
Ooh...
Oh, my.
After the supermarket,
we'll go to the video store,
grab a Krusty Burger
and head for the arcade.
Bart, Grampa's a kindly
old man who trusts us.
Are you sure it's right
to take advantage of him?
Lise, in these crazy,
topsy-turvy times,
who's to say
what's right or wrong?
But right now, my gut's
telling me "bleed Gramps dry."
Ah, Mr. and Mrs. Simpson,
welcome.
Hello, Reverend.
We're glad we could come.
-Hello, Helen.
-Hello, Marge.
Why, Homer Simpson.
Here to give your marriage
a little spit shine?
None of your business,
Flanders.
Say, Reverend, are we gonna get
a chance to do any fishing?
Oh, I'm afraid not. A marriage
can't be reconciled in a few hours, Homer.
It takes a whole weekend
to do that.
-Oh.
-We must bait our hooks with honesty,
that way, a happy marriage
won't be the one that got away.
I see.
I also understand
bowling expressions.
Ah! Three couples.
Our best turnout yet.
Why don't we go around the room
and everyone
can introduce themselves
and tell us a little bit
about why they're here?
John, Gloria?
My name's Gloria.
I'm here because Johnny-boy
hasn't been able to cut it
man-wise for some time.
Not that I'd want his odor
of gin and sour defeat
pressed against me.
-That's enough, Gloria!
-Thank you, Gloria.
John, why don't you tell us
a little about why you're here?
She never cooks, she keeps
a filthy house and she talks profanely.
-She's the queen of the harpies.
-No, I'm not.
-Queen of the harpies.
Here's your crown,
Your Majesty!
-Queen of the harpies!
-Get away from me, you swine!
You've come
to the right place.
First, I want you to look
into each other's eyes.
-(both gasp)
-Your eyes,
I've forgotten
how beautiful they are.
-Let's never fight again.
-We were fools to argue.
-Let's not talk about that.
-Let's not talk at all!
Remember my saving your lives
and bringing you happiness
when we pass the collection
plate next week.
(chuckles) All right, Ned, Maude,
what brings you here?
-Well...
-Go on, Neddy.
Sometimes Maude,
God bless her,
she underlines passages
in my Bible
because she can't find hers.
Oh, lucky you don't keep guns
in the house.
-Homer, why are you here?
-Oh...
Because I got drunk
and looked down her dress.
-(gasps)
-No, no, Homer.
Marge is going to tell us
all your faults.
Why don't you tell us
about hers?
-Oh, she's perfect.
-Come on, Homer. What are her faults?
-Well, sometimes it can be annoying.
-Oh, Homer.
-Marge, don't interrupt.
-You'll get your turn.
-I'm done.
-Okay. Marge?
Well, it's not that
I don't love the guy.
I'm always sticking up for him.
It's just that he's
so self-centered.
-(gasps) Wait! Oh!
-Now, Homer.
He forgets birthdays,
anniversaries, holidays--
both religious and secular.
He chews with his mouth open.
He gambles.
He hangs out at a seedy bar
with bums and lowlifes.
(sobbing) It's true.
It's all true.
-Homer, don't interrupt.
-Sorry.
He blows his nose
on the towels
and puts them back
in the middle.
I only did that
a couple of times.
-Half a gallon of chocolate.
-Check.
-Half a gallon of chocolate brownie fudge.
Half a gallon of chocolate
chocolate chocolate chip.
Yep.
Did your mom really write
that shopping list?
-Grampa, what a question.
-What's next, Lise?
Sprinkles and syrups.
Hey Grampa, aisle six,
and step on it.
All right,
but put out that cigar.
MARGE:
He drinks out of the carton.
He never changes the baby.
When he goes to sleep,
he makes chewing noises,
and when he wakes up,
he makes honking noises.
Oh, oh, and he scratches himself
with his keys.
I guess that's it.
Oh, no, wait.
He kicks me in his sleep,
and his toenails
are too long and yellow.
That's all I can think of
right now.
I guess you're all tired.
I want to thank you for letting
me get some things off my chest.
(groans)
Well, we've missed the luau.
What's say we call it a night.
But, Captain I can't avenge
my partner's death
with this peashooter.
I don't want to hear it, McBain.
That cannon of yours
is against regulations.
In this department,
we go by the book.
Bye, book.
-Cool!
-All right, McBain!
You know kids,
it's getting pretty late.
Yeah, you should go
to bed, Grampa.
We've had a big day.
You wise guy,
little smart aleck.
It's no use kidding myself.
I'm having an ethical crisis.
Out at 5:00.
Catch General Sherman at 5:30.
Clean him at 6:00.
Eat him at 6:30.
Back in bed by 7:00
with no incriminating evidence.
Heh-heh-heh,
The perfect crime.
Homer?
(gasps)
You're sneaking out
to go fishing.
I can't believe
your selfishness.
You can go fishing anytime,
but we're here trying
to save our marriage.
You're thinking about fishing
even when I'm talking
right now, right?
Would this be a good time
to be honest?
-Yes.
-You're right, I am.
Help me, Marge.
What do I do to be a good guy?
Get back in bed.
Oh, all right.
But I can't sleep.
Can I take a walk?
Sure.
Got to be a good husband.
I got to be a good husband.
Hey, kid,
you forgot your...
(screams)
(screaming)
Go ahead, General Sherman,
foist your strength,
you big, ugly catfish.
I got a skillet and a stick
of butter with your name on it.
Hmm? Hmm? Homer?
(Homer yelling)
Hmm? Hmm.
-Sugar?
-Yes, ten please.
Hey, Grampa, top me off.
Are you sure your Ma
lets you kids drink coffee?
For the last time, yes!
Come on, give up.
Huh?
D'oh!
Hey, Milhouse.
Big blowout at Casa de Simpson.
The only adult
is frail and old.
Bart's joint.
Uh, two-ish.
Be there or be square.
Tell my friends?
All right,
but I got some
pretty funky friends.
All right.
I get out at noon
and I'm already invited
to a party.
Now, this is a trust exercise.
You fall backwards
and rely on your spouse
to catch you.
Do I have to do this?
No. Even if your husband were here,
I wouldn't recommend it.
Marge, as a trained marriage counselor,
this is the first instance
where I've ever told one partner
that they were 100% right.
It's all his fault.
And I'm willing to put that
on a certificate
you can frame.
♪ Over there ♪
♪ Send the word,
send the word ♪
♪ Over there ♪
♪ That the Yanks
are coming... ♪
-(heavy metal music plays)
-Ahh!
(crowd clamoring)
Okay, fish, you're probably
wondering why I'm still here.
Catching you will make me the most
famous fisherman there is...
right up there with that...
the, uh...
the bald guy
on the cable fishing show.
Whoa! Holy mackerel!
-(music continues)
-(clamoring continues)
Milhouse, didn't see you, pal.
Look out, my man.
Cherry party, Bart.
Any chicks over eight?
Not yet,
but the afternoon is young.
-Lisa, what's wrong?
-Isn't it obvious?
We've degraded ourselves
and set back
the children's rights movement
for decades to come.
You're great at a party, Lise.
Really great.
Hey, you! Don't!
Shut that door! Stop it!
-Put that away!
-(plates crashing)
No! Stop! Oh!
-Ow!
-(laughing)
You young hellion,
you want me to take off my belt?
-Yeah.
-All right, I'll show you.
-(laughing)
-Doggone it.
(straining)
I love you,
but I must kill you.
Yeah, take care, man.
Hey, thanks for coming.
Hey, nice tie, Nelson.
Oh, thanks.
It's your dad's.
(crying)
I tried to be a good baby-sitter
but I failed.
I'm a feeb, a useless,
old, worn-down...
(crying)
Lisa, I have this strong unpleasant
feeling I've never had before.
It's called remorse, you vile
burlesque of irrepressible youth.
How do you make
this feeling go away?
You grab a bucket and a brush
and you clean harder and faster
than you ever have before.
(crying)
-Huh?
-(door slams)
(laughing)
♪ I am the champions ♪
♪ No time for losers ♪
♪ 'Cause I am the champions
of the world ♪
Uh-oh.
Hi, honey.
Uh, how's the marriage
retreat going?
We came to this retreat because
I thought our marriage was in trouble.
But I never for a minute thought
it was in this much trouble.
Homer, how can you expect--
Marge? Marge, you don't know
what this fish means.
This fish represents
a better life for both of us.
This fish makes me a champion
and a hero.
-To who?
-To those weirdos in the worm store.
All this fish represents
is just how selfish you are.
Well, if that's the way
you feel, I'll throw it back.
-Oh, yeah, sure.
-Watch!
(grunting)
Whoa, I did it.
I gave up fame and breakfast
for my marriage.
I fought it for six hours.
She says one word,
and I toss it back.
And you're telling me
our marriage is in trouble?
Come here, baby.
Oh, Homer.
(grunting)
Uh-huh. Mm-hmm.
Eww.
Hmm.
Mmm.
(tires screech)
-We're back.
-How's your marriage?
Same as usual--
perfectomundo.
Oh, my!
The house looks wonderful!
Grampa, what's your secret?
Pretending to cry.
(laughing)
That's right, you heard me!
Pretending to cry!
(laughing) I can turn it
on and off like a faucet.
(crying)
Oh, I'm crying. I'm so sad.
Way to go, Grampa.
I'll never trust
another old person.
I fooled you.
So long, suckers.
(chuckling)
Yeah. General Sherman.
They say he's 500 pounds of
bottom-dwelling fury, don't you know.
No one knows how old he is,
but if you ask me,
and most people do,
he's a hundred years
if he's a day.
And no one's ever caught him?
Well, one fella came close.
Went by the name of Homer.
Seven feet tall, he was,
with arms like tree trunks
and his eyes were like steel:
cold and hard.
Had a shock of hair--
red, like the fires of hell.
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.