♪ The Simpsons ♪
(chalk screeches)
(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
Hello, I'm Kent Brockman,
and this is
"Eye on Springfield."
♪♪ (rock and roll theme)
Wow. Info-tainment.
Tonight we salute
the silver anniversary
of The Great Springfield
Tire Yard Fire,
25 years
and still burning strong.
We watch
Springfield's oldest man
meet Springfield's
fattest man.
He's not so fat.
And we visit with
heavyweight champion Dredrick Tatum
who reminisces about
growing up in Springfield.
That town was a dump.
If you ever
see me back there,
you know I really
(bleeped) up bad.
But first, part seven
of our eye-opening look
at the bikini.
♪♪ (rock instrumental)
Whoa-- T and A!
Bart, why are you still up?
Lisa's slumber party.
(girls giggling)
Who can sleep
with those five evil hens
cackling
and plotting against me?
Boy, they've got better things
to talk about than you.
Sheesh, what an ego.
Lisa, your brother
is so gross.
You should smell
his room.
(giggling)
Now remember, Wanda,
whatever shape the wax takes
that's what your
husband's job will be.
It's a mop.
My husband
will be a janitor.
That looks like
an Olympic torch to me.
Your husband could be
an Olympic athlete
who will go on to have
a great acting career.
It's a dustpan.
The wax never lies.
GIRL:
Let's play Truth or Dare.
ALL: Truth or Dare!
Truth or Dare!
I'll take... dare.
I dare you to...
kiss Lisa's brother.
ALL: Eww!!
(humming)
What the--?
Aaaaahh!
I'm telling Mom and Dad.
-You're telling who?
-BOTH: Mom and Dad.
GIRLS: Jinx!
(singsongy) Now you can't talk till
somebody says your name.
(giggling)
Coming up next: an elephant
who never forgets...
to brush!
What is it, boy?
(grunting)
Is anything the matter,
my son?
Talk to me, young man.
(grunts)
Say your name?
Why should I do that,
my lad?
Because I'm jinxed,
damn it! Ow!
What was that for?
You spoke
while you were jinxed
so I get to
punch you in the arm.
Sorry, it's the law.
(girls giggling)
There he is.
Let's give him
a make-over.
-Ahh!
-Run for it, boy!
♪♪
(girls chattering)
(grunting)
(whirring)
Aaaaahh!
(gulps)
Oof!
Come here, Maggie.
Huh?!
That's it, I'm out of here.
Hiya, Homer.
(sighing)
What's the matter, Moe?
Oh, business is slow.
People today are healthier
and drinking less.
You know, if it wasn't for
the junior high school next door
no one would even use
the cigarette machine.
Yeah, things are tough all over.
Increased job satisfaction
and family togetherness
are poison for a purveyor of
mind-numbing intoxicants like myself.
-Can I get a beer?
-Oh, yeah, sure.
Oh, sorry. I forgot
we're out of beer.
-Aahh!
-I know.
I got behind
on my beer payments.
The distributor
cut me off
and I spent my last ten grand
on the Love Tester.
(slurping)
You're too late,
Homer.
Barney sucked it dry.
Cut his gums up
pretty bad.
Ohh!
Take it easy, Homer.
I learned how to make other
drinks at Bartender school.
Gin and... tonic?
Do they mix?
Hey, I know a good drink.
Really hits the spot.
I invented it myself.
One night,
Marge's beastly sisters
were showing slides
from their latest vacation.
And this is Patty
trying to plug her leg razor
into one of those ungodly
Czechoslovakian outlets.
As you can see, we
never did get the hang of it.
Ay, caramba!
As I stared up at that
hairy yellow drumstick
I knew I needed a drink.
Patty, Selma, would you
excuse me for a moment?
If you're going for a beer,
this is the last one.
D'oh!
I decided to mix
the little bits that were
left in every liquor bottle.
In my haste,
I had grabbed a bottle
of the kids' cough syrup.
It passed the first test--
I didn't go blind.
They say everyone can float
in the Dead Sea,
but Selma sank
right to the bottom.
HOMER: Huh?!
I don't know the
scientific explanation
but fire made it good.
Sounds like one hell
of a drink.
What do you call it?
A Flaming Homer.
Okay. Why don't you
make us up
a couple
of Flaming Homers?
Hey, Moe, you got any
cough syrup?
Let me check the lost and
found. What do we got here?
Bowie knife, troll doll...
glass eye...
(shattering)
Oh, here we are.
It's not without it's charm.
Try lighting it on fire.
Hmm?!
Wow!
Homer, it's like there's
a party in my mouth
and everyone's invited.
Hey, your
Love Tester's busted.
I want my nickel back.
(coughing)
Hey, buddy,
have one on the house.
Hey, this drink is delicious
and my phlegm feels looser.
What do you call it?
Well, it's called a Flaming--
Moe!
It's called a Flaming Moe.
That's right, a Flaming Moe.
My name is Moe,
and I invented it.
That's why it's
called a Flaming Moe.
What? What are you
looking at, Homer?
It's a Flaming Moe.
I'm Moe.
-Oh!
-Hey, what's this?
-A sneeze guard.
(sneezes)
Wow, it really works!
Moe, I haven't seen
the place this crowded
since the government
cracked down on you
for accepting food stamps.
Do you think my drink has
something to do with it?
Who can say? It's probably
a combination of things.
Another pitcher of those
amazing Flaming Moes.
I hate this joint,
but I love that drink.
Ohhh.
Barkeep, I couldn't
help noticing your sign.
The one that says
"Bartenders do it 'til you barf"?
No. Above that
store-bought drollery.
Oh, great. Why don't we
fill out an application.
I'll need your name,
measurements, and turn-ons.
You really expect me
to tell you my measurements?
You could,
but I find this way
is much more accurate,
and fun.
Ugh! What do you offer
in the way of salary?
Minimum wage and tips.
Of course,
there are fringe benefits.
Such as?
An unforgettable weekend
at Club Moe.
I'd prefer to take
my vacation someplace hot.
-(all exclaiming)
-(laughing)
I like your moxie, kid.
You're hired.
You shan't regret this.
Me thinks I shan't.
Pardon me, are you the
genius behind the Flaming Moe?
-Why yes, I--
-I'm your man.
Uh-huh. My name's
Harv Bannister.
I work for
Tipsy McStagger's
Good Time Drinking
and Eating Emporium.
Oh, yeah? Hey, what's
Mr. McStagger really like?
Actually, there is no
Tipsy McStagger.
He's just a composite
of other successful logos.
Well, you tell him for me
that he makes
one great mozzarella stick.
Yes, fine, I will.
Anyway, I've got a
proposition for you.
Keep talking.
We feel your Flaming Moe
is perfect for our
restaurant chain.
We want to buy the recipe.
No dice. The Flaming Moe
is not for sale.
Do you know how much
of my blood and sweat
are in this drink?
(spitting)
Uh... figure of speech.
Sorry, Harv.
(chuckles)
I'll be back.
Good for you, Moe.
Only an idiot
would give away
a million-dollar idea
like that.
Ohhh.
MARTIN:
So the next time you use
a gas chromatograph,
remember to thank
Mr. A.J.P. Morton.
Brilliant, Martin.
Brilliant.
Once again you've wrecked
the grading curve.
I pity the poor student
who has to follow you.
Bart Simpson,
you're next.
"The Inventor I Admire"
by Bart Simpson.
The inventor I admire
is not a rich man
or a famous man,
or even a smart man.
He's my father, Homer Simpson,
creator of--
♪ dun-da-da-dah ♪
the Flaming Homer!
The Flaming Homer?
You mean the Flaming Moe
and your dad
didn't invent it, you wuss.
Moe the Bartender did.
Yes, everyone knows that.
It's not true.
My father invented that drink.
and if you'll allow me
to demonstrate.
Bart, are those
liquor bottles?
I brought enough
for everybody.
Take those to
the teachers' lounge.
You can have what's left
at the end of the day.
♪♪ (jazzy rock)
-(indistinct chatter)
-MAN: Hey, Bernard!
Good evening,
Krusty.
Nice to see you,
Bernard.
Thank you very much.
Right this way.
-Krusty, over here!
-Krusty, one more!
What the--
♪♪ (jazzy rock continues)
Henceforth, this date
shall forever be known
as Flaming Moe's Day.
Sir, this is already
Veteran's Day.
It can be two things.
Mom, instead of milk for dinner,
can I have a Virgin Moe?
(groaning)
Honey, what's wrong?
I'll tell you what's wrong.
That rotten Moe is getting rich
off a recipe I gave him.
(whistling)
Take that off
this second.
Okay.
Homie, why don't you
just go down to Moe's
and talk to him?
I bet he'd be willing to share
some of his success with you.
Nah.
Marge, I'm too upset to eat.
I think I'll go to Moe's.
D'oh!
(indistinct chatter)
Oh!
Hey!
Can I help you, sir?
I need to talk to Moe.
Your name's
not on the list.
I didn't even
tell you my name.
-Okay, what's your name?
-Homer Simpson.
-Not on the list.
-But--
We're all filled up.
Fire laws!
Ladies and gentlemen,
some new buddies of mine
stopped by tonight.
Maybe we can get them
to come up here.
How about a warm
Flaming Moe's welcome for...
Aerosmith!
(girls squeal)
-I don't think so, Moe.
-Nah.
We're just hanging out.
Come on, guys.
Free pickled eggs.
-All right!
-Yeah!
(cheering, applause)
Hello, St. Louis!
That's Springfield,
Steven.
Oh, yeah. Right.
Are you ready to rock?
ALL: Yeah!
I said, are you ready to rock!
-ALL: Yeah!
-Hit it!
♪♪ (intro to
"Walk This Way")
♪ Backstroke lover, I was
hiding 'neath the covers ♪
♪ You was talkin' to
your daddy and sayin' ♪
♪ Said you ain't
seen nothin' ♪
♪ Till you're down
on the muffin ♪
♪ Then you're sure to be
a-changin' your way ♪
♪ I met a cheerleader
was a real young breeder ♪
♪ All the times
I can reminisce ♪
♪ 'Cause the best things
of lovin' ♪
♪ Was a sister
and a cousin ♪
♪ Only started
with a little kiss ♪
♪ Like this... ♪
(grunting)
-Barney?
-Hi, Homer.
I want you
to meet my friends
Armando and Raffi.
(grumbling)
♪ So I took a big chance
at the high school dance ♪
♪ With a missy
who was ready to play ♪
Hey, Moe, come on.
Get up here.
♪ And I know that love
was here to stay ♪
♪ When she told me to
Walk this way ♪
♪ Walk this way ♪
(cheering)
Hiya, scrumptious.
Do you want to ignite my drink?
You're my kid's teacher.
Single parent, are we?
No.
Well, let's pretend you are.
Get away from me.
-Hey, Moe!
-Oh, hi, Homer.
How about a beer?
I'd rather have
a Flaming Homer.
A what?
Oh, I get it.
How could you
do this to me, Moe?
This bar was going under,
and it was the drink
I invented that saved it.
If there was any justice,
my face would be on
a bunch of crappy merchandise.
Morris, is what
this man saying true?
Well, it's hard to say.
He may have come up
with the recipe
but I came up
with the idea
of charging $6.95 for it.
-(phone rings)
-Uh-- telephone.
Flaming Moe's.
Yes, I'm looking for
a friend of mine.
Last name: Jazz.
First name: Hugh.
Hold on. I'll check.
Hugh Jazz?
Somebody check the men's room
for a Hugh Jazz.
I'm Hugh Jazz.
Telephone.
Hello, this is Hugh Jazz.
Uh... hi.
-Who's this?
-Bart Simpson.
What can I do for you, Bart?
Look,
I'll level with you mister.
This is a crank call
that sorta backfired
and I'd like to bail out
right now.
Alright.
Better luck next time.
What a nice young man.
Homer, I'm sorry you're mad
at me, but this isn't personal.
This is business.
Business, eh?
Well, let me tell you something.
You just lost
yourself a customer.
What? I'm sorry.
Homer, I couldn't hear you.
I said, you just lost
yourself a customer!
-What?
-You just lost yourself a customer!
Homer, you're gonna
have to speak up.
You just lost yourself
a customer, Moe!
I forced myself to what?
You just lost
yourself a customer!
Homer, I'll talk
to ya' tomorrow.
You just lost yourself
a customer!
Yeah, you can use it.
(indistinct shouting)
♪♪ ("Cheers" style
theme music)
♪ When the weight of the world
has got you down ♪
♪ And you want to end
your life ♪
♪ Bills to pay,
a dead-end job ♪
♪ And problems
with the wife ♪
♪ But don't throw
in the towel ♪
♪ 'Cause there's a place
right down the block ♪
♪ Where you can drink
your misery away ♪
-♪ At Flaming Moe's ♪
-CHORUS: ♪ Let's all go to Flaming Moe's ♪
♪ Let's all go
to Flaming Moe's ♪
♪ Where liquor in a mug ♪
-♪ Can warm you like a hug ♪
-CHORUS: ♪ Flaming Moe's ♪
♪ And happiness is just
a Flaming Moe away ♪
♪ Happiness is just
a Flaming Moe away. ♪
ALL: Barney!
How's the world treating you,
Mr. Gumble?
(belches)
Hey, there!
What can I do
for you, Harv?
Well, sir, Tipsy McStagger
would like to buy your drink.
(gasps)
He's here?
No, no, no.
I mean my company is
willing to do what it takes
to get that recipe.
We're prepared
to offer you $1 million.
(all gasping)
Sorry, Harv,
but like I told you before
it ain't for sale.
Don't be stupid!
We have a laboratory for
this kind of thing.
We've got it all figured out,
except for one ingredient.
Brace yourselves, gentlemen.
According to
the gas chromatograph,
the secret ingredient is...
Love?!
Who's been screwing
with this thing?
I'm sorry, but the secret
ingredient dies with me.
30 cases of cough syrup.
-Sign here.
-(nervous laugh)
I got hooked on this
stuff in the service.
(siren blaring)
HOMER:
Ah! My new watering hole.
Yeah, what do you want?!
-A beer.
-Okay, then.
Can I have a clean glass?
(growls)
Here you go,
your majesty.
Next on
"Eye on Springfield,"
a toast to Moe,
the wizard of Walnut Street.
MOE: The Flaming Moe
dates back to my forefathers
who were bartenders
to the czar.
So, Mr. Hutz,
does my husband have a case?
I'm sorry,
Mrs. Simpson
but you can't
copyright a drink.
(moaning)
Ohh!
This all goes back to the
Frank Wallbanger case of '78.
How about that?
I looked something up.
These books behind me don't
just make the office look good.
They're filled with useful
legal tidbits just like that.
Stupid Moe.
Non-inventing,
recipe-stealing, pug-nosed--
Well, Homer, maybe you
can take some consolation
in the fact that
something you created
is making so many
people happy.
Ooh! Look at me.
I'm making people happy.
I'm the magical man
from Happy Land
in a gumdrop house
on Lollipop Lane.
Oh, by the way,
I was being sarcastic.
Well, duh!
Now, that's what I call
a happy hour.
(deep sigh)
Morris, something troubles me.
Don't worry baby.
My mother won't be home
for another 20 minutes.
No. I was just thinking
about Homer Simpson.
That's okay.
I was just thinking
about Sybil Danning.
I meant, I think you
should sell your drink
and give half the money
to Homer.
But, honey--
He's your friend, Morris,
and you took advantage
of him.
All right.
I'll split the million
with Homer.
Jeepers, Mary and Joseph!
I sleep with a chick once
it costs me
half a million bananas.
Moe, Moe, Moe...
Bart, are you going
to mow the lawn today?
Okay, but you promised me
Moe money.
I Moe, I Moe.
Moe, Moe, Moe...
When Bart's done,
can we Moe
to the Moevies?
There's a Moetinee.
Of course. All work and Moe play
makes Moe a Moe Moe.
-Moe Moe Moe Moe Moe?
-Moe Moe Moe.
Moe Moe Moe Moe Moe.
Moe Moe Moe Moe.
Moe.
Moe, Moe...
Moe...
Moe....
Moe, Moe...
-Hey, Homer.
-Huh?
Aaaaahh!
Hiya, Homer!
What's the matter?
Aaaaaaahhh!
♪ Sneakin' out
the back way ♪
♪ Sneaking
down the alley way ♪
Hey, where's Joey?
JOEY: Mrs. Krabappel,
I really need
my drumsticks.
Come and get 'em!
You're going to be
a rich man, Moe.
I gotta tell you.
The way we usually work
in these situations is
to steal the recipe
and run the inventor
out of business.
Ah, c'est la vie.
(fiendish echoing laughter)
What the--?
(fiendish laughing)
Fools!
You poor, pathetic
misguided creatures
choking down your Flaming Moes
all the time wondering,
"How does he do it?"
Well, I'm going to tell you.
Hee-hee-hee-hee-hee!
The secret ingredient is...
Homer, no!
...cough syrup.
Nothing but plain, ordinary,
over-the-counter
children's cough syrup.
(laughs maniacally)
Shoot.
Thank you, Mr. Nutball.
Got to go, Moe.
Tough luck.
Aaaaaaaahhh!
Holy cow,
you just fell
on Aerosmith!
MOE: Hey, Homer.
Come in here.
Hi, Moe.
Where's that waitress
of yours?
She left to pursue
a movie career.
Frankly, I think she
was better off here.
Moe, sorry I lost you hundreds
of thousands of dollars.
Oh, hey, hey.
Maybe some things are too good
to be kept a secret.
I guess so.
Compliments of the house--
one Flaming... Homer.
HOMER: Aw, thanks, Moe.
You're the greatest friend
a guy could ever have.
Hey, do you think Aerosmith
will be in tonight?
MOE: I doubt it.
♪♪
♪ Do it in the sunshine ♪
♪ Hangin' from
a clothesline ♪
♪ Find another tree
to climb ♪
♪ Young lust ♪
♪ There's no time
for lovin' ♪
♪ Young lust ♪
♪ I don't need one
in the oven ♪
♪ Young lust ♪
♪ I'm a-pushin'
and a-shovin' it ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Young lust ♪
♪ Come on now
I just can't wait ♪
♪ Are you fishin' or
you gonna cut bait ♪
♪ Everybody body doin' it ♪
♪ Young lust ♪
♪ There's no time
for lovin' ♪
♪ Young lust ♪
♪ I don't need one
in the oven ♪
♪ Young lust ♪
♪ I'm a-pushin'
and a-shovin' ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Young lust ♪
♪ Come on now
I just can't wait ♪
♪ Are you gonna finish
or you gonna cut bait ♪
♪ Everybody body doin' it ♪
♪ Young lust ♪
♪ There's no time
for lovin' ♪
♪ Young lust ♪
♪ I don't need one
in the oven ♪
♪ Young lust ♪
♪ I'm a-pushin'
and a-shovin' ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Young lust ♪
♪ Come on now
I just can't wait ♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.