2:00 a.m. ham,
2:00 a.m. ham
Everything rhymes with
So many lies.
What else was he hiding
from the world?
How could the deception
go so deep?
Can we ever trust anyone?
My daughter's roaming
the house in the middle
of the night looking terrified.
I should probably go talk to...
2:00 a.m. ham
You look like
you didn't sleep a wink.
Looks can be deceiving.
Nothing is as it seems.
The world is a dark place.
Oh, Lisa seems really frazzled.
Did the climate change again?
I don't know. Probably.
She's been like that for hours.
What is she doing under there?
Something so troubling
she doesn't want us to find out.
As her friends,
we should respect that.
The confession was coerced.
Honey, what are you
listening to?
You know, just some
gentle ASMR noises
to soothe me to sleep.
You know, like...
And...
Oh, that stuff doesn't work...
Good night.
Music in a minor key?
You've been listening
to true crime podcasts?
Hoda Kotb said on The Today Show
those are really disturbing.
- Hoda.
- Mom, I can handle it.
There's no swear words,
just killing.
How many of these
have you listened to?
I don't know.
Just two or three a day.
And then maybe a couple more
to take the edge off.
And then one in the morning
just to get normal.
Wha...
I'm not addicted, I swear.
I just need to know
who killed everybody!
I just need to know.
I just...
Aw, she's all murdered out.
These titles.
It's like they're trying
to intrigue people.
I better listen to one and make
sure Lisa's not too traumatized.
Whatever. I'm hitting the hay.
Okay, I'm on episode eight
of Killing Her Softly.
We need to talk about
Angela's landlord.
Why did he allow her
to pay for a year up front?
What did Sergei know?
We have much to discuss.
Okay, pause.
It's like
the police intentionally
screwed up the investigation.
Right? Drops of blood
you can explain,
- but drops of brain?
- I know.
Okay, play.
Okay, pause. They totally
ignored the text messages
- from the coroner's mistress.
- Okay, play. Play.
Oh, yeah.
How could a woman
with four PhDs be so dumb?
So dumb.
I've never seen two people
agree with each other so much.
I disagree. Come on, you two.
We're supposed to visit
Grampa today.
- Homie, we can't go.
- Our favorite podcast
is recording a live episode,
and we have tickets.
If we gasp loud enough,
we might hear ourselves.
Save it for the show, Mom.
Now, remember, Bart,
Grampa's life is
very lonely and boring.
So make sure to look at
your watch every few seconds
so he knows you want to leave.
Here, take some of these.
Why is my dad's weird old tie
hanging on his doorknob?
You idiots!
Don't you know the code?
If the bolo's a‐hanging,
the dentures be clanging.
This is my new girlfriend,
Vivienne Saint Charmaine.
Abe‐y, you didn't tell me your
brothers were coming to visit.
- Oh, well. Oh, my.
- Aw, shucks.
Say, you look familiar.
Did you used to be younger?
Vivienne was a big‐time TV star.
She was on all the hit shows,
and I was a huge fan.
A little magazine.
But you probably know me best
as the scheming yet conniving
Olympic diver Darcy Covington
on Falcon Landing.
Ma'am, if you're
a big shot has‐been,
why are you dating
a small‐town never‐was?
All my life,
I dated unwrinkled men
who told short, concise stories.
But Abe here showed me
what I've been missing.
He's so sweet he should
come with an insulin pump.
Well, thanks for stopping by,
but we've got two bingo games,
a couple's colonoscopy...
and then we're off
to a romantic dinner cruise.
- Dude.
- Bro.
- Seriously.
- I know.
From This American Crime
and KBBL Springfield,
it's Interminable,
one grisly story
told week after week after week
after week.
Hello. I'm Tabitha Shingle.
She's even more dry in person.
Some people look
at a neck and think...
What a great place
for a scarf,
and others think,
I'd like to choke that.
For Jackson Reeb of Lansing,
Michigan, it was the latter.
Hey, hey, hey.
Easy on the hurricane hold.
We're just doing a story
on the podcast craze.
Podcast?
Flash‐in‐the‐pan
wannabe journalism.
Mark my words, Jerry,
nobody cares.
Now to open this door.
Our podcast has gotten
over 20 million downloads
and is being adapted
into a streaming series
starring Alexander Skarsgard
on Amazon Prime.
Stupid podcasts.
Thank God I have my family.
Now to open this door.
This is Kent Brockman,
yesterday's news.
And in the end, the donkey
turned out to be a horse.
You're only watching this
because somebody left the TV on
in a doctor's waiting room.
Wait, wait a second.
We have breaking news!
There's been a murder
on the high seas.
A local woman is presumed dead
after going overboard
on a cruise ship.
A woman disappears
from a cruise.
I wonder who did it.
Could it be...
The husband or boyfriend?
That's the lady
Grampa was kissing.
Grampa's the husband
or boyfriend?
Authorities say the missing
woman is retired starlet
Vivienne Saint Charmaine.
Her boyfriend or husband,
Abraham Simpson,
has been detained
for questioning.
Grampa? A killer?
He doesn't have
that kind of follow‐through.
Did Abe Simpson do it?
No one can say for sure.
But this story has the makings
of a hit crime podcast.
Join me as I take a fair and
unbiased look on Guilty Grampa.
This has been Kent Brockman,
bailing on TV news forever.
This is horrible.
What are we gonna do?
I've already subscribed.
A romantic sunset cruise,
the perfect setting
for new love between
a fading Hollywood actress
and a fully faded old man.
But only one of them
would return to port alive.
I'm Kent Brockman,
and this is Guilty Grampa.
Guilty Grampa is sponsored
by Shampoo Shuttle,
seasonal‐flavored shampoos
drone‐delivered
direct to your shower.
Showbiz princess
Vivienne Saint Charmaine
had finally met her prince,
local census resistor
Abe Simpson.
Together they boarded
a romantic seniors cruise
across Springfield Harbor.
It was 2:33 p.m.,
and the passengers
were finishing dinner.
Suddenly, there were
the sounds of a commotion,
a scream and then a splash.
Vivienne was gone,
but did the truth
go overboard with her?
I have with me a woman
who was on that fatal cruise,
disgraced docent Agnes Skinner.
Tell me about that night.
I was at the buffet when I heard
a woman scream, Abe, don't!
Then a splash.
What did you do next?
I saw they were refilling
the shrimp tower,
so I had to get over there
and touch them all.
Abe, don't.
Whatever could
Vivienne have meant by that?
Naturally, the police
questioned Abe Simpson.
His only defense?
I don't remember.
The old man would not confess.
Rude.
So we swabbed his hands
to see if they tested positive
for pushing.
It came back as no such test.
The only thing we could do
was let him go.
So maybe the old saying is true.
To catch a murderer,
you have to set them free
to murder again.
This has been Guilty Grampa.
Ah, that podcast sucks butts.
Grampa's not some monster.
Am I inside?
Vivienne and I went on
the cruise, had dinner,
drinks, dancing, drinks.
The rest is kind of a blur.
And the next thing I know,
the cops are telling me
- I'm a person of interest.
- That's ridiculous.
You've never been a person of
interest, not for one second.
I don't remember nothing.
But I would never hurt Vivienne.
She was my last chance at love,
and now she's gone forever.
Whoop. Got to take a zizz.
Okay, quick,
he's in the bathroom,
so we only have an hour to talk.
Now, on the count of three,
say if you think
he's guilty or not.
One, two, three.
- Not guilty!
- If I'm being honest, I think he's capable
of anything,
up to and including murder.
You're talking about
your own father.
Grampa's a good man,
and everyone in this town
knows that.
You're protecting a killer!
Murderer!
Grampa boat‐pushed
my favorite sexy TV lady.
I had a poster where she was
on top of a Trans Am
and it said,
finely‐tuned machine.
It referred to both her
and the car!
Crime podcasts should be about
exposing truth,
not irresponsible speculation.
If only Kent knew Grampa
like we do,
he would call that show
Not Guilty Grampa,
which I bet would get
even more listeners.
Hey! We got an ender.
Ender!
Homer, tell me about the
Abe Simpson you knew and loved.
I mean, I knew him.
Was he abusive?
Oh, sure.
I mean, he was a quiet loner,
but he could be abusive
when he wanted to be.
Really?
And your mother...
how did she deal with all this?
You know, I'm not really sure.
She disappeared
when I was quite young.
Another woman in his life
vanished.
Stick some foghorns under that
and put it up stat.
Wait, that may have
sounded bad.
You're not gonna podcast that,
are you?
Imagine the worst person
in the world.
Now imagine his father.
That's Abe.
His roommates
kept turning up dead.
90‐year‐old people don't just
suddenly stop breathing.
Come on.
He murdered me once.
That's why
my family doesn't visit.
My grandfather is not only
a great man,
he's a World War Two hero.
They used to call him
Johnny Flamethrower.
He said the fires
would tell him who to burn.
So I say to Ira Glass, NPR?
What does that stand for?
No Possible Revenue?
Hey, Kent. I'm Yeardley Smith.
Your voice sounds familiar.
Where do I know you from?
From my true crime podcast
Small‐Town Dicks,
and nowhere else.
Can I give you a word of advice?
I'd be a fool not to say,
make it quick.
As much as it's fun to report
on murder and mayhem,
these podcasts are accusing
real people of serious crimes.
Without solid proof,
we can ruin lives.
You're right.
We do rule the universe.
Can I ask you a question?
- Of course.
- Who's doing your merch?
Because I'm only netting two
dollars a hat and 50 cents a mug
and I'm getting completely
screwed on onesies.
Today's podcast has
a killer bombshell
about the killer
of the bombshell.
Grampa's motive for murder?
Money.
You see,
Vivienne Saint Charmaine
had a million‐dollar
life insurance policy.
Ooh, and the beneficiary
was her new boyfriend,
Abraham J. Simpson.
The moment she drowned,
Guilty Grampa
was swimming in cash.
Motive enough for you?
He did it for money.
No. No, no, no.
I don't care what it looks like.
I know Abe.
He would never
do something so horrible.
I did something so horrible.
I finally listened
to that dad‐gum podcast...
And it convinced me
I'm a killer.
Lock me up.
You're under arrest
for spoiling the ending!
I was only on episode two.
Oh, and for murder. Yeah.
Abraham Simpson,
as you have pled guilty
to the murder of
Vivienne Saint Charmaine,
I'm giving you life in prison.
And I'm giving your podcast
five stars
but no comment.
Who has the time?
Why did you confess, Dad?
A majority of the family
believes you're innocent.
But what that Kent Brockman said
about me was so darn convincing.
I began to suspect myself
around episode four.
Then by episode six,
it seemed like it was
that hot‐tempered deckhand.
But by episode nine,
I knew I'd done it,
just as sure as Shampoo Shuttle
is the future of hair care.
We can't give up hope.
I know Grampa's situation
looks bad,
with the insurance money,
what Mrs. Skinner heard, but...
And the confession
didn't help, either, but...
Take it, Mom.
But... But...
Oh, my God.
I'm not sure I have a but.
I'm not sure
I have a but either.
I think Grampa
might have done it.
He might have.
He totally might have.
Oh, no.
With all our
true crime training,
how could we have missed this?
We've become the people
that we hate most.
The family members too deluded
to see the obvious truth.
For the record,
I was willing to believe
he was the murderer
back when there was no evidence.
Just saying.
Come back later.
Were in the middle
of a terrible reckoning.
I have shocking medical news
that will blow
your father's case wide open.
Is there somewhere public
we can talk?
I don't know.
Welcome, listeners around the
world and our proud astronauts
downloading in the darkness
of space.
Tonight we both wrap up and drag
out the story of Guilty Grampa.
You'll get a chance to hear
from the hottest stars
of this heinous crime.
We love you,
someone else's tragedy!
And I'm thrilled to announce
the Guilty Grampa
streaming series,
starring the Skarsgard
that started it all, Stellan.
I only have a deal memo.
I haven't signed
the final paperwork.
Kent, there's something
you've got to know.
Something everyone's
got to know.
On the day of
Vivienne's disappearance,
she and Abe went in
for a couple's colonoscopy.
They each swallowed
a tiny IntestoPod,
which records internal data
and broadcasts a precise
GPS signal for 24 hours.
You can see here.
Once Vivienne fell off the boat,
she moved directly to shore.
She didn't sink. She swam.
Vivienne's signal
then traveled south
to a resort
in Zihuatanejo, Mexico,
where the guacamole
is made table‐side.
Vivienne is alive.
She faked her death.
Which means
Grampa didn't kill anyone.
But your podcast
convinced him that he did.
I wanted to say that part.
Well, that's...
that's all very interesting,
but it doesn't really fit
with the title of my podcast,
to say nothing of the merch.
Guilty Grampa! Guilty Grampa!
You sent me to jail.
You're no journalist.
You made us a murderer.
I have a confession to make.
Guilty Grampa is not guilty.
Oh, we all wish he did it.
Everyone here loves DNA swabs,
cell phone pings
and spatter analysis,
that fantasy that
the bad guys will be caught
and the police
will save the day.
Geez. That's a lot
to put on a guy.
From now on, I will report
with judicious restraint,
leaving behind
sensational revelations
in favor of painstakingly
accumulated uncertainties.
And I know you will all
come along with me
on this slow, measured ride.
And with that
out‐of‐touch statement,
Kent Brockman bid
a big fat farewell
to his relevancy.
Come on, Dad, cheer up.
You're an innocent man.
Or so you'd have us believe.
I thought Vivienne loved me,
but she played me for a sap.
Why'd you set me up, baby?
Well, if it makes you
feel any better,
I never believed she liked you
for one second.
Well, I did.
I thought she was gonna be
the last love of my life.
Hi, Abe.
What the...
Vivienne. Why'd you set me up?
We set you up.
You weren't supposed to confess.
You were supposed
to meet me in Mexico
with the insurance money.
- That was the plan.
- What plan?
The plan where I faked my death
and waited for you
to meet me in Mexico
with the insurance money.
That's why I yelled,
Abe, don't... forget the plan,
- as I was diving off the boat.
- What boat?
I love you,
you senile old sex machine.
Oh, what do we do now
that we're on the run?
We live out the rest of our days
in a place where no one
will ever notice us.
I'm putting
the space heater on ten.
Ooh, Abe.
Oh, you naughty boy.