CHORUS SINGS:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(exclaiming)
(school bell ringing)
(Barney belches)
(whistle blows)
(yells)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
Ooh!
(gunfire)
(tires screeching)
(horn honking, Grampa shouts)
D'oh!
(tires screeching)
(grunts)
♪ On the twelfth day
of Christmas ♪
♪ My true love gave to me ♪
♪ 12 Grampas grumbling ♪
-♪ 11 Barneys belching ♪
-(belches)
♪ Ten Lennys leaping ♪
♪ Nine Carls dancing ♪
♪ Eight Moes a-milking ♪
♪ Seven Selmas smoking ♪
♪ Six Flanders praying ♪
♪ Five golden Frinks ♪
♪ Four crawling nerds ♪
♪ Three-eyed fish ♪
♪ Two special Ralphs ♪
♪ And a Maggie in a snugglie. ♪
(Bart and Milhouse laughing)
So, what prank are you
going to lead off with?
The exploding pen.
Don't think
I've heard of it.
(groans)
Let the games begin.
(all laughing)
(laughing stops)
(laughter resumes)
(kids cheering)
(engine stalling)
(exclaims)
(kids cheering)
(Milhouse screams)
Simpson, that is a rebuilt
Yugoslavian engine.
There isn't even
a Yugoslavia anymore!
Bring it back at once!
You're the boss.
(crashing)
(laughing)
(groaning)
(grumbling):
Stupid punishment.
I hate hard work,
unless it's on pranks.
Shiny enough to see
Skinner's ugly face.
(Bart screams)
Come with me.
I'll grill your cheese yet, boy.
You weren't the first prankster
to destroy
the car I rent from mother,
and you won't be the last.
-"Rent"?
-Rent to own.
Just 35 more payments,
and it's halfway mine.
The point is, I've seen
hooligans like you come and go.
You're all just a big blur
of short pants
and sinister smiles.
Well, maybe so,
but I'm the best.
(chuckles)
The best of your era, maybe.
Are you saying
was worse than me?
(scoffs):
Way worse.
Anyway, think
no more about it.
You're dismissed.
Wait! Wait!
If there's someone worse,
I have to know who he is.
"He"?
It's a she?
Just kidding,
it's a guy.
(both laughing)
But let's not dwell
on a mysterious figure
from the past who was
your superior in every way.
Out you go.
Milhouse, there was
a guy who pulled
even bigger pranks
than me!
Wow! Imagine his sidekick.
(growling)
(inhales)
Man, if he lost
that giant inhaler,
he'd really be in trouble
with his parents.
MARGE:
Hmm.
KIDS (on tape):
♪ Tubs are for bath-time
and water is splashy fun ♪
♪ But there's one thing
that must never be done ♪
MARGE (singing along with tape):
♪ Poop in the tub ♪
♪ I'm not gonna
poop in the tub. ♪
MARGE:
Okay, everyone!
Snack time!
I've got milk and cookies.
-Hydroxeos?!
-(all gasping)
Marge, how could you?!
Those cookies are full of
high fructose corn syrup
and partially
hydrogenated oils.
Have you even read
the books I've read?
But this is
from the Kwik-E-Mart.
You and your husband
work there.
I would sooner pour
the polluted water of the Ganges
down their gullets than give
them this carton
of cow cancer
you call "milk."
Sorry. I didn't know.
Marge, until you start
serving healthy food,
the Midday Mommies are
pulling you from snack rotation.
(gasps)
SELMA:
Hydrogenated, ugh!
Mm-hmm.
A prankster that awesome
must've made
the school paper.
Hmm. Lis,
I just discovered
something weird.
Ten years ago,
this paper didn't publish
for two whole weeks.
Now, before the gap,
look at Skinner.
LISA:
Hmm.
And here he is
after the gap.
(Lisa groans)
Hmm, something must've
happened during those two weeks
to turn Skinner from cool to,
as you would say, "tool."
I know what happened:
the ultimate prank.
A prank that changed
Skinner from cool to tool.
Is that a backhoe
behind him?
Huh.
It is!
-Zoom in and enhance.
-Mm.
Willie!
He must know the answer.
Before you go,
can you distribute
these newspapers
throughout the school?
Well, I'd be a pretty
lousy brother if I didn't.
Willie, I know
you witnessed
the most awesome prank
since creation.
Can you tell me about it?
I'll nae speak to ye
of those dark times,
Bart Simpson.
But if there was
a more awesome dude than I,
I've got to know who he was,
what he did
and how many days
detention he got.
Something happened.
Something that changed
Skinner and you.
I haven't changed!
I've always been
Swim Teacher Willie
and I always will be!
See, oh...
All right, I'll tell ya.
Years ago,
this school had a pool.
I was an eager, young swim
coach, teaching American youth
the revolutionary
Aberdeen crawl.
It was a talented group,
and we were
all set to go
to the state finals.
I shaved and waxed
the boys myself.
Then came
the Night of the Wigglers.
What an awesome day!
BOY:
Yo, Skin-man!
Little help?
Right back at you, Jason.
-Stay in school.
-I will.
I am so stoked
for my daily swim.
(whistling)
Had he stopped whistlin'
and looked down,
the world wouldn't
have changed that night.
But he didn't, and it did.
Worms!
(muffled screams)
(muffled protests)
He spent all weekend in that
crypt full of creepy-crawlies.
Monday was
Teacher Development Day,
so Skinner wasn't rescued
till Tuesday morn.
And by then, he was the twisted
monster you see today.
Shut this pool down,
Groundskeeper Willie.
Willie. Bart.
Monster.
So my ass isn't the baddest
in the history
of this school!
Who did it, Willie?
His name is Andy Hamilton.
Andy Hamilton.
But whatever you do,
never tell me where
you learned his name,
or I'll kill
whoever told you!
Marge, what
are you doing?
This junk food has got to go.
It's full of chemicals,
trans fats
and hard-pore corn.
(gasps)
No!
Don't worry, my sweets!
I'll put out the fire!
Homie, no!
That topping
is a petroleum by-product!
(screams)
-(explosion)
-Ow!
"Andy Hamilton,
53 Hyperion Drive."
Bart, it's not
always a good idea
to meet your hero.
I once followed Santa home
from the department store,
and what I saw
wasn't pretty.
I can't live my life,
knowing there might be
someone better than me
at the one thing I'm good at.
(doorbell rings)
ANDY:
Entré and partay!
(grunts)
Krazy Glue!
Bart, you've been pranked!
Eh, it needs a topper.
And look, some idiot
left glue loosener
just lying around!
Ah! Here it comes.
Ay, caramba!
(groans)
Man, it is an honor
to meet the guy
who wormed Skinner.
You know, when I was your age,
we couldn't film
our pranks for YouTube.
It was local news or nothing.
Potato chip?
Hmm, wait a minute.
Are there spring snakes
in this can?
No, no-no, no-no, no-no.
Give me some credit.
It's a real snake.
-(snake hisses)
-Whoa!
Don't worry, it's defanged.
(snake hisses, Milhouse screams)
Although he can still
rub poison on you
with his gums.
I would really wash
that arm if I were you.
-Can I go home now?
-You should probably wait.
You're going to be
very sleepy for the
next few hours.
Isn't this the best
day of your life?
(shuddering)
So, you want to be
Springfield Elementary's
next Andy Hamilton?
Then you'll have to top
these awesome pranks.
The bear traps
in gym class.
The fire in
the drinking fountain.
And, of course,
the fake heart attack
-on an international flight.
-(chuckles)
They had to land
the plane in Nairobi!
Some chick missed
her own wedding!
(clicking)
I am impressed.
-(clicking)
-(shivering)
BART:
Oh, Andy has the perfect life.
All he does is reminisce
about his pranks.
And when his mom
gets home from work,
she makes him whatever
sandwich he wants.
(wan chuckle)
This Andy sounds
like kind of a loser.
How could someone so
much like me be a loser?
♪ Loser! ♪
Would a loser have showed me
how to put printer's ink
in a bottle of shampoo?
I've never felt so clean!
♪ A loo-oo-ooser! ♪
Yeah, but, uh, uh...
Dad, Lisa's making me see
things from both sides again!
HOMER: Lisa, I warned
you about that!
Shouldn't Bart have all
the information he needs
to make an informed decision?
Well,you...
Now you're doing
it to me!
Oh!
Mom, what would you do
if someone you cared
about might be a loser,
but they thought
they were awesome?
Are you talking
about your father?
That loser? No.
I'm talking about this guy who's
19 and never really grew up.
Well, when you care
about someone,
it's not out of line
to give them a gentle push
in the right direction.
Got it. Did you
wash those carrots?
(scoffs)
No.
(sighs)
You could have washed them
after you cut them,
but now they're
done for.
(sighing):
Oh!
Well, I don't like the looks
of this place, Marge.
I don't see any standees
for chips, standees for soda.
I don't see any standees at all!
From now on, our family
is eating healthy food
that looks bad on the shelf,
but good in our colon.
Why is that man
carrying a purse?
That's a reusable
grocery bag.
This store doesn't
use plastic bags,
because they end
up in the ocean
and upset jellyfish
mating rituals.
Stupid horny jellyfish--
neutering our dudes.
Hmm.
Almond butter,
soy milk,
non-soy dairy-based
soy sauce,
steel-cut spelt husk,
Chef Soy-ar-dee soy-based
spaghetti and soy balls,
free-range gluten,
ultra-vegan
invisible cheese...
You know, you don't have
to read the items aloud.
I know what they are.
Okay, that comes to $790.
800 bucks?!
Oh, wait. I didn't see
these blueberries.
$830.
Fine, but we're going
to a regular grocery store
next week.
A week?
Without preservatives,
this food won't last a day.
Look.
Oh!
(laughs)
Huh.
Well, I guess, uh,
they can go either way.
(horns honking)
(car crashing)
WIGGUM:
Oh, God!
Oh, I'm in
horrible pain!
(laughs)
(sighs)
Andy, man,
is this the way
you want to spend
the rest of your life?
Having to borrow spray paint
from a ten-year-old kid?
I told you, okay?
I'll pay you back when
I get my allowance.
I mean, not this one,
but the one after next.
Oh, God,
you're right.
Look, I think
I can get you a job.
Krusty owes me a favor
after I perjured myself for him
during a deposition.
You would get me a job?
Thank you, man.
Um, I would keep that on
for the interview.
(horn honking)
Hey, hey, if it isn't
my old friend... you!
Krusty, I need a favor.
For you kid, anything,
anything at all!
Although I won't
read screenplays.
That's for your protection.
Oh, and you can't ride
on my private jet.
And I won't give a struggling
young comic his first chance,
I won't give a broken-down hack
his last chance,
I won't buy you kids booze.
The judge was very clear
on that.
Now, what can I do for you?
Oh, and I don't sign footballs
unless you're dying,
and it reverts back to me after
six months if you're not dead.
(horn honks)
As my new second assistant,
you've got to drive me
from my office to the stage,
and if you see anybody
I've screwed over on the way,
avoid them!
Whoa! Ex-wife!
Former writing partner!
Bookie!
Dog I abandoned!
A.A. sponsor!
Love child!
-Tiddly.
-Wink.
Tiddly.
Wink. Didn't Andy
start work today?
Yes. Tiddly.
Then why is he standing
in our driveway?
Wink.
You're supposed
to be at work!
I tried, man, but he was, like,
"Do this thing."
And I'm, like, "Why, dude?"
And he's, like, "I'm your boss!"
And I'm, like, "I quit."
Then you're, like, "You're
supposed to be at work, man."
Then I'm, like, "What?"
You quit after one day?
Yeah.
But today wasn't
a total loss.
On the way home,
I got this--
an ice cube with
a fly in it.
If that was in your drink,
you'd be, like,
"I'm not drinking that!"
I stuck my neck out for you,
and you screwed it up!
(bicycle bell dings twice)
We're not losers!
No, you two
are winners.
Big winners.
When I grow up,
I want to marry a big
winner like you guys.
Shut up!
♪ Doggies and kitties
don't last forever ♪
♪ But they do a lot better
than fish! ♪
♪ Flush, flush, fish,
fish, fish, flush... ♪
It's healthy
snack time!
Is it?
We've got sulfite-free
grape juice
and homemade, organic,
non-gluten,
fair-trade zucchini cupcakes!
-Oh!
They don't rise by themselves,
so I was up all night
blowing air bubbles into them
with a straw.
Mmm! Delicious!
What percent milk fat
unsalted butter did you use
to grease the cupcake tray?
None percent.
I used a nonstick pan.
(all retching)
Don't you know that nonstick
pans are made with P.F.O.A.s?
Oh, boy, here it comes.
There is only one thing more
dangerous than P.F.O.A.s, Marge.
Plastics made with B.P.A.s.
Never, ever let your child near
any product with the number...
Seven!
Good Lord,
they've been sucking seven! Oh!
(siren blaring)
(groans)
All right, Andy.
It was not easy
to get your job back.
You did me a solid, man.
And I promise you,
I will not leave this job
unless I flake
or it becomes bogus.
No, that's not
good enough.
I want you to shake my hand
as a fellow prankster
and swear you will
try your best.
-Psych!
We have a deal.
(humming)
Marge?
Sorry I'm late.
I was working overtime,
so we'd have extra money
to buy fruit salad.
-Honey, what are you doing?
-Hmm?
Nothing!
(swallows) Nothing!
It's okay.
You can tell me.
I found your stash.
(gasps)
You found the precious!
I know, I know.
I've eaten
your trans fats,
your red dye number two.
Even this!
Oh, Marge, I'm seeing
a brand-new
side of you-- me.
(Homer and Marge laughing)
More Lard Glug, my sweet?
I never want to stop.
Did you know
that Lard Glug
contains neither
lard nor glug?
From now on,
we'll only make
the kids eat healthy.
I can't believe
Andy's lasted a week.
Yeah, to congratulate him,
I got him the most
grown-up thing I could
think of: a Caesar salad.
Excuse me, I'm looking
for Stage 6.
I've got a delivery
for a Mr. Andy Hamilton.
-Right over there.
-Oh, thank you.
(gasps)
(bell ringing)
Louie, have you
seen Andy?
I think he's gonna
ruin the show!
Eh, he's about
20 seasons too late.
(laughing)
(coughing)
(gasps)
(drumroll)
Now, to dive in this pool
of clear, blue water.
(gasps)
(Krusty yelps)
Put me down!
You're ruining the bit!
No! I won't see you end up
like Skinner,
twisted and deranged.
Watch the Krusty Show,
they tell me.
You'll forget your troubles,
Uh, how much
do you weigh?
Oh, 180, maybe 190.
Plus I'm wearing about 30
pounds of pancake makeup
and I'm always packing heat.
Plus the owner's manual
for my Cadillac.
(straining)
(screaming)
(gasping)
I wanted warm water,
not worm water.
(audience laughing)
What's going on?
Krusty needed a bit.
And I got a great one.
Thanks to my new
head writer, Andy Hamilton.
(Krusty laughs)
Bart, thank you for believing
I could grow up.
My pranking days
are over, for good.
What's gotten into you, man?
Andrew, I wanted
to show you something
in the make-out room--
uh, makeup room.
I'll be right there
in a minute, babe.
Looks like I just bought
some property on Boner Way.
So now Andy's a TV writer.
Loser.
♪ Loser, loser. ♪
Loser!
Shh!
Enhanced by Fotokem