♪ The Simpsons ♪
-(chalk screeches)
-(bell ringing)
(work whistle blowing)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(tires screeching)
(car horn honks)
-Aah!
-(tires screeching)
Hey, you punk, you...
(humming "We Gather Together")
♪♪ ("Washington Post March"
playing on TV )
(muffled screaming )
Bart! Stop fighting
with your sister!
-She took my glue.
-It's not yours, Bart.
This is family glue.
Stop it, you two.
This is Thanksgiving, so glue friendly,
or I'll take your glue away and then
no one will have any glue to glue with!
Dad, this isn't about glue.
It's about territoriality.
He only wants the glue
because I'm using it.
-Oh, yeah? Prove it.
-Here.
Hey man, I don't want
your stupid glue.
TV ANNOUNCER: Uh-oh, here comes
our friend, Bullwinkle J. Moose.
Bullwinkle's antlers
sprung a leak.
Uh-oh, looks like ol' Bullwinkle's
kind of got a taste of his own medicine.
-He certainly did, Bill.
-Wait.
Wait, what did--
Did what I say make sense?
Well, no,
not really, Bill.
Boy, now I know how
the pilgrims felt.
What are you
talking about, Bill?
Who the hell is that?
-Bullwinkle.
-Who?
Wait a minute.
Who's that?
Underdog.
Don't you know anything?
I know it wouldn't hurt 'em
to use some cartoons made
in the last 50 years.
Son, this is a tradition.
You start building a balloon
for every flash in the pan
cartoon character
you'll turn the parade
into a farce.
Maggie, I'm about to unveil
my centerpiece to the family.
It's a tribute to the trailblazing women
who made our country great.
See? There's Georgia O'Keeffe,
Susan B. Anthony.
And this is
Marjory Stoneman Douglas.
I'm sure you haven't
heard of her.
But she worked her whole life to
preserve the Florida Everglades.
As one of the Simpson women,
would you like to contribute
something to it?
Oh, thank you.
Honey, please,
you're in the way.
Can't I help you, Mom?
Well, Okay.
Let's see. Can you
do the cranberry sauce?
Yeah! Where is it?
The can is in the cupboard
on the bottom shelf.
-Here?
-No, no, no. The other shelf.
Oh! Got it. Now what?
-Open the can.
-No problemo.
-Where's the can opener?
-It's in the second drawer
from the right.
No, no, no, no.
The other one.
Oh, I got you.
It's broken, Mom.
Mom, it's broken.
♪ Mom, it's broken,
Mom, it's broken ♪
I don't think that
it's broken, honey.
Here, let me try.
There you go.
(slurping)
Ah, cranberry sauce,
a la Bart.
MARGE: Just stick it in the refrigerator
when you're done, Bart.
Bart?
(sighs)
See, Maggie,
those silver and blue guys
are the Dallas Cowboys.
They're Daddy's favorite team,
and he wants them to lose
by less than five and a half
points. Understand?
SPORTSCASTER: Kogen's got
Wolidarsky open way down field.
And it's complete!
Ooh, what a hit.
SPORTSCASTER #2:
Oh yeah, he's out cold, Gill.
GILL: Yes sir. Looks like
they'll be feeding him
Thanksgiving dinner
through a tube.
SPORTSCASTER #2: Heh-heh.
If they can fit a turkey in there--
GILL:
Get on with it.
Homer, shouldn't you go
pick up Grampa?
Half time, Marge,
half time.
-(knock on door)
-SELMA: Ding-dong. Here comes the cavalry.
-D'oh!
-Homer, you promised
to be nice to my sisters.
I know. I will.
-You brought food.
-Just a few things.
Swedish meatballs.
Mm-hmm.
And my trout almondine.
You knew that
I was cooking a turkey.
-Which is fine.
-More power to you.
It's just that some people find
your turkey a little dry.
Mm-hmm. And if they want
an option, they'll have it.
-(groans)
-Hi, Patty. Mwah!
Hi, Selma. Mwah.
Well, it's good to see you.
Well, got to pick up
my old man. Bye.
So insincere.
I don't know how
she puts up with him.
(angrily imitating
Selma and Patty)
(radio stations tuning)
ANNOUNCER: And now, get set
for our fabulous half time show
featuring the well-groomed
young go-getters
of Hooray For Everything.
Oh, I love those kids.
They got such
a great attitude.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Hooray For Everything
invites you to join them
in a salute to the greatest
hemisphere on Earth.
The Western Hemisphere.
The dancingest hemisphere
of all.
♪ Do da do da do da da ♪
♪ Do da do da
do da da ♪
♪ Dancin', dancin', dancin' ♪
♪ Do da do da do da da... ♪
Now, before we sit down
to our delicious turkey puree,
I have some happy news.
The following people have relatives
who wish they could be here today:
Antonowski, Conroy, Falcone,
Martin, Thorson and Walsh.
(beeps)
Oh, and Mrs. Spencer.
You too.
Oh, I knew they
wouldn't forget me.
Come on, Dad,
let's get outta here.
Calm down, boy.
What's your hurry?
-This place is depressing.
-Hey, I live here!
Oh! Well, I'm sure it's a blast
once you get used to it. Let's go.
Mom, you made it.
-How are you?
-I have laryngitis.
It hurts to talk,
so I'll just say one thing.
You never do anything right.
♪ Do da do da do da da ♪
♪ Do da do da
do da da ♪
♪ Dancin',
dancin', dancin'! ♪
-MAN: Thank you!
-WOMAN: You're super!
MAN:
Be good to each other!
ANNOUNCER: In the Silver Dome,
now ablaze with flashbulbs
as Hooray For Everything
leaves the field.
Of course, a stadium's
much too big
for flash pictures to work,
but nobody seems to care.
That's no way to lay a fire.
Where's your kindling?
This thing's going
to be blowing any time now.
-Even a caveman could start a fire.
-D'oh!
MARGE: Dinner! Dinnertime,
everybody! Dinner!
The hell with this.
Okay, Lisa, we're ready
for your centerpiece.
(gasps)
Lisa, my goodness.
That's very impressive.
Holy moly!
That's the biggest...
one of those I ever saw.
Hmm. I always said
she was gifted.
Definitely from our side
of the family, right, Mom?
Leave me alone.
How long did that
take you, honey?
I couldn't tell you
how many hours.
It was a labor of love.
It's my homage
to some American heroes
who may not have fought in any wars
but who nevertheless--
(singing fanfare )
Speaking of heroes,
here's mine-- Tom Turkey.
-(chuckling)
-(electric knife whirrs)
-Unh. Yikes, what is that?
-It's the centerpiece, Bart.
Well, it's taking up
valuable real estate.
-Hey, Bart, stop it!
-Move it or lose it, Toots.
-Mom!
-Now just a minute.
I'm sure there's room for both.
(straining)
Bart, you're wrecking it!
Let go!
I worked forever on this!
Ooh.
(screaming)
-Hey, that got her going.
-Bitchin'.
Bart!
You don't even care!
(crying)
-(door slams)
-All right, Bart,
That's it!
Go to your room! Now!
Okay. I'll take some
white meat and stuffing to go.
And send up the pumpkin pie
in about 20 minutes.
-I said, now!
-Mom, do I have to?
Yes, you do.
I hope you're happy, Bart!
You've ruined Thanksgiving!
BART: I didn't ruin
Thanksgiving, she did. (mutters)
I always get blamed
for everything.
And Lord, we're especially
thankful for nuclear power--
the cleanest, safest
energy source there is
except for solar,
which is just a pipe dream.
Anyway, we'd like to thank you
for the occasional moments
of peace and love
our family's experienced.
Well, not today.
Well, you saw what happened.
Oh, Lord, be honest.
Are we the most pathetic family
in the universe or what?
ALL: Amen.
Worst prayer yet.
(saxophone playing)
D'oh!
Why don't I go talk
to the children?
Don't worry.
Marge'll fix everything.
(saxophone continues)
Honey, your food
is getting cold.
(sniffling)
That's all right.
Lisa, I'm very sorry
about what happened.
Mom, I poured my heart
into that centerpiece.
Things like that
always happen in this family.
I've noticed that too.
Well, when you feel
like coming down,
-we'll be there.
-(keys clacking)
(playing saxophone)
Bart, you can
come down to dinner
as soon as you're ready
to apologize to your sister,
and it's going to be a real
apology in front of everybody,
and you have to mean it.
Apologize? For what?
Clearing the table?
Having a sense of humor?
They think they can starve
an apology out of me? Ha!
Uh-oh.
I mean... good!
(grunting)
HOMER: Hey,
what are you doing?
No! Drop that drumstick.
-Bad dog.
-(dog snarling)
Bad Santa's Little Helper.
Come on, give me that.
Give-- Give me that. D'oh!
Okay, out you go!
-(whimpering)
-Hey, boy, come here.
You're a good dog.
Come on.
We don't need them to
get a Thanksgiving dinner.
(barking)
(dog barks)
Wow! Swanky!
Mmm, delicious.
Smithers, every year
you outstrip yourself
in succulence.
Oh, thank you, sir.
Oh! Would you like
some candied yams?
Oh, no, I couldn't eat
another bite.
Dispose of all this.
I did however,
save room for your
special pumpkin pie.
It's cooling
on the windowsill, sir.
Mmm.
Stay here, boy.
(whimpering)
-(alarm beeping)
-Uh-oh.
(alarm sounding)
-(camera whirring)
-(alarm beeping)
Mr. Burns,
this is base command.
The intruder appears
to be a young male, age 9 to 11.
Release the hounds.
(barking, snarling)
(gasps)
Ahh!
(panicked grunting)
"I saw the best meals
of my generation
"destroyed by the madness
of my brother,
"my soul carved in slices
by spiky-haired demons."
(whimpering)
Don't worry, boy.
We'll get some grub,
even if we have
to pay for it.
-(stomach growling)
-(dog growling)
(birds chirping)
-(machine gun fire)
-(woman screaming)
Cool! The wrong side
of the tracks!
-(gunshots)
-(siren wailing)
(helicopter whirring overhead)
(police chatter on radio)
Twelve bucks?
Hey, I can bleed.
WOMAN: Hey, you've got
to be 18 to sell your blood.
Let's see some I.D.
BART:
Here you go, dollface.
-WOMAN: Okay, Homer, just relax.
-BART: Ow!
At the risk of
losing my voice,
let me just say
one more thing.
I'm sorry I came.
When is that boy
going to apologize?
He sure is stubborn.
Homer was never stubborn.
He always folded instantly
over anything.
It was as if he had
no will of his own.
Isn't that true, Homer?
Yes, Dad.
Twelve bucks and a free cookie.
What a country.
Cute little guy.
He's starting
to come around.
You look a little pale, son.
We better get you
some food.
Here we are.
(cheerful music playing)
All right!
Twelve big ones
and free grub to boot.
Viva, skid row!
Hey! It's that anchor dude
from Channel Six.
Oh, yeah.
He's doing one of those
"Be thankful
for what you got" stories.
ANCHOR: Oh, we have lots
of names for these people--
bums, deadbeats, losers,
scums of the Earth.
We'd like to sweep
these people into the gutter,
or, if they're already
in the gutter,
to some other
out-of-the-way place.
Oh, we have our reasons.
They're depressing.
They wear ragged clothes.
They're "crazy."
-They smell bad.
-Hey, listen, man...
Wait. I'm going somewhere
with this.
So, every year on one lone,
conscience-salving day
we toss these people a bone--
a turkey bone--
and that's supposed
to make it all better.
No, you won't find
Freddy the Freeloader
or Emmett Kelly
or even Charlie Chaplin's
beloved Little Tramp
down here...
Pompous, blow-dried
college boy.
You know, his girlfriend
is the weather lady.
You don't say?
Everyone, Lisa wants to
read us a poem she's written.
-Sounds interesting.
-Okay.
"Howl of the Unappreciated"
by Lisa Simpson. Ahem.
I saw the best meal...
-(gasping) It's Bart!
-What show is this?
KENT: And how long have you
been on the streets?
-Going on five years, Kent.
-Hmm.
KENT: Son, your family
may be watching.
Is there anything
you'd like to say to them?
Yes, there is, Kent.
Ha-ha! I didn't apologize!
Oh, no!
My sweet, little Bart.
Hello, operator?
Give me the number for 911.
Hey, thanks for your help,
fellas.
This reporter smells
another local Emmy.
Yeah, we're rooting
for you, guy.
Hey, you got someplace
to sleep tonight, Bart?
Yeah, there's this family
I kinda hang out with.
-Sounds pretty sweet.
-Yeah, I guess it is.
See you at Christmas.
Listen, guys,
I was thinking, um,
unless you feel weird about
taking money from a kid
I thought maybe...
I wouldn't feel weird,
would you?
No, I'm comfortable
with it.
Will you forget
the report?
He's down at
the rescue mission.
Nah, we checked.
He's long gone.
Can you think of any reason
he might have run away?
Anything at all?
Well, we did
kind of yell at him
and sent him to his room
and tried to force him
to apologize to his sister.
-Uh-huh.
-MARGE: And...
I said
he ruined Thanksgiving.
Oh, I see.
Best Thanksgiving ever,
eh, boy?
Good-bye.
Sorry. I'm sure Bart
will be back.
I would say something
comforting,
but, you know, my voice.
Let's go! If I'm not back
at the home by nine,
they declare me
legally dead
and collect my insurance.
Homer, this is a terrible thing
that's happened.
but we can't blame
ourselves.
-We can and will.
-Children need discipline.
You can ask any syndicated
advice columnist.
Marge, are we ever
gonna see him again?
Hmm, should I or shouldn't I?
Hey everybody, I'm home.
Bart, you're home!
Mwah! Mwah! Mwah!
Oh, my special little guy.
Mwah!
We were so worried.
Oh, it's great
to have you back, boy.
We were afraid
we'd lost you.
Welcome back, Bart.
I'm sorry we had
such a terrible fight.
Bart, isn't there something
you'd like to say
to your sister?
Okay. I'm sorry too.
No, no, no,
that won't do at all.
Yeah, boy. Get down on your knees
and beg for forgiveness!
Yeah, beg me, Bart.
Beg me!
Lisa, I beg of you,
please, forgive me.
(evil laughter)
MARGE: Now we can blame him
for everything!
-It's your fault I'm bald!
-I'm sorry.
-It's your fault I'm old!
-It's your fault I can't talk!
-I'm sorry.
It's your fault America
has lost its way.
-I'm sorry.
-It's all your fault!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, all right--
sorry I came back here.
Aha!
(grunting)
Whoa! My wiffle balls!
My frisbees!
My water rockets!
(gasps)
I've hit the jackpot!
A sell-out crowd
at the Super Bowl,
Simpson down by six
with two seconds left.
Simpson fades back.
He's got Simpson in the open.
Touchdown Simpson!
(mimics stadium cheers)
The boy nobody wanted
just won the Super Bowl!
(imitating crowd cheering )
Dear log, my brother
is still missing
and maybe it's my fault
because I failed
to take his abuse
with good humor.
I miss him so much already
that I don't know...
(Lisa sobbing)
(whispering)
Hey, Lise. Lisa.
It's me, Bart.
(sniffles)
Bart, where are you?
Shh. I'm on the roof.
(grunting)
Bart, what are you
doing up here?
Everybody's worried.
-Really? Did they cry?
-Yes.
Whoa, bull's-eye.
Bart, why did you burn
my centerpiece?
Aw, come on.
Was it because you hate me
-or because you're bad?
-I don't know.
I don't know why I did it.
I don't know why I enjoyed it.
And I don't know why
I'll do it again.
-Just tell me you're sorry.
-Why should I?
Bart, the only reason
to apologize
is if you look deep down
inside yourself
and you find a spot.
Something you wish
wasn't there.
Because you feel bad you
hurt your sister's feelings.
-Leave me alone.
-Just look!
Okay, okay.
(muttering)
Looking for the spot.
Still checking.
This is so stupid.
I'm not going
to find anything.
Just because I wrecked something
she worked really hard on
and I made her cr--
Uh-oh.
I'm sorry, Lisa.
Apology accepted.
You know, Marge,
we're great parents.
Oh Lord, on this blessed day,
we thank thee
for giving our family
one more crack at togetherness.
ALL: Amen.
(all munching, slurping)
(munching, slurping continue)
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.