CHOIR:
♪The Simpsons♪
Hello, darkness.
(school bell ringing)
BARNEY:
Morning!
(whistle blows)
(yells)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
(grunts)
-(explosion)
-Ha! Ha!
MOE: Springfield, U.S.A.
A town where everyone's
got a story.
I moved here
'cause on a calculator,
the zip code spells "boobs."
It's a town filled with winners
and Skinners.
Why couldn't you have died
instead of the car?
MOE:
But everybody comes to Moe's.
(people chattering)
(Homer laughing,
crowd cheering)
(Barney snarling)
(crowd exclaims)
(Lenny shouting)
(Barney snarling)
MOE: Moe's Tavern,
presided over by Moe Szyslak--
handsome, suave, debonair.
(sneezes)
Hey, get the camera off of me.
I'm narrating here.
MOE:
Anyway, here's my little tale.
As the town's bartender,
I know everyone's problems.
And everyone's got problems,
especially the married ones.
Be they Bible-thumper...
Timothy, I finished
saying my prayers.
Not now, Helen.
Today's the day
I paint moustaches
on my Pullman porters.
Mmm...
MOE:
...or jerky jockey.
♪ Go to sleep, sleepy head ♪
♪ May a cloud be your... ♪
Where did we
get this dreck?
Oof. Typical.
Here's the kind of lullaby
my sweet mother sang to me.
(woman singing loudly in Hindu,
babies crying)
Oh!
Why do you always change it
to Sanskrit 93.7: The Dot?
I like Rajiv, Rubaba
and Big Brahmin in the morning!
No caste is safe
from their merry japes!
Having a Ma-hot-ma or Man-not-ma
contest is not a jape.
It is sexist sacrilege!
I hate that channel!
But you have so much
in common with them--
nonstop chatter
during drive time!
Take it back.
I take it back.
MOE: And now
you're probably wondering,
what's this all building to?
It's a timeless tale of...
Hello!
Are you seein'
what I'm seein' here? Ooh!
This omniscient point of view
has got
some surprising bonuses!
Yeah.
Aw. No! No! No! Oh!
What the hell
was I talking about?
Oh, yeah. It was just
before Mother's Day.
I destroyed my body
to give birth to you?!
(sentimental tune plays)
Kids, this Mother's Day,
why don't you give your mom
what she really wants:
a break from you?
Have your dads
take all you annoying kids
on a Krusty Krustival Kruiseline
Day-Kruise
to historic Weasel Island,
one of America's
ten roundest islands.
Explore a dark,
dark weasel cave.
Tour the historic
Civil War prison,
and picnic where the bodies
were once stacked
like cordwood.
Plus some kind
of amusement park!
ANNOUNCER:
Warning: you may not be amused.
You guys should
go on that cruise.
You'll have
a great time,
and you kids can spend the day
getting to know your father.
I like beer, hot dogs, and
long blackouts on the beach.
And I can spend my Mother's Day
taking care of something
I've been putting off
for a long time.
Cleaning the gutters?
That's something
you've been putting off.
(gasps)
Cartoons! Everybody, be quiet!
(ragtime piano playing)
(moaning)
♪ ♪
(laughter)
So, Marge,
what were we talking about?
(sighs)
Why do I waste
my breath?
Sorry, honey.
I wasn't listening,
and I won't
be listening now.
Hey, Homer,
what do you think Mom meant by
"taking care
of something"?
Son, I'm a bit of an expert
on the female gender,
and I can tell you, women don't
mean anything by anything.
Dad, that's a dangerous attitude
for you to take
towards your wife.
I hear what you're saying, Lisa.
(whispers loudly):
Nothing.
Into the playpen, sweetie.
And if you get hungry,
there's lobster.
(boat horn blows)
(bicycle bell dings)
Special delivery letter
for Misters Simpson, Lovejoy
and Nahasapeemapetilon.
(grunts)
(yells)
APU:
It's going to drop.
What?
It's from Moe.
MOE:
"Dear friends, I have some news
that is doubly sad.
First off,
I am leaving town forever.
And my going away present?
One of your wives
is running off with me."
One of our wives is
leaving us for Moe?!
Moe's leaving town?!
MOE:
"Perhaps I should've told you
in person,
but there's no easy way
to say goodbye forever.
So I'll say it the hardest way
I can: in Mandarin Chinese.
Zai jian yong yuan!"
(all gasp)
MOE:
And now, as our teakettle
starts to toot,
I'm gonna take a little break.
(clears throat):
Boy, this voice-over thing
is killin' me.
Whatever that Don Pardo
gets paid, it ain't enough.
DON PARDO:
I make more
than you can possibly imagine.
And I'm making it right now.
-(gull screeches)
-MOE: Where are you?
Moe is running off
with one of our wives?!
Well,
the stationery's legit.
It's got the Moe watermark.
So I guess
the question is,
which one of our wives
got Moe-jacked?
Well, I will end
this suspense
with a simple cellular
phone call to Manjula.
(beep)
-No signal?!
-No battery?!
-I got Marge!
-MARGE (staticky):
Homer?
Marge, are you running off
with Moe?
Homer? I'm... you!
You're losing me,
or you're leaving me?!
We're breaking up!
-(phone beeps)
-Aw, damn it!
(grunts)
Homer?
Ooh, can't talk.
Must text.
Marge, have you left me for...?
(anguished moan)
We needed that pole
to hook the dock.
(people screaming)
(explosion)
Most of our cargo
is explosives.
(weasels chittering)
You rebel scum
make me sick.
This is sweet justice
for how you greybacks treated
our boys at Andersonville!
(grunting)
When there's cruelty involved,
Bart sure knows his history.
Well, if Moe were leaving
with one of our wives,
it wouldn't be my Helen.
We just started
a new jigsaw puzzle last week.
We're still on the edges.
Well, Marge and I don't have
any problems.
We never even fight anymore.
What?
When a woman is peaceful
and content,
that means all hell is about
to break loose.
Think back, Homer.
When did you first realize
Marge was checked out
like a Harry Potter book
at the public library?
Think back,
think back,
think back...
(rattling)
Not that far back.
Homer, my Mother's party's
starting any minute. Get busy.
Moe, my in-laws are coming.
I need something strong enough
that I forget I hate them,
but not so strong
that I tell them I love them.
Sorry, Homer, I ain't
serving no liquor.
Just O'Glums non-alcohol beer.
Marge, this is crazy!
This is my mother's
80th birthday party,
and you're not ruining it.
Oh, you'll have a good time.
I invited a friend for you.
-Knock-a-doodle-you!
-Flanders?!
Neighbor Marge
invited me over
to be the little angel
on your shoulder,
so you wouldn't listen
to the 400 devils on the other.
D'oh!
D'oh! D'oh! D'oh! D'oh!
♪ ♪
Hey, Chunky
with the Pants of Meatballs.
Take our picture.
All right.
I wasn't smiling!
What the...
I had something
in my teeth.
Why you...
My eyes were shut.
Lousy...
-My sweater's
on backwards!
-(groans)
He can't do
anything right.
Except setting off car alarms
with his big fat footsteps.
You take that back!
(Homer grunts and stomps,
car alarms sound)
(both laughing)
Go ugly up someone
else's house,
you penis-curling
she-devils!
Ah, you got it.
We're not staying
where we're not wanted.
Every time I
plan something
that means something to me,
you somehow mess it up.
(snapping)
I need some cash, man.
"You will lose all your money."
(scoffs)
We'll see about that.
(woman cackling)
One, please.
You had that scar
before you got on.
-What scar?
-Oh, you'll find out.
Oh, I like keeping, I like
keeping records of myself.
Oh. Ah, man, do I make the soup.
My goodness,
do I make the soup.
Oh, I'm doomed!
Now, we don't know
for sure it's your wife.
It could be yours.
Oh, no, sir.
My marriage is solid.
Manjula would never cheat on me
like I cheated on...
-Oh, boy.
-That's right.
Now, was there
ever a time
when your wife might
have found comfort
in Moe's hairy arms?
Think back, Apu.
Think back, Apu...
(Ralph yelps)
(thunder crashing)
May we use your restroom
to change our kids out
of their cricket uniforms?
We got caught in the rain
because someone wouldn't use
international short form rules.
All right, calm down there,
'Pu and She-Pu.
-You can use the
restroom.
-(sighs)
My one day off
and it is miserable.
This is my day
every day.
You see this?
I'm playing the world's
smallest sitar for you.
(thunder crashing)
One, two, three,
four, five, six...
(gasps, screams)
We are missing
a tuplet!
We must have left it
at that godforsaken pub!
How could you forget
your own child?
your own child?!
Oh, I can't believe
I married you.
What my grandfather saw
in your grandfather,
-I will never know.
-(phone beeps)
MOE:
Uh, hey, 'Pu.
I just want you to know that
I got one of your kids here.
This ain't a kidnapping thing,
but if you're in the mood
to give me a million dollars,
that's cool.
This should not be interpreted
by federal agents as a threat.
Once again, uh, no threat,
but will take the dough.
Well, one of us has to go
back to Moe's.
Maybe have a beer or two,
shoot a game of pool,
and if I win,
I have to play the challenger,
such are the customs
of billiards.
(tires squealing)
What a great father,
I say sarcastically!
If only that mark on your
forehead was an off button!
Hours later,
she returned--
smelling of beer
and pickled eggs.
I know no more.
Uh... I do.
You do?! Tell me!
I was there when your
wife got to Moe's,
being my usual
effervescent self.
(snoring)
-(giggling)
-(gargling)
Oh, thank you for saving
my precious...
...Gheet! (sighs)
Sounds like you had a rough day.
It's true.
My eyes have more bags
than the Darjeeling Limited.
(laughs)
Yeah, that's-that's
probably a good one.
Here, I got somethin'
that might cheer ya up.
I got this for women
that came to the bar,
and, uh, Low-Blow Boxing
for the guys.
My nards! My nards! My nards!
So, uh, would you
like to cut one?
I mean a rug.
Oh, God, I always say
the wrong thing.
♪ Red One, Konvict GaGa... ♪
You said you'd be
home by 7:00
to help with my
mother's birthday!
(Marge grunting, Homer groaning)
-Then what happened?
-I don't know.
(children moaning)
Teacup? How'd that get in there?
Question me,
you little rutabaga brain,
I'll take your eyeball
and make soup out of it.
Well, how can you be sure
your wife is not the putty
in the bartender's hands?
Yeah, Padre.
How innocuous
are your flashbacks?
Well, I, uh...
(ferry horn honking)
The ferry will be back
in ten minutes.
It'll take us home to
find out the truth.
-The truth.
-The roof.
(honking continues)
(car horns honking)
I'm still mad at you
from last night.
Today's the first,
which means it was last month,
which means you're
being ridiculous.
Hmm, I'm glad we never
argue like that.
Yes, to argue, you have to
actually talk to each other.
Way to bitch up the
conversation, Helen.
(grunts)
Oh, Tim.
As your spiritual
advisor,
I'm afraid you two have
a b-b-b-big problem.
Me and Helen?
Why, we're as happy
as Adam and Eve
before Eve munched us
all to hell.
Mm-mm-mmm.
I'm gonna let you in
on a little trick
they taught us in
Divinity School.
Now take a look at
Helen over there.
She seems happy as a
clam, am I right?
LOVEJOY:
Oh, happier.
Where a clam has only one
pearl, she has many.
Now, don't you
jive me, Tim.
Just take your thumb and
put it over her mouth.
(growling)
See?
Looks like that she-cano
is about to blow!
♪ Krakatoa, east of java ♪
♪ Never spewed
a hotter lava ♪
♪ Than a Mount Saint Helen
who's mad at you ♪
♪ Kilauea or you
will pay her... ♪
(both scatting)
Is the preacher here?
'Cause there's somethin'
I gotta get off of my chest.
Somethin' more suited
for the town gossip
than the minister's wife.
Do tell.
Uh... well,
there's this married woman
that I have feelings for.
And her husband don't realize
how upset she is with him.
Do I know her?
I'm, uh...
I'm sure you do.
Oh.
(giggles)
What's so damn funny?
I mean... (chuckles)
Oh.
That's right.
She touched his knee.
-His knee.
-LISA: Dad,
I'm gonna need some help
getting this off.
(Lisa grunting,
metallic squeaking)
Otto, you got to get us
back to town.
Oh, nobody told me
I had to drive the bus back.
(grunts)
I've mistimed some substances!
(metallic snapping)
Here it comes,
the moment of truth.
(gasps):
She's packing her bag.
So it is you,
Mr. Homer.
But let's be honest.
A woman her age
married to a man of--
how old are you, 65?
Thirty-nine.
Dear God, this day gets
more and more disturbing.
(Homer moaning)
(gasping)
Marge! No!
Stop packing your...
painting supplies?!
BART AND LISA:
Grandma?!
What do you think?
You're not leaving me?
My mother explained
that what happened at the
party wasn't your fault.
It's that Patty and Selma.
There's something evil
about them.
Did you know they smoked
when I was pregnant?
Oh, Marge,
you're not leaving with Moe
is the best thing
that never happened to me.
(Marge moans)
OTTO:
Okay, Reverend,
your place is next.
Actually, Milhouse
and I are next.
Huh. There's no suspense
at your place.
Even I've hooked up
with your old lady.
Sorry, kid.
You were my favorite uncle,
Uncle Otto.
Two tickets to Istanbul?
That's right, Tim.
I'm taking these bags,
and I'm walking out that door.
Meanwhile, you'll be
setting the alarm,
and then you'll join me
in the cab.
You're leaving... with me?
Would you rather
I bring someone else
on the world's most
romantic train?
Oh, Helen.
(moans)
Is that a train in your pocket
or are you just happy
to see me?
Both.
And so it is me.
(sad melody plays)
I feel the pain of
a thousand Squishee headaches.
My worst fears
are confirmed.
Apu, this man has come here
to convince me
to do something I never
thought I would do...
stay with you.
(gasps):
You mean you are
not leaving me for him?
(laughs)
Don't be ridiculous.
What am I,
blind and noseless?
Hey, hey,
I'm right here.
Believe me, I know.
Apu, our marriage
will never be easy.
But nothing worth
doing is ever easy.
It is true.
The tastiest ice cream
is the hardest to scoop.
But if you wrap something
warm around it...
Oh.
Very nice.
Well all's well that
ends well, huh?
Yes, except for...
why did you write
that horrible letter?!
When I saw how much trouble
your marriages were in...
...I knew I had to act fast.
I got Marge's mother
to go to Marge,
convinced Helen to ride
the rails of romance
with the padre,
then I bought some
roadside corn, ate it raw,
got a kernel in my teeth,
flossed with the corn silk,
and then I came over
to fix things with Manjula.
And I wrote that letter so
you three chumps would realize
that you have not been treatin'
your wives the way they deserve.
Think of it as
a wake-up call
from a man who ain't got
nothin' but a blow-up doll.
And even she left me.
Should not have used helium.
Moe, I don't know whether
to punch you or kiss you.
So I'm gonna do both.
-(grunts)
-(groans)
Yeck.
MOE:
So all you mugs out there,
be sure you don't take
for granted the woman you love.
Oh, and it's Mother's Day,
so call your ma.
Take her down to the diner
at the department store there.
Get her a roast beef on rye.
Oh, and make sure she gets
a fruit cup on the side.
She's worth it.
("I'll Always Love My Mama"
by The Intruders playing)
♪ I'll always love my mama ♪
♪ She's my favorite girl ♪
♪ She brought me
in this world ♪
♪ Sometimes I feel so bad ♪
♪ When I think of all the things
I used to do ♪
♪ How Mama used to clean
somebody else's house ♪
♪ Just to buy me
a new pair of shoes ♪
♪ I never understood how Mama
made it through the week ♪
♪ When she never ever got
a good night's sleep ♪
♪ Talking about Mama ♪
♪ Oh, she's one of a kind ♪
♪ You've got yours
and I've got mine ♪
♪ Talking about Mama ♪
♪ My Mama ♪
♪ Hey, Mama,
my heart belongs to you, yeah ♪
♪ I'll always love my mama,
she's my favorite girl. ♪
(people talking)
Shh!
Enhanced by Fotokem