Yes, another glorious Sunday.
Scone for my muffin?
And for you,
five breakfast burritos.
Ah, the Voltron.
Our lives are
in perfect balance.
Oh, it is just last‐second
birthday gift shoppers.
Ignore them.
I know you're in there,
you lazy dork.
I can smell the burritos!
Four. No! Five!
They can't be closed.
We're booked solid
with birthday parties today,
and we have no presents.
Don't worry, I got this.
Auto Trader for the girls.
Adult Escort Express
for the boys.
Kids are adults, right?
Fine, fine, whatever.
Let's just go.
Let us wander as aimlessly
as the plots
of the four
upcoming Avatar sequels...
I can only assume.
I love your contempt
for things that don't matter.
Do you hear that?
Ah, silence.
Come on, let's go.
Time to go
to Milhouse's puppy party.
If we go late,
you'll get a crappy dog.
That's it, I'm coming in.
Ow! No! Ow! No!
That's where I had my surgery!
Miyazaki marathon with
chilled lobster spring rolls.
Oh, crap!
I just realized
I haven't eaten anything all day.
They're out of pizza,
but I built you a slice
out of trash scraps.
Well, hide me behind your coat
while I eat it.
I need to be around grown‐ups.
Excuse me.
You just passed my street.
Who the hell are you?
Leland Huebner III.
Go back and get Bart.
Hold on,
this one seems all right.
A little stuck up,
but all right.
Thanks so much for the
last‐minute dinner invitation.
There never was any dinner.
You fell for a scam.
You're babysitting.
No money.
Adults!
Pull over!
Wow, Moe, you really gussy up
the place for trivia night.
Hey, where are the regulars?
Ah, keg storage.
Hey! We're thirsty!
Thank you.
I've always wanted to do
a trivia.
Who knows what I might know?
Please, join our team.
But they're noobs.
Even the humble noob has a place
in the seasons of trivia.
Once again
I am in awe of your decency.
All right, all right, weirdos.
I want to welcome you dorks
to trivia night.
Now, shut your nerd faces
for the first question.
List the four players
with the most fighting penalties
in NHL history.
Oh, sports.
The very lowest genus
of trivium.
Let's see. Tie Domi,
Dave "Tiger" Williams,
Dave "The Hammer" Schultz,
and, of course,
Stu "The Grim Reaper"
Grimson. Duh.
All right, next category,
20th Century Vacuum Cleaners.
Just give me the pencil.
The mascot
for this Boston‐based...
Cuppy, the Dunkin' Donuts
coffee cup.
This English
prog rock supergroup
scored a hit
with 1970's Lucky Man.
Emerson!
Lake!
And!
Palmer!
Okay, okay.
And the winning team is...
Han Shot First.
What does that mean?
- Is that dirty?
- It's from Star Wars.
I never heard of it.
Is it dirty?
Who cares, who cares.
Here's your trophy.
To fat guys with hot wives.
This one's for you, Kevin James.
Take a poncho.
I always carry extras in case
Homer eats anything slurpable.
That's so clever.
What other big‐and‐tall
wife hacks do you have?
Oh, I've got all kinds of tricks
for fat‐proofing your house.
Come over sometime
and I'll show you.
My chashu!
See? Here I've welded
high‐tensile steel
under the cushions
to reduce sofa‐sag.
I've lost a lot of furniture
to chubby hubby couch droop.
Oh, Maggie's up.
Can you go sit with her
while I warm a bottle?
Oh, but I don't know much
about babies.
Except how to dress like one.
All is well.
Silence.
You are loved!
Look how much she likes you.
You're a natural.
I just remembered something
I must tell my husband.
Impregnate me at once!
But you never wanted children.
You always said our marriage
is perfect as it is.
I mean, can you imagine a child
playing in this room?
It's full of toys.
Yes, well, but yeah,
but it's selfish
to bring a new life into a world
with diminishing resources.
The planet is running out
of watchable IP!
They say by 2028
all we will have left
is the General Mills
Cinematic Universe
starring Hamburger Helper.
If I can't convince you,
maybe she can.
Greta, the sexy Gremlin
from the underappreciated
but‐still‐terrible Gremlins 2.
I know this is
your ultimate fantasy.
It's time to feed your desires
after midnight.
I must resist.
My will is stronger
than The Great Resisto,
a hero I am inventing
as I reference him.
My darling, my darling,
I am sorry.
But I have spent every working
hour of my life around children,
and one thing
I know for certain.
I don't want any.
And... banked.
I want a baby.
I don't want a baby!
Kumiko's baby fever is
out of control.
Look at all these comments
she left.
It goes really quick
from smiley face
to without a baby,
all is horror.
Well, I think Comic Book Guy
should have kids.
Oh, that's so sweet.
'Cause screw that jerk!
Thinks his childless life
is so great just because it is.
Wakes up whenever he wants.
Doesn't have to lug car seats
onto the plane.
He can store poison in the
fridge so it's nice and cold.
And don't get me started
on their sex life.
They can do it anywhere.
Kitchen floor, bathroom floor,
on the microwave.
Set that baby on popcorn.
Pop! Pop! Pop!
So... we'll help them?
Anything
to destroy their paradise.
Remember, it's up to you two
to make children seem
like a blessing.
Got it. And when she pops out
that kid, we each get a 20.
- Or equivalent gift card.
- That's the stuff.
Oh, look,
it's our trivia buddies!
You see movies
at the same cemetery we do?
What a pleasant surprise.
Speaking of children,
these two were completely
planned and wanted.
Shrug, he shrugged.
Why don't we get
some more snacks?
Hello, little azuki bean.
Yo, Kingpin!
How's the ponytail hanging?
Don't patronize me,
Bart and She‐Bart.
I need silence
to watch the iconic '80s
time travel epic,
Forward to the Past.
Never heard of it.
Is it any good?
Okay, it's a consensus
top ten family action comedy
that has been delighting
bedwetting piglets
like yourself for eons!
Feh! Wah! Hooof!
And again, feh!
It's so sweet you're helping
the Book Guys become a family.
I mean, without kids, come on,
they're just dating
with rings on.
Oh, Marge, I love your takes.
Ooh, model crypt.
Fancy! Want to see
how the other half dies?
We can return to our time
if we can just get
this paddle steamer
up to 99 miles an hour.
Is that relative
to the shore or the water?
Great Steve, Mickey!
I don't know!
Golfer Aoki, four letters.
Isao.
Hello? Hello?!
The show is up there,
not on your lap.
Look, I got to be honest.
I only like movies
where Deadpool talks
to the camera,
so I'm watching Deadpool.
Okay, eyes up, TikToks!
Tonight, you watch a screen
that is unswipeable!
Premium sound system. Sweet.
Honey, just think.
Someday, you and I will be
snuggling next
to each other for eternity.
Oh, Homie, I never
thought about it that way.
'Till death do each other.
Rivers? Where we're going,
we don't need rivers.
Yes, all right,
you little trolls.
If you must,
tear the classic down
with your snarky little remarks.
Go.
An emotionally satisfying
ending.
Are you sure
this is an American movie?
I can't believe it.
I... cared what happened.
What is that thrill
I'm feeling?
You are experiencing this movie
again for the first time,
but through the eyes
of children.
Oh, Homie,
that was so dangerous.
I feel like Mrs. Dracula.
I definitely had a...
good evening.
Hey, it's locked.
Oh, no!
We're trapped
in a crypt full of...
smooth jazz.
Little known trivia,
the time travel vehicle
was originally a tanning booth.
That's crazy!
The little ones love
your useless knowledge.
Yes, my factoid will be
passed on for generations,
and in that way,
I will never truly die.
You know, maybe I was wrong
to dismiss the idea
of children so... so quickly.
Do you mean it?
Hurry. Let's return
these loaner kids
and go home
to make a mixed‐race nerd.
Hey, shouldn't Mom and Dad
be showing up about now?
Mom? Dad? Where are you?!
We are in a cemetery,
so maybe
they were attacked by zombies.
Stop it! Stop saying that!
Our parents are undead.
Dad will eat your head.
Let us out!
Great Steve! They are zombies!
They demand...
emotional support.
You can do it.
Give them comfort.
Must... act like...
loving father.
I flee.
But you caved!
Mom! Dad! You're okay!
Hey, where'd the dork go?
Your children's emotional needs
have pushed him away.
If I know him, and I don't,
I'm sure he'll be back.
No. He has run to a place
where there is no hope.
I have returned. Forever.
Your room is unchanged...
as are your sheets.
So... your husband ran away
to his childhood home,
leaving you alone.
Maybe forever.
Also, childless.
I'm sure you're experiencing
a lot of feelings right now.
It's okay to let them out.
I hate you,
you shameless womb tease!
You're like a baby drug dealer!
You give me a taste,
and now I'm hooked!
This is on you too!
You've crushed
my only chance at happiness,
you ape‐faced
cheeseburger goblin!
Make this right.
Bring back my husband!
So this is where
Comic Book Guy grew up.
We'll finally see what kind
of its created a that.
Ah, you must be delivering
my 1912 Polish coronation stamp.
Actually,
we're looking for someone
we call Comic Book Guy.
Enter.
My son is in here... somewhere.
Oh, well, thank you, Mr...
You may refer to me
as Postage Stamp Fellow.
What is this crazy place?
This crazy place
is Comic Book Guy's
childhood home.
An only child,
he grew up surrounded
by an eccentric extended family
of childless aunts and uncles.
However, his family poured their
love into their collections,
instead of into the lonely
little boy wandering the halls.
His aunt collected taxidermized
chestnut‐tailed starlings,
causing her to form a tacit
alliance with her twin brother,
who collected
brutalist birdhouses.
His great step‐uncle,
who had once had his heart
broken by a meter maid,
was a gatherer of discredited
obstetric equipment,
while his younger dowager aunt
collected antique
Chinese cricket boxes
and filled them
with live crickets,
who frequently escaped.
The only thing of value
the family did not display
in the home was love.
And the love he sought most
was that of his father,
who spent his days
as an avid philatelist.
Mint. Mint.
Near mint. Very fine.
Hi, there.
Maybe you might feel better
if you came home with us?
I am home.
From now on,
my only companion is
my comic book collection.
Mint. Mint. Near mint.
Gem mint. Mint. Mint...
- Look at the sad little boy.
- Mint. Mint. Mint. Mint.
- Is that you?
- Mint. Mint.
Worst... day... ever!
There's got to be more
to this story.
There was more to this story.
Without anyone to play with,
the lonely boy turned to baseball.
His favorite pitcher
was Sandy Koufax,
and he perfected a curveball
of rare devastation.
However, his team
would never give him a chance.
But on the day
before the big game,
all the starting pitchers were
injured in a multi‐canoe pile‐up
caused by the sighting of an
unusually large lake sturgeon.
He got the call to pitch.
His dearest hope was that
his father would finally see
his masterful curveball
in action.
But during the biggest moment
of his young life,
his dad was nowhere to be seen.
He escaped his sadness
into a world of heroes,
villains and jugheads.
In that moment, he became more
than a boy but less than a man.
He became Comic Book Guy.
Marge then confronted
Postage Stamp Fellow
about this life‐changing
incident with his son.
What? Okay.
Why weren't you there
for your son when he needed you?
This is not a family
to rummage through the past.
Emotionally.
You tell me why you didn't go
to your son's baseball game,
or I'll lick it.
My Inverted Dendermonde?
You wouldn't dare!
All right, all right!
I'll tell you!
I was buying him that.
Go ahead. Tell him.
I didn't go to your game,
because I was afraid
if you lost,
I wouldn't know how
to comfort you.
So I supported you
the only way I knew how.
I purchased you a collectible.
Which I never had the heart
to give you.
Sandy Koufax,
the left arm of God!
Son, perhaps we should do
something we've never done.
Have a catch?
I think I would like that.
Everyone,
my son and I are having a catch.
Love was finally on display.
Well, maybe Comic Book Guy won't
be so afraid to be a father.
Sucker.
Wife, I have returned...
healed!
I am now...
Changed Better Guy.
My ultimate fantasy.
Mr. Beaver from The Lion,
the Witch and the Wardrobe.
You are ready to make a baby.
Poor old Granddad
I laughed at all his words
I thought he was
a bitter man
He spoke of women's ways...
They trap you
and they use you
Before you even know
But love is blind
and you're far too kind
Don't ever let it show
I wish that I knew
what I know now
When I was younger
I wish that I knew
what I know now
When I was stronger
The can‐can's
such a pretty show
Will steal your heart away
But backstage
back on Earth again
The dressing rooms are gray
They come on strong
and it ain't too...