♪ The Simpsons ♪
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
(chanting)
All we own we owe.
Shh!
(chanting softly)
All we own we owe.
(groaning)
♪ Tra-la-la la-la-la ♪
♪ Tra-la-la-la-la ♪
I am the happiest boy there is.
Aren't I, Bobo?
Happy! Come here, Happy.
Yes, Mummsy?
Happy, would you like to
continue living with us,
your loving natural parents?
Or would you rather live
with this twisted, loveless billionaire?
Let's roll.
Wait! You forgot your bear,
a symbol of your lost
youth and innocence!
(sighs) Oh, well.
At least we still have
his little brother, George.
♪ Bum-bum-bum bum ♪
♪ Oh, the sun shines bright
on my old Kentucky home ♪
♪ Bum-bum-bum bum ♪
Trust me, it'll be funny
when I'm an old man.
(groans)
I want my teddy.
Bobo. Bobo.
Oh, it's you.
The bedpan's under my pillow.
Who's Bobo, sir?
Bobo? (stammers)
I meant Lobo.
Sheriff Lobo.
They never should have
canceled that show.
I see.
On another topic,
preparations for your
birthday have begun.
-I won't get what I really want.
-No one does.
♪ Happy birthday,
Mr. Smithers ♪
(Smithers moans)
Lobo. Lobo.
Bring back Sheriff Lobo!
Lobo. Lobo! (screams)
What, Homie?
Oh, no, Burns' birthday!
-What's wrong?
-Every time Mr. Burns has a birthday,
all his employees have to
help out at the party.
And I always get some
terrible job.
Where is that dreaded piñata?
Ow! Ow! Ow! Missed me.
Heh heh. Ow.
(grumbles)
(people laughing)
It's not funny.
And the one in my pants
really hurts.
That man who's getting all those
laughs, Smithers, who is he?
Homer Simpson, sir.
One of the carbon blobs
from sector 7G.
But I don't think that--
I want this Simpson fellow
to perform comedy at my party.
I must harness his
fractured take on modern life.
Fine, sir. I'll get him started
on some snappy Sinbad-esque material.
(laughs)
I'm so funny.
This is gonna be great.
What are you doing?
I'm writing a delicious
send-up of Mr. Burns
for his birthday party.
Is "poo-poo" one word or two?
(laughing)
I don't think it's a good idea
to humiliate
your boss on his birthday.
Actually, Mom, a tweaking
of Mr. Burns' foibles,
if done with
the greatest of care,
could earn Dad a special
place in the old man's heart.
Well, I also do
a delightful impression of him.
I paint a frowny face on
my butt and pull down my pants.
BOTH: Yeah!
(concerned groaning)
Now, I'm not saying Mr. Burns
is incontinent--
(chuckles)
Incontinent.
Too rich.
Does either of you know
what "incontinent" means?
-Lisa, don't spoil our fun.
-Come on, dear, it's time to go.
Okay, stupid.
Homer, you've got to
stop insulting everyone,
especially your boss.
Marge, the comedy roast
is an American tradition.
It's what gives us the freedom
to criticize our social betters.
Hey, Flanders,
you smell like manure!
Uh-oh. Better cancel
that dinner party tonight.
Thanks for the nose news,
neighbor.
(groaning)
Hey. No one-termers.
You too, huh?
Hey, I know a good yogurt place.
Get away from me, loser.
SMITHERS:
Ladies and gentlemen,
I give you
"Montgomery Burns: The Life."
(applause)
Ah, Bobo.
Hmm.
(applause)
Here are several fine young men
who I'm sure are gonna go far.
Ladies and gentlemen,
The Ramones.
Ah, these minstrels will
soothe my jangled nerves.
I'd just like to
say this gig sucks.
Hey, up yours,
Springfield.
One, two, three, four!
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
-♪ Happy birthday ♪
-♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
-♪ Happy birthday, Burnsy ♪
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
Go to hell, you old bastard.
Hey, I think
they liked us.
Have the Rolling Stones killed.
-Sir, those aren't--
-Do as I say.
(Burns scoffs)
Stinks. Piffle.
Dust Buster? Yeech.
Hmm.
Sir, I've arranged
for the people of Australia
to join hands tonight
and spell out your
name with candles.
There's a satellite hookup
on that monitor,
if you'll just turn
your head slightly.
Bah, no time. Next!
I have some sad news to report.
A small puppy,
not unlike Lassie,
-was just run over in the parking lot.
-(crowd gasps)
And now it's time for the comedy
stylings of Homer Simpson.
♪♪
Are you ready to laugh?
Oh, that poor dog.
I said, are you
ready to laugh?!
Quiet, you awful man.
-You know, Mr. Burns is so cheap--
-What?
I-- I mean, you know,
Mr. Burns is so old--
How dare you!
Woo-hoo. Tough crowd.
Better bring out
the big guns. Ahem.
Here's an impression
of Mr. Burns
that you might find
a little cheeky.
(crowd gasps)
I'm Mr. Burns. Blah-blah-blah.
Do this, do that.
Blah-blah-blah.
I think I'm so big.
Destroy him.
Blah-blah-blah.
Look at me-- Ow!
This party is over.
(screaming, shouting)
Ow. Where did I lose them?
I'll never wiggle my bare butt
in public again.
I'd like to believe that
this time.
I really would.
Bart, run down to the store and get
a big bag of ice for your father.
Yes'm. Dad,
I know you're discouraged,
but please, don't deny
the world your fat can.
Don't worry, boy.
She'll be ready
for your Aunt Selma's birthday.
I knew it.
(sighs)
Look at all the wonderful
things you have, Mr. Burns.
King Arthur's Excalibur. The only
existing nude photo of Mark Twain.
And that rare first draft
of the Constitution
with the word "suckers"
in it.
-Yes, yes, yes. So what?
-You want your bear, Bobo, don't you?
Liar! I'll give you
the thrashing of a lifetime!
Resistance is futile.
Oh, God, how I want my bear.
But he's gone.
Gone forever.
I'd give anything to know
what happened to him.
Why, put some grease in your
garter, Lindy. You're late!
(crowd cheering)
(distant explosions)
This is all your fault.
You've gotta start selling this
for more than $1 a bag.
We lost four more men
on this expedition.
If you can think of a better way
to get ice, I'd like to hear it.
-He's got us there.
-Beats me.
Hey, Apu, this bag of ice
has a head in it.
Ooh, a head bag.
Those are chock-full of...
head-y goodness.
Hey, it's a teddy bear.
(sniffs) Ew, gross.
It's probably diseased
or something.
Here, Maggie.
(♪♪ dramatic sting)
(record scratch)
SMITHERS: Here's something
that should cheer you up, sir.
It's me, sir. Bobo.
Hug me. Squeeze me.
Tug at my fur.
Ooh! Enough.
Stop this grotesque charade.
Now, find my teddy.
Oh, and, uh,
leave the costume.
The Burns bear, perhaps the most
valuable "wittle" bear in the world
could be anywhere.
It could be in your house.
You could be
looking at it right now.
It could be right in front
of your face as I'm saying this,
waggling back and forth, perhaps
being held up by a loved one.
Maggie, I'm trying to watch TV.
Put that moldy old bear down.
Moldy? Old?
I'm gonna get
something to eat.
Well, it's not your original bear,
of course. Mm-hey!
But it is programmed to be
just as cuddly.
Aw, doggone it.
(growls)
It's supposed to be...
doing a little dance.
-BURNS: Get the bear off.
-SMITHERS: I got him.
Trying to turn it off.
No. Bear want to live.
(bear growling)
(soft music playing)
(grunts)
(screaming)
Son of a--! D'oh!
Stupid stair!
(gasps)
How long have we
had these fish?
Wait, the bear.
Burns' bear.
"Bobo." It's Mr. Burns' bear,
all right.
Well, Burns isn't getting this
back cheap, I can tell you that.
He's gonna have to give me
my own recording studio.
♪ Two all-beef patties,
special sauce, lettuce, cheese ♪
♪ Pickles, onions
on a sesame seed bun ♪
Oh...
MAN: Homer, you're drooling
on the mike again.
I think we should just
give him the bear
that he cherishes
so much.
Hmm. Better sew
that eye back on.
No, let's send Burns
the eye in the mail.
He'll pay more money if he
thinks the bear's in danger.
Yes, we'll send the eye.
I'm sure he'll offer us
a fair reward.
And then we'll
make him double it.
ALL: Huh?
Well, why can't I be
greedy once in a while?
Bobo. My beautiful Bobo.
I promise I'll never
leave you behind again.
(clears throat)
Oh, yes.
Naturally, I can't pay you
much of a reward
because I'm
strapped for cash.
(creaking)
As you can see, this old
place is falling apart.
But I'm sure we can come
to an understanding.
Yes, sir.
(thinking) Reject the first offer.
Reject the first offer.
May I offer you a drink?
Sorry, Burns. No deal.
Don't worry, Smithers.
He's playing hardball now,
but it won't take him
long to crack.
(neck cracking)
I gotta call Burns.
I gotta call Burns!
Maybe I can still
get that drink.
Dad, the longer he has to wait,
the more he'll pay.
Right. That makes sense.
Yah!
No! No! Let me go!
I knew you'd come
crawling back.
-How much do you want?
-$1 million
and three Hawaiian islands.
Good ones. Not the leper one.
Done.
Now give me that bear.
Woo-hoo! I'm rich!
Rich, I tells you!
Here you go.
(straining)
It seems to be stuck.
Bad baby. Bad Maggie.
(whimpers)
Give me the bear.
The bear. The bear.
(sighs)
HOMER:
Here you go, Maggie.
The deal's off, Mr. Burns.
The bear stays here.
You've made a mistake, Simpson.
(groans)
Ah, big deal.
Who needs his money?
We're getting by okay.
-(crash)
-Son. You gotta help me.
I hit three people
on the way over here,
and I don't
have any insurance.
So how's about you?
Excellent shot, Smithers.
I'll be squeezing my Bobo
in no time.
Howdy, gents.
What can I diddily-do you for?
(whimpers)
(thumps)
Remember Smithers,
in and out in 18 seconds.
(both grunt)
-More cocoa, Mr. Burns?
-Yes.
Mmm. Sixty-four slices
of American cheese.
Sixty-four.
Sixty-three.
Two.
One.
Have you been up all night
eating cheese?
I think I'm blind.
-(Burns grunts)
-Wha?
Good day to you.
(moans)
Excuse me, we wanted
to see the geek
who valued the happiness of
his children more than money.
Right here.
Ah, you said his head was
the size of a baseball.
My life can't get any worse.
SMITHERS (over intercom): Homer Simpson,
report for much worse duties.
D'oh!
Ow! Ow!
-After lunch, can I whip you?
-MAN: Nope.
Aw, no fair.
-(whip cracks)
-Ow!
Hmm. I wonder
what makes it turn.
Who cares?
Maggie, I know you
like the bear,
but wouldn't you be just as
happy playing with...
this box?
See, Maggie?
See the fun box?
(humming and laughing)
No! My box. My box!
(giggles)
Mmm. I think we need
a new hair dryer.
Marge, you must hate me
for not taking Mr. Burns' money.
I don't hate you.
I'm proud of you.
You came through
for your daughter
when she needed you
the most.
Aw, thanks, Marge.
But it'll take a lot more than that
to comfort this tortured soul.
(giggles)
HOMER:
Hey, boxy. Heh heh heh.
Give me that.
Aw.
♪ 2 plus 2 is 4 ♪
♪ 2 plus 2 is 4,
(Homer laughs)
I can see why this is
so popular. Look at him.
-(Homer laughs)
-♪ 2 plus 2 is 4 ♪
-Give me my bear, Simpson.
-Ah!
It's The Soul
Mass Transit System.
(panting)
Give it to me.
El yo-yo es grandé.
Ai, chihuahua.
As you can see, Simpson,
I have taken over
all 78 channels.
And you won't see any of
your favorite shows again
until you give in.
-Whoa, that bites.
-Holy crap.
-(gasps)
-BURNS: What's that you say?
You can live
without television
-as long as you have beer?
-That's right.
Wrong. All beer trucks
heading towards Springfield
have been diverted.
This town will be
as dry as a bone.
And if the rest of you beer-swilling
tube jockeys out there
have a problem with this,
talk to Homer Simpson.
(laughs)
(doorbell rings)
Homer, give him
what he wants.
Oh, Barney, leave me alone.
-Whoops!
-(gunshot)
-(glass shatters)
-(woman screams)
(siren wailing)
BARNEY:
Oh-oh.
My old man can't get a beer
because his old man
won't give a bear
to another old man.
Let's get him!
Wait. Why are
we getting him?
Look, fellas. The first
snapdragon of the season.
-Never mind. Let's just get him.
-Yeah!
♪♪
Smithers, I'm home.
(laugh track plays)
What? Already?
Yes.
(laugh track plays)
Is it my imagination,
or is TV getting worse?
It's about the same.
Uh-oh! Look out, Smithers!
-(glass shatters)
-(laugh track plays)
I love this show.
(crowd shouting)
Well, well, look who's
come to apologize.
Come on, let's go in there
and get the bear.
ALL:
Yeah!
Ha! I got it.
(crowd cheers)
Aw, jeez,
will you look at that?
(whimpers)
-WOMAN 1: Hmm?
-WOMAN 2: Hmm?
(whimpers)
What have we become?
We've given the word "mob"
a bad name.
(indistinct crowd chatter)
Well, what should we do now?
Hey, everybody,
let's go sing at the hospital.
♪ For we've got... ♪
♪ High hopes ♪
♪ We've got high hopes ♪
(doorbell rings)
Simpson, look what
you've reduced me to.
Please. Please.
But, Mr. Burns,
it's not my bear.
It's Maggie's.
Ah....
So, good sand today, hmm?
Oh, well,
I don't usually....
Well, just this once.
Ew.
Damn you, paparazzo.
Well, Maggie, I've given
this a lot of thought.
I'm sure we can come
to some sort of agreement.
(straining)
Beaten by an infant.
What could be more humiliating?
What a scoop.
Okay, Maggie.
You win.
But I want you
to do something for me.
Hang on to that bear.
Don't make the same
mistake I made.
(sighs)
(Maggie sucking on pacifier)
For me? Bobo?
(gasps)
Smithers, I'm so happy.
Something amazing has happened.
I'm actually happy.
Take a note: From now on, I'm only
going to be good and kind to everyone.
I'm sorry, sir,
I don't have a pencil.
Don't worry.
I'm sure I'll remember it.
Well, we didn't
get any money,
but Mr. Burns
got what he wanted.
Marge, I'm confused.
Is this a happy ending
or a sad ending?
It's an ending.
That's enough.
There you go.
Ah, Bobo,
reunited at last.
But I can't help but wonder
what the future holds for you.
(yawning)
Ah, yes, wonder....
HOMER LOOK-A-LIKES:
D'oh! D'oh!
(sighs)
Bobo, I know I say this
every century,
but I'll never
leave you behind again.
Wait for me, sir.
Woof!
♪♪
Shh!
SUBTITLES ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.