♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
(snoring)
(alarms blaring)
WOMAN'S VOICE:
Core meltdown in 10 seconds.
Nine, eight--
-(alarms stop)
-Meltdown averted. Good boy!
(moaning, yawning)
(snoring, purring)
(whimpering)
(buzzes)
MR. BURNS:
(groaning) What?
How dare you disturb me
during nap time?
We're from the nuclear
regulatory commission.
This is a surprise test
of worker competence.
There must be
some mistake.
We, uh-- We make
cookies here.
Mr. Burns's old-fashioned
good-time extra-chewy--
Get the ax.
The watchdog of public safety.
Is there any lower form of life?
Don't worry, sir, I rounded up
our less-gifted employees
and led them into the basement.
-(dripping)
-(mouse squeaking)
Duh, Homer,
why are we down here?
Oh, geez!
I told ya, Bernie--
to guard the bee!
-But why?
-Oh, you guys are pathetic.
No wonder Smithers
made me head bee guy.
-Uh, it's gettin' away.
-Oh, we did bad!
-(buzzing)
-Hey! Uhh! Oh!
Hey! Come back!
Is there
a Homer Simpson present?
Oh, I'm afraid
he couldn't "bee" here.
(both chuckling)
Oh, yes,
he's in Geneva,
chairing a conference
on nuclear fission.
(mutters)
Yes, that should stick.
D'oh!
The bee bit my bottom!
Now my bottom's big!
-(sighs)
-Homer, this is
an exact replica of
your workstation.
Hmm?
Now we're going to simulate a
power surge in core sector 8.
What the hell
are you talking about?
What do I do?
(sobbing)
In the name of God,
you've gotta tell me!
MAN: Relax.
It's just a simulator.
Nothing can go wrong.
Just poke blindly
at the controls
until they let you go.
-(rumbling)
-(both exclaiming)
Oh, no. No!
This can't be happening!
(screaming)
(gasps)
For the love of God, sir!
There are two seats!
I like to
put my feet up.
(engine sputtering)
(Mr. Burns groaning)
(roaring)
Must destroy mankind.
(beeping)
Ooh! Lunchtime.
(blubbering)
We're still not sure
how he caused the meltdown.
There wasn't any
nuclear material in the truck!
Very well.
It's time for your bribe.
Now, you can either have
the washer and dryer
where the lovely Smithers
is standing,
or you can trade it all in
for what's in this box.
The box.
The box!
Look, Burns,
this is a big problem.
You just can't throw money at it
and make it go away.
Gentlemen, I've decided
there will be
no investigation.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'll go away.
You're in big trouble, Burns.
Homer Simpson's job
requires college training
in nuclear physics.
Now, you get your man
up to speed,
or we'll be forced
to take legal action.
Is that so?
Well, I have the feeling
you'll be...
dropping the charges.
-Oh.
-The painters moved your desk, sir.
Oh, yes.
(doorbell rings)
-(screams)
-Hello, Simpson.
My lawyers and I were in
the neighborhood
and thought we'd stop by.
Would you like to come in for
tea and marshmallow squares?
(murmuring)
Yes, he would.
So you want me
to go to college?
College?
-Ha! Barber or clown?
-Bart!
Remember, your job and
the future of your family
hinges on your
successful completion
of Nuclear Physics 101.
Oh, and one more thing.
You must find
the jade monkey
before the next full moon.
Actually, sir,
we found the jade monkey.
It was in
your glove compartment.
And the road maps
and ice scraper?
They were in there too, sir.
Excellent!
It's all
falling into place.
I think this is
a great opportunity.
You could learn so much.
Maybe you're right.
I did always want
to go to college.
But fate stood in the way.
Homer, sign this application
and you're a shoo-in.
-(panting)
-(laughing)
That dog
has somebody's ham!
This I gotta see!
(door opens)
(growling)
Give me that ham,
you stupid dog!
-(grunting, yelling)
-(sighs)
(groans)
Dad, don't let these
application essays throw you.
Let's see: "List your three
favorite books
and how they've
influenced your life."
-Is TV Guide a book?
-No.
-Son of Sniglet?
-Katherine Hepburn's "Me"?
-No!
Ohh! I suck!
It was the most I ever threw up,
and it changed my life forever.
You the man, Homer!
Thanks, boy.
Now for the crowning touch.
I don't know, Dad.
Don't you have
a better picture?
Relax. A photo
can't make any difference.
-He looks crazy.
-Agreed.
Reading his essay would
only waste valuable seconds.
ANNOUNCER (on TV): Finally,
the great taste of Worcestershire sauce
in a soft drink!
MAN: Ahh! Steaky!
Sorry, son, but there's
a program about campus life
that I really should watch.
ANNOUNCER: We now return to
"School of Hard Knockers,"
starring Corey Masterson.
Dean Bitterman,
I hope nothing unsavory
happens during my visit.
As you know, I am
the president of the United States.
Oh, don't worry.
I've expelled
those rowdy members
of Chug-a-Lug House.
Oh, I hate
that lousy dean.
Your bra bomb better work,
Nerdlinger.
-Mm-kay!
-(explosion)
(gasps)
Cory!
(chuckles)
Don't worry, Mr. President.
I-- Mr. President!
Lighten up,
Bitterman!
That youngster will make
a perfect addition
to my cabinet.
Secretary of
partying down!
(angry growling)
Yes!
Take that, Bitterman!
Homie,
here are the responses
from the colleges
you applied to.
D'oh!
D'oh! D'oh!
Whoo-hoo! A flyer
for a hardware store!
-D'oh!
-Well, Pop, what are you gonna do?
Something I should have done
a long time ago.
-You don't know, do you?
-No, ma'am.
Don't worry, Simpson.
It just so happens
I have a chair
at Springfield University.
(growling)
I'm sorry, Mr. Burns,
but I must object.
This Simpson
is not qualified.
(all murmuring agreement)
-(growling)
-I see.
Well, you know, fellas,
I look at the admissions board
a lot like a baseball team.
You all like baseball,
don't you?
(all murmuring agreement)
Yes, well, to have
a successful baseball club
you need teamwork.
Not some hot-dog
admissions officer
playing by his own rules!
(grunting)
Excuse me.
What are you doing?
(grunting)
I'm giving you
the beating of your life!
Look, if--
Stop that.
If you wanted him that badly,
why didn't you just say so?
(yells)
Smithers, dismember the corpse
and send his widow a corsage.
Whoo-hoo!
I'm a college man!
I won't need
my high school diploma anymore!
♪ I am so smart,
I am so smart ♪
♪ S-m-r-t
I mean, s-m-a-r-r-t ♪♪
My first day of college.
I wish my father
was alive to see this.
-Hey!
-How long have you been back there?
Three days.
Nerd!
Homer,
that isn't very nice.
Marge,
try to understand.
There are two kinds
of college students:
jocks and nerds.
As a jock, it is my duty
to give nerds a hard time.
Hey, pal!
Did you get a load
of the nerd?
Pardon me?
♪♪ (rock)
(chuckling)
I'll be a campus hero.
(spits)
Attention, everyone.
The punch has been spiked!
(all gasping)
Don't worry.
Your parents have been called
and will be here
to pick you up shortly!
ALL: Yay!
Marge, someone squeezed all
the life out of these kids.
And unless movies and TV
have lied to me,
it's a crusty,
bitter, old dean.
Hi there. Hello,
I'm Dean Peterson,
but you can call me Bobby.
I just want you to know,
if you ever feel stressed out
from studying or whatever,
I'm always up
for some hacky sack.
Or if you just want to
come by and jam,
I used to be the bass
player for the Pretenders.
♪♪ (fast riff)
Boy, I can't wait to take
some of the starch
out of that stuffed shirt.
Good morning and welcome
to Nuclear Physics 101.
I see a lot of new faces,
but you know the old saying--
"Out with the old,
in with the nucleus."
(laughing)
Now we'll begin by--
Oops.
(laughing loudly)
Ah, did you see
that jerk?
(laughing)
Dropped his notes!
(laughing more loudly)
Now, if anyone
would like to stay,
I'm going to hold
a comprehensive review session
after every class.
-Do we have to?
-No.
Then kiss my curvy butt
good-bye.
-(giggling)
-(squirrels chittering)
Whoo-hoo!
♪♪ ("Louie, Louie")
Homer, we have
a perfectly good bookcase.
Yeah, but this is what
they're doing on campus.
Besides, it isn't costing us.
I swiped the cinder blocks
from a construction site.
Sir, six cinder blocks
are missing.
There'll be
no hospital then.
I'll tell the children.
This proton accelerator
destabilizes the atom
in this chamber here,
then propels it--
HOMER: Uh, excuse me,
Professor Brainiac,
but I worked in
a nuclear power plant for 10 years,
and, uh, I think I know
how a proton accelerator works.
Well, please come down
and show us.
All right. I will.
(screaming)
-In there, guys.
-BOTH: Thanks, Homer.
Homer, no one blames you
for the accident.
We simply feel
you might benefit with
a little outside tutoring.
I researched
these names myself.
Yeah, you won this round,
Dean,
but the war isn't over.
-(phone rings)
-Hello.
HOMER: Hello, Dean.
You're a stupid-head!
-Homer, is that you?
-(yelps)
Hiya, gang.
Intruder alert.
Stop the humanoid.
(chortling)
Look, I'm supposed to
get a physics tutor.
Well, you've come to
the right place, then.
If there's one thing we know,
it is science.
And math.
And the words to every
Monty Python routine.
ALL: We are the knights
who say "Ni!"
NERDS: Ni! Ni! Ni!
(giggling)
(chuckles)
Ni.
We played
Dungeons & Dragons
for three hours.
Then I was slain
by an elf.
Listen to yourself, man.
You're hangin' with nerds.
-You take that back!
-Homer, please.
These boys sound very nice,
but they're clearly nerds.
Really? But nerds
are my mortal enemy.
Dad, nerds are nothing to fear.
In fact, they've done some
pretty memorable things.
Some nerds of note include
popcorn magnate
Orville Redenbacher,
rock star David Byrne,
and supreme court justice
David Souter.
(gasps)
Oh, not Souter!
Oh, no!
Come on, Mr. Simpson.
You'll never pass this course
if you don't know
the periodic table.
-I'll write it on my hand.
-Oh!
Including all known
lanthanides and actinides?
-(chuckling) Good luck.
-(all chuckling)
Come on, guys.
Look at yourselves!
All you do is study.
I'm gonna show you
the true meaning
of college.
We're gonna go out
and par-ty!
Wait a minute.
I'll put on my snow pants.
-Me too.
Ah, the college road trip.
What better way to spread
beer-fueled mayhem?
If you're going for a ride,
I'd like you to take
Bart and Lisa.
But, Marge, we're college guys,
and we're up to no good.
Mr. Simpson, Gary spilled
his ear medicine.
Oh, those baby ducks
were so cute.
I can't believe they let us
walk right up and feed them.
-I need to go to the bathroom.
-We stopped five minutes ago.
Yeah, but someone
knocked on the door,
and I couldn't go.
I'm telling you.
A big, crazy prank is just
what the doctor ordered.
(giggling)
The dean will go nuts.
(gasps)
I got it!
We wait by his mailbox,
and when he comes outside,
we roll him up in a carpet
and throw him off a bridge!
(laughing)
-(scraping sound)
-(all groaning)
So it's a prank
you're looking for, is it?
I'll give you your prank.
The only other college
in 50 miles
is Springfield A&M,
so they're
our best target.
Those bastards.
Meet Sir Oinkcelot,
the beloved mascot
of Springfield A&M.
Here he is presiding
over last year's homecoming.
Here he is conferring
an honorary degree
on Richard Nixon.
And here he is rolling
in his own filth.
Gentlemen, I propose
we kidnap Sir Oinkcelot.
And then we roll him up
in a carpet
and throw him
off a bridge!
(laughing)
What?
-(squeals)
-Look,
you pull
its tail straight,
and it curls
right back up again.
Curly, straight.
(squealing)
Mr. Simpson, I don't think
he likes that.
(giggles) Of course he does.
He's a cute little piggy.
Curly, straight.
Curly, straight. Ow!
-Why, you little--
-Mr. Simpson, stop!
-It's a defenseless animal!
-(screams)
(groaning, snorting)
Hey, the pig's
acting kinda funny.
He and Mr. Simpson split
a case of malt liquor.
Guys, he's really sick.
Hello! That sounds like
a pig fainting.
(squealing)
I'm sorry, boys.
I-I've never expelled
anyone before,
but that pig
had some powerful friends.
Oh, you'll pay.
Don't think you won't pay!
Guys, believe me.
I didn't mean
to get you expelled.
Oh, don't worry, Mr. Simpson.
We can take care
of ourselves.
Uh, wallet inspector.
Oh, here you go.
I believe that's all
in order.
I can't believe
that worked!
Hey! That's not
the wallet inspector.
-(humming)
-(groans)
Marge, they don't have
anywhere to stay.
And they're geniuses.
They'll solve
all our problems.
They'll elevate us
to the status
of kings on earth!
Mr. Simpson,
we all have nosebleeds.
Oh, for the love of--
-(loud beeping)
-(groans)
What's wrong with this phone?
It's making crazy noises.
Those crazy noises
are computer signals.
Yeah, some guys at M.I.T. are
sending us reasons why
Captain Picard
is better than Captain Kirk.
Ha! They're out
of their minds.
(groans)
Oh, I heard about this.
This is the one where Scratchy
finally gets Itchy.
Wow!
(cackling)
(whistles)
My purpose in life
is to witness this moment.
(screaming)
We need the outlet
for our rock tumbler.
BOTH:
Plug it in! Plug it in!
What, the rock tumbler
or the TV?
BOTH: The TV! The TV!
-♪ ...show ♪
-(cheering)
Wow! They'll never
let us show that again,
not in a million years!
(chortling)
(screaming)
Dad, start digging
some nerd holes.
It's bad enough they put their
retainers in the dishwasher.
Can't we do something?
Look, I'm sure we can
work something out
where we can all live
in harmony. Right, Marge?
No, I want those geeks
out of my house.
You really think you can
get us back into college?
Absolutely.
Now, the only antidote
to a zany scheme
is an even zanier scheme!
Why does it
have to be zany?
(gasps)
I've got it!
We're gonna fix it
so you guys save
the dean's life.
-(engine revving)
-Perfect.
(tires screeching)
(whistling)
Okay, guys.
We push him out of the way
in exactly three seconds.
Should we correct
for wind resistance?
Hmm, possibly.
What do you think?
-(thudding)
-Oh, my.
Well, Dean, I'm really sorry
for the running-you-over prank.
Prank?
And all those other pranks
were my idea too.
I'm the one
who should be expelled.
Well, I'm touched
by your honesty.
And who knows--
perhaps I've been a bit
of an ogre myself.
-Yes, you have.
-How's this?
I'll re-admit your friends,
and we'll forget this whole
silly incident ever occurred.
Oh, Dean.
This is what your new hip
is going to look like.
(nervous chuckling)
You're gonna have to
go easy on it.
Oh, it's good to be back
after all these weeks.
Better check our
answering machine, huh?
WOMAN'S VOICE: Number of
messages received: zero.
(all sighing)
We really want to
thank you, Mr. Simpson.
Ah, no problem, guys.
The important thing
is that we wrapped up
all the loose ends.
So, in conclusion,
good luck on tomorrow's
big final exam.
Exam? Oh!
This is just like one
of those bad dreams!
(screams)
What are you gonna do,
Mr. Simpson?
Actually, I've been
working on a plan.
During the exam,
I'll hide under some coats,
and hope that somehow
everything will work out.
Or with our help,
you can cram like you've
never crammed before!
Whatever.
Either way is good.
(grunts)
Whoo-hoo!
Oh, man. I can't believe
you failed.
Oh, I'm gonna lose my job
just 'cause I'm
dangerously unqualified!
Mr. Simpson,
there is a way.
We could, well,
use a computer
to change your grade.
(gasps)
Computers can do that?
Oh, yes. The only problem is
the moral dilemma it raises,
-which requires--
-(kissing)
Oh, I love--
Moral whuzzah?
An A-plus!
How did you do it?
Oh, let's just say
I had help from
a little magic box.
You changed your grade
with a computer?
D'oh!
Way to go, Dad!
Look, the important thing
is that
we all learned a lesson.
These guys learned
the richness and variety
of the world outside college.
-No, we didn't.
-Oh.
Then I learned
the real value of college
is to study and work hard.
No, you didn't.
You only passed
your course by cheating,
which you always taught us
was wrong.
-Hmm. True.
-And I learned that
in order for you to set
a good example for your son,
you're gonna take that course
over again without cheating.
Oh, Marge!
You're worse than
that crusty old dean.
(sighs)
Well, I guess it's back
to college for me.
And that means it's time to--
What did I teach you guys?
NERDS: Par-ty down?
Yes!
♪♪ (rock)
♪ Louie, Louie,
oh, no ♪
♪ We gotta go ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
I said, Louie, Louie ♪
♪ Oh, baby
we gotta go ♪
♪ A fine little girl
waits for me ♪
♪ Catch a ship
across the sea ♪
♪ Sail that ship about
all alone ♪
♪ We never think how
I'll make it home ♪
♪ Oh, Louie, Louie,
oh, no, no, no ♪
♪ We gotta go ♪
♪ Oh, no,
said Louie, Louie ♪
♪ Oh, baby,
say that we gotta go ♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.