Art lovers of Springfield, good news.
The art museum is closed forever.
[scattered applause]
Instead, our entire collection
will be digitized
and sold for a fortune on the blockchain
as non-fungible tokens or NFTs,
whatever the hell those are.
[chuckles] Now, let's turn some of
our crappy art into computer money.
Starting with
a true masterpiece, my butt.
Uh, Dad.
[yelps] Technology!
[phone beeps]
I've lost Bart forever.
No!
[phone beeps]
Yes!
Honey, remember how we're always
saying we wish Bart was less fungible?
Did something happen to Bart?
Only the parts you can hug.
The rest is alive
right here on my phone.
[screams] My baby is an app.
Uh, no. Apps actually do stuff.
He's an NFT.
But look how much he's worth.
[gasps] For Bart? Hmm,
imagine what we'd get for Lisa.
He is the first NFT
of an actual person.
I don't care.
We've gotta find a way
to get him back.
[distorted, echoing] To do that, you
yourself must enter the blockchain.
- Who are you?
- We are the enlightened intellects
who safeguard the cryptoverse.
[Homer] Kylie Jenner,
Rob Gronkowski and Jimmy Fallon.
I thought you were just
celebrity shills.
Ugh. We would never promote
a technology
if we didn't understand the
distributed ledger underpinning it.
Der!
I can't stop laughing, buddy.
[Homer] Shut up!
You ruined "Cowbell"!
This key is a back door through the
blockchain's cryptographic protocol.
Once you're inside, find Bart
and use it to get both of you out.
[Rob grunts]
Huh. So this is the blockchain.
No, noob.
This is the block-train.
[digital turtle] Speeding forever
through the loveless icy world
created by Crypto Bros.
Powered by the most abundant
fuel in the universe:
FOMO, the fear of missing out.
For a digital incarnation of an
abstract mathematical concept,
it could use a good dusting.
[British accent] Well, that's because
this is the last car of the train, innit?
The dwelling place of NFTs
with no value,
which is 99% of all NFTs
ever created.
Hmm. I guess being the second-ever
human NFT isn't worth a whole lot.
Where do they keep my son?
[French accent] At the very front
of the train where you can never go.
Watch me.
[grunting]
[NFTs laugh]
[cracks]
[retches] You killed
Ennui Oeuf 116. [retches]
[groans] Hmm?
[electrical humming]
Congratulations.
You've moved up the train because
you are now as valuable as us,
the Cuddle Kittens.
That's why there's an Internet.
For looking at cats.
But why am I worth more?
Because you killed another NFT.
What you call mindless slaughter,
Crypto Bros call disruption
and then pour cash into it.
So to rescue Bart, I need
to kill a bunch of you guys.
[grunts]
Ooh.
Well, I guess I gotta do this.
[cats yowling]
Sorry. Nothing personal.
- Hope you can't feel pain.
- [cats screeching]
[Lisa] Mom's price is
skyrocketing. Look at the FOMO.
Now everyone's gonna
want human NFTs.
Dad, you said you were
taking me to Bumper Boats.
I am. Have some more chocolate milk.
No one is putting another child
into that scanner before mine.
[Chief Wiggum grunting]
Hey!
Please kill Ralphouse.
[grunting]
[squelches]
The front of the train.
I made it.
Bart, we're getting out of here!
Whoa, Mom. What's the rush?
Grab yourself a Jaded Ape
and take a load off.
Mine was stolen from Seth Green.
[grunts]
You never like my friends.
Mom's almost got Bart out.
Don't let your son
become a worthless human again.
Sell him to me for $100 million.
- Hmm.
- No, Dad!
If you sell Bart to Mr. Burns,
he'll be trapped
on the blockchain forever.
But this is my chance
not to miss out
after I've missed out
on everything.
The housing bubble,
the first tech bubble,
the second tech bubble,
the current tech bubble.
Just one time, I wanna be the guy
that gives all his money to Bernie Madoff.
Mom, get out of there.
Dad's gonna crack.
[dramatic music playing]
He did it.
I can't believe he did it.
We made it.
Where's Homer? I wanna tell him
the inside of his phone smells.
He... He sold himself.
He was so afraid of missing out,
he tokened his own life.
Woo-hoo!
Eternity on a super swanky train.
Ooh! Twerked chicken.
[metal clanging]
What happened?
Our FOMO, it's gone.
The NFT craze is over.
D'oh!
Ah, the romance of train travel.
["For He Is an Englishman" playing]
♪ And it's clearly
To his credit ♪
♪ That he is an Englishman ♪
♪ He remains ♪
♪ An English... ♪
Wait. Did you only ask me to sing
to forestall your gruesome end?
Guilty as charged.
- [Bart grunts]
- [Sideshow Bob] Aha! Aha!
Ha!
[screaming]
It was only by following my hunch
that we found the Eastside Strangler
on the west side of town.
Can you explain how you
overcame childhood trauma
to become the nation's most
renowned criminal psychologist?
For that story,
you'll have to read my book.
[bell rings]
[student] Finally.
Wanna get some lunch?
Officer Muntz.
Told ya I'd smell you later.
Been a long time.
Ah, look at us.
We thought we were gonna stay
young forever.
Some of us did.
Oh, right.
Like Bart, because he got murdered.
Speaking of gruesome junk,
we could use your help on a case.
I'm flattered, but I'm the dean
of the True Crime Department.
I can't just run off and...
The killer left a message,
and we think it's for you.
[foreboding music playing]
Maybe Rod Flanders did grow up to become
a shockingly foulmouthed prop comedian,
but he didn't deserve this.
Only a super traumatized profiler like
you can piece together what happened here.
[Lisa] Our killer took his time.
Had fun with it.
Enjoyed a game of solitaire.
Red king on a red queen.
This psycho doesn't
play by the rules.
Damn, she's good.
Here, he had one of those moments
where you walk into a room
and forget what you came in for.
How did my guys miss that?
One more thing.
This killer won't stop now.
There will be others.
Sarge, there's been another.
How can he also be the first?
Sarge, we got another one.
[whistles] Boy, that's something
you don't see every...
One more, Sarge.
Got another one, Sarge.
The severed hand
opens the fridge
which tugs on that strip of
sinew, turning over the eyeball cup,
which rolls down the spine,
startles the cat,
which leaps onto the butter
dish seesaw
and sends the other eyeball
flying, turning on the coffee maker.
- Thanks.
- You'll have to take that to go.
They're about to do
a walk-through.
Forensics?
Podcasters.
The smell was overpowering.
A lover's quarrel or maybe
something much darker...
Use code "entrails" for 15% off
at toothpaste-warehouse.com.
Even I can't get inside
a mind this deranged.
There's only one person who can.
Little Lisa Simpson.
You really made something of yourself
after I made mincemeat of your brother.
Come to thank me?
- No.
- Rude.
I don't have time for your
games, Bob. I'm working on a...
Yes. A case so confounding,
you're actually willing to seek my help.
The Rube Goldberg Sherri
is actually quite impressive.
Hat tip, psychopath.
What about the identical
messages?
How can they all be the first?
Really, Professor Simpson?
Am I meant to spoon-feed you
all the answers?
Speak in riddles or drop a clue
in a clever anagram
hidden in something
I've just said right now?
This is a waste of time.
Perhaps a limerick will help.
There once was a shiny machete
that turned poor Bart's head to spaghetti.
You're gonna die
in that cell, Bob.
And when that happens,
wherever I am, I'll be dancing.
Can you think of anyone who
would've wanted to hurt Sherri?
No. Everybody loved
my big sister.
Big sister?
You guys were twins.
Yes, but Sherri was born first.
Probably makes sense for you
to be my husband now, huh?
Sherri is the first.
Rod Flanders, Dermott Spuckler,
all firstborns.
That's the pattern.
And Bob said something
about an anagram
taking us to the killer's lair.
[gasps] That's it.
- [metal clangs]
- Stay here.
[metal creaks]
Hey, meat hooks. Hook meat much?
Ha-ha... [grunts]
[whispering] Nelson?
Nelson, where are you?
[gasps]
The killer's lair looks
just like my old bedroom.
But how?
Oh. Maybe the killer's
on the security footage.
No, it can't be.
[grunts] Freeze.
Wha... I can't be the killer.
I turned my trauma into healing.
Oprah said so!
I'm sorry for the imbroglio,
but if the chef de cuisine insists
on calling it Taco Tuesdays,
he can't very well serve flautas
and expect us not to make a fuss.
Hello, Bob.
[whimpers] How did you
get in here?
Well, I knew if I killed enough people
in the most gruesome possible ways,
they'd send me to your prison.
But to get into your cell,
I had a little help.
Lisa the Killer. I never thought
you had it in you.
The Lisa you knew didn't.
But I'm another story.
Oh, really?
Split personalities?
Trope alert.
Call the first-thought police.
Professor Lisa had no idea
she was my accomplice.
But she's gone now.
She was my last victim,
or rather, second to last.
The penultimate.
[groans]
♪ He remains an Englishman ♪
[screaming, groaning]
[chewing]
Simpson, no eating
in the turbine room.
Since when?
Pfft. The nanny state
wins again.
No tanning in the reactor core.
No texting while driving
and eating ribs.
Can't even trim your hedges
with a machine gun.
When did everyone get so scared?
The world would be fine if people
just used common sense like me.
[yelps] Jailbreak!
[grunting]
Woman. Woman.
Homer 1, nanny state 0.
[groaning]
Stupid radioactive garbage doughnut
mutating my DNA while I sleep.
Hey, who stole
my Flanders' newspaper?
Sorry about that, Homerino.
But I... I whited out the crossword
after I did it so you can enjoy it too.
Better from the chimney
than the furnace. Am I right?
So, you see there's nothing
in the Bible that says
a pastor and his wife can't
take separate vacations.
[groaning]
Daddy, are you being tickled
by the Holy Spirit?
[stomach rumbling]
[groaning]
[as Homer, gasps] I've been
neighborino'ed
into Home-diddly-omer. [groans]
And why am I in church
when football is on?
[all gasp]
- [congregation screaming, crying]
- [belching]
[as Homer] Kiss my ass,
"church-os."
I'm fat, I'm bald, and I've
never felt sexier, baby.
Why you little...
[Milhouse choking]
Woo-hoo!
[Kent Brockman]
A mysterious affliction
has descended upon Springfield.
Citizens of every age, race,
and catchphrase
are mysteriously transforming
into bald, pear-shaped "doofi."
[as Homer] Donut Stu
has diabetes type 2.
[as Homer] News is stupid.
Somebody put on wrestling.
Do all these burping baldos
remind you of anyone?
I'd know that butt scratch
anywhere.
Everyone's turning into Dad.
[children scream]
[all belching]
Uh, children, your father's
less-than-stellar genetic code
is spreading through
burp-born transmission.
If we're going to cure
this virus, we need his DNA.
You three are the only ones
impervious to the virus.
You have got to find him.
Hmm. It is 11:30 in the morning.
- Beer, Moe.
A beer, a-Moe.
Have you seen our dad?
No, just these hundreds
of silly versions of him,
which is the greatest thing
that has ever happened to me.
I mean, I'm printing money
over here.
[dog barks]
Coming right up,
Santa's Little Homer.
Real Dad wasn't
at the bowling alley,
the candy store or mocking
the hippos at the zoo.
Wait, Dad ate a bucket
of this chicken last night.
When that happens, where does
he always spend the next day?
[Homer] I'll be out in a minute.
Um, is this really the most
convenient bathroom for your father?
It's the closest one
Mom will let him use.
Dad, we need you
to save the world.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Can you believe some idiot left
his perfectly good
back scratcher in there?
Look, it goes all the way down.
[moans]
What?
Now, if you'll just board
the "Frink-o-ma-copter"...
We're not calling it that.
[mutters] And then we'll pop your
DNA into the "Frink-tabulizer"...
We're not calling it that.
[muttering]
And everything will go back
to the way it was.
Wait, hold on.
Why would I want that?
Finally, everyone thinks
the way I do.
Nobody's making up stupid rules
about bicycle helmets
or where you can smoke cigars.
You wanna drive without
a seat belt?
FaceTime while jaywalking?
Enjoy a sugary soda?
Go ahead. You're not
hurting anyone.
It's a utopia.
No, a "me-topia."
Yes. Well, you don't really want
everyone to be like you.
Earth-shattering reveal!
[Bart, Lisa scream]
[chuckles]
[as Homer] When did insurance
commercials get so funny?
[screams] Marge.
Cooperating with us is the only
way to get your wife back to normal.
You've never looked
more beautiful.
Scooch over, gorgeous.
When we get home,
let's you and I bump muzzles.
Please, please.
If we don't have some competent
people left to run things,
society will collapse.
Coders to run the Internet that
feeds you the latest misinformation.
Pilots to fly the planes
you need to be restrained on.
I mean, a world
without experts...
Does Beaker ever shut up?
[chuckles] Good one, Me-Marge.
Well, you leave me no choice.
I'm calling in
a nuclear air strike
to obliterate all
the "Homerized" Springfielders,
including... very sadly... the
touring company of Kinky Boots.
Obliterating in three, two...
Hey, you know what you need?
A nice relaxing scratch
on the back.
No! No!
Oh! A lifetime of study
and education down the...
[grunts]
♪ This must be just like
Livin' in paradise ♪
♪ And I don't want to go home ♪
[all] Woo-hoo!
♪ This must be just like
Livin' in paradise ♪
♪ Just like paradise ♪
[all cheer]
♪ And I don't want to go home ♪
♪ And I don't want to go ♪
♪ This must be just like
Livin' in paradise ♪
[belching]
♪ And I don't want to go home ♪
[burps]