♪ The Simpsons ♪
-(chalk screeches)
-(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(tires screeching)
(horn honks)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
Huh?
(barking)
(yelping)
HOMER:
Marge, mail's here.
Bills, bills...
Ooh, a free sample of gasoline!
Um, a note from
Publisher's Clearinghouse
saying we're out
of the running.
Oh, look, Lisa
you got something.
Oh, foreign language
institute.
Oh, my German verb wheel.
Ich esse, er isst, wir essen...
When, when?
Ich bin hungrig.
Homer, this is yours.
Yes!
My precious cartoons.
(laughing)
"Who pumped ethyl?"
Oh, how come
I never get any mail?
I'm sorry, honey.
Here. You can have
the junk mail.
"Gas your termites."
"Freeze your termites."
"Zap your termites."
"Save the termites."
Hello.
"Dear occupant,
"because of your
fine credit history,
you have been pre-approved
for a Moneybank charge card."
Oh, baby!
Okay, let's see now.
"Occupation."
Hmm...
Butt doctor.
"Income."
Whatever I finds, I keeps.
"Name."
Hmm...
"Name. Name."
My name is...
Santa's Little Helper.
(dog barking)
(body thuds)
HOMER:
Marge, mail's here.
Bills, bills...
Oh, a rejection letter
from the New Yorker
subscription department.
Hmm. Who or what
is Santos L. Halper?
Wow! My own credit card!
Thanks, Santos.
(hacks)
A quarter?
Well, you're just the dog
that keeps on giving,
aren't you?
And Zebra Girl and Zillionaire
and Zoidzilla.
And will there be
any more splurging today?
Oh, my, yes. Hmm.
I'll take that hardbound
Radioactive Man collection.
Ah, a superb choice.
In Volume II, Radioactive Man
travels through time
to defeat Jesse Owens
at the 1936 Olympic Games.
Put it all on my credit card,
my good man.
Oh, pardon me, Santos--
if that is your real name,
Bart Simpson--
but your phony credit card
is no good here.
Now, make like my pants
and split.
Oh...
What good's a credit card
if you can't even use it?
Hmm.
"Order by phone.
1-800..."
Our phone doesn't go up to 800.
Unless...
Mom, this is for you--
15 pounds
of Vancouver smoked salmon.
Here. Smell it.
Oh, Bart, you didn't
have to do that.
(sniffs)
Mmm...
And for Homer...
Wow. A golf shirt.
With my corporate logo on it.
(sniffs)
Oh, it smells like salmon, too.
-Thanks, boy.
-And for the college-bound,
500 stay-alert capsules.
Wow. Trucker's choice.
That is so sweet.
Bart, where did you get
all this stuff?
Let me answer
that question with...
Cookware!
A frying pan radio?
Wow.
♪♪ (rock plays)
♪ Girl, you really
got me going ♪
♪ You got me so I don't know
what I'm doing... ♪
(bells ringing,
electronic warbling)
(computerized Japanese voice):
You a winna, ha ha ha!
Halogen lamps? Kilim rugs? You can't
afford this. How can you afford this?
You've been all edgy and suspicious
ever since I gave you those pep pills.
What are you talking about?
I don't need pep pills to be suspicious.
If I want to comment on it,
I'll comment on it.
Who's going to stop me--
you, pep pill boy?
Pep Boys pills,
Beverly Sills.
Oh, boy. Oh, boy. Oh, boy.
Uh-oh. Uh-oh. Oh, boy.
I got to start taking
those pills again.
You think you're so great.
Whoa!
"The crowning achievement
of the dogmaker's art.
"This limited edition collie
comes fully trained
"by Major Jonas Fong,
A.L.B.D.A.
"Only 800 will be bred.
Quite possibly
the world's best dog."
1200 bucks?
I better just get one.
(doorbell chimes)
(barking)
(gasps)
Hey, where you going?
"Hello. My name is Laddie.
"I've been trained
to gather fruit for you
as a welcome gift."
(barks)
Good dog.
(screeches)
Okay, watch this. Watch.
Do a backflip, Laddie.
ALL: Oh! Oh!
He's so smart.
And so handsome.
Bart, I just love him.
Hi, Marge.
Hi, Santa's Little Helper.
Hi, kid.
Hey, that's not
Santa's Little Helper.
That's Laddie.
Bart says he won him
at a church carnival
two towns over.
In a truth-telling contest,
right, Bart?
To the best of my
recollection, yes.
Wow. I got to start
going to church.
What have you got
for me, boy?
Hey, this says
we should feed him
lots of eggs and olive oil
to ensure a glossy coat.
Oh, yes. A dog like this
you have to feed every day.
He's trained to do
all sorts of stuff.
He can herd sheep
and perform C.P.R.
"Some call it the dog
that never sleeps,
though it actually does...
while jogging."
Jeez, that dog has
more education than I do.
He's some kind of super dog.
Hey, where'd he go?
(toilet flushing)
-Ooh!
-Wow!
(phone rings)
Hello.
MAN:
Hello, Mr. Halper.
I'm calling from the Moneybank
credit services department.
I was wondering
if you had a chance
to read the threatening letter
we sent you.
Uh...
Because you sound like
a mature, responsible person
who wouldn't want
an unpaid credit card bill
to spoil all his hopes
and dreams for the future--
dreams such as home ownership,
boat ownership
and event attendance.
Now, when can I tell my
supervisor, Mr. Robinson,
to expect payment?
Good dog.
Come on, boy!
Let's go for a walk!
No, not you. Laddie.
Come on, I got a job for you.
(whimpers)
Good boy.
We didn't see nothing
if you didn't see nothing.
(gasps)
Oh, no.
Repo men!
Laddie, hide behind
that bush there.
Mom and Dad
aren't home, are they?
No. They went for a walk
with the Flanders.
Bart, what's going on? Why are those
repo guys taking all your stuff?
The dog and I got
a credit card and--
Credit card? Oh, I knew you were
up to no good.
Okay, so I committed
a little mail fraud.
Haven't I been
punished enough?
Hey, stop! You can take back
the bassinet,
but the baby's ours!
And the last item
is one $1,200 dog.
-Is that him?
-(snarling)
Well, is he the dog
or isn't he?
(gulps)
Yeah. That's him, all right.
Sorry, boy.
I didn't plan this.
It just sort of happened.
Mom, can I feed Laddie
at the table?
Oh, it's against
the house rule...
Oh, I guess just this once.
Oh, I don't know
about this dog.
He's kind of... snooty.
Homer, are you wearing a tie
to impress Laddie?
Do you think he noticed?
(grumbling)
Where's Santa's Little Helper?
Who?
Um, I took him to a kennel...
two towns over just till
the new dog gets settled.
Well, we wrecked
the first dog.
We've got to treat
this one right.
Bart, why don't you take Laddie
for another walk?
No. Bart had his turn.
Let me!
I can't resist his charms.
Let's all walk Laddie.
Hey, this park is great!
How come we never take
Santa's Little Helper here?
Crowds give him gas.
Besides, he's happy just hanging
around the house with Bart.
Um... yeah.
Hey, that is one fine-looking animal
you got there.
Wow. T.V.'s Kent Brockman!
(laughs)
Hey, this fellow's not
available to stud, is he?
You want some puppies,
eh, Mr. Brockman?
No, no.
Jessica's been fixed.
She just needs a little...
attention.
Why, that canine has
the proud bearing
and glossy fur coat
of a Yale man.
Hello, little fella.
Smithers, I believe this dog
was in Skull and Bones.
Whoa, cool dog!
Can he catch a Frisbee?
(barking)
(cheering)
Boy, Bart Laddie's
the best dog in the world.
He's nothing like
your old dog.
Santa's Little Helper?
Guess I was the only one
who loved him.
You got that right.
Remember the time
he ate my goldfish
and you lied to me and said
I never had any goldfish?
But why'd I have
the bowl, Bart?
Why did I have the bowl?
Yeah.
He was a great dog.
Oh, Santa's Little Helper,
I was crazy to give you up
for another dog.
What have I done to you?
(horn blowing)
Captain, can't we go
any faster?
I greatly fear we shan't be
in Wimbledon by noonfall.
No worries, madam.
Lumley! Shovel on
more dogs, won't you?
Aye, aye.
More dogs!
-(bell ringing)
-More dogs!
In you go.
(gasps)
Nah. That's not too likely.
But still...
you're gone.
Oh.
Where you are you, boy?
(horn blowing)
"Time for a walk."
Ohh! Again?
We got to find out
where he's keeping these.
I'd take him, but those cards
are nontransferable.
Ohh...
CHILD: Help! Help!
(barking)
Now what?
Aw, come on.
I want to go home.
So, Laddie,
thank you for
your heroic rescue.
And, baby Gerald,
we can't help but wonder
what mischief
you'll get into next.
(applause)
Now can we go home?
Laddie saved the day, Simpson.
Boy, we sure could use
a dog like that on the force.
Why don't you guys
take him?
I thought he was
the right dog for me
but I guess
I made a mistake.
Really? No fooling?
Aw, gee,
thanks, mister.
We'll take real
good care of him
and we'll play
with him every day.
Honest.
(grunting)
Oh, Maggie,
you got oatmeal all over.
Homie, would you
clean her off?
Can do.
Laddie!
(whistling)
Come here, boy!
Who wants to lick a messy baby?
-Laddie?
-Uh, Dad?
Laddie's not coming.
-I gave him away.
-What's the matter, Bart?
Weren't you happy with him?
No. He just wasn't
the right dog for me.
I'm sure he'll be happy
as a police dog.
He better know
how to keep his mouth shut.
Well, if that's what
you think is best.
Let's just go down
to the kennel
and get Santa's
Little Helper back.
Uh, well, we can't.
He's not in a kennel.
I gave him away, too,
and I don't know where he is.
You gave both dogs away?
You know how I feel
about giving!
I'm sorry. I know it's wrong.
I messed everything up,
and now I don't have
any dogs at all.
There, there.
Shut up, boy.
We'll just get you a new dog.
I don't want a new dog.
I want Santa's Little Helper.
Well, crying isn't going
to bring him back...
unless your tears
smell like dog food.
So you can either
sit there crying
and eating can after can
of dog food
until your tears
smell enough like dog food
to make your dog come back
or you can go out there
and find your dog.
You're right.
I'll do it.
Rats. I almost had him
eating dog food.
I'm going to get the dog back.
HOMER:
The bad dog or the good dog?
-The bad dog.
-Oh, good.
You got to give me back
my floor.
My customers are walking around
on the pipes!
Hey, next time,
pay your bills.
But I don't want to.
Excuse me, sir. Did you repossess
this dog from a guy
named Santos L. Halper?
Hmm. Yeah, yeah.
I remember this mutt.
We, uh, sold him
to some guy
wearing a dress.
No, I didn't buy your dog.
I got to go keep
an eye on Selma.
She thinks
she swallowed a Band-Aid.
(heavy brogue) Yeah, I bought
your mutt, and I ate him.
(gasps)
I ate his little face.
I ate his guts.
And I 'ate the way
he's always barking!
So I gave him to the church.
Oh, I see. You hate him
so you gave him to the church.
Aye. I also ate
the mess he left on me rug.
You heard me.
Mmm, yes, I remember
Satan's Little Helper...
littering the rectory
with his dirt,
biting me in the apse.
He unholied the holy water.
That's him, all right.
I'll be happy to take him
off your hands.
I'm afraid
that's impossible, Bart.
He's no longer among us.
(gasps)
You didn't crucify him?
(hearty laugh)
No. He's safely with
one of our parishioners.
I'll give you his address,
if you like.
And then,
buy something or get out!
Angel.
Hey, it's him.
It's Santa's Little Helper!
-(buzzes)
-MAN: Yes?
My name is Bart Simpson.
I have to talk to you
about your dog.
Give me one minute.
Okay... showtime.
(wicked laugh)
Please, mister...
(clears throat)
No. Let me do that again.
Please, mister.
(sobbing):
Ple-he-he-he-ase...
(gasps)
Hi, there.
How can I help you?
You're the guy
who owns the dog?
Yep. His name's Sprinkles.
-Sprinkles?
-Yeah. He's my best buddy, huh?
Especially since my parrot
decided to stop talking.
Polly? Polly want to say hi
to our guest? Huh?
Fine. Be that way.
Now, what can I do
for you, son?
Oh, nothing.
Forget it.
So, that's my plan.
I'm gonna break into
the blind man's yard
and swipe the dog.
Bart, that is a new low.
Hey, I'm not saying it's going to be
a dance around the maypole.
I won't tell Mom and Dad
but only because
I want the dog back.
Just try not to freak out
the blind man.
I can't promise I'll try,
but I'll try to try.
(whistles softly)
(whispers):
Here, boy. Come on.
(muffled yelp)
Oh...
(water splashing)
-(squishing)
-Ew!
Psst!
Oh! I missed you
so much, boy.
Come on.
Let's get out of here.
Now, keep quiet, okay?
(barks)
MITCHELL:
Sprinkles?
Is there somebody down there?
Come on, boy.
Let's blow.
Who's there?
I can take you on.
You want to try me?
Come on!
Where is he, Sprinkles?
Come on. Let's get him.
No, no, no. Not the piano.
I can't play now.
-(squeaks)
-(door slams)
Ha! I may be blind,
but you just ran
into a closet.
-D-ohh!
-(lock clicks)
Heh-heh!
Hey, burglar!
I hope you're having
a good time in there,
'cause the police
will be here any minute.
No, mister.
Please, I 'm just a kid.
I... I only came
to get my dog back.
Your dog?
(whines)
And I miss him so much.
And I know you like him,
but I like him, too.
And he was mine first.
I know I don't deserve him.
So what this
comes down to is
you want a blind man
to give up
his only companion?
Yes, please.
Hmm. Tell you what:
Why don't we let
the dog decide?
-Come on, Sprinkles!
-Come on, Santa's Little Helper!
-Here, Sprinkles!
-I'm sorry!
I'm blind,
Come to the blind man!
I'll let you be with me
all the time.
I need you more, come on!
(overlapping chatter)
Come on!
Attaboy!
Oh, I knew you'd come!
Give me a kiss!
Oh-oh-oh. Yeah.
Sounds like you won.
Congratulations.
Oh, geez.
I'm sorry.
I wish there was some way
we could both have a dog.
(pounding)
-(doorbell rings)
-Hello.
Police.
Ah, man, if this one's
not the right house, I quit.
It's okay, Officer.
False alarm.
(barking)
Uh... hey, who's that!
Well, I like you, too.
Well, looks like somebody's
made a new best friend.
(laughs)
Okay, boy.
That's enough.
That's...
That's not for doggies.
Don't...
Oh, jeez.
(barks)
(sniffs)
Marijuana.
Well. I guess he didn't
like you after all.
He just smelled
your narcotics.
Book him, boys.
Hold on, Chief.
It might be medicinal.
Uh... yeah.
M-medicinal.
I... without it,
I could, uh...
go even... blinder.
Right?
Eh, this might take
a while, kid.
Why don't you and your buddy
run along?
Bye, Laddie.
Come on, boy. Let's go home
and have some fun, huh?
That cat's been strutting around
like she owns the place.
(reggae music playing)
♪ Ooh, yeah ♪
LOU:
Hey, hey, everybody.
How are you doing?
Hey, what's up there?
-WIGGUM: I love this song.
-LOU: Hey, Chief.
WIGGUM: Shut up!
I love this song.
-LOU: ♪ Ooh, yeah ♪
-WIGGUM: Shut up, Lou!
♪ I want to jam it
with you ♪
(Wiggum sings over Bob Marley)
♪ We're jammin' ♪
♪ Jammin' ♪
♪ And I hope you like
jammin', too ♪
-LOU: Yeah!
-♪ Ain't no rules, ain't no vow ♪
♪ We can do it anyhow ♪
-♪ I and I will see you through ♪
-LOU: See you through, baby!
♪ 'Cause every day,
we pay the price ♪
-♪ With a little sacrifice ♪
-WIGGUM: ♪ The thing with sacrifice ♪
♪ Jammin' till
the jam is through ♪
-LOU: Jammin's through, baby!
-WIGGUM: ♪ Jamming ♪
-♪ We're jammin' ♪
-WIGGUM: I can't really remember that.
WIGGUM: ♪ We're jamming ♪
♪ To think that jammin'
was a thing of the past ♪
♪ We're jammin'... ♪
LOU: Hey, man, I'm jammin'.
♪ And I hope you like
jammin'... ♪
-Shh!
-WIGGUM: Jamming.
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.