CHOIR: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(exclaiming)
(school bell ringing)
(Barney belches)
(whistle blows)
(yells)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
(grunts)
('60s themed music)
('70s themed music)
(thud)
('80s piano music)
(all yelling)
(sighs)
And that's why I really don't
believe there's a God.
Thank you,
and God bless America.
You were only supposed to lead
us in the Pledge of Allegiance.
I'm pretty sure it was
in there somewhere.
Oh. Now, let me conclude by
thanking Moe the bartender
for hosting this meeting while
City Hall is fumigated for bedbugs.
Bedbugs?
Just why is there a bed
in City Hall?
(crowd murmurs)
Er, uh, meeting adjourned!
(record scratches)
♪ All night long ♪
♪ All night ♪
-♪ All night ♪
♪ All night long ♪
♪ All night ♪
-♪ All night ♪
♪ All night long ♪
♪ All night ♪
-♪ All night ♪
♪ All night long ♪
♪ All night ♪
♪ Unh! ♪
♪ Everyone you meet ♪
♪ They're jamming
in the street ♪
-♪ All night long ♪
-♪ All night ♪
♪ Yeah, I said... ♪
This is so convenient!
I can go straight from
doing my civic duty
to having a beer with
my best friend Carl.
And I can toss back a Duff
Sangre de los Muertos
with my best friend:
Mexican Duffman.
Ho-la!
Hey, Moe,
who's your best friend?
Uh...
Well, uh...
Well, I just made friends
with Pepto-Bismol on Facebook,
and, uh... um...
Hey, would you look at that?
There's a spot on the bar.
-Come on! (grunting)
-(squeaking)
You know what?
I think Moe's best friend
is really that bar rag.
(laughter)
That's even sadder than being
friends with Milhouse!
(chuckles)
You know something, Bart?
I'm getting tired
of things like that.
Tired of what?
I dump on you, and you take it.
That's how friendship works.
Not anymore.
Friendship over.
-Taxi!
-(door slams)
What gives?
He's not crawling back.
Even a kid who wears a "Finding Nemo"
back brace has some pride.
You went too far this time, Bart.
Hey, Moe! I got a job here for
your "best friend," the bar rag.
Me, too!
(laughs)
-(all laughing)
-Oily.
(growls)
Great meeting, though.
Yes, that's right,
everyone laugh at the rag.
But I was not always
this be-stained swatch
you see before you.
Oh, no, gentles.
We begin in early
medieval France...
♪ ♪
BAR RAG: A young peasant wife
struggles to feed her family...
Maman,
we are starving...
Listen to the grumbling
of our estomacs!
(grumbling sounds)
That's not your
estomacs!
It's some men speaking French!
(speaking French)
Now, I have work to do.
Complain to your papa.
Papa?
He is no help at all.
Marguerite, I leave to fight
in Flanders!
Stupid Flanders.
(trumpet fanfare blows)
All tremble before
the duc de Springfield!
That's enough!
Madame, I would like you
to weave me a tapestry
with the following images:
Me healing the sick.
Me killing the healthy.
Me marrying my sister.
A long winter
where nothing happens.
Me relaxing with friends.
You know, the standard stuff.
For this, I shall pay you
two copper coins.
You have 25 years
to complete it.
You may have one
15-minute déjeuner.
(bleating)
Oh, these innocent creatures
are blocking my path.
I could walk six paces
that way...
or I could
kill them all right now!
I am heartily sorry
and confess all my sins.
Absolved!
-Allons-y!
-(neighs)
BAR RAG:
In their dying fury,
those beasts began
expelling demon wool.
And the restless spirits
of those murdered sheep
compelled Marguerite
to loom ceaselessly,
even as her husband
went off to fight
again and again...
and again.
(grunting)
BAR RAG:
As the years went by,
the images she loomed
were not of the Duc,
but rather depictions
of the adventures
that cloth would experience
over the centuries.
Oh, and by the way...
that tapestry was me.
Right, and I was
the Gutenberg Bible.
Maman,
we have failed to grow.
We've had too little food!
Is it too little food
or too much complaining?
Maman, you are overstressed.
You need a vacation.
Perhaps to the
South of France.
We're in the
South of France!
BAR RAG:
One day, as rosy-fingered Dawn
wiped the morning gunk
from her eyes,
the Duc came to claim
his infernal drapes.
What an age for prosthetics
we live in.
Silence!
I have reached my verdict.
-It's not what I expected.
-(gasping)
-And yet... it's beautiful!
-(sighing)
But it's also
not what I expected.
Burn down their house!
(hoofbeat)
(explosion)
BAR RAG: But Le Duc was
about to be called home
to the worst kind of hell:
medieval hell.
-(neighs)
-(yells)
Hey, let's show some French courage
and beat up the corpse!
Come on, Ralphie,
have a try.
Oh! We're submitting that
to France's
Funniest Cave Paintings.
(humming)
Mm-hmm, hm.
BAR RAG: Even for a tapestry
made of demon wool,
this was hard to watch.
I was moved to a
magnificent cathedral
and learned that tapestries
were the rock stars
of the Middle Ages.
(excited screaming)
I had legions of what
you now call groupies.
It felt like the good times
known as the Dark Ages
would never end.
But then cruel fate knocked
upon the door...
(yelling)
Guys, it ain't working--
the door's too strong.
(grunting)
(yelling)
Go, Vikings.
Ow! Stop it!
You just broke
your vow of silence.
It wasn't a vow.
I just didn't want to talk to you.
Oh!
This Viking stuff
is too dangerous.
I'm going to become a gentleman
art thief.
(yells)
(laughing)
Huh?
Hmm, what the...?
(delighted chuckle)
(gasps)
Spooky.
Hmm... hmm.
BAR RAG: That was the first time
I knew anguish and fear.
Nothing will ever staunch
the pain of that memory.
Oh. Well, that helps.
(belches)
-(rock hits window)
-BART: Milhouse!
-Milhouse!
-(sighs)
What do you--
(choking)
Hmm?
What is it, Bart?
Listen, um... after our fight,
I couldn't sleep.
Well, I was doing fine.
Warm glass of milk, some choice cuts
from The Wriggles
and I was out.
Come on, man. At least listen
to what I have to say.
Okay...
Um... well...
this is usually the part
where you say you're sorry.
Bart, I'm not your puppet.
I know, I made you
into a real boy last week.
And I'll always be grateful.
But it's time you started
treating me with respect.
(rocks hitting window)
(sighs)
They're a tough pair, huh?
Kirk--
(choking)
If you let me in,
I'll give you the Heimlich.
Hm-mm.
So to recap:
I had been unjustly torn
from my lofty perch.
I wound up as a barter
in Persia.
You have taken our gold
and jewels and given us
this faded cloth?!
That's right. And if anyone
asked who swindled you,
it was Christians.
Remember that name:
Christians.
(growling)
BAR RAG: I found myself in the court
of the young Persian king,
a cruel king who demanded
constant entertainment
from his wives.
♪♪
Eh. Throw her in
the pit of boring wives.
(thud)
We never go out anymore.
Are you even
listening to me?
My sister
has a much bigger pit.
Dude, you've already discarded,
like, 500 wives.
I think it's weird
that you're counting.
Send in the next one!
Good evening, Your Majesty.
May I tell you your slippers
are as curly as everyone says?
(laughing nervously)
Eh, pit her.
Wait, wait, wait!
I can, uh, tell you a story!
Cease your dragging!
Uh... There once was a boy
named Ali Baba.
He and his elder brother Cassim
were the sons of a merchant
who traded in camels
and spices and--
Okay, just a couple thoughts
on your direction so far.
One day, while out for a walk,
Ali Baba was set upon
by a thief.
-(yawning)
-Make that two thieves!
-(more interested yawn)
-A million thieves!
(yawning)
Too many.
(sighs)
Forty thieves.
(pleasant yawning)
BAR RAG:
With her inventiveness and wit,
the clever wife
entertained her king
for a thousand and one nights.
And while he slept, she freed
her imprisoned compatriots.
Uh, it was cooler in the pit.
And that's how the camel
got its hump. (sigh)
Another story!
(exasperated sigh)
For once, couldn't you just take
a few minutes to let the
previous story sink in?
You dare refuse your king?
Guards!
Uh-oh.
BAR RAG:
My downward spiral continued.
Only cowards use blindfolds.
(screams) I didn't know
you were doing that!
BAR RAG: I was unfit for even
the most sordid uses.
How's your neck, Your Lordship?
No splinters or nuffin'?
I fear the ax
less than that filthy rag.
You talk fancy now, but you'll
twitch like the rest.
All too true, I fear.
Shut up!
Your tongue is even
sharper than your--
BAR RAG: But then, at my lowest ebb,
a moment of hope.
I played a pivotal role
in creating
one of the masterpieces
of Western art.
Michelangelo!
When will you be finished?
Hey, you want a quickie?
You go to Raphael, baby.
BAR RAG:
The artist was never satisfied.
How about now?
Nope.
That's perfect!
Now would you like to
protect your investment
with a clear coat?
Hm, let me discuss it
with my wife.
BAR RAG:
The masterpiece was finished
and so was the use for me.
And then...
(pained moaning)
You know, Moe, it might be time
to buy a new bar rag.
Yeah, yeah, sure thing.
I'll get right on it.
No way I would
abandon you, Raggie.
(sobs)
You're my best friend.
("The Great Pumpkin Waltz"
playing)
(contented sigh)
(music continues)
So, I guess you didn't eat
that "special cheese"
that I gave you yesterday, huh?
(wry chuckle) Yeah.
Oh, Milhouse,
what do I have to do,
besides changing in any way,
to get you to forgive me?
Gee, Bart, you seem,
uh-- how can I put it?--
Milhousey.
Really?
It's not that bad, is it?
(sighs) Bart,
you'll never learn.
"Milhouse, you're the closest
thing I have to a brother.
A brother with the wisdom
of an older sister.
And that's why we squabble,
'cause families always do.
But in the end,
they're still a family.
What do you say... brother?"
Not bad.
Did Lisa write that?
Yes, I did.
Now I'm going to bed.
(sucking pacifier)
I want something that comes from you,
Bart. We're done here.
But-but-but...
The glasses are off!
My degradation continued.
BAR RAG:
An enterprising seamstress
turned me into the flag
of a fledgling nation.
Unfortunately, a nation
on the wrong side of history.
("Dixie" playing)
(chuckles)
BAR RAG: Like everyone else,
I was hit hard by the depression.
(Southern accent)
What's for dinner, Ma?
Rag soup!
(slurping, lips smacking)
Needs flavor.
Mmm, that's better!
BAR RAG:
I was part of an expedition
to the top of Mount Everest,
one that had the distinction
of failing un-heroically.
(panting)
Oxygen...
I need oxygen!
Come on, man.
A few more balloons
and this'll look
really awesome.
D'oh!
Worst... climbing... Everest.
BAR RAG:
A yeti found me
and brought me home
as a present to his son.
Ah, ah!
Mmm...
(sighs) And now my thousand-year
fall from grace is complete.
I guess I should be happy here,
with my sad, but predictable...
Moe! Moe! Wake up!
Oh no, I don't want to find out
what's worse than you!
BART:
Milhouse!
I've been out here
all night, man.
Just let me know what it'll take
for you to forgive me.
-Can I punch you?
-Sure.
Can I have someone else
punch you?
Sure. What've you got?
Puppy Goo-Goo coming my way?
(snaps)
Ay carumba!
I'm glad it's over.
I wasn't comfortable
having the upper hand.
From now on I'll dominate you
in ways you don't realize.
That's all I ever wanted.
Where'd it go?
Hey, Chief Wiggum!
Can you help me find my bar rag?
I can't even find my car
in the parking lot at the mall.
There was half a kilo of heroin
and two suspects inside.
-Hey! Hey!
-(tires squealing, gunshots)
Can you throw me my house key?
Please!
It's got a green thingy on it!
-Stop!
-(tires screech)
Ooh!
Hey, there's some
Pringles in here.
-(metal tab pops)
-(coughs) Nope. Tear gas.
-(coughing)
-(tires squealing)
Haven't forgotten
about your rag, Moe!
I'm in hell, I'm in hell,
I'm in hell,
I'm in hell... (grunts)
(wearily)
Perhaps one of you garments
would like to narrate
for a while.
Men's extra large underwear?
I'm saving my strength.
He's going bike riding today.
(humming)
-(doorbell rings)
-Come on in!
You've got my rag!
But how?
Well, during
the town meeting,
which now seems
like years ago,
I forgot my purse
at your bar.
MARGE:
And when I came back to get it,
I saw how much
you love that rag.
Num-num-num-num-num-num.
MARGE:
It seemed a little "ripe,"
so I brought it home
to clean it for you.
Thanks, Marge.
That rag is my only friend
in the world.
Well, that's not true!
Everyone in this family
is your friend.
Your bar is the closest
thing this town has
to an Algonquin roundtable.
What about that Round Table Pizza
run by that Algonquin guy?
Yeah, yeah,
okay, second closest.
So you's all like me?
Even you, Maestro?
Milhouse.
Yeah, I, I knew
it was something stupid.
Well, thanks, everybody.
I... I'm always gonna
remember today as the day
that I learned to open
my heart to human beings
and not old pieces of cloth.
Ha, crazy me, thinking
I needed a rag for a friend.
(chuckles)
So, this is how it ends.
The once magnificent
tapestry tossed aside
yet again like a common Kleenex.
Good-bye, cruel...
What the...?
In all my years,
this is a love
like I have never felt.
Sweet, pure and forever.
(sweet melody playing)
(growling)
BAR RAG: Well, all marriages
have their ups and downs.
BAR RAG:
I'm in hell.
Subtitled by A. Vandelay