♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
Okay, Ron.
Which one of our girls
said the following about you?
"He looked so sexy,
I hoped we would have sex."
Well, that's a tough one,
'cause I did the deed
with Ouda, Candy, and Shasta.
(giggling)
It's true, alright.
But I'm going to have
to go with Shasta,
'cause she liked makin' bacon
on the beach.
Ooh. Me too.
-Ohh, bacon.
-(knocking)
Mr. Simpson, my husband and I
have decided to move.
Going to run out the clock
in Florida, eh?
Yes. Well,
there's a few things
you could do
to help us sell our home.
First, whenever you walk
in front of your window,
-could you please wear pants?
-Mmm, no.
Second, could you please take in
your jack-o'-lanterns
from past Halloweens?
Mmm, no.
And please cover your garbage.
It's attracting wildlife.
What?
Hey, moose! Shoo!
Yeah, I'm talking to you.
Get off my lawn. Now!
(yells)
Hello. What's this?
Wire hangers, expired medicine,
old newspapers...
(gasping)
Okay, Homer, stay calm.
Just quietly get this stuff
inside your house.
Homer, you're not listening.
That medicine's not for you.
Come on, Marge.
Maybe I'm not getting enough...
"Estrogen."
Give me that.
Ahoy, mateys.
Had your fill of tacos?
Would ye sooner eat a bilge rat
than another burger?
Then come for
all-you-can-eat seafood
at the Frying Dutchman.
(moaning)
Is it more iced tea
ye be needing?
-Okay.
-(laughs gruffly)
Set sail
for the Frying Dutchman.
Aye, aye, Captain.
Marge, we're going
to that restaurant.
But I think
I'm allergic to seafood.
The last time I ate shrimp,
my throat closed up
and I went into convulsions.
Mmm... shrimp.
Now, I don't know much
about haggling or bargaining,
so why don't we just agree
to pay whatever the Winfields want.
-That could work.
-(belch in distance)
-What was that?
-Sigh.
HOMER:
Hmm? There you are.
Thought you could get away, huh?
Good-bye.
Hmm!
I don't think
we should be down here.
Nervous, Lise?
I don't blame you.
This is where the Winfields hid
their mutated son.
Bart! The Winfields
didn't have a son.
See that sock over there?
It was his only friend.
Hello, Lisa.
Here in the dark
you won't need those eyes.
Let me have them.
Bart! That's not funny.
There are some who say
the monster is still...
-here!
-(screaming)
(yells)
(laughs)
Friend.
Friend...
(yells)
(body thuds)
-GIRL: Hey, kid, wake up.
-BART: Who are you?
I'm Laura, your new neighbor.
You all right?
She's beautiful.
Say something clever.
I fell on my bottom.
D'oh!
(glass shatters)
Oh, not again.
My mother's inside,
Mrs. Simpson.
Please go right on in.
Oh, you speak so politely
to adults.
My upbringing
was painfully strict, ma'am.
That's sweet.
MARGE: And finally,
Moe's tavern has contributed a coupon
as their way of saying
"Welcome to Springfield."
Thank you,
this is all so nice.
I actually had some doubts
about moving to Springfield.
Especially after
that Time cover story,
"America's Worst City."
-You can see our house in that photo.
-Oh.
And this is for the man
of the house...
Mmm... which I guess is you.
-Mmm.
-I guess I should explain.
Laura's father and I
divorced two years ago.
They're so sweet
when you marry them.
But soon it's just
career, career, career.
My hammock!
Do you understand?
Mine! Don't look that way.
(groans)
I bet you don't know
this one.
How would you like
a hurts doughnut? Ow!
Hurts, don't it?
(chuckles)
Right. Do you know
what a wet willy is?
Is it this?
Hey, baby, how about putting
your finger in my ear?
I don't know. Your boyfriend
looks like the jealous type.
-Hey, what the--
-That kid's messing with our minds.
-Let's get out of here.
-Now, where were we?
-Oh, yeah, I was gonna tell your fortune.
-Huh?
Oh, man, you're gonna be rich.
Whoa!
There's your mansion.
There's the tennis court.
(hawks and spits)
And there's the swimming pool.
See you later, Bart.
(chuckles)
I'll never wash this hand
again.
LISA: Dad, make Bart
wash his hand.
Sorry, Lise, I no longer
control the hand.
-The hand controls me.
-Dad!
Shut up,
you little monsters!
Hello, I was wondering if you'd
like to baby-sit my little angels?
Sorry. This isn't Abby.
This is her sister.
I look after her now.
No, Bart, put it down.
Put it down, Bart.
Bart, put it down.
Aw, no all-you-can-eat
seafood.
I wore my extra-loose pants
for nothing.
Nothing!
-Maybe Laura could watch us.
-Oh, I get it.
Bart, the baby-sitter's here.
Let me tuck you in.
(kissing)
Silence!
Huh?
(yells)
Maybe it's time
I washed my hand.
I'll send Laura over
to baby-sit
as soon as she gets home.
Great. Oh, and there was
something else--
something I was supposed
to tiptoe around.
-My divorce.
-That's it. Whoo-hoo!
I'm glad one of us
remembered.
That could have been
embarrassing.
Well, I know what
you're thinking,
and the answer is yes.
I want to be fixed up
with one of your friends
as soon as you can arrange it.
After all, Homer,
I do have the normal appetites.
(chuckles)
I know what you mean.
Just let me make sure
we're not talkin' about food.
-I'm not.
-Right. Me neither.
-We're talking about sex, right?
-Right.
I hear you loud and clear.
(purrs)
Bart, are you taking a bath?
Yes, I am,
and it would be nice
to have a little privacy
around here for a change.
This wouldn't have anything to do
with Laura coming over, would it?
Hey, sometimes a guy just likes
his skin to look its yellowist.
Why, Laura,
what a pleasant surprise.
Cute. What do you
guys want for dinner?
I don't care.
Ask Hef over there.
Ladies' choice.
(clock ticking)
Sometimes I think you want
to fail!
Shut up. Just shut up!
(ringing)
We used to eat this
when my dad was stationed
in Vandahar.
Take your kafta bi sanya
and dip it in the labna.
Now that is good labna.
I'm sorry, ma'am, but everything
on the menu has fish in it.
What about the bread?
Does that have much fish in it?
-Yes.
-Well, I have some Tic-Tacs in my purse.
Excellent choice.
And for the gentleman?
All you can eat!
All right, when you're ready,
take this plate over--
Please, don't take
the steam tray. Sir!
Come on, Bart,
if I can teach Maggie to waltz,
I can teach you.
Just follow me
and put your hand on my hip.
(voice cracking)
Okay.
♪♪ (waltz)
-Wedgie!
-Whoa.
(neon sign buzzing)
(chomping and chewing)
(snoring)
That man ate all our shrimp
and two plastic lobsters.
'Tis no man.
'Tis a remorseless
eating machine.
Arrrggg.
Six bells.
Time for closing.
Can't talk.
Eating.
Fairly warned be thee, says I.
(snapping fingers)
Hey. Hey!
(Homer yelling)
But the sign said
"All you can eat."
Mmm.
I'm going to fight
this thing.
Oh, please don't.
For me.
Sorry, Marge,
this is my quest.
I'm like that guy.
That Spanish guy.
You know,
he fought the windmills?
-Don Quixote?
-No, that's not it.
What's his name?
The Man of La Mancha.
-Don Quixote.
-No!
I really think that was
the character's name, Don Quixote.
Fine.
I'll look it up.
Well, who was it?
-Never mind.
-Mm-hmm.
(bell ringing)
Oh, no, here comes
the conservative judge.
(judge growling)
-Plead insanity. Plead insanity!
-It's not working.
All right. Hit the change
of venue button! Now!
Oh, no,
you're in Texas.
If I'd hit the remorse button
one more time I would have made it.
Oh, Bart, I gotta go.
See you around.
-I am thinking you like this girl, yes?
-How did you know?
My ceiling mirrors and video cameras
sometimes see more
than who is
about to shoot me.
All you can eat. Ha!
Mr. Simpson, this is
the most blatant case
of fraudulent advertising
since my suit
against the film
the Neverending Story.
So, do you think
I have a case?
Homer, I don't use the word
"hero" very often,
but you are the greatest hero
in American history.
(cheering)
-I'm here to see my Grampa.
-Here I am, sonny.
You're not my Grampa.
Aw, come on,
give me a chance.
Hey, can your grandfather
do this?
Hey! Ha! Hoo!
Hey! Ha! Oh!
Bart! Aw, you remembered
my birthday.
Huh? Oh, I sure did.
Here's a bus schedule.
Wow! Fits right in my pocket.
Grampa, I need some advice.
Did you ever have a crush
on an older woman?
I had a crush
on the oldest woman.
120 years old, she was.
Here's a picture of her
delivering Eubie Blake.
What happened?
She fell in with that
Guinness Book of Records crowd.
Suddenly she didn't
have any time for me.
Oh, I wore a 15-pound
beard of bees
for that woman,
but it just wasn't enough.
Dad, I have some questions
about women.
Uh, can't you see I'm reading
the... cultural calendar?
Ooh, "Mostly Mozart" is in town.
Homer, Bart's at
a very curious age.
As his father,
I think you should have
a frank and earthy
discussion about...
Mmm, you know.
But Marge,
I think he should learn
about it
the same way I did.
Are you sure?
Hmm...
Zoo keeper! Zoo keeper!
Those two monkeys
are killing each other.
(whispers)
They're having sex.
Oh.
Maybe you're right.
Now if you'll excuse us...
this is a sacred moment
between a boy and his father.
Son, a woman
is a lot like, um...
a refrigerator.
They're about six feet tall,
300 pounds.
They make ice, and...
Oh, wait a minute.
Actually, a woman
is more like a beer.
They smell good,
they look good.
You'd step over your own
mother just to get one.
But you can't stop at one.
You want to drink
another woman.
So I says, "Yeah?
If you want that money,
"come and find it,
"'cause I don't know
where it is, you baloney.
You make me want to retch."
(snoring)
Hmm, how can I get her
to notice me?
Meet me at the tree house, Bart.
And come alone.
(gulps)
Thanks for coming.
(voice cracks)
I please to aim.
I'm so happy.
I just had to tell someone.
I have a boyfriend.
You won't be needing this.
(pumping)
(groaning)
A boyfriend?
I really think
you'd like him, Bart.
His name's Jimbo.
Jimbo Jones?
(toilet flushing)
-(muffled yelling)
-(knocking)
You've been flushing
for 20 minutes.
Is there a problem?
Uh... no, Principal Skinner.
Very well.
I'll continue to wait.
-(toilet flushing)
-(Skinner humming)
(whistling)
(flushing continues)
How can you like that guy?
I don't know, maybe
'cause he's an outlaw.
You know that dead body
they found
behind the mayor's house?
Jimbo killed him?
No, but he poked him
with a stick.
Hey, Laura,
Dr. Tongue has arrived.
That's him, Bart.
-Who's the dork?
-Leave him alone.
He's just a kid.
(echoing)
Just a kid...
I'll show them
who's just a kid.
MARGE:
Bart, it's your bedtime.
I laid out your jammy-jams.
(groans)
(growling and chomping)
Dad, if there's
a really special girl
and she likes some clod
who's beneath her,
what should you do?
I married her.
(chuckles)
Homer, please.
(hiccups)
I just had eggs.
Good luck in your trumped-up
lawsuit, Dad.
Thanks.
That means a lot to me.
All right, you guys, I want you guys
in bed before Jimbo gets here.
What do you like about him?
He's just a good-looking rebel
who plays by his own rules.
-(sighing)
'Twas a moonless night,
dark as pitch,
when out the mist
came a beast
more stomach than man.
-Hey!
-So I says to me bosun's:
"Batten down
the mizzenmast, mateys."
Captain McAllister,
isn't it a fact
that you're not
a real captain?
-Aye.
-(murmuring)
Your Honor, I would like
to show the court
just how much shrimp
Mr. Simpson ate.
Bring it in, boys.
18,000 letters all addressed
to Santa Claus.
You want The People of
Springfield v. Kris Kringle.
-That's next door.
-Oh.
Mrs. Simpson,
isn't it true
your husband once consumed
a ten-pound bag of flour
when no other food
was available?
-Yes, but it was--
-Your witness.
-Uh, there's a pizza here for--
-Right here.
Mrs. Simpson, what did
you and your husband do
after you were ejected
from the restaurant?
We... pretty much
went straight home.
Mrs. Simpson,
you're under oath.
We drove around
until 3:00 a.m.
looking for another
all-you-can-eat fish restaurant.
(excited murmuring)
And when you
couldn't find one?
We went fishing.
(sobbing)
Did these sound like
the actions of a man
who had all he could eat?
-Not at all!
-No!
That could have been me.
Homer,
I've a proposition for ye
fair and true.
Come on, Marge.
Let the people see
your pretty face.
Come see Bottomless Pete,
nature's cruelest mistake.
Come for the freak,
stay for the food.
WOMAN:
Oh, he's hideous.
MAN:
I heard they shaved a gorilla.
Hey, baby,
my shirt's chafing me.
Mind if I take it off?
Well... okay.
I got to do something.
Hmm.
But it says "Good for
one free beer at Moe's."
This is Moe's tavern,
isn't it?
No. This is Bo's Cavern.
Give me my beer.
Stupid welcome-mobile.
I knew it would ruin me.
(phone ringing)
Just a sec, I'll check.
Uh... Amanda Huggenkiss?
Hey, I'm looking
for Amanda Huggenkiss.
Why can't I find
Amanda Huggenkiss?
(loud laughter)
Maybe your standards
are too high.
You little S.O.B.!
If I ever find out
who you are
I'm gonna shove a sausage
down your throat
and stick starving dogs
in your butt.
My name is Jimbo Jones
and I live
at 1094 Evergreen Terrace.
Aha! Big mistake, pal!
I knew he'd slip up
sooner or later.
Ah, yes. Rusty and dull.
Barney, don't steal
any beer while I'm gone.
What kind of pathetic drunk
do you take me for?
(gasps)
Somebody spilled beer
in this ashtray.
-(slurping)
-Ah.
(grunting)
(maniacal laughter)
MOE: Let's see,
where is that map?
Evergreen Terrace...
There it is, F-5.
(maniacal laughter continues)
I don't believe it.
Now my pants
are chafing me.
(shouts)
All right.
Who's Jimbo Jones?
I am.
You just made your
second mistake, buddy boy.
Please, dude,
don't hurt me.
Oh, man!
-(crying)
-That's your outlaw?
I wasn't really going to kill ya.
I was just going to cut ya.
(sobbing)
Aw, forget it.
Ouch! I better
go check on Barney.
(slurping)
Uh-oh, my heart just stopped.
Ah! There it goes.
(grunting)
-(loud thud)
-Ow!
Stupid wishing well.
Jimbo, I don't think
we should see
each other anymore.
You're just not the guy
I thought you were.
(sniffling)
Can I have my shirt back?
(blows nose)
Well, Bart,
you were right about him.
As usual,
a knife-wielding maniac
has shown us the way.
You know, if you
were only old enough
to grow a bad
teenage moustache,
I'd go out
with you in a second.
Wow.
Hello. I'd like to speak
to Ms. Tinkle.
First name...
(whispers)
Ivana.
Ivana Tinkle.
Just a sec.
Ivana Tinkle?
Ivana Tinkle!
All right, everybody,
put down your glasses.
Ivana Tinkle!
(loud laughter)
Har, har, har.
(laughing)
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.