Everyone...
...was napping.
- Ahmed Adoody.
- Wait, there's...
- My people...
- Come down to the stu...
Steamed ham.
The cosmic ballet goes on.
- Gigantism.
- King of the world!
Oh, this is the best gift
of all, Homer.
- It is?
- What's his name?
Number Eight.
I mean,
Santa's Little Helper.
Why does Homer talk
like Walter Matthau?
Hey, Martin Princess.
If you like that cello so much,
why don't you marry it?
- No heckling.
- Way to quash 'em, sir.
Hey, Skinner, if you like
Chalmers so much,
why don't you marry him?
Well, as the superintendent,
he's married to all
the principals.
Thank you.
You've made the anniversary
of my wife's death
even more depressing.
Who likes happy songs?
Well, for those of you
who didn't cheer,
here's a very sad song
about the world today.
She loves me.
She loves me not.
Oh, why do I always use flowers
with two petals?
Simpson, pull the fire alarm.
You want me
to embarrass my sister
in front of the whole school?
No.
I dared you.
Don't do it, Bart.
Please. I love you.
I'm not doing it.
I'm refusing a dare.
You just signed
your death warrant, Simpson.
And we're the witnesses.
All we need is a notary.
- Notary. Notary.
- We'll see.
Oh, it's that kid
who refused a dare.
His life is ruined.
I'm turning my back on you.
Hi, Bart.
Simpson, I'd like to see you
in my office.
Your parents are waiting.
Bart's got a dad.
I do not.
Bart, I just want to say...
I'm so proud of you.
Dad, do you think
I did the right thing?
Of course, absolutely.
You did the worst thing
any boy can do.
It's worse than wetting
your pants while on Santa's lap,
and I've been on both sides
of that one.
I'm sorry.
Bart, you have to take a dare.
- But what if it's...?
- Any dare.
Grampa, Dad says
I have to take a dare.
I had Homer on a dare,
and as horrible as that
worked out, I'd do that again.
Why did someone dare you
to have Homer?
It was after the war,
we needed babies.
Bart, I have a secret.
I've never been happier
to be your mother.
You're a good boy.
Mom, please.
Somebody might hear you.
Oh, look at him!
Bart's mom wears
a seat belt.
Let them laugh, Bart.
This is wonderful.
Every laugh turns into one more
smoochie-poo from Mom.
Cut it out.
Three cheers for
the mama's boys.
Sorry to do this
on Mother's Day!
So, Simpson,
word on the street is
you're looking for a dare.
Yeah, fine.
I need to get this monkey
off my back.
Hey, how about that for a dare?
Putting a monkey on his back.
And after we're done, then what?
We have a monkey that's
our permanent responsibility.
Yeah, think ahead, dingus.
Simpson, I dare you to jump
into the reservoir
from Dead Boy's Ledge.
We'll be watching
from Haw-Haw Heights.
Simpson, is that your kid?
Oh, my God.
I've got to stop him!
I dare you not to.
It was a joke, idiot.
Get your kid.
Bart!
Do I really have to do this?
I dare you.
Dare you. Dare you.
Dare you.
I love Echo Canyon.
Oh, this place sure has
a lot of names.
Cowabunga!
We've done all we could.
Run!
Beat it!
He'll be fine.
And my burrito's ready.
Your boy should wake up soon.
All right. This time,
he's really done it.
We're gonna have
to do something.
Change schools. Move.
Whatever it takes.
Mom?
- Sweetie, are you okay?
- I am.
Then why would you do such
a stupid, stupid thing?
Marge, Marge.
As someone who's fallen off
a cliff multiple times,
the best thing we can do
is teach him how
to fall off cliffs.
I just want to know, Bart.
I had hope and now I don't.
Why?
Please, O Lord.
Let him think of an awesome lie.
Well, when I was
in the other world...
What other world?
I'm not sure.
But it was joyful, clouds,
harps, Abe Lincoln.
Oh, my God, Marge!
I think our son went to heaven.
Were there any other presidents?
- No.
- It was heaven. What else, boy?
I have a message for you, Mom.
- From who?
- Jesus.
Don't say that if it's not true.
You have to believe him, Marge.
It's a deathbed confession.
He's not on his deathbed.
The guy in the bed
before him died.
Mom. Jesus said to tell you,
things will get better.
Oh, I really want
to believe that.
If you saw Jesus,
did you see anything else?
I saw your dad, Grandpa Bouvier.
Tell me something he said
that only I would know.
He said...
he thinks Homer is an idiot.
Oh, my God, I can hear
his voice through you.
Excuse me a minute.
Good work, boy.
You got us off the hook
in the short term,
which is all that ever matters.
- Tell me more about heaven, son.
- Jesus rides a rainbow horse.
Fascinating.
Is the horse rainbow-colored?
Or does it walk on a rainbow?
Rainbows come out
its butt.
Let me ponder that with joy.
Tell me more, son.
Well, there's no cracks
on the sidewalks.
And saying you brushed
your teeth makes it true.
You can go to baseball games
with all the dead players.
And you always catch a home run.
And the angels talk
to each other like this...
Does this Jesus
have any tattoos
or distinguishing marks?
No, but he really thinks
the sermons are too long.
Boys, we're gonna have a talk
with the Reverend.
Bart.
I've held my tongue,
because I appreciate
you not ruining my song.
Can't ruin what already sucks.
Burn.
All right.
I'm just gonna say it.
I don't think
you really saw Jesus.
You know, the Lord warned me
there'd be disbelievers.
Begone!
I don't know why you're
doing this, but beware,
little lies lead to big lies.
And big lies get punished.
That's the Devil ringing
that bell.
Are you gonna answer?
Hey, don't think you can scare
the boy who died
and went to heaven.
Get the door.
Hey, cut it out.
Oh, no, it's stuck.
Hello, Bart.
We are Christian
movie producers.
So, you give all your profits
back to the church?
You...
Could you...
Could you get your dad?
Homer, we're the best
in the business.
Our films average 98%
on Rotten Communion Wafers.
Now, we'd like to tell
your son's story.
You want to make a movie
out of what happened to Bart?
Well, absolutely.
Unless it's not true.
Okay, I could admit
the boy totally lied
or I could make a movie
inspired by true events.
Brother Homer,
why do you hesitate?
I hesitate because I am stunned
that you doubt the Word of God!
Then we have a deal.
Not so fast.
Like most of America, I think
I know the movie business.
Please. What would you like?
I want input on the script.
I want two seats
to the premiere.
And my wife needs
a seat as well.
And I'm not thanking
the Georgia Film Commission,
no matter what.
We will need to pray on this,
Brother Homer.
Of course. So will we.
Kneel down, boy.
What for?
Because we're going to pray
like we often do.
Heavenly God, who art in heaven,
holler out your name.
Thy Kingdom come.
I'm almost done.
Can this square join
your circle?
Absotively-posilutely.
In that same spirit,
I'm glad to hear it.
- Oh, hi-diddly-do. A-dum-dum-diddly.
- Diddly-doodly, brother.
- Diddly-doodly-diddly-dice.
- Diddly. Diddly.
- Nice to diddly meet you.
- Brotherino.
I heard movie meetings were
horrible, but I had no idea.
Well, perhaps you could write
the screenplay
with Brother Homer.
I don't think so.
Wait, wait, wait.
I'm being filled
with the spirit of Jesus.
Oh, yeah? What's he saying?
He says he wants Dad
and Mr. Flanders
to work together day after day
in a tiny room,
preferably holding hands.
Why, you...
No booze, sodas,
or chocolate milk.
And the only snacks
are celery sticks.
Celery sticks.
Not done yet.
Dad, Jesus wants you
to take Flanders bowling.
Tie his shoes for him.
- What for?
- And kiss his ball.
- Why, you...
- This is the Word of the Lord.
With that kind of attention,
I could roll a 73.
What are you guys doing?
What's it look like?
We're working.
Maybe we should take a break.
Good idea.
Okay, come on.
Lenny, you've pitched, that's
what she said, 30 times already.
I highly doubt
that's the Word of God.
- Try something else.
- That's what she said.
That's great!
That's going in.
Mine. Mine. Mine. Mine.
Lenny and me. Mine.
Mostly mine. Mine. Mine.
I was thinking it
when Barney said it. Mine.
Reading for Marge...
Emily Deschanel.
Oh, yeah. First,
I have a question for you.
On Bones, did you ever have any
bones with meat left on them,
and if so,
where are those bones?
Maybe she should just
read the part.
Homie, because
of everything that's happened,
I think we need to take a break.
No! Marge, no!
A break means forever.
I'll change. I will.
No, Homer,
she's just acting the part.
Oh, of course,
of course, yes.
As a help to me,
when you're acting,
could you hold up one hand
so I'll know?
Oh, okay.
- Thank you.
- Homie.
Yes, Marge.
You have a question?
She's acting!
Right, right, right.
She's acting.
When you're acting,
could you raise one arm
and swing your foot in a circle
and keep winking?
Listen, Homie.
Marge, what are you doing?!
You're acting really weird.
Is he okay?
You thought I was okay
when you married me.
Actors.
Gal Gadot reading for Lisa.
- You've got the part!
- Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I know you were great
in Fast and Furious,
but what else have you been in?
Did you see Wonder Woman?
Whenever I see the DC logo,
I immediately fall asleep.
Homer, she's got the part.
Okay, you get this
and I get Gene Hackman for me.
He already said no.
Then you have
to help me kidnap him.
Excuse me.
So, do you want
to put me on tape or...?
Hey! Can we use your magic lasso
to kidnap Gene Hackman?
No.
Barney is here to read for Noah.
There's no Noah in this movie.
All right,
but you better tell the camels.
Mom, do you really believe
Bart's story?
Lisa, do you know how I've
gotten to this point in life?
Two things...
blind faith and a little wine.
Can you get me the wine that
I keep in Mommy's knitting basket?
I know where you keep it.
There was no knitting in there.
Jesus said to tell you,
things will get better.
And... cut.
I wish you and I had
a relationship like that.
Why, you little...
They wish they had
a relationship like us!
There is nothing a director
can do on set that's wrong.
Take five, everybody.
What do you want?
I told you,
lies lead to punishment,
especially when you film them.
What are you talking about?
If you really saw
Grandpa Bouvier,
which finger was he missing?
I believe he was wearing
a beekeeping outfit
when I saw him.
Trick question.
He's missing a leg.
Okay.
So maybe I fudged a few things.
It's not the original lie
that gets people.
It's the cover-up.
It's gonna get worse and worse
and worse and worse and worse.
Dad, I'm starting to feel weird.
I'm not your Dad.
I'm the actor playing him.
You need all that
padding to play Homer?
Yes, and I'm fat to begin with.
Okay, this one's for China.
This one's for Australia.
And this one's
for the youth market.
- Dad?
- This is all because of you.
I have never been so excited.
Now what do you want to say?
Is there anything
you want to tell anyone?
Any inaccuracies
or blatant lies?
The scene we said is New York
is actually downtown Calgary,
and vice versa.
No, no. I'm going to heaven!
Hello, Bart.
Didn't they give you
a real leg in heaven?
I lost it in a bet.
A bet that my grandson
was a good boy.
Save me, Jesus!
I'm trying very hard
to forgive you.
It is very tough.
What are you gonna do to me?
Bart, God is love.
And here's Marge
with the actress who played her.
Oh, in real life
we don't get along.
Who are you worshipping?
Are you telling the truth?
He will not be taking
any questions
unless they're submitted
in writing
on an index card
with some bacon on it.
Turkey bacon does not count.
Tell the people what
you have witnessed, Bartholomew.
And if they doubt you, viciously
attack their character.
Yes, Jesus.
Bart, you're my hero.
Now, who wants a hamburger?
I would never say any
of those things.
Now sing, Bart.
Sing because I cannot.
One more chance
It is my destiny
To start my road
To Christianity
I always knew
he had a mission
Thank God we called off
the mortician
One more chance
He's alive,
someone quick call Channel 5
One more chance
Not enough Bart.
Oh, someone pinch me.
Thank you. Thank you
for this Christian Oscar.
And I'd like to thank
the Academy of Arts
and Anti-Sciences.
Are you guys awake?
What's the matter, sweetie?
Mom, I lied about everything.
Oh, my God!
Don't worry, Marge.
It's just a little movie.
Nobody will see it.
Mr. Flanders just called.
The movie's on pace to make
a hundred million dollars.
It crushed all the good movies
that came out this week.
Take that, Paul Thomas Anderson.
Oh, my God.
Our movie's a hit and a lie.
Oh, all hit movies are lies,
Marge.
Did you see Argo?
None of that happened.
And I have strong doubts
about The Incredibles.
Well, we have
to tell people the truth.
Of course, of course.
Could we do it after
the Golden Globes?
No!
But that's the one
with TV people
and movie people
in the same room.
We said no!
First off,
we will donate every penny
of our profits to charity.
Keeping only enough money
to cover changing our lives
in a major way.
Hey, what is this?
Fine, fine, fine, all of it.
Okay, look, I just want to say,
I'm just a man
trying to raise his son.
I make mistakes.
Sometimes they're little,
sometimes they're big.
Blame me, but don't blame
the boy for being a boy.
And let me just ask this.
Is it possible
any other religious beliefs
are founded on myths?
This interview is over.
God created the world
in seven days. See you later.
In what some are calling
the worst scandal
in the history of religion,
Bart Simpson lied
when he claimed
he had talked to Jesus.
But maybe
part of the fault lies with us
for desperately wanting a
miracle in these troubled times.
Times which we bring into your
homes at 5:00, 6:00 and 11:00.
Here's a hobo lost
in a hurricane.
I had a hat!
Hey, Bart.
I brought you some ice cream.
Up here.
The only friend I have is
the Frisbee on the roof.
Well, you'll always have me.
Careful.
Dad didn't nail these in
too well.
You think God will forgive me?
Don't tell anyone I said that.
Well, if there is a God,
from what I know,
said God will forgive you
if you truly have remorse
in your heart.
Well, thanks, Lis.
Don't tell anyone
I asked you that.
I did it 'cause you're
the smartest person I know.
And don't tell anybody
I said that.
I won't!
Dad must have raked
the leaves today.
Now that's a miracle.
I made it.
Gal Gadot?!
They like me so much,
I get to visit.
I made it too, boy, and
Jesus really wants to meet you.
Go on in!
Where are you going?
This place is so boring.
Time for another game
of Mother, May I?
Please send me back to Earth.
Yes, yes. You can be a turtle
or a pharmaceutical CEO.
Turtle, please.
He's alive,
someone quick call Channel 5