The Simpsons
D'oh!
Dream
Dream, dream, dream
Ooh, Jar Jar,
everyone hates you but me.
In my arms when I want you
Cool! Mom's on drugs.
If we turn her in,
we can get a form letter
from Dick Cheney.
She's not on drugs.
She couldn't sleep
because of Dad's
chronic snoring.
I'm taking him
to Dr. Hibbert's
this afternoon.
You know how hard it is
to get a doctor
on Wednesday morning.
Yah!
I haven't lost
so much sleep
since little Bartie
had the scoots.
Well,
there's a surgical option,
but it's not cheap.
Here's what it costs.
Interesting.
Here's my counteroffer.
Get out.
I'll get it!
Pedals, people!
So Lisa,
do you have a date
for the harvest dance?
This is not a good time!
It's never a good time!
Overnight bag,
no husband in sight!
It's happened!
She left Homer?
I'll get the Champale.
And let's get
that ring off.
Whoa, whoa,
whoa, Delilah.
I didn't leave Homer,
and I never will.
I just need one night away
from his snoring.
Great. We'll have
a girls night.
No bras!
Let's catch the tail end
of Nooky in New York.
Nooky in New York?
It's a cable show
about four single women
who act like gay men.
That sounds great!
If I'm not having sex
by the end of this
goat cheese quesadilla,
I'm gonna scream.
I also enjoy sex.
Since this morning,
I've had sex with
a New York Knick,
two subway cops
and a guy who works
on Wall Street.
Broker?
Nah, she's just
really sore.
This is so like our lives.
It's like
they hid a camera
in our apartment.
Coming up next
on BHO, it's Arli$$.
Ah!
Gentlemen,
start your envy!
Men's World Magazine
has listed the 100
richest men in the country,
and coming in
at number five
is Springfield native
Artie Ziff.
Ooh.
Whoa! Your old boyfriend.
Please.
We went out once.
Artie made mega bucks with
a revolutionary invention,
a converter that changes
that horrible modem noise
into easy listening music.
Also available
with lyrics.
Hey, computer geek
You will be
connected in no time
What a catch.
Why didn't you sink
your claws into him
at the prom?
Yeah. He was warm
for your form.
Well, he seemed like
a sweet little shrimp.
But then he turned
into an octopus.
Artie! Artie, no!
Stop!
Marge. Marge, you know
you can't resist
my busy hands.
Artie, get off of me!
Well, I think you should
get in touch with him,
you know, just to
congratulate him
on his success.
Well, I suppose
I could write him
a letter.
Are you nuts?
E- mail, female.
You just tell us
what you want to say.
Okay, hold onto your hats.
Dear Artie.
Dear Hottie.
Congratulations
on your recent
TV appearance.
I want to sex you up.
Your love slave, Marge.
You can't
use the word "sex"
on the Internet.
Watch me!
Anti-trust suit.
Anti-trust suit...
A note from
Marge Simpson?
Well, isn't that
a coincidence?
I was just
thinking about her.
For the last 20 years.
Mom,
did you sleep well
at your sisters'?
Mmm-hmm.
Whoo!
Mmm.
For you.
Ooh!
Here's to a happy,
well-rested Marge.
Hey, a helicopter's
landing on our lawn.
Let's approach
with caution.
Unguarded breakfasts.
The sweetest taboo.
Ooh.
Well, well,
Marge Bouvier.
Artie Ziff?
Oh.
That e-mail. Look,
I got a little drunk
and we were...
I'm not surprised
you want me back
in your life.
You can't spell party
without Artie,
if you misspell party.
Or Artie.
How you doing?
Look, it's great
to see you,
but you should know
I'm happily married.
Married?
Was it consummated?
Pretty much, yeah.
What's going on?
Homer, don't talk
with your mouth full.
I've told you before,
it's rude!
Oh-ho.
Trouble in paradise.
Hey, Marge!
It's that guy who
couldn't get any off you!
How would you all like
to take a ride with me?
You're the old flame.
Homer, Marge,
I have a rather
delicate proposition.
Spill it, moneybags.
Yes, I do have
everything,
but yet I often wonder
what life with Marge
would've been like.
It's like being married
to my best friend,
and he lets me
feel his boobs.
Homie!
Homer, I will
give you $1, 000,000
to let me spend
a weekend alone
with your wife.
Mmm. A million dollars.
Wait a minute.
How much sex
would be involved?
Because if it's some...
No, no, no.
All I want is
to show her
what life would be like
had she chosen me.
Artie, that's a sick idea.
Come on, Homer.
We're leaving.
Just think about it!
You'll win her yet, Artie.
I mean, Arr-tie!
Hey, where's
our parents?
Hey, Marge,
I just thought
of something.
What?
If we had Artie's money,
I could get that
snoring surgery.
Plus at least two of
those other surgeries
I desperately need.
No way, no how.
I'll get used
to the snoring.
Just like I got
used to saying
"Courteney Cox-Arquette. "
Besides, I like
some of the noises
you make in bed.
One squeaking
spring symphony
coming up.
Wow! Homer,
that was amazing!
Yeah, I...
Honey, did you
get any sleep?
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Are you snoring
while you're awake?
Huh?
You need that surgery.
We'll have to call Artie.
Okay, Ziff. You get her
for the weekend,
but no funny stuff.
And by funny stuff,
I mean hand-holding,
goo-goo eyes,
misdirected woo,
which is pretty much
any John Woo film.
Your wife's
virtues shall remain
as untouched as
Bill Gates' weight room.
Remember, Homie,
I'm doing this for us.
See you on Monday,
This round's on me, Moe!
I got a big payday coming.
Yeah.
Homer sold his wife
for a million bucks.
I didn't sell her.
I just rented her
to an old boyfriend.
Gee, a million bucks.
That's gonna buy him
a lot of swings
in the old batting cage.
Looks like
everyone's a winner.
Marge gets
a great new life...
And you get
more sprawl space
on the bed.
Wait. You really think
Marge is gonna fall
for this guy?
Even after I bought her
that hockey fight tape?
I'd dump your ass.
Me, too.
Yeah, I can't get Artie
out of my head.
He's like a spy
in the house of Moe.
Oh, God, you're right.
I gotta get her back
before it's too late!
Hello, Artie.
Where are you
taking me?
We're taking
a trip through time.
Forwards?
No.
Backwards!
To the sexy '70s!
Oh, my God!
Artie, it's our senior prom.
Burn, baby, burn
I can't believe
he's paying us
a thousand bucks to
pretend it's the '70s.
Disco Stu is
working pro bono.
Marge, many years ago
I turned a groovy night
into a complete bummer.
Tonight you get the prom
you always deserved.
Precious and few
are the moments
we two can share
That's very sweet, Artie.
Come, dear.
We can dance all night.
The band hasn't worked
since the wrap party
for James at 16.
Some say they're cursed.
Oh, my God,
it's our high school prom!
And once again
I have no date!
Simpson!
Hello, Dondelinger.
You're not on
the guest list, Simpson.
Orders of Prom King Ziff.
And have you
been drinking?
Just for 25 years.
Let's go, mister.
Oh.
You're very sweet,
but no fake prom
could make me
forget my husband.
I'm sorry.
Very well, Marge.
I see you'll never feel
about moi the way
I feel about toi,
but before
the evening ends,
may I request
an innocent peck
on the cheek?
Okay.
Oh, no!
If Marge marries Artie,
I'll never be born!
Get off me,
you little nerd!
I knew this weekend
was just an excuse
to get in my mouth.
Keep your money.
I'm going home.
Stop looking at me!
Keep dancing!
Don't you know
how to dance?
Watch me!
Aw! He's gonna
sleep tonight.
Oh, guys, it was horrible.
I saw Marge kissing
a far superior man.
Well, if it makes
you feel any better,
he's probably
doing her right now.
Oh, yeah.
Make me the bad guy.
My life here is over.
Lenny, how'd you like
to leave town with me
and never come back?
Sounds like a plan.
Then it's settled.
We leave Springfield
forever.
What'd I miss?
Anything good?
That's $912.
Send the bill to
Baron Von Kiss-a-lot.
No problemo.
This just arrived,
Herr Baron.
Okay, who's the wise guy?
Oh, Homie,
I'm so glad to see...
A tape on the bed?
Marge,
if you're watching this
then it means
I've figured out
how to work the camera.
Last night I crashed
a certain fake prom.
That's right.
Artie Ziff's fake prom.
Homer was there?
I saw something terrible
and I can't even say it.
So I'll have these
two dolls do it for me.
Kiss me, Artie.
With pleasure.
Homer's a big jerk.
Ooh.
But I can explain!
I'm leaving you, Marge.
The next time you see
my name will be in
the hobo obituaries.
Don't worry about the kids.
I'll drop them off
with Patty and Selma.
Patty and Selma?
Screw that!
Just run the camera,
you little...
Goodbye, my darling.
Oh.
It's no good. Everything
reminds me of Marge.
I know what
you're going through.
We're coming up
on Mount Carlmore.
I carved that
one wonderful summer.
What did Carl think?
You know,
we've never discussed it.
Do you have any jobs for
a man who wants to die?
Something indoorsy.
Close to a bathroom?
I'll put you on rig 13
as soon as they
burn off the corpses.
This job
will be perfect.
I'm gonna leave this world
the way I entered it,
dirty, screaming,
and torn away from
the woman I love.
Oh.
Quick and pointless.
That's the death for me.
Thank you.
You've been very helpful.
Dad just got a library card
in West Springfield.
He checked out
10 books on oil rigging
and a book called
Dying for Dummies.
He must have
taken a job
in the West Springfield
oil patch.
That's practically
a death sentence!
What happened now?
Homer bowled a 300 game?
Grampa, that happened
a year and a half ago.
We have to
go save Homer.
But West Springfield's
three times the size
of Texas.
We'll never
find him there.
Unless...
I really appreciate you
helping me find Homer.
Think nothing of it,
Marge.
I hope we can
always be friends.
Of course.
With privileges?
Mmm? Mmm?
Does that work on anyone?
No.
But when it does,
hello!
Another oil well
successfully capped.
Let's raise our
goggles in triumph.
Oh, no! This is how
Faceless Joe lost his legs!
Looks like we're goners.
Oh, well. Circle of life.
Marge!
Climb up!
Ain't you coming,
Homer?
Why?
So I can watch
my wife spend
the rest of her life
in the arms
of another man?
I don't think so.
Good day!
But Homer...
We said good day!
Listen to me, Homer!
You've won!
You own Marge's heart,
and that's something
I could never buy.
Woo-hoo!
There's nothing on
that helicopter for me.
Don't be so sure.
Carl Carlson?
Artie, thanks for
saving my life.
Now, I believe
there's the little matter
of the million dollars.
We can't
take his money.
Oh.
I can't take his money.
I can't print my own money.
I have to work for money.
Why don't I just
lie down and die?
Now, Homer,
if there's one thing
you should've
learned from all this,
it's that I'm rich,
rich, rich! And now,
I bid you adieu!
I'm Artie Ziff!
I gotta hand it
to Artie Ziff, Marge.
That little nerd
saved my life.
And our marriage.
With his latest invention,
the snore converter.
Goodnight, Homie.
Goodnight, honey.
He's a loser, Marge.
Dump him!
I travel the world
and the seven seas
I am watching you
through a camera!
English - US - PSDH