♪ ♪
(couch and TV grunting happily)
(giggles, gasps)
(both laughing playfully)
(both panting, sighing)
(grunting)
(groaning)
HOMER:
Wow, an indoor water park.
Hopefully, this will put the final nail
in the coffin of lakes and rivers.
-Well, as a mother, I...
-We all know you're a mother.
As a mother,
I like that wherever I look,
I can see a lifeguard.
I'm finding Nemo!
I saw heaven!
(cheering)
-(grunting)
-My head!
(groaning)
-(laughter)
-(groans)
-(grunts)
-(laughs)
Mom! Bart got my hair wet,
and I wasn't ready to get it wet yet!
-(hair dryer whirs)
-Hmm.
I'm afraid you're going
in the kiddie pool.
Oh. I've had baths
that were more exciting. Baths!
(kids gasping happily)
Oh, my God, a plastic ring.
Out of my way, you little twerps!
I want that ring.
(grunting) Ow!
Hmm.
Hey, uh, do you have any waterslides
for the gentleman
of leisurely proportions?
Right this way, sir.
This park specializes in extra-wide
double-reinforced tubing
for the modern American fatso.
(chuckles) Oh, well.
Cola wars veteran coming through!
Whoo-hoo! I'm exercising!
(laughing)
(mechanical bear roars)
(gunshot)
Awesome.
Milhouse, how long
you been waiting in line?
You mean you didn't
use the app last week
to get your Slammin' Salmon
line number?
What are you, Amish?
(groans) Hmm.
All right, time to thin out the herd.
(grunting softly)
(static crackles)
(deep voice, over P.A.): Attention,
bathers, this is water park president
Cal A. Bunga.
Do not panic,
but the pools are infested
with those tiny fish
that swim up your wiener.
-Get out of the way!
-(crowd clamoring, screaming)
Again, do not panic.
If you think a wiener fish
has entered your dingus,
the only cure is to roll around
naked in the snow.
(clamoring)
(people gasping, groaning)
Uh, Lou, I need a big favor from you.
Oh, man. I... They don't train
you for this at the academy.
Well, they should.
(laughing)
-(mechanical bear roars)
-(hawk screeches)
(gunshot)
(laughing continues)
Whee! Yes!
(wind whistles)
(sniffs)
Oh, dear God! Bio breach!
(grumbles)
(shrieks)
(gasps) That poor raccoon!
Isn't anyone gonna do anything?
He committed nature's greatest
crime-- coming inside.
(grunts)
No heartbeat.
Finally, a chance to use
my online CPR training.
(whispering)
One, two, three, four five. (blows)
One, two, three, four, five. (blows)
(singsongy) Lisa has a boyfriend!
Lisa has a boyfriend!
Oh, a boyfriend?
And raccoons are such good providers.
Come on, come on.
You have so much more trash to eat.
Steal one more breath, noble bandit.
(grunts)
(coughs)
It worked. I saved you.
-(chitters)
-(sighs) My first rescue.
And my first real kiss.
She'd have chosen me
if I was wearing a real bathing suit.
(groans)
For once, a life saved
at a Springfield water park,
where a quick-thinking second grader
performed emergency CPR
on a drowning nuisance animal,
while dozens of unheroic onlookers
just stood around.
Where was Channel Six news?
Filming gas pumps
and their ever-changing prices.
Which accomplishes what?
I don't know.
DIRECTOR:
There's eight minutes left.
-Uh, did we do gas prices?
-Yes!
(giggles)
We saw you on the picture radio.
They chyroned your name.
They described you as "Local Girl."
Hubba, hubba.
They sure got that right. (growls)
Lisa, it looks like
you're the perfect student
to look after Nibbles the hamster here
during spring break.
I'd take him with me, but I'm doing
Jell-O shots with former students.
This spring break,
I'm gonna go wild with responsibility!
My dad's spending spring break
in a cage, too.
And for saving that raccoon,
I got the opposite of teasing.
I bet the Germans
have a word for it, like, uh,
gerstronkenplatzen or something.
(chuckles)
I wish the Germans had a word
for this terrible traffic.
And so ends the moment being about me.
What's going on, Chief?
Oh, nasty car crash.
Can't let traffic through
until the cleanup crew mops up this mess.
Which is a problem,
because they're stuck in traffic
behind you.
Okay, who did that?!
We need to get home.
I left my father-in-law on the sofa.
He's got to be turned.
Yeah, well, that ain't gonna happen.
Not unless you clean up
this accident scene. (chuckles)
Actually, seriously, could you do that?
Hmm, I don't know.
I'm one of those people who doesn't like
being traumatized by horrifying sights.
Marge, do you know why
I became a cop?
If you do, could you tell me?
'Cause it's-it's really dangerous.
B-But these crime scene cleanups,
they're totally safe.
All the bad people are dead
or, uh, at large.
So give it a shot.
Please. Please, Mom.
Huh?
Oh, all right.
There you go. Spick and span.
Wow, you even made
the homeless guy look nice.
Yeah, still crazy, though.
You know, Marge, uh, you ever want
some fast extra cash,
we are always looking
for crime scene cleaner-uppers.
You know what they say--
crime always pays.
Plus, you can keep any money you find,
and any jewelry that isn't monogrammed.
(bicycle bell dings)
Hello, little girl.
Oh, does your hamster
have Tyzzer's disease?
That would've been interesting,
but I swabbed him for Tyzzer's
and it came up negative.
My. You certainly know
a lot about animals.
That's just it, I do.
I saved a raccoon's life the other day.
It was the best feeling I've ever had.
Is there any way
I could work in your office?
I mean, as an intern or anything?
Oh, do you know how many people
walk in here every day
looking for just such a thing?
-A lot, I bet.
-No, it's never happened.
Grab a clean smock and follow me.
Oh, okay! (giggles)
I can't find a clean smock.
Then your first job
is to clean the smocks.
-(bell dings)
-I'm ready, Dr. Budgie.
Oh, it's a shame to ruin
such a clean smock,
but, uh, let's go.
Hmm.
(squeals)
(sputters)
This is heaven.
You got to help me, Doc.
My pet ferret has lost
its terrible stink!
Well, that won't do.
Let me have a go at jump-starting
the old stink gland.
Lisa, my dear,
can you restrain the ferret?
It would be my honor.
-Clear!
-(electrical buzz)
We have stink lines!
Well done, Lisa.
Heaven! (chuckles)
Ew.
-(barking)
-(meowing)
-(horse neighs)
-All right, Veggie Kibble for Daisy here.
Chairman Meow is having surgery tomorrow,
so only liquid for you.
And no more food for you, Mr. Snake,
until you finish shedding your skin.
Oh. You have.
Dr. Budgie, I'm really enjoying
cleaning out these cages.
No, really, I am, but are there any jobs
that are more exciting?
Absolutely.
You can hobble these crickets.
We have a hungry chameleon
who's slowing down with age,
but he still loves
the thrill of the hunt.
Mm. Anything more life or deathy?
I could take the animals' temperature.
I know what that means,
and I am up for it.
Oh, Lisa, slow down.
Do you know how many
awkward courses I had to take
before they let me
put my arm inside a horse?
I understand.
I just feel like I could be doing more.
Oh, you remind me
of a certain young man
growing up
in Stratfordshire-on-Corningwell.
He, too, was impatient.
Always thinking he could do more.
-Was that you?
-No.
If that was me, I would have said "me."
This eager beaver
had to leave veterinary school
and become--
-ugh-- a people doctor.
-Ooh.
MAN (on TV): And with the 27th pick
of the 14th round of the NHL draft,
the Phoenix Coyotes select...
Lubochuck, Lubochuck,
Lubochuck, Lubochuck.
-...Cédric Bélanger.
-But Lubochuck.
Homie, I think we need a new ceiling fan.
The old one doesn't seem safe.
(electrical crackling)
It's fine.
And it saves us money on haircuts.
(Bart gasps)
Not bad, but I miss the social aspects
of the barbershop.
MAN: The St. Louis Blues
are now on the clock.
Lubochuck, Lubochuck,
Lubochuck, Lubochuck.
Hmm.
-(phone rings)
-Springfield PD.
PD... police department!
Ha! I just got that.
Chief, Chief, this is Marge Simpson.
I think I'd like to do
some of those crime scene cleanups.
Oh, great, great.
Hey, I got a job for you right here.
Uh, murder-suicide.
Or possibly a suicide-murder.
Just bring a mop and your imagination.
Hey, it can't be worse
than what I've seen.
Homer, I told you not to eat chili
out of the colander!
Uh, it's pronounced "calendar."
What's the matter, little guy?
You haven't touched your berries.
Do you need aphids for flavor?
Mmm. Aphids.
DR. BUDGIE:
Lisa, could you come here for a moment?
(gasps) At last.
I'm trying to give this
Saint Bernard a shot,
but my hands are a little shaky.
I had an extra gallon of tea for lunch.
-Oh, my.
-If I hold him,
do you think you could attend
to the matter of the needle?
Of course!
-Mm.
-Careful, careful.
A single millimeter either way
would not make much of a difference.
LISA: Huh. Why am I not feeling
the same rush I did with the raccoon?
(barking)
(shudders) There it is!
-(humming)
-Be careful, Mrs. S.
I've never seen an angel-dust-
for-guns swap go so wrong.
Hey, a mess is a mess.
Huh?
Let me start with this
filthy crime scene tape.
(humming)
Yarr, is the doctor in, miss?
Little Goldie here
is listing hard to starboard.
I fear he may have tangled
with the wrong plastic diver.
Hmm. Could be fin rot.
Oh, no, not the big F. Arr!
Do what you must.
I'll say my good-byes.
You were more wife to me
than any woman I ever knew.
Captain, the diagnosis of fin rot
is not the death sentence it used to be.
A couple drops of medicine in the water,
and he'll be fine.
Hmm.
Yarr, that's amazing!
Eh, I've just got one more
little problem.
He, uh... he ate me car keys. Yarr.
(grunting)
Hurry, Doc!
His lungs are full of seltzer!
(sobbing)
(grunting)
(chattering)
(grunts)
Homie? Notice anything?
(beeping)
(alarm beeping)
Um, are you having an affair?
What? No.
I bought a new ceiling fan. Huh?
Ooh, I thought the air felt
a little more lively.
But where did you get the money?
Actually, I made a little extra
by cleaning up crime scenes.
What? Poor Marge.
I heard that can really mess you...
Oh, baby, that cool air is sweet!
...up.
Are you sure you're not living
a waking nightmare?
No. Not one little bit.
And I get the police discount
on cleaning supplies.
I can finally clean Grampa's dentures.
Yeah, I got popcorn in there
from Kramer vs. Kramer.
I was rooting for Kramer,
but was dismayed
when Kramer finally won.
That's a twist I didn't see Kramer.
Happy birthday, Martin.
Where's the gift table?
(chuckles)
Right over there, my friend.
(humming)
Haw haw!
(chicken clucking)
-(giggles)
-Some zoo.
Where are the rental strollers?
Actually, it's not so bad.
The animals are healthy.
A couple of paddock scrapes,
but nothing overly concerning.
Oh, knock it off. You're not a vet.
You're a glorified cage scrubber.
Dr. Budgie depends upon me!
I have felt the cold breath
of kennel cough in my face.
I have seen tabbies
that were more tick than cat.
I know why the caged dog scoots.
So when your lizard loses its tail,
you're gonna need me to tell you
-it's gonna grow back.
-(sighs)
Want some peanuts, Mr. Elephant?
Uh, it's a goat, not an elephant,
and those are shrimp, not peanuts.
And that goat is allergic to shrimp!
Your breath smells like
"don't drink that."
(worried bleat)
Milhouse, give me your EpiPen!
You're not a professional.
I am a self-selected
unpaid veterinary intern.
Now let me practice my craft!
(bleating excitedly)
Hey, he's as good as new.
Look at him play with the kids!
(kids grunting)
See, Bart? Life or death.
I make the choice.
Okay, time to cut the cake.
(bleats triumphantly)
That's my patient.
Guess what, sweetie.
I'm wearing my snuggle socks.
They're compression socks
from your heart surgery.
All the same...
(purring)
(sighs)
I'm not in the mood.
What?! You've never said that before!
I've thought it three times.
Each time was after
a burrito-eating contest.
But I won!
What's wrong?
It's just that seeing you, lying down,
reminds me of this bloated corpse
I had to clean up today.
Hey, I look damn good for someone
who eats the crap I do.
Maybe we should just go to sleep.
I wasn't done with my drink.
Would you like
my itty-bitty booze light?
I've never seen him like this.
He's so listless.
Who's lost the urge to kill?
I'll tell you what's wrong with him--
-you.
-What? Me?!
This dog is badly behind on his shots.
He's displaying the symptoms
of early onset parvo.
I'm confiscating your dog.
And, you, get out!
Smithers, I've been shamed.
Prepare a thimble of ice cream.
Some people don't deserve to own pets.
BART: And you get to decide who?
Don't fold your arms at me.
Lis, look at yourself.
You've become so arrogant,
you've forgotten who you are.
And even worse, you've forgotten Nibbles!
(gasps) Nibbles!
My pet! My responsibility!
My homework!
(gasps) Matted hair, dry tongue...
Is this true, Lisa?
Did you let this happen
to a creature in your care?
I'm so sorry.
I'm so, so sorry.
Pet hamsters need to be
played with regularly,
or they feel abandoned.
And that can lead
to stress polyps on the heart.
The heart is the seat of love, Lisa.
If you'd gone to veterinary school,
you'd know that.
I've got no choice but to operate.
And I need your help.
You still want me to help you
after I was so arrogant?
Lisa, arrogance
is what made the British Empire.
Then lost it.
Then pretended it didn't happen.
(monitor beeping steadily)
Well, we've done all we can.
The next 24 hours will be crucial.
-(monitor flatlining)
-Oh, he's gone.
(crying) No, no, no.
He can't be dead!
He can't!
I thought we could save every animal
if we just cared enough.
Okay, Marge, sweetie, look at this one.
See, Marge? The baby laughs
every time the toaster pops.
(chuckles) It is pretty hysterical.
-That's nice.
-Nice?
Something in you is dead, Marge,
and that's one crime scene
you can't clean up.
And all for a fan.
A stupid ceiling fan that...
Oh, man, that's refreshing.
I want my Marge back.
(cell phone rings)
Hello? What is it, boy?
Uh-huh. I see.
Fine, Marge.
You sit here,
watch your boob tube, have a beer.
That's not how Homer Simpson
does things.
I have to go help Lisa!
Lisa?
Wait! Wait, I'm coming with you.
-(door closes)
-(phone ringing)
(line ringing)
No answer.
I guess we got to do this ourselves.
Oh, geez.
All right, get some paper towels, boys.
(chain saw buzzing)
-Lisa.
-(sniffling)
Oh, Mom, he trusted me
as only a hamster can!
(crying)
If there's one thing
I'll always clean up,
it's my baby's tears.
Oh, I should've been here for you.
You would've never let
anything happen to him.
-I was too busy being dead inside...
-Wherever he went,
-I hope they have hamster balls.
-...doing I don't know what!
-But I'm here now, and I'll never leave.
-(chuckles)
Well, I'll be.
Lisa's learning about death
helped Marge feel again.
Yes, a perfect dovetail.
Thank you for curing Walter Pigeon here.
I can't afford to pay you,
but I can give you
front row seats to my magic show.
-The theme is boxing.
-Sounds marvelous.
Oh, yeah, no. Come on, it is.
I want to thank everyone
for coming to Nibbles' funeral today.
BART (over P.A.):
This is President Cal A. Bunga.
On this sad occasion,
the school flag
will be flying at half-ass.
Bart! (groans)
I know that this is
an especially hard time
for the other classroom pets,
including Mrs. Nibbles,
Shelly the turtle,
Sally Mander, Hamilton Fish,
and Willie's chicken.
Willie, where is your chicken?
-It was either him or me!
-I see.
Please stand for Nibbles' final journey.
(bagpipes playing "Amazing Grace")
♪ ♪
(theme music playing)
Shh!
Subtitled by A. Vandelay