The Simpsons
D'oh!
We now
return to The Planet
from Outer Space.
Captain, we've been attacked
by some sort of force ray.
Space air is flooding in.
Right. Goggles on!
Good Lord!
We're on a collision course
with a monster from space!
That's just a dog
in a spacesuit!
From the looks
of it, a male dog.
We'll return
to our film after these
very loud messages.
Hi. I'm Colonel Chet Manners,
five-time space
shuttle alternate.
Loser.
Do you want to boldly go
where people like me,
but not me,
have gone before?
Then get the Orbit King,
with yaw control
like you've never seen.
Hey, Lise,
is Dad's credit card number
5784365343410709?
You know it is.
When you have a rib-eye steak
You must floss it
Oh, that meatloaf
tasted great
You must floss it
Now floss it, floss it good
Hey, Dad, will you help me
build this model rocket?
Just a second, Son.
I gotta put on my contacts.
I didn't know
your dad was so
interested in science.
Science?
He didn't say "science. "
He said "pie pants. "
Mmm. Pie pants.
This is launch master
Homer counting down,
five, four, three...
My eyebrows!
My beautiful eyebrows!
Over here, guvnor.
The word "unblowupable"
is thrown around
a lot these days,
but I think I can
say with confidence...
Okay, that shows you what
could potentially happen.
What was that?
Greetings from
Neddedy Space Center
on Cape Flandaveral.
We noticed your
"sky-rotechnics"
and thought we'd join in.
Ooh, looks like
a perfect landing.
Wow! Did you see
that yaw control?
I have eyes, don't I?
I would really like
to thank you nerds
for helping me out.
And could you stop
calling us "nerds"?
"Dweeb," "wonk," "spaz. "
It's all good.
Who wants some
astro-lemonade?
What precisely
makes it astro?
Look, I don't want
to start a whole
thing with this.
Okay,
the rocket's ready to go.
Super.
Now if you'll gather round,
I'd like to say a few words.
All nerds clear
the launch area!
Let's wait in the car.
Now, all we need
is our astronaut.
Bart, where's
America's newest hero?
He's saying goodbye
to his wife.
He's leaving her
with five babies.
She already ate three.
That's sensible.
Son, we are about to break
the surly bonds of gravity
and punch the face of God!
Five, four,
three, two, one,
countdown!
Wow! That's it.
I'm off the hooch.
Hey, wine!
Dad,
the rocket's off course!
Okay, Nibbles.
You can guide her down.
"Step one,
right in front of you
is a blue handle.
"Pull for a controlled
burn of 2.4 seconds. "
Now it's heading
for the church!
Don't worry.
I planned for this.
This is the worst thing
you've ever done!
You say that so much,
it's lost all meaning.
I have convened
the church council to see
what we should do now.
Fixing this church
should be our top priority.
And I say that
as a teenager, and the
parent of a teenager.
Fixing all that damage
is gonna be very expensive.
Yes, barring some
sort of miracle...
All right! We'll help
ourselves, yet again.
People, we need
some fundraising ideas.
Let's just write to
David Bowie again.
No, he's done enough
for this church.
Anyone else?
I've got the answer.
Just let me run this
church like a business.
It's kind of you
to offer, Mr. Burns,
but the buzz around town
is that you're, well, evil.
That's just
a skip-rope rhyme.
Believe me,
the Lord's gonna go
for this in a big way.
Now, who's with me?
I guess we have
no choice.
Excellent.
You'll get yours.
This is Lindsay Naegle.
And don't let
the skirt fool you.
She'll have this place
making money in no time.
Isn't that skirt
a little north of the knee?
You're telling me.
I guarantee I can find
some new revenue streams.
Step one,
let's sell some ad space.
Reverend, how would you feel
about wearing this robe?
Conflicted.
Too bad!
You've already signed
the deal!
Actually, he hasn't.
Well, we highly value
your input,
until you sign the deal.
Let me handle this,
Monty.
Good idea.
I'll be hiding
behind that tree.
What are they
doing to the church?
We're re-branding it.
The old church
was skewing pious.
We prefer
a faith-based emporium,
teeming with
impulse-buy items.
I feel like
I want to throw up.
Then my work is done.
Why does Jesus
have a lasso?
Because he's all man.
Money changed.
Get your money changed,
right here in the temple!
That could not be
more blasphemous.
Where's Bart?
Do a nice one
for Grandma.
Fine.
These new pews are so comfy.
I am not going to be
taken in by all of this.
Lisa, don't sulk.
You're on the JumboTron.
Adorable.
And Lord, please remember
our infirm parishioners,
especially Mrs. Glick,
who's recovering
from hip surgery.
And now,
let us rise and...
Um...
He's not gonna say it.
Trust me. He'll say it,
or I'll bust him down
to Thursday night vespers.
...and thank
Crazy Larry
whose big-screen TV
prices are insane!
And now, to deliver
a special sermon
on the sanctity of
deliciousness, the Noid.
That's it!
Quiet, Lisa.
Everyone in the store
is looking at you.
They should take a good look
at themselves
and what their
church has become!
Lisa, it's still the
same basic message.
We've just
dressed it up a little.
Like the Whore of Babylon?
That is a false analogy.
No, it's not.
It's apt. Apt!
Don't you see
what Mr. Burns has
done to this church?
He restored it
from nave to narthex!
He super-sized the pews
for the zaftig believers.
He put ice in the urinals.
Those are all
wonderful things,
but they've cost
the church its soul.
And I, for one,
will not be a part of it!
Do you want your hand stamped
so you can come back in?
No! I'm leaving
this church forever!
Oh, no!
I don't know how to feel.
You should be very upset.
Got it.
How is that?
A little much.
Lord, I'm not
turning my back on you.
I just need to find a temple
that's free of corruption.
Why do you have
to be so different?
Always making a big deal
out of everything?
Mom, I know it's you.
I can't believe
you're eavesdropping
on my prayers.
Honey, I'm worried
about your soul.
I want at least one
person from this family
to go to heaven.
I still believe in God.
I just think
there's another
path to him or her.
Her?
She's just kidding,
Mr. Lord.
Still looking
for a new faith?
Yeah.
Hey, how about one
of those religions
where you eat a human heart?
No.
How about Methodist?
No!
Look, I'm not just
gonna pick a religion
that seems cool.
I'm gonna pick one
that's right for me.
How about Judaism?
When you turn 13,
cha-ching!
I'm going out for a walk.
Lenny and Carl?
You guys are Buddhists?
Yeah. If I didn't
have inner peace,
I'd completely go psycho
on all you guys all the time.
Well, I'm looking
for a new faith,
one that isn't
so materialistic.
Well, you've come
to the right place.
Buddhism teaches
that suffering is
caused by desire.
Richard Gere?
The world's most
famous Buddhist.
What about the Dalai Lama?
Who?
You know,
the 14th reincarnation
of the Buddha Avalokiteshvara.
Who's Buddha?
It's a good thing
Buddhism teaches
freedom from desire,
'cause I've got the desire
to kick your ass.
Mr. Gere, I was hoping
Buddhism could
bring me inner peace.
Or is that
just a pipe dream?
We all have dreams.
Mine is of a free Tibet.
That would be so great.
I dream about
meatball sandwiches,
all-you-can-eat
for two bucks.
Good luck.
This pamphlet contains
the teachings of the Buddha.
"All things are impermanent,
and are empty of
inherent existence. "
Hey, Richard,
in An Officer
and a Gentleman,
did you really do
all those sit-ups?
I wish. I did one,
and they just
showed it 1,000 times.
"Nirvana is achieved
through right views
and right speech.
"Positive actions
lead to happiness
"and negative actions
lead to unhappiness.
"No creator gods,
just the pursuit
of enlightenment. "
I'm a Buddhist!
Hey, I'm a Buddhist!
My Satan-sense is tingling.
Into the root cellar, boys!
When can we come out?
Maybe never.
Yay!
So, you think
you know better
than this family, huh?
Well, as long as
you're in my house,
you'll do what I do
and believe what I believe.
So, butter your bacon!
Yes, Father.
Mom, Dad,
my spiritual quest is over.
Hold that thought.
Bacon up that sausage, boy.
But, Dad, my heart hurts.
I'm a Buddhist.
What?
That's it.
No more chat rooms
for you!
You know, Lisa,
around here,
Buddhists don't get
any desserts
in their lunches.
A Buddhist
wouldn't want any.
Hey, Simpson,
I hear your sister
dumped Christianity.
Who cares?
I'll tell you
someone who cares.
He's got long hair,
works as a carpenter,
has a lot of crazy ideas
about love and brotherhood.
His name's Gunnar,
and he's dating my mom.
Sometimes,
he buys us beer.
I thought Kearney
was dating your mom.
Hey, she came on to me!
Get him!
Hey, Lisa.
What are you doing?
I'm planting my
own Bodhi Tree.
If I meditate under it,
perhaps I can
find inner peace.
Honey, is this
about some boy at school
who doesn't like you?
No!
Good!
I'm just saying
that any boy who
doesn't like you
is not worth your time.
You're gonna get
a bath tonight!
So, the good news is
church revenues
are up 1,073%.
And when will the church
see any of this money?
When hell freezes over,
suckers!
Whatever. Just take it.
Well, next on our agenda,
Marge Simpson's
devil daughter.
She's not a devil.
I just don't know
what to do.
Well, Christmas is
coming, huh?
Yeah. And Santa
doesn't leave presents
under the Bodhi Tree.
You think we
can bribe her back
with Christmas?
Marge, you can
save more souls
with roller skates
and Easy-Bake Ovens
than with this
2,000-page sleeping pill.
Time to begin
Operation X-Mas
Remind of How Good Is.
Just do it!
Do it! Do it now!
I think this tree
could use an angel.
Well,
at least it's tasteful.
I was just making
Christmas cookies.
But since you
don't believe in
Christmas anymore,
I guess you don't want any.
Well, they do smell good.
It's a pity.
All right!
Trash cookies!
Uh-oh.
I think I ate
a dog food lid.
Here she comes!
And a-one,
and a-two, and a...
We wish you a Merry Christmas
We wish...
Hello, Lisa.
I just came down
for a glass of water.
Well, you do have
a present under the tree.
I guess no one told Santa
you were a Buddhist.
Well, Santa can take it back
because I'm not
ruled by material...
Is that a pony?
I don't know
what Santa left you.
I just know
his name is Clip-Clop
and he loves sugar.
Lisa, we love you,
and we're not trying
to put any pressure on you.
Aw.
Lick it. Lick it.
No!
Oh, no!
Our daughter's run away
on Christmas Eve!
More sugar, please.
Bag's in the kitchen.
All right!
My family tried to trick me
into celebrating Christmas.
You know,
we are meditating.
Oh. Sorry.
That's all right.
I was only about to
achieve enlightenment.
But who'd want that?
Who likes short-shorts?
I like short-shorts.
Those guys are way off.
Anyway, your family
didn't have to trick you.
Buddhists respect
the diversity of
other religions
as long as they're based
on love and compassion.
It's true.
So, why don't you go home?
I'm sure your family
really misses you.
I can really
celebrate Christmas?
You can celebrate
any holiday.
And, you know,
my birthday is August 31.
Oh. I'll send you
an e-mail greeting card.
Sweet.
Now I really should
be getting back
to my family.
Yeah. I'm spending tonight
with my step-daughter,
Hannah.
I do her hair,
then she does mine.
We're gonna go
spend Christmas
with Moe,
you know, so he don't
have one of his
Christmas "accidents. "
Hey, he can't do
much without this.
I did it!
I found our dog!
Now our Christmas
is complete!
We were looking for Lisa!
I thought
we were caroling.
We better call
the police.
Lisa?
You came back!
Yeah.
I wanted to spend Christmas
with you guys.
So, you're back on
the winning team?
No, I'm still Buddhist.
But I can worship
with my family, too.
So, you're just going
to pay lip service
to our church?
Uh-huh.
That's all I ever asked.
Well,
I'm just glad you're back.
And don't worry, honey.
I'll pray double hard
for both of us.
Now let's get you
some Christmas cookies.
Thanks, Mom.
Hey, where's my pony?
Yes!
Merry Christmas to us all!
I'm serious.
Make with the pony.
And a happy and
healthy New Year!
Here, Clip-Clop!
Here, pony-pony!
Happy, happy New Year!
ENGLISH - US - PSDH