CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screeching)
♪♪
D’oh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
(children's music plays)
♪♪
Ah... nothing beats
taking a family drive
with our new
satellite radio.
Which of the 25
easy-listening stations
should we listen to?
I say "Cool Waves."
BART: "Neon Breeze!"
LISA: "Chill Thunder!"
"Chill Thunder!"
(chuckling):
You’re all idiots.
I’m putting it
on "Chill Thunder Lite."
Oh, now
that’s smooth.
-(beeping)
-Out of my way,
you seat belt-wearin’
cowards!
Hey! Nobody cuts me off!
(growling)
Homer, no!
Revenge never
solves anything.
Then what’s America
doing in Iraq?
Well, let me
tell you a story
about a time
revenge brought
only unhappiness
and misery.
It happened
many years ago in Paris.
Texas?
No, France.
MARGE: There was
a happy young family.
Papa, may we
have chocolat?
Papa, may we have
petit fours?
May we? May we?
Mais oui!
(all French laughing)
Oh, mon cher,
I am the luckiest wife
in the entire
16th arrondissement!
Let us kiss
with the tongues.
(groaning)
(tongue trilling)
I hate that Homer jerk
with his beautiful wife
and loving family,
when all I got
is this doorway.
Well, enjoy your sensual
tongue-play while you can
’cause I’ve got a plan
to take everything you got!
(groaning)
(snoring)
(snoring continues)
Monsieur Simpson.
You’re under arrest
for treason.
Treason?
But I love France.
The way all our words
are either a girl or a guy.
Oh, that’s the best.
Tell it to le baton!
(grunts)
(groaning)
I don’t want the kids
to see me this way.
Don’t worry!
They’re still
drunk from school.
(gurgling)
Uh... deux...
trois.
Listen to this
letter he wrote.
(clearing throat):
"Dear England,
how I love
your moors and heaths.
For you, I’d do
whatever it takes,
especially treason."
I didn’t write that!
Even if I did love England,
I’d play it cool.
Wait for it
to come to me.
I sentence you to life.
You moron!
I’m already alive.
In prison.
(screams)
(groans)
(imitating European
siren noises)
I’m gonna stop now.
(rattling)
I shouldn’t be here.
I was framed.
You think you
got problems?
The man in the iron mask
over there
is the rightful
King of France.
Hey, wait,
did you guys hear that?
He just admitted it. Guys?
Oh, man, this place
is so unfair.
Are you going
to torture me?
We can’t tell you.
Not knowing is
the worst torture of all.
Well, that and
the rat helmet.
(groaning)
Now get some sleep.
You’ve got a 9:00 a.m.
rat helmet.
Oh, 9:00 a.m.
(music swells)
I swear
revenge on Meaux!
Even if it takes me
the rest of my life!
Can you loosen my arms
so I can shake my fists?
You’re the traitor.
Revenge!
Okay.
Thank you.
(hooting)
Oh, little mouse.
You are the only thing
that keeps me sane.
(gulping, slurping)
Now I have nothing.
Perhaps
I may be of help.
(gasping):
Where did you come from?
I’m your cell mate.
You never noticed me
because frankly,
you’re extremely
self-centered.
Oh, sorry,
I wasn’t listening.
I was checking out my reflection
in this yellow water.
Ho-ho-ho-ho,
looking good.
Young man, I have the answer
to your problems.
(grunting)
(gasping)
I spent 30 years
digging this tunnel,
but now I can’t use it.
I’m simply too old.
And decrepit.
(shudders): But you can escape
and use this map
to retrieve
my buried treasure.
With it you can
have your revenge.
Ooh, the-the!
But why are
you helping me?
Well, because before
my wretched life
comes to a close,
I want to know that
I had one friend.
Also, because
while you slept,
I violated you repeatedly.
So this map leads
to a treasure, huh?
I wonder how long
this tunnel
...iiiiiiiis!
(splashing)
(gurgling): D’oh!
(mysterious music playing)
(gasping)
Damn it!
How’s it going?
(softly):
D’oh!
Uh-huh. Hmm.
Mon Dieu!
(wondrous music playing)
(gasping):
Whoo-hoo-hee!
(coins clinking)
Ha-ha! Do-do-do.
Ew! Silver.
Ooh, a penny.
This is my lucky day!
(fanfare playing)
♪ Frère Jacques,
Frère Jacques ♪
♪ Dormez-vous, dormez-vous ♪
Oh, I love today’s music.
Frère this,
and Jacques that.
Out of sight.
(knocking)
"The Count
of Monte Cristo
invites you
to a formal gala."
Ooh, the Count
of Monte Cristo!
Can we go?
We haven’t been
to any parties
since that soirée
at the Bastille.
Ah...summer nights.
(horse sputtering)
(regal music)
When will we meet
the count?
Do you think
he’ll like us?
I’ve heard rumors
he’s mysterious.
(trumpet fanfare)
(all gasping)
(kissing)
Madame, you have the shapely,
hairless knuckles of a queen.
(laughs):
Oh. Well.
Monsieur Meaux,
I would be honored
if you would be the first
to enjoy the evening’s
entertainment.
Here it is:
the harmless chair
of relaxation.
I heard about
these things.
They’re good for
doing the wife, right?
Oh!
Little do you know
that the Count of Monte Cristo
is in fact
an old acquaintance of yours.
Ma?
I have returned!
-I don’t get it.
-(crowd chatter)
Oh, hold on.
-It’s him!
-Monsieur Simpson!
Homer,
you’re back!
Oui, oui! And I have spent
the last five years
plotting the most
exquisite revenge!
(whirring)
Okay, lesson learned.
Friends again?
(metallic creaking)
(sizzling)
Crêpes?
Suzette!
(all gasping)
Homer?
Yes, my love?
You killed
my husband.
(groans)
No!
BOTH: Papa Meaux!
Papa Meaux!
You guys liked him?
We were together
for five years.
Now who’s going
to take care of the triplets?
(low, Mo-like crying)
But Marge, I did
it all for you.
For me, huh?
What took you so long?
It takes time
to make a revenge machine
this awesome.
Plus, in the middle,
I had to take revenge
on some of my contractors.
You spent so much time
plotting your revenge,
you lost everything
that really mattered.
Come on, kids.
So you see, Homer,
revenge only leads to misery.
(singing Jamaican rap)
(turns radio off)
Weren’t you listening?
I just told you a whole story
about revenge.
Oh, right.
(engine revving)
Revenge!
♪♪
I’m gonna get my revenge,
and if I get caught,
I’m pinning it on the baby
like the time
I shot Mr. Burns.
Dad, wait.
I’ve got a story
about why revenge is wrong.
Is it The Count
of Monte Cristo?
’Cause I love
that story.
-No.
-Oh!
I call it
Revenge of the Geeks.
(collegiate music plays)
(high-pitched groan)
(grunts)
I’m so sick
of those bullies.
We got to figure out
some way to stop ’em.
Perhaps we could tell
the principal.
Tell me what?
(crickets chirping)
(mysterious music)
Behold the Get-back-inator.
(dramatic sting)
We’re gonna beat those bullies
with a glove?
This is far more
than a mere glove.
This is the turning point
in the eternal battle
of brain v. brawn.
All it requires is
a small amount of coordination.
(groaning)
I can handle the glove.
I took juggling at camp.
-Wow!
-Ah!
Good morning, dinguses.
What are you doing,
touching each other’s butts?
Oh, you are so dead
you’re alive.
(grunts)
What is
this place?
Ah, what
a pleasant surprise.
It seems that now
the shoe is on the other...
Revenge!
(whirring)
(groaning)
(sizzling)
(whirring)
(high-pitched groaning)
My fun bags!
Please, have mercy!
I always thought
you were the coolest dork.
(sizzling)
(clicking)
(whirring and pulsing)
ROBOTIC VOICE:
Stop hitting yourself.
-(grunting)
-Stop hitting yourself.
Why are you
hitting yourself?
(laughter and chattering)
♪♪
Milhouse, thanks to you,
the nerds can breathe easy.
Except the ones with asthma,
which is all of them.
But still,
it’s great.
Yup, having a weapon at school
has really made things awesome.
Ow!
(stifled giggles)
Pardon my
birdie.
I misjudged
the prevailing winds.
You embarrassed me
in front of Lisa!
(whirring)
(goofy groaning)
(laughing maniacally)
Milhouse, what’s
gotten into you?
Over the years,
a lot of people have hurt me.
Good thing
I kept this list.
(laughing)
Oh, no, you’ve already
got your revenge!
You wouldn’t give me
Chinese cuts in the lunch line.
(whirring)
You laughed when I threw up
on the glass-blowing tour.
(whirring)
Girls like you better.
Your parents
are married!
(whirring)
Ay caramba!
That’s the only line I get
in your stupid story?!
There are no small parts,
just small actors.
(laughs)
(whirring)
This is my first day
at this school.
I haven’t done
anything to you!
You will.
This is prevenge.
(whirring)
(groaning)
Why, look,
it’s Milhouse.
What’s the
power glove for?
Opening the cap on
your weirdo pills?
(whirring)
(grunts)
Willie, clean up
this mess.
All right.
(slurping)
Milhouse,
don’t you see?
You’re addicted
to revenge.
You’ll learn to love it
when you’re my queen.
I see.
(nervous chuckle)
While it would be an honor
to be your queen...
Go on.
...I feel it would be best
if we just stay friends.
Nobody spares
my feelings!
(tense music)
(grunting)
I can’t do it.
I can’t hurt
you, Lisa.
(Milhouse gasps)
Ha-ha! You
forgot about me
’cause I had the mumps.
(whirring)
(goofy groaning)
(pulsating whirring)
Wow!
That had what I really
like in a story:
an ending.
The point, Dad,
is that when you take revenge,
you become just as bad
as the person you harm.
No, sweetie,
the lesson is:
never put down
your weapon.
Revenge!
Look at that view.
It reminds me
of how insignificant
we are in the world.
Yeehaw!
This is it.
It’s taken all day.
We’ve missed our flight
to Hawaii,
but finally
I’ll get my revenge.
Dad, wait!
You haven’t
heard my story.
You?
You’re too dumb
to tell a story.
No, seriously,
you’re great.
Let’s hear it.
Oh, geez.
My story takes place
in a time I call the past.
♪ ♪
Ugh, that stunk worse
than boiled cabbage.
You should
feel lucky.
Not many boys have
parents who can afford
to take them to the
opera every night.
Parents who
are still alive,
I might add.
Hmm, well, this alley
looks dangerous.
I better turn
my ring around.
Oh, boy.
Hand over your wallet.
You don’t frighten me!
Or my wife!
Or my...
Shut up.
Avenge me.
In flamboyant,
impractical fashion.
♪♪
(somber music)
I want to avenge you,
but I don’t know how.
With my help.
Grandpa?
In my younger days,
I was an ace
crime fighter.
The "Crimson Cockatoo."
(laughing)
Now let’s get you in shape
in an old-timey way.
(20's jazz music playing)
Holy Hannah!
I’ve got more muscles
than a New England Clam Bank.
Now all I need
is a superhero name.
You can be
the Crimson Cockaboy.
Hmm?
I’ll keep thinking.
(exciting orchestral music)
(gun clicks)
Help! Somebody help!
That thief stole all
my Heralds, Tribunes,
and Herald-Tribunes.
A k-k-k-kid!
I’m Bart-Man.
(grunts)
-(yelling)
-(sizzling)
Thank you,
masked vigilante.
Your overzealous homicide
has saved me 80 cents.
Now, if you’re not going to buy
anything, please move along.
Tonight, the Springfield...
I mean Gotham underworld
is trembling
while solid citizens sleep
snug as a bug.
Why? Because Bart-Man
is knocking down bad guys
like Howard Hughes
knocks up young starlets!
Bad guys like
The Toker...
D'oh!
The Diddler...
(groans)
Mr. Mole...
-(grunts)
-Oh!
Sugar and Spice.
BOTH: Oh!
And Poison Lenny.
Oh!
No snake tattoo.
(groaning)
When will I find the man
who murdered my parents?
When?
(speaker):
Attention, Bart-Man.
This is The Serpent,
saying "fangs a lot"
for getting rid
of the competish.
More stuff
for me to steal!
Ha-ha!
No villain is safe from me,
Serpent!
But I’m not a villain.
I’m a transvestite.
Explain that
to your maker.
(sizzling)
I’ll take it from here,
Bart-Man.
(gun shots)
(mysterious music)
(people chattering)
No sign of
the Serpent, Chief.
Everything’s work
with you. Lighten up.
(snake charmer music playing)
That music--
it’s so hypnotic.
My bone has
a mind of its own.
I’ll be snaking those jewels
and venom gotta go.
Sorry I didn’t asp
your permission.
Hope that’s cobracetic.
Hey, jerk,
puns are lazy writing.
D’oh!
Huh?
(glass shattering)
Party’s over, Serpent!
No kidding because
you’re standing in the dip.
(gasping)
(guns clicking)
(dramatic orchestral music)
You!
You’re the man
who killed my parents!
Oh! Ahh! Ooh.
I did it.
I finally got my revenge.
But it didn’t bring
your parents back.
Tell me, big boy,
was it really worth it?
Well, I do feel
a little better.
Plus, I got
zillions of dollars
and no parents to
tell me what to do.
Bart-Man, don’t you
want to join us?
Don’t talk to me
when I’m vibrating.
So you see,
revenge is great,
and there’s three ways
to talk about it.
Although two of the ways
were kind of the same way,
and even the third one
might have worked better
as a Halloween story.
(laughing):
That’s okay, boy.
The two of us
got to talking.
Yeah, turns out we have
a lot in common.
We’re both
from Connecticut.
Look at all them stars.
How many do you
think there are?
Two.
What the...
Two? You think
there are two...
Well, I never.
How could you...?
Why do you think
it is that mankind
is so inclined towards
hating one another?
I don’t know.
Let’s just lay here
till we figure it out.
(dramatic, solemn
orchestral music)
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Shh!
Enhanced by Fotokem