♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-(screams)
-(tires screech)
Wow.
You know, most of my life,
I've had to live with the shame
of being a screw-up.
But now, as I stand here
with the award
for the district's
safest bus driver...
well, it...
it's like a dream come true.
MILHOUSE:
Otto, wake up!
Huh?
(screaming)
(children screaming)
(machinery clanging)
So, um... who's good
at keeping secrets?
"Dear parents,
"Due to yesterday's
unscheduled field trip
"to the auto wrecking yard,
"the school bus will be
out of commission for two weeks.
"By reading
this letter out loud,
"you have waived any legal
responsibility on our part
"in perpetuity
throughout the universe."
(groans)
Well, we'll have
to organize a car pool.
Hey! Every day will be
like a road trip
with your dad to school!
(grumbling)
So...
How about those
rainbow suspenders, huh?
Dad?
Pretty cool way to keep
your pants up, eh?
-Dad.
-I see these kids now
with "jive" printed
on their shirts.
Now, I can teach you
how you're supposed
to say "jive."
Dad. Please just
drive the car, Dad.
I'm watching the road, sweetie.
You jive turkey.
See? You got to sass it.
Quit jivin' me, turkey.
You got to sass it.
A "turkey" is
a bad person.
MAN (on radio):
K-F-S-L-- Fossil 103.
Classic hits from Abba
to Zeppelin, comma, Led.
♪ We are winners and losers ♪
♪ We're the mellow choosers ♪
Tell him.
Uh, Mr. Simpson, sir?
Can you please change
the radio station?
But this is
Grand Funk Railroad.
You guys back there
know Grand Funk, right?
(grumbling)
Nobody knows the band
Grand Funk?
The wild shirtless lyrics
of Mark Farner?
The bong-rattling bass
of Mel Schacher?
The competent drum work
of Don Brewer?
Oh, man!
For more information
on Grand Funk,
consult your school library.
("Mississippi Queen"
playing in distance)
♪ Mississippi queen ♪
When I listen to
a really good song,
I start nodding my head
like I'm saying
"yes" to every beat.
Yes! Yes! Yes!
This rocks!
And then sometimes
I switch it up like--
No! No! No!
Don't stop a-rockin'!
Dad, please.
You're embarrassing us.
No, I'm not.
I'm teaching you
about rock music. Now...
Grand Funk Railroad paved the way
for Jefferson Airplane
which cleared the way
for Jefferson Starship.
The stage was now set for
the Alan Parsons Project,
which I believe was
some sort of hovercraft.
Dad! No one cares about any
of your stupid dinosaur bands!
You have the worst,
lamest taste in music ever.
(turns off radio)
I'm just trying to
party with you guys.
Homer, first of all,
it's "par-tay,"
and second, we wouldn't
par-tay with you
if you were
the last dad on Earth.
Hmm.
Hi, there.
It's been a while
since I set foot
in Good Vibrations Music.
Where can I find the latest
releases by Bread?
-Oldies.
-Oldies?
But you've got
all the top bands in here.
Styx? I just heard them on
"The King Biscuit Flour Hour."
Now, here are some
of your no-name bands.
Sonic Youth?
Nine Inch Nails?
Hullabalooza?
Hullabalooza is
a music festival--
The greatest music festival
of all time.
There can only be one
truly great music festival
a lifetime and it's
the "US Festival."
-The what festival?
-The "US Festival"! Jeez!
It was sponsored by the guy
from Apple Computers.
-What computers?
-(groans)
Well, why do you need new bands?
Everyone knows rock
attained perfection in 1974.
It's a scientific fact.
("Frankenstein" playing
in background)
Quadraphonic sound,
a waterbed,
and now a strobe light.
Gentlemen, say hello
to the Second-Base Mobile.
ALL:
Wicked!
(music continues)
♪♪
HOMER: Back then, we didn't
care what anyone thought,
and the chicks
found that irresistible.
I think you're cool,
Homer Simpson.
Sandra,
that was mean.
But most of all,
I remember the music.
(falsetto): ♪ You make me feel
like dancing ♪
♪ I want to dance
the night away ♪
What the hell
are you two doing?
It's called "rockin' out."
You wouldn't understand, Dad.
You're not with it.
I used to be with it
but then they changed
what "it" was.
Now, what I'm with
isn't it,
and what's "it" seems
weird and scary to me.
(ominously):
It'll happen to you.
No way, man.
We're going to
keep on rocking forever.
Forever, forever, forever...
forever... forever...
What's wrong, Homey?
(sighs)
I went to the record
store today
and they were playing
all this music I never heard of.
It was like the store
had gone crazy.
Hmm. Record stores have
always seemed crazy to me
but it doesn't upset me.
Music is none of my business.
That's fine for you, Marge
but I used to
rock 'n' roll all night
and party every day.
Then it was
every other day.
Now, I'm lucky if I can
find half an hour a week
in which to get funky.
I've got to get out of this rut
and back into the groove.
Well, good.
Try to include Bart and Lisa.
(whistling tune)
Dear Lord, if you keep Homer
from embarrassing us today
we promise to build several
churches in your honor.
Bart, no!
Hey, wait!
I'm okay today.
My Mom bought me deodorant.
Dad, you forgot
to pick up Milhouse.
I did?
I must be getting
forgetful in my old age.
Open the glove
compartment
and fetch me
my brain medicine.
What are you talking about?
-(gasps)
-Well?
What have we here?
Looks like your uncool Dad
scored tickets
to Hullabalooza!
(gasps)
Bart, these look real.
Check the authenticator spot.
MAN: This is an authentic
Hullabalooza ticket.
For authentic refreshment,
eat Clark bars.
And for totally outrageous
class rings, it's Josten's.
Go, Josten's!
You're not going
to school today.
Today, your classroom will be
the Capitol City Amphitheater.
Your teacher--
four dozen rock bands.
So get ready for some
well-supervised craziness
while you rock out
with your father.
Whoo-hoo!
Wow. It's like Woodstock
only with advertisements
everywhere
and tons of security guards.
People, have your tickets out.
Throw your cameras out.
Surrender all identification.
Oh, my homemade Kahlua.
Generation "X" may be shallow,
but at least they have
tolerance and respect
for all people.
Hey, a freak show.
(barking)
-Ow! Aah!
-(crowd cheering)
Thank you. Thank you very much.
And now the band
you've all been waiting for--
Cypress Hill!
-Yeah!
-Before we start,
we have a lost child here.
If she's not claimed
within the next hour,
she will become property
of Blockbuster Entertainment.
♪ Throw your set in the air ♪
♪ Come on! ♪
♪ Wave it around like
you just don't care... ♪
(sniffing)
What is that smell?
It smells like Otto's jacket.
-Dude, karma.
-What?
Karma. Karma.
Oh, I get it.
Dad, you cannot wear that.
That's a Rastafarian hat.
Hey, I've been safari-ing
since before you were born.
Wearing a Jamaican hat
makes a bold statement
about your connection
to reggae music.
Well, excuse me!
You know what, Dad?
Maybe we'll go exploring
on our own for a while.
Well, Homer, this is it.
Time to get back
with the people--
the young people.
All right! Yeah!
Cool concert, am I right?
-Yeah, nice try, narc.
-Where's a narc?
-Who?
-That fat Jamaican guy.
What'd I say?
What's goin' on?
Hey, we're just trying
to have a good time, narc.
Why do you want
to destroy us?
Don't commit your
hate crimes here.
Hate crime!
Okay, I'm heading out now.
More butt support.
D'oh!
(playing mid-tempo rock)
♪ My reflection ♪
♪ Dirty mirror ♪
♪ There's no connection ♪
♪ To myself ♪
♪ I'm your lover ♪
♪ I'm your zero ♪
♪ I'm the face
in your dreams of glass ♪
-♪ So say your prayers... ♪
-It may be bleak,
but this music is really
getting to the crowd.
Eh, making teenagers depressed
is like shooting fish
in a barrel.
♪ Throw your cares
and fly... ♪
Oh...
Makes no sense.
I haven't changed
since high school,
and suddenly I'm uncool.
I've been kicked
out of paradise.
-(snorts)
-I'll never be part of the scene again.
(powering up)
Uh-oh.
(grunts)
Aw, man. There goes
Peter Frampton's big finale.
He's going to be pissed off.
You're damn right,
I'm going to be pissed off.
I bought that pig
at Pink Floyd's yard sale.
Dad, are you okay?
I'm fine.
(murmuring)
Sir, I run
Hullabalooza's Pageant
of the Transmundane--
the freak show.
And I've been looking
for a big fatso
to shoot with a cannon.
I'd like very much
for you to be that fatso.
So, you want
to go on tour
with a traveling
freak show.
I don't think I have
a choice, Marge.
-Of course, you have a choice.
-How do you figure?
You don't have to join
a freak show
just because the opportunity
came along.
You know, Marge, in some ways
you and I are very different people.
(cheering)
MAN (over P.A.): And now,
get ready for the man
with the iron stomach!
(drum roll)
(gulps)
Hi, everybody.
Is everybody--
(feedback)
...good?
(grunts)
(cheering)
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
"Stay in school.
Your hero, Homer."
(thud)
Hey, Cannonball,
I like your statement.
When life takes a cheap shot at you,
you stand your ground.
Billy Corgan,
Smashing Pumpkins.
Homer Simpson,
smiling politely.
You know, my kids
think you're the greatest.
And thanks to
your gloomy music,
they've finally
stopped dreaming
of a future I can't
possibly provide.
Well, we try to make
a difference.
"Dear Bart and Lisa..."
HOMER:
All is well on tour
with America's most popular
alternative music festival.
Our first job is to entertain.
-(grunts)
-(cheering)
And I like to think sometimes
we get a message across as well.
(grunts)
(cheering)
But the main thing is,
I've finally tapped into that
spirit of self-destruction
that makes rock 'n' roll
the king of music.
(cheering)
Whoo-hoo!
Hello, ticket holders!
Oh, here comes
that cannonball guy.
He's cool.
Are you being sarcastic, dude?
I don't even know anymore.
(grunts)
(cheering)
Thank you!
And remember!
Don't trust anyone over 30!
And now, Peter Frampton!
(cheering)
Thanks, Homer.
Homer Simpson, everyone!
(strikes chord)
Hey, Homer, looks
like our next stop
is your hometown,
Springfield.
Is it true that we have
to bring our own water?
We got a little
rule back home.
If it's brown,
drink it down.
If it's black,
send it back.
The hometown show's
the big one, Homer.
Yeah. People who called
you a weirdo in high school
get to see what a successful
freak you've become.
Hey, I wasn't a weirdo.
I was in the audio-visual club.
Really? Me too.
But I got kicked out
'cause of my views
on Vietnam.
Also, I was stealing
projectors.
Anyway...
get ready, beer belly.
We're going
to show Springfield
what we're made of.
All right, Homer!
Yeah!
(echoey belch)
That was odd.
Gee, I don't like
the sound of that.
(echo)
No biggie. I'm cool.
Homer, nothing's more
important to me
than the health and
well-being of my freaks.
I'm sending you to a vet.
My, God.
Those cannonballs
have practically demolished
your stomach.
From now on, no cannonballs,
no spicy foods.
And when you lie
in a hammock,
please, rest your
beer on your head
or your genitals.
(scoffs)
Rules. I'm a rocker.
I don't care for rules.
Mr. Simpson,
this is serious.
If you take one more
cannonball to the gut,
you will die.
Die?
Well, you don't scare me, Doc,
'cause dying would be
a stone groove.
Got any messages
for Jimi Hendrix?
Yes. Pick up your puppy.
BART: So, what's it like
being famous, Dad?
HOMER: People know your
name, but you don't know theirs.
It's great.
Dad, do you wear boxers
or briefs?
-Nope.
-What religion are you?
You know, the one with
all the well-meaning rules
that don't work out
in real life. Uh...
Christianity.
What's with all
the questions?
Just some report
I gotta do for school.
Hey, you want some pie?
Sure. We got a lot
of catching up to do.
Hmm...
(rumbling)
Clear the way,
clear the way.
Performer coming through.
This is so exciting.
Last time I got
to go backstage
was when Bart ripped his pants
at the Christmas play.
-Mom!
-Ha-ha!
Hello, bands. Who is playing with
the London Symphony Orchestra?
Come on, people. Somebody ordered
the London Symphony Orchestra--
possibly while high.
Cypress Hill,
I'm looking in your direction.
Hey, man, did we
order a orchestra?
(whispering)
What's up with this orchestra?
Where'd the orchestra come from?
I don't know, man.
They didn't tell me
about this, man.
We got to do something.
Uh, oh, yeah, yeah,
we think we did.
Uh, do you know
"Insane in the Brain"?
(British accent):
We mostly know classical,
but we could give it a shot.
(hip-hop beat playing)
♪ Put the water on the flame,
boiling temper ♪
♪ Just toss that ham in the
frying pan like spam... ♪
Now this, I like.
(synthesized voice):
♪ Do you feel... ♪
(crowd cheering)
♪ Like we do? ♪
Man. That guy's guitar
is talking.
Hey, my shoes
are talking too.
Don't worry.
We won't hurt you.
We only want
to have some fun.
(chuckling)
And to think, Smithers,
you laughed when I
bought Ticketmaster.
"Nobody's going to pay
a 100% service charge."
Well, it's a policy that
ensures a healthy mix
of the rich
and the ignorant, sir.
♪ Do you feel like we do? ♪
Springfield, yeah!
Do you-- Wait, what's this?
♪ Do you, do you feel ♪
♪ Do you feel ♪
-(squeaking)
-Oh, come on.
Do you feel!
God. Homer Simpson wrecks
my pig,
Cypress Hill steals
my orchestra,
and Sonic Youth's
in my cooler!
Get out of there,
you kids!
Aw, come on, Mr. Frampton.
You're not going to eat
all that watermelon.
Please.
I'm trying to perform.
Go ahead.
We'll stay here and
guard your cooler.
Oh, 25 years I've been in this.
I've never heard
anything like...
(crowd cheering)
And now, Springfield,
this is the moment
that you've been waiting for.
The man who embodies everything
about rock 'n roll, except the music--
Give it up for your
very own homegrown hero...
-Homer Simpson!
-(cheering)
I used to carpool
with that guy.
Oh, this is heavy.
Okay, Homer,
don't fear the reaper.
(stomach rumbling)
Oh, I'm going to die.
Cannons are designed
to hurt.
They're designed to hurt.
Shh! Mom, Dad needs our support.
You're the coolest Dad alive.
(drum roll)
(gasps)
(crowd gasping)
(crowd jeering)
Oh, Marge,
I thought I had
an appetite for destruction,
but all I wanted was
a club sandwich.
There might be one
in this cooler.
Oh, here we go.
Ohh!
Aw, man. Homer wussed out.
I'm so disillusioned.
Hey, Hullabalooza
isn't about freaks.
It's about music
and advertising
and youth-oriented
product positioning.
That and getting toasted--
nicely toasted.
Homer, I'm sorry.
There's nothing worse
than a yellow-bellied freak,
unless that's his act.
I expect your letter
of resignation on my desk.
-You have a desk?
-No, I mean, the hood of my car.
I'll miss you, Pumpkins, but I just
can't share your bleak world view.
I've got too much
to live for.
We envy you, Homer.
All we have is our music,
our legions of fans,
our millions of dollars,
and our youth.
Whoo-hoo!
Let's all go out
and buy fur coats!
I want a walk-in
humidor.
So, I realized that
being with my family
is more important
than being cool.
Dad, what you just said
was powerfully uncool.
You know what
the song says:
"It's hip to be square."
That song is so lame.
So lame that it's... cool?
-No.
Am I cool, kids?
Good. I'm glad.
And that's what makes me cool--
not caring, right?
-No.
Well, how the hell
do you be cool?
I feel like we've tried
everything here.
Wait, Marge.
Maybe if you're truly cool,
you don't need
to be told you're cool.
BART:
Well, sure you do.
LISA:
How else would you know?
♪♪
(guitar feedback)
(Sonic Youth playing
"The Simpsons" theme)
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.