♪ The Simpsons ♪
(chalk screeches)
(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
(sucking)
(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
(humming)
Is it done yet?
Your meat loaf will be ready
in eight seconds, Homer.
D'oh! Isn't there anything
faster than a microwave?
Four, three, two, one,
bing!
We have meat loaf.
Get it while it's
unbelievably hot, kids!
Yum. I've got
a dried-out end piece
with your name on it,
Lisa.
(sighing)
Thursday. Meat loaf night.
As it was is now
and ever shall be.
What are you
getting at?
Well, you're always
trying to teach me
to be open-minded.
Try new things, live life to--
What are you talking about?
Nobody's trying to teach you that.
-(sputtering)
-Ha! Ha! Ha-ha-ha!
-Shut up, boy.
-Well, maybe Lisa's right.
Tomorrow night, it might be nice to
go out for dinner.
Tomorrow night? Friday?
Pork chop night?
Marge, we haven't missed
pork chop night
since the great pig scare
in '87.
(sighs)
Friday night, pork chops.
From cradle to grave,
etched in stone
in God's library
somewhere up in heaven.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Where do you want to go?
Anywhere but hamburgers,
pizza or fried chicken.
Fine. We'll go to Mars.
There's that new
sushi restaurant on Elm Street.
Sushi? Hey maybe this is
just one of those things
you hear on the playground,
but isn't that raw fish?
As usual, the playground
has the facts right,
but missed the point entirely.
Sushi is considered
quite a delicacy.
-Please, Homer. Can't we try it?
-No!
Please Dad, this argument
humiliates us both.
If I said no the first time,
what makes you think I'm gonna
say yes the second time?
Nothing, but you may say yes
the 99th time.
Oh? Try me.
-Please, Dad.
-No.
-Please, Dad? Please, Dad?
-No. No.
-Please, Dad.
-Oh, okay, okay.
-BOTH: Ureshii mase!
-(screaming)
Please,
do not be alarmed.
Our chefs are
just saying hello.
Oh, okay.
-(loudly) Hello!
-(screaming)
This is our karaoke bar.
Now it is empty,
but soon it will be hopping
with drunken
Japanese businessmen.
I am Akira, your waiter.
May I take your order?
What would you recommend
for a family
that's not sure
they should be here?
The sushi surprise--
a little bit of everything.
It is very non-threatening.
I'll have
one of those.
-Make it two.
-Akira, my good man.
I'd like
two sharks, an octopus
-and an eel.
-Very good.
Do you have any giant squid?
The kind that drags men
-to their deaths?
-Not today. Sir?
It's so hard to choose.
It all looks
so terrible.
Just bring me one of these,
and one of these,
and one of those.
(grunting)
(disapproving grunts)
What do you think, master?
No, no, no. Toshiro,
that squid looks like
it's been hacked
by a blind woodsman.
Hang your head in shame.
(sighs)
Good thing I'm open-minded.
Not bad.
Interesting.
Let's try
this little pink one here.
Mmm, very good.
And another one.
Oh, boy, this fish
is delish.
(nervously)
Hi, my name is Richie Sakai.
I'm an anesthesiologist,
and I'd like to dedicate
this next song
to my wife, Patty.
♪ I was born in the wagon
of a traveling show ♪
♪ Mama used to dance
for the money they'd throw ♪
♪ Papa would do
whatever he could ♪
Oh, ooh! And two
of these things.
-Two uni?
-And, ooh, ooh,
I don't believe I've tried
the flying fish roll.
I recommend it with
a roe quail egg on top.
You're the doctor.
♪♪ (Theme from "Shaft")
♪ Who's the black
private dick ♪
♪ That's the sex machine
to all the chicks? ♪
♪ Shaft ♪
♪ You're damn right ♪
♪ Who's the cat
that won't cop out ♪
♪ When there's danger
all about? ♪
♪ Shaft ♪
♪ Right on ♪
There's got to be something
I haven't tried. Huh?
Hey, what's this?
Fugu.
(gasps)
It is blowfish, sir,
but I should warn you
that one--
Come on, pal.
Fugu me!
♪ They say this cat Shaft
is a bad mother-- ♪
♪ Shut your mouth ♪
♪ But I'm
talkin' about Shaft ♪
♪ Then I can dig it ♪
♪ He's a complicated man ♪
♪ But no one understands
him but his woman ♪
♪ John Shaft ♪
-(horn honks)
-Oh, she's here.
Cover for me.
-One fugu.
-(gasping)
Not fugu. If it is
cut improperly it's--
Yes, yes, it is poisonous,
potentially fatal,
but, if sliced properly,
it can be quite tasty.
I must get master.
Oh... oh... oh,
Miss Krabappel.
Oh, your hair smells so...
so clean.
Uh, master, you are needed
in the kitchen.
I said cover for me,
damn it!
But, master,
we need your skilled hands.
My skilled hands are busy.
You do it!
Hmm, hmm...
(sighs)
Poison, poison. Tasty fish.
Concentrate.
HOMER:
I want fugu!
Mmm. Fan-fugu-tastic.
(whistling)
Oh, no!
(yelling in Japanese)
Beautiful language,
isn't it, Marge?
For God's sake,
don't eat another bite.
Oh, I couldn't possibly.
Mr. Simpsonsan,
I shall be blunt.
We have reason to believe
you have eaten...
-poison.
-Poison! Wha!
What should I do? What should I do?
Tell me quick.
Oh, no need to panic.
There's a map to the hospital
on the back of the menu.
(siren wailing)
Try something new, Homer.
What will it hurt you, Homer?
I never heard of
a poison pork chop.
Um, your wife agreed that
I should break this to you.
No need, doc.
I can read Marge like a book.
(groans)
Whoo! It's good news,
isn't it?
-No, Mr. Simpson.
-Oh.
If in fact you've consumed
the venom of the blowfish--
and from what the chef has
told me, it's quite probable--
You have 24 hours to live.
-24 hours!
-Well, 22.
I'm sorry
I kept you waiting so long.
Oh, Marge
I'm gonna die.
(sobbing)
Well, if there's
one consolation
it's that you'll feel
no pain at all
until some time
tomorrow evening
when your heart
suddenly explodes.
Now a little death anxiety
is normal.
You can expect to go through
five stages.
The first is denial.
No way,
because I'm not dying.
-Second is anger.
-Why, you little--
(stammering)
Then after that
comes fear.
What's after fear?
-Bargaining.
-Doc, you gotta get me out of this.
I'll make it
worth your while.
And finally, acceptance.
Well, we all got to go sometime.
Mr. Simpson, your progress
astounds me.
I should leave you two alone.
Perhaps this pamphlet
will be helpful.
(Homer reading)
(sobbing)
Hello, Marge, hello.
I'm the one who's
dying, not you.
(sniffles)
Oh, I'm sorry, Homer.
Have you thought
about what you want
to tell the kids?
Nothing.
It'll just upset them.
I want my last hours
of family life
to be happy ones.
Well, have you decided
what you want to do tomorrow?
Almost.
(Marge muttering)
Oh, good. Aw!
I'm not done yet, Marge.
What's that word you use
for when you and I--
-You know.
-When we're intimate?
Be intimate with Marge.
Aw... Can I just make
one suggestion?
Can we get up early and
watch the sunrise together?
Ah... watch the sunrise.
Till 6:00 a.m.,
my dearest darling,
and my last day
on Earth.
(alarm beeping)
(snoring)
11:30!
Oh, that's just great.
Marge, why did you
let me sleep so late?
You looked so peaceful
lying there.
There'll be plenty
of time for that!
I got tons of important
stuff to do.
Bart. Bart!
"Have man-to-man with Bart."
Come here, boy.
Oh, man.
No!
I just want to have
a heart-to-heart talk.
-Oh.
-You know, Bart,
after me, you're the man
around the house.
And that means you're
gonna have to help out--
Aw, come on, I do
plenty around here.
Lisa never lifts a finger
Why don't you go yell at her?
Shut up, Bart!
This is good stuff.
I want to share
something with you.
The three little sentences that
will get you through life.
Number one--
Cover for me.
Number two--
Oh, good idea, boss.
Number three--
It was like that
when I got here.
-Hey, this is good stuff.
-Told 'ya. Now c'mon.
You're going to learn
how to shave.
And finally, the little spot
under your nose.
Next, we take
some toilet paper,
tear off some
teensy little squares
and stick one there...
and there...
and anyplace
you're bleeding.
There and there.
Don't worry.
The blood will hold it
right on your face.
And now... some aftershave.
Oooh! Ahh! Eee! Ahhh!
Hnnn!
Ooh, ahh!
Son of a-- oh!
-And that's how we shave.
-Ooh--
-(glass breaks)
-D'oh!
-Oh!
-Why, you little--
It was like that
when I got here.
Oh, that's my boy.
"Listen to Lisa play her sax."
♪♪ (saxophone)
Hi, Dad.
Want me to cut out
this infernal racket?
Oh, let me hear you play.
-Why?
-Does a father have to explain?
Let's just share your gift.
Okay?
♪♪ (somber blues)
Oh!
(sobs)
-♪♪ ("When the Saints Go Marchin' In")
-Huh?
Yeah, that's
more like it.
Ho-ho! Whoo!
♪ Oh, I want to be
in that number ♪
♪ When the saints
go over there ♪
♪ Oh, over there! ♪
♪ Oh,
over there! ♪
(Homer humming)
"Make videotape for Maggie."
(doorbell rings)
Simpson, what
a pleasant surprise.
We were just
pulling taffy.
Gee, the fun never stops
at the Flanders house,
-does it?
-No siree, Bob.
Hey, Flanders, could I
borrow your camcorder?
Okie-dokle.
Hey, why don't you
your family
come over for a
barbecue tomorrow?
-No, thanks.
-Oh, are you sure?
We got that new propane beauty
just sittin' in the back yard.
-No, I don't--
-It's crying out
to cook up
some good eatin'.
Flanders!
I said I didn't--
Tomorrow?
Sure, what the hey.
I'd love to come
to your barbecue.
Heh-heh-heh.
I'll even bring the thickest,
juiciest T-bones
you've ever seen.
Mm-mm,
sounds terrif.
(chuckling)
The joke's on him.
I'll be dead by then.
(Homer muttering)
Is that it?
(clears throat)
This is a videotape
for my daughter, Maggie.
Hi, Maggie.
I'm speaking to you
from beyond the grave.
Whoo-hoo!
(laughs)
Hope that didn't scare you.
Well, Maggie,
you're grown up now,
and unless you taped over this,
you're probably wondering
what kind of man
your father was.
He was a simple man.
A kind man.
A gentle man who loved
his children and--
-(phone rings)
-D'oh!
(angrily)
Hello!
Yeah, he's here.
Who is this?
Bart's friend, Milhouse?
Bart, get your
butt down here!
(tires screech)
-Dad?
-Huh?
Oh, it's you.
What do you want?
Dad, we've never been
too close, have we?
Not to my knowledge.
Never went fishing
or played catch
or even hugged each other.
We never danced
the hootchy-koo either.
What's your point?
(voice breaking)
I just want you to know
that I love you, Dad.
-You do?
-(sniffles) Uh-huh.
Oh, son, I love you too.
Hey, how about a hug?
-Dad.
-Sonny-boy.
-Papa!
-Junior!
My old man.
Well, I got to go.
Oh, son, no. We got a lot
of catching up to do.
Whaddaya say we go fishing?
Gee, Dad, if I wasn't on such
a tight schedule...
-(sniffles)
-Well, I--
Oh, let's get some worms.
Ooh! Oh!
Hey!
Well, no time for that.
-(grunts)
-(chuckles)
Aw, I really wanted to
do that one.
-(grunting)
-I got you!
Aargh!
Gee, Dad, way to hog
my last moments.
Just a quick game
of hacky-sack.
I love you, son.
Yeah, yeah.
Gee, the old guy's a little love-starved.
Get moving, you hunk of junk.
I gotta make up for lost time.
-(siren wailing)
-D'oh!
(police radio chatter)
I'm sorry, officer.
I know I was going too fast.
-Just give me a ticket.
-I beg your pardon?
Just give me a ticket!
Whoa. That sounded
like an order.
I pay my taxes,
and they pay your salary.
So when I say give me a ticket,
just give me a ticket.
Uh-huh. Maybe we don't want
to give you a ticket.
Maybe we wanna haul
your butt in, wise guy.
(grunting)
OFFICER: Look what else your
tax dollars pay for, huh?
-(door slams)
-(officers laughing)
(whimpers)
♪♪ (harmonica)
That's sort of nice.
What are you in for?
Atmosphere.
Okay, flash,
you get one phone call.
Wait. I can't call Marge.
It's our last day on Earth
together.
I can't drag her into
this mess.
I know--
I'll call Barney.
(ringing)
♪ Nobody's here, nobody's here,
nobody's here ♪
Damn those novelty telephone
answering machine tapes!
HOMER:
Thanks a lot, Barney!
I just wasted my
one phone call on your--
Wait! I'm home, I'm home.
Oh. Hi, Homer.
You gotta help me Barney,
I'm in jail.
You are? Hey, Homer,
go to the window.
Hi, neighbor.
I can see you!
Aah! Just get over here
and bring 50 bucks for bail.
50 bucks?!
What did you do,
kill a judge?
Where am I gonna get
50 bucks?
Hey. Pizza!
Why are we all
dressed up?
Because sometimes it's fun
to dress up for dinner.
Why are we using
the good china?
Because sometimes it's fun
to use the good china.
What's with
the candles?
Sometimes it's fun
to use candles.
Why are we waiting
for Dad?
Because we love your father
and enjoy his company.
Why are we really
waiting for Dad?
Ha! $48.70.
You know, we don't usually
take rusty money.
You're dying, and you weren't
even going to stop at Moe's
for a last beer
with your buddies?
(sobbing)
Hey Barney, look,
it was on my list
along with a lot of other things
I didn't get to do today.
Hey, my boss!
Smithers, check out the
luscious pair on that redhead.
That's it, baby.
Work those ankles.
Ring-a-ding-ding, sir.
Hey, Burns!
Eat my shorts!
Who the Sam Hill
was that?
Why it's...
Homer Simpson, sir.
One of the schmoes
from Sector Seven-G.
Simpson, eh?
I want him in my office
at 9:00 Monday morning.
We'll see who eats
whose shorts.
HOMER:
Wow, of all the luck.
To think I almost died
without telling the boss
to eat my shorts.
Oh, Homer, come on.
You got time
for one last beer.
Please!
I got to call Marge.
Ha!
(makes whipping sound)
-(ringing)
-Hello, Moe's Tavern.
Birthplace of the Rob Roy.
Is Seymour there?
Last name Butts.
Just a sec.
Hey, is there a Butts here?
Seymour Butts?
Hey, everybody,
I want a Seymour Butts!
(laughing)
Oh, wait a minute.
Listen, you little
scum-sucking, pus bucket.
When I get my hands on you
I'm gonna pull out your eyeballs
with a corkscrew.
Oh, it was busy.
Moe, another last beer,
please.
(sniffles)
Guys, keep it down.
I got some last words.
I never told you this before,
but sometimes when I'm at work
I think of you and smile.
So often I think that--
Oh, words won't do it.
I love you, Moe.
Please, not in public.
You better be dying.
I love you, Barney.
Whoa! How European.
-(belches)
-(screams)
C'mon, Barney.
I got to get home.
Faster, Barney, faster.
I'm twirling
as fast as I can.
Oh, I can't wait any longer.
Hold on, Marge.
I'm coming home, baby!
(panting)
Come on, come on.
Oh, where can he be?
Marge! Marge!
Homer!
There's no time
to explain.
Love you, love you,
love you.
(gargling)
I wrote a poem for you
this afternoon, Homer.
It's called "To a Husband."
Okay, okay.
(clears throat)
"The blackened clouds
are forming..."
Oh, give me a break, Marge.
"Soon the rain
will fall.
"My dear one
is departing
"But first,
please heed this call
"That always
will I love you
My one, my love, my all."
That was beautiful.
(kissing)
(sighs)
Good-bye, Maggie.
Stay as sweet as you are.
Good-bye, Lisa.
I know you'll make me proud.
Good-bye, Bart.
I like your sheets.
The good book.
On tape?
Ooh, it's read by Larry King.
Hi, I'm Larry King.
In the beginning, God created
the Heaven and the Earth
and the Earth
was without form...
Alzeah begat Phineas,
Phineas begat Abushua, and...
(tape fast-forwarding)
...begat Ahamas,
Ahamas begat...
(tape fast-forwarding)
...onward, Amariah begat
Aerito, Aerito begat...
(tape fast-forwarding)
...Shalam begat Hilchia...
...and he shall turn the heart
of the fathers to the children
and the heart of the children
to their fathers
lest I come and smite the Earth
with a curse.
Well, that's it.
My old friend Duke Seaver's
standing by.
We'll get some coffee.
We'll get some
matzo ball soup.
I love the San Antonio Spurs,
by the way,
If you're betting
in the N.B.A. this year,
I think they're gonna
win it all.
So I guess there's
nothing more to say but...
(tape stops abruptly)
Homer?
(gasps)
Oh, Homer...
Homer...
Hmm...
His drool--
it's warm.
He's alive!
Homer! Homer, wake up!
You're alive!
-Marge, stop it. Cut it out.
-Wake up, you're alive!
You're alive!
What are you
talking about?
-You're alive!
-I'm alive!
I'm alive,
and I couldn't be happier!
(laughing)
From this day forward,
I vow to live life
to its fullest.
(crunching)
COMMENTATOR 1(on TV):
Strike! That's three in a row.
COMMENTATOR 2: That's right.
Let's see that one again.
Yeah, here we go.
Here he comes.
Note the excellent
wrist action.
It's just about to go
into the gutter
and then a nice spin.
-Ouch! A split.
-My, my.
Well, if he makes this,
he'll be down by 40 pins.
This match, though, is far
from over, as you know.
COMMENTATOR 1: Yeah,
it is far from over
but his approach has been
wrong from the beginning
as far as I'm concerned.
COMMENTATOR 2: Well, he's
an erratic bowler, Jim.
He tends to explode
in the seven, eight,
nine frames...
(pins falling,
people cheering)
...Moline, Illinois.
Actually, that was
Pontiac, Michigan.
38 pins going into
the eighth.
COMMENTATOR 1:
Yeah, that's right.
Well, uh,
he's stepping up now.
In fact, he needs to get
at least a spare.
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.