♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
(goofy laugh)
I hope you enjoyed
my one-man pie fight, kids.
Now it's time for another
fanshmabulous episode of...
-Itchy & Scratchy!
-♪ The Itchy and Scratchy Show! ♪
(screaming)
(laughing)
(sighs)
Uh-oh.
(screaming)
Kids?
You're missing
"The Itchy & Scratchy show."
Don't you
like it anymore?
Sure. We love it.
But how can we watch TV
when it's so beautiful out?
Well, yeah, Mom.
I mean, we love you
and Dad, too,
but God knows, we don't
need to see you every day.
An occasional hug
is all I ask.
Mmm...
Mom! You can hug me
when I'm asleep.
-I do.
-(screams)
(Krusty groaning)
Hey, Krusty,
you look great.
You get your
teeth bleached?
Yeah, it's a new kind
of polymer treatment...
Hey, shut up!
You're here 'cause your
Itchy & Scratchy cartoons
are stinking up
my ratings.
Look at this breakdown
of yesterday's show.
Uh... Uh...
Eeyah... Kaboom.
What happened here?
Lightning hit
the transmitter?
See, that's what I thought
at first...
Hey, shut up!
That crater is where your
lousy cartoon crash-landed!
It's ratings poison!
But Itchy & Scratchy
is critically acclaimed.
Acclaimed?
(spits)
I ought to replace it right now
with a Chinese cartoon
where the robots
turn into... Blingwads!
But I'm a lazy,
lazy man, Roger.
So I'll give you
one more chance.
Now, get out!
Don't come back till you've
fixed Itchy & Scratchy.
(crashing glass)
WOMAN: Okay, Mel,
you can go in now.
Krusty, I've come
to solicit donations
for the rock 'n roll museum,
and I'll come back later.
I need to purchase
a brassiere.
You kids wait over here
in the credit department.
Oh, can't we just
wander around
and meet you back here
later?
Mmm...
Okay, just be careful.
Would you kids
like to come with me?
-Okay, I guess so.
-Sounds good to me. Let's go.
All right, thanks for participating
in our focus group, kids.
Today, we're going
to show you some
Itchy & Scratchy
cartoons.
(all cheering)
Cool!
We want you to tell us
what you think
and be honest because
no one from the show
is here spying on you.
(muffled sneeze)
Why is that
mirror sneezing?
Uh, look, it's just
an old, creaky mirror.
Sometimes it sounds
a little like it's
sneezing or coughing
or talking softly.
Hmm...
Now you each have a knob
in front of you.
When you like what you see,
turn the knob to the right.
When you don't like
what you see, turn it left.
My knob tastes funny.
Please refrain from
tasting the knob.
♪♪
(cries out)
(laughter)
Hey, quit it!
They like Itchy.
They like Scratchy.
One kid seems to
love the Speedo man.
What more do they want?
Okay, how many of you kids
would like Itchy & Scratchy
to deal with
real-life problems
like the ones
you face every day?
-I would!
-Great idea! Yeah, that's it!
And who would like to see them
do just the opposite,
getting into
far-out situations
involving robots
and magic powers?
-Oh, cool!
-Me!
-Cool!
-Yeah, that's I want!
So, you want a realistic,
down-to-earth show...
that's completely
off the wall
and swarming
with magic robots.
-That's right.
-Yeah, good.
And also, you should
win things by watching.
(sighs)
You kids don't know
what you want!
That's why you're still kids--
'cause you're stupid!
Just tell me what's wrong
with the freakin' show!
(crying)
-Mommy!
-(buzzer sounds)
Um, excuse me, sir.
The thing is, there's not
really anything wrong
with "The Itchy
and Scratchy Show."
It's as good as ever.
But after so many years,
the characters just can't have
the same impact they once had.
That's it.
That's it,
little girl!
You've saved
"Itchy & Scratchy"!
Please sign these papers
indicating you did not
save "Itchy & Scratchy."
I have figured out
how to rejuvenate the show.
It is so simple
you egghead writers
would've never thought of it.
What we need is...
a new character!
One that today's kids
can relate to!
Are you absolutely sure
that's wise, sir?
I don't want to sound
pretentious here, but...
Itchy & Scratchy
comprise a dramaturgical dyad.
Hey, this ain't art;
it's business!
What do you got in mind?
Sexy broad?
Gangster octopus?
No... No.
The animal chain
of command goes
mouse, cat, dog.
D-O-G.
Uh, a dog?
Isn't that a tad predictable?
In your dreams.
We're talking
the original dog from hell.
You mean Cerberus?
We at the network
want a dog with attitude.
He's edgy.
He's in your face.
You've heard the expression
"Let's get busy"?
Well, this is a dog
who gets biz-zay...
consistently and thoroughly.
So, he's proactive, huh?
Oh, God, yes.
We're talking about
a totally outrageous paradigm.
Excuse me, but "proactive"
and "paradigm"--
Aren't these just buzzwords
that dumb people use
to sound important?
Not that I'm accusing you
of anything like that.
I'm fired, aren't I?
Oh, yes.
The rest of you writers
start thinking up a name
for this funky dog.
I don't know, something along
the lines of, say... "Poochie"
only more proactive.
Yeah!
-(door slams)
-So, "Poochie" okay with everybody?
-Yeah.
-Yeah. You know, it's good.
No, no, no.
He was supposed
to have attitude.
Um, wh-what do
you mean, exactly?
Oh, you know,
attitude, attitude!
Uh... Sunglasses!
Can we put him in more
of a hip-hop context?
Forget context.
He's got to be a surfer.
Give me a nice shmear
of surfer.
I feel we should
rasta-fy him by 10% or so.
Mm.
I think he needs
a little more attitude.
-Oh, yeah, bingo.
-Yeah!
-There it is, right there. That's it.
-I love it.
Hey, Lis, look,
they're adding a new character
to "Itchy & Scratchy"!
Poochie the Dog?
Adding a new character
is often a desperate attempt
to boost low ratings.
Yo, yo! How's it hanging,
everybody?
Morning, Roy.
Yeah, hi, Roy.
Hey! They're having
open casting
for the voice of Poochie.
You should try out, Dad.
-You have a funny voice.
-I do not!
Haven't you ever listened to
yourself on a tape recorder?
I prefer to listen
to Cheap Trick.
Well, here,
say something.
Hey... This is
Homer Simpson saying
howdy to all the girls
out there in radio-land.
(tape rewinding)
Hey, this is
Homer Simpson saying...
Ah! I don't sound
like that, do I?
Oh... I don't like having
such a hilarious voice.
That hilarious voice could be
your ticket to stardom.
Whoa, a talking dog!
(chuckles)
What were you guys smoking
when you came up with that?
We were eating
rotisserie chicken.
Can you just
read the line, please?
"Ruff, ruff!
I am Poochie,
the Rockin' Dog!"
You're perfect!
In fact,
you're better than perfect!
Next to you,
perfection is crap.
"Ruff, ruff! I'm Poochie,
the Rockin' Dog!"
Hi. I'm Troy McClure.
You may remember me
from such cartoons
as "Christmas Ape"
And "Christmas Ape
Goes to Summer Camp."
You're even better
than this guy!
Take a hike, you bum.
(grumbles)
(clears throat)
"Ruff, ruff!
I'm Poochie,
the Rockin' Dog!"
Now, that's just bad. You got no attitude,
you're barely outrageous
and I don't know what you're in,
but it's not my face.
Next.
Oh, no attitude, eh?
Not in your face, huh?
Well, you can cram it
with walnuts, ugly!
That's it,
that's the Poochie attitude!
Do that again.
Huh? I can't.
I don't remember what I did.
Then you don't get the job.
Next!
Oh, I don't
get the job, do I?
Well, boo-hoo...
I don't get to be
a cartoon dog.
That's it!
You've got the job!
Oh, now
I got the job, huh?
Oh. Thank you.
Okay, Homer,
let's get a level check
on your voice.
She smells sheet smells
by the sheet store.
Wait, wait.
Let me try it again.
Relax, Homer.
You'll do fine.
I'm June Bellamy.
I do the voices
of Itchy and Scratchy.
You?
But you're a lady.
(as Itchy)
She's a lady, all right.
(as Scratchy)
A beautiful lady.
(laughing)
Hey, that really is you.
How'd you get
to be so good?
Oh, just experience,
I suppose.
I started out
as Roadrunner.
-(as Roadrunner): Meep!
-You mean meep-meep?
No, they only paid me
to say it once
then they doubled it up
on the soundtrack.
Cheap bastards.
-You folks ready to begin?
-Uh, I guess.
Is this episode going
on the air live?
No, Homer.
Very few cartoons
are broadcast live.
It's a terrible strain
on the animator's wrist.
Hi, question
for Miss Bellamy.
In episode 2f09
when Itchy plays Scratchy's
skeleton like a xylophone
he strikes the same rib
twice in succession
yet he produces
two clearly different tones.
I mean, what are we to believe
that this is some sort of...
(derisive snort)
Magic xylophone
or something?
Boy, I really hope somebody
got fired for that blunder.
Uh, well, uh...
I'll field this one.
Let me ask you a question.
Why would a man whose shirt
says "Genius at work"
spend all of his time watching
a children's cartoon show?
I withdraw my question.
Uh, excuse me,
Mr. Simpson.
On the "Itchy
& Scratchy" CD-ROM
is there a way to get
out of the dungeon
without using
the wizard key?
What the hell
are you talking about?
You're a lifesaver, Homer.
I can't deal with
these hardcore fans.
(clears throat)
Your attention, please!
MAN:
Uh, in episode--
Eh, your attention, please!
Mr. Simpson
will now be autographing
8-by-10 glossies of Poochie.
One per customer.
Please form a line.
There will be no cutting.
I'm talking to you,
Mr. Cutter.
Pardon me. Look out.
Pardon me. Excuse me.
Hot soup.
Hi. Kindly make
one out to me
and three out to my friend
of the same name.
MARGE: I'm so glad
you could join us
for Homer's big premiere.
BARNEY:
Poochie's based on me.
Is this seat taken,
little girl?
I'm not a girl.
Are you blind?
Yes.
I am stoked, Mr. S.
Shh. Everybody,
it's coming on.
Once in a great while
we are privileged
to experience a television event
so extraordinary
it becomes part
of our shared heritage.
1969:
Man walks on the moon.
1971:
Man walks on the moon, again.
Then for a long time
nothing happened...
Until tonight.
Behold the future of comedy:
Poochie!
(all cheering)
♪ They fight and bite ♪
♪ And bark ♪
♪ They fight and bite
and bite and bark ♪
♪ Fight, bite, bark
woof, woof, woof ♪
♪ The Itchy & Scratchy ♪
♪ And Poochie show ♪
Look, Scratchy.
It's our new friend,
Poochie.
What's that name again?
I forgot.
♪ The name's Poochie D ♪
♪ And I rock the telly ♪
♪ I'm half Joe Camel
and a third Fonzarelli ♪
♪ I'm the kung fu hippie
from Gangsta City ♪
♪ I'm a rappin' surfer ♪
♪ You the fool I pity ♪
Ooh, Poochie
is one outrageous dude.
He's totally in my face.
Wiggity-wiggity word up.
Rock on, party.
When are they
going to get
to the fireworks factory?
(sobbing)
Could somebody tell me
what the hell is going on?
Midge,
help me out here.
Quiet.
You're missing the jokes.
♪♪
Catch you on the flip side,
dudemeisters.
Not!
Hey, kids,
always recycle...
to the extreme!
Bust it!
Ah, that stunk.
Well, what did
everybody think?
(murmuring)
(clearing throats)
Homer,
I can honestly say
that was the best episode
of "Impy and Chimpy"
I've ever seen.
Yeah, you should be
very proud, Homer.
You, uh... You got
a beautiful home here.
So, it was
pretty okay, huh?
Mom, can we go to bed
without dinner?
Yes, we can.
(doors slam)
Well,
at least I liked it.
Didn't I?
HOMER'S BRAIN: Oh, you don't want
to know what I really think.
Now,
look sad and say "D'oh."
D'oh.
I'm the worst
Poochie ever.
No, it's not
your fault, Dad.
You did fine.
It's just that
Poochie was a soulless
by-product
of committee thinking.
You can't be cool
just by spouting
a bunch of
worn-out buzzwords.
Don't have a cow, Lis.
Bart's right.
Let's none of us
have a cow.
All that matters
is that the fans
of the show liked it.
Last night's
"Itchy & Scratchy" was,
without a doubt,
the worst episode ever.
Rest assured that I was
on the Internet within minutes
registering my disgust
throughout the world.
Hey, I know it wasn't great,
but what right do you have to complain?
As a loyal viewer,
I feel they owe me.
What?
They're giving you thousands of hours
of entertainment for free.
What could they possibly
owe you?
I mean, if anything,
you owe them.
Worst episode ever.
It looks like
the beginning of the end
for the venerable
"Itchy & Scratchy" program.
For years, TV critics such
as yours truly, Kent Brockman,
have waited impatiently
for cracks to appear
in the show's
hilarious facade.
Yesterday our prayers
were finally answered
when Poochie the Dog made
his howlingly unfunny debut.
Far be it for me
to gloat at another's downfall,
but I have a feeling
no children
are going to be crying
when this puppy
is put to sleep.
(laughing)
(bawling)
What the hell happened?
Well, I'd attribute
the product failure
to fundamental shifts
in our key demographic
coupled with the overall
crumminess of Poochie.
Whoa! You got to stop
this thing!
(bawling)
Please! I'm getting
egged on the street!
Do something!
(sobbing)
(knocking)
Uh, hi, Mr. Myers.
I've been doing
some thinking
and I've got some ideas
to improve the show.
I got it right here.
Uh, one: Poochie needs
to be louder, angrier,
and have access
to a time machine.
Two: Whenever Poochie's
not on screen,
all the other characters
should be asking,
"Where's Poochie?"
-Three...
-Great, great.
Just leave them
right there on the floor
on your way out.
WRITER:
Thanks, Homer, great.
Hmm...
(muffled voices)
Listen, guys we got to do
something about Poochie.
KRUSTY: There's only one thing
we can do.
Then they said they were going
to kill Poochie off!
Really?
Oh, how terrible.
Yes. Terrible.
It's not your fault, Homer.
It's those lousy writers.
They make me madder
than a, um...
Yak in heat!
You're right, Marge.
It's not my fault.
I'm not gonna let them treat
Poochie like dirt anymore
just because
he's the new guy.
Right on, Mr. S.!
Put a sock in it, Roy.
Okay, so here's where
Itchy lunges at Poochie
with a rusty
chain saw.
Cue sound effects.
(chain saw buzzing)
Rustier!
(shrill buzzing)
Are you prepared to die,
Poochie?
No, I am not.
Oh, cut, cut, cut, cut!
Just stick to the script
as written, Homer.
You're supposed to say,
"Please, cut off my head.
I don't deserve to live."
Never!
(murmuring)
You can't just kill off
a classic TV character.
Poochie could be bigger
than curly fries
but first he has to
win back the audience.
That's why I'm going to read
these lines I wrote myself
with my own two hands.
Forget it, Homer!
We can do this show
without you if we have to.
But not without me.
Aw, jeez.
Let him try
the new lines.
All right.
We'll try it.
Action.
Hi, Poochie!
You look like you've
got something to say.
Do you?
Yes, I certainly do.
Hello there, Itchy.
I know there's
a lot of people
who don't like me
and wish I would go away,
but I think we got off
on the wrong foot.
I know I can come off
a little proactive
and for that, I'm sorry.
But if everyone could find
a place in their hearts
for the little dog
nobody wanted
I know we can
make them laugh
and cry... until we
grow old together.
And... cut.
Now kids, I know you loved
the old Poochie,
but the new one's
going to be better
than ten Super Bowls!
I don't want to oversell it.
Judge for yourself.
(buzzing)
Well, look who's here!
Hi, Poochie!
You look like you've
got something to say.
Do you?
Yes,
I certainly do.
MR. MYERS VOICE:
I have to go now.
My planet needs me.
BART: Wow! Poochie came
from another planet?
Uh, I guess.
Hey, that wasn't
supposed to happen!
Those finks
double-crossed me!
Poochie's dead!
(goofy laugh)
(cheering)
Now kids, we all know that sometimes
when cartoon characters die,
they're back again
the very next week.
That's why I'm presenting
this sworn affidavit
the Poochie will never,
ever, ever return!
This document conforms to all
applicable laws and statutes.
(kids cheer)
Oh, yeah.
Tough break, Dad.
I guess people just
weren't ready for Poochie.
Maybe
in a few years.
Good news, everybody.
I'm moving into my own apartment
with two sexy ladies.
Oh, then I guess
this is good-bye, Roy.
Maybe we'll see you
in a few years.
-(kisses)
-(clicks tongue)
Well, I guess
I learned my lesson.
The thing is,
I lost creative control
of the project.
And I forgot to ask
for any money.
Well, live and learn.
♪♪
(sighs)
(screams)
(Bart and Lisa laughing)
It's back to the basics.
Classic "Itchy & Scratchy."
We should thank
our lucky stars
they're still putting on
a program of this caliber
after so many years.
What else is on?
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.