CHOIR: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
Hey.
(exclaims)
(school bell ringing)
(burps)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
(grunts)
(clacking)
Aw.
(choking)
♪ ♪
(sniffing)
(Homer doing Tarzan yell)
And that's amore.
(confused bark)
(head knocks)
(Homer chuckles)
Let the word go forth.
With the kids
gone for the summer,
we have snuggled
in every room in the house.
Thank you, Kamp Krusty.
(footsteps rumbling)
-WIGGUM: Um, excuse me.
-(yelps)
(footsteps rumbling)
Um, putting on a little
weight there, huh, Chief?
Our freezer broke, Lou.
Any bacon we buy
we have to eat it all
and right away.
Uh, now, Simpson, we received
an anonymous call about a gong.
Chief Wiggum, can't a man enjoy
the company of his wife
in his own son's tree house?
What, you didn't
see the sign?
Hmm?
That's just some nonsense
a kid wrote, Chief.
That is what they said
about the Declaration
of Independence, Lou.
Uh, who said that?
King Shut-the-hell-up.
Look, we're married.
This is our home,
and our kids are fine.
♪ Hail to thee, Kamp Krusty ♪
(kids clamoring)
Death to tennis camp!
(kids screaming)
I can't believe
it's been six weeks
since we've seen the kids.
Ooh, I wonder
if Bart has a mustache.
(tires screech)
Your kids are back.
Except for the Johnsons',
who I need to speak to privately.
(chuckles nervously)
(kids clamoring)
(shuddering)
I have lemon-lime disease!
The basketball teams
were skin versus bones.
I'm tellin' ya,
it was a real rough camp.
I see you're sucking your thumb again.
Kirk, you said he'd stopped.
Uh...
Kirk, we discussed this.
It's the only vice I can afford!
Oh, my poor, poor babies.
Do you know what kids get
after a scary experience?
ALL:
Ice cream!
No. Counseling.
Oh.
Kids, you've been through
a horrible experience,
but there is good news
at the end of that pain-bow.
A pot of goals. All right.
How long you gonna
talk this way?
Well, let's just say,
"I wish eyes were smiling."
(chuckles)
Now, kids,
how bad could it have
really been?
Hey, Doc, I'm fine.
But other kids in my generation,
I love 'em,
but they're total wusses.
Well, every night,
they showed us The Parent Trap.
I mean, what kind of
parents break up twins
and never tell them
the other exists?!
-Oh, that's Disney magic.
-(shudders)
Now, you all need
to decompress,
so it is essential you do not
go right back to school.
-No school?
On second thought, I'm fine.
Look, I can sit
with my chair turned around,
just like you.
I knew one day
there'd be another.
Go. Go with God.
Bart, are you coming?
(blubbering)
Ooh, definitely no school for you.
Or church.
(blubbering)
Mrs. Simpson,
I would watch him very closely
for the next couple of days.
Geez, I was thinking
about taking him shopping
for school clothes.
(high-pitched blubbering)
Why not just buy a suit
for his coffin.
Oh. Oh, okay. Sorry.
Uh, somebody parked me in.
Toyota Corolla.
Well, it's got to be
one of you.
Try the karate studio.
I tried the damn karate studio.
(groans) All right, it's me.
I blocked you in.
Okay? Sorry.
BART: Okay,
time to fake me some PTSD.
(sniffs)
And maybe bloodshot eyes.
Eh, too far.
(yawning loudly)
Oh, I don't know, Homie.
The kids seem upset.
Oh, they'll be fine.
Marge, children and summer
are natural enemies.
Now, why don't we
mix things up?
Tonight I'll be Penn
and you be Teller.
Oh, okay!
Uh! Teller doesn't talk.
(both moaning)
(laughs) Ooh.
BART:
Mom! Dad!
I'm scared.
I can't sleep.
(whimpering)
I'm sorry, Homie.
Bart's ten.
That could be the last tear
that ever comes out of him.
He's sleeping here.
(whimpers)
Take a hike, homeboy.
(Homer grumbling)
What the hey?
Just giving him his allowance.
This pamphlet on trauma
they gave Bart is very alarming.
Loss of appetite?
Thousand-yard stare.
-I'm not hungry.
-Where are you looking?
A thousand yards away.
(gasps)
No school for you, young man.
I'll set up the couch as a bed.
Can I put Homer's pillows
under my butt?
Of course.
You don't need pillows
under your butt.
Your butt is pillows, genius.
♪ The Itchy & Scratchy Show ♪
And now,
Itchy and Scratchy
perform their
cutting-edge version
of the "Sabre Dance."
("Sabre Dance" playing)
(screams)
-(laughs)
-(TV clicks off)
Mom, can I have
a jellybean sandwich for lunch?
Mm, how about a fruit salad?
Fruit? (sighs)
What's the matter?
That's what they served at camp.
Fine. Fine, jellybeans.
(groans)
(disco music playing)
(quietly)
Marge, voulez vous rendezvous
at the dog's bed?
I can't move.
His head's on my arm.
(normal voice)
Can you give me a foot rub?
Also, we both have to sign
his permission slip.
(groans) Maybe we should
just go to sleep.
Oof! Can't sleep, can't snuggle.
Gonna do the unthinkable.
Homie, what do you mean?
Gonna go to work early.
(loud screeching gasp)
(rooster crowing)
Geez, there's a lot of spaces
when you get in early.
Geez, there's a lot of
donuts when you get in early.
Hot coffee?
Whoever heard of such a thing?
(grunting)
Hmm.
I was supposed to read this
when I started the job,
but I didn't want
the other workers
to think of me as a nerd.
(alarm blaring)
(alarm stops)
What's he doing?
-He's reading.
-Nerd.
Hey, Homer, settle a bet.
Red beans and rice
or red beans on rice?
Winner gets 3,000 bucks.
Sorry, guys,
maybe another time.
Homer Simpson
don't want to screw around?
That's like Aquaman
moving to Phoenix.
You know, Lenny,
seeing Homer acting responsible--
Oh, Aquaman to Phoenix,
I just got that--
Uh, makes me want
to buckle down and do my job.
You know,
vice president of marketing.
Hey, if you need me,
I'll be cold-calling people
to see what they think
of electricity.
(Homers chattering excitedly)
Uh, Mr. Smithers, I, uh, I noticed
the plant's free subscription
to Nuclear Safety magazine
was hitting
the six-month mark.
They're gonna start charging us
the full newsstand price.
And no one pays
those prices.
(chuckles)
Nice catch, Simpson.
(cheering)
So I had the idea
to cancel it
and sign up for another
free trial under a new e-mail.
Wow. Wow!
Simpson, something
is very different about you.
(hushed voice)
I am sexually frustrated.
Tell me about it.
Kamp Krusty! Kamp Krusty!
Homie, listen.
No ketchup!
Oh, no,
not the hamburger dream.
♪ ♪
(thunder rumbles)
(Bart and Lisa gasping,
screaming)
(screams)
Oh, my God,
I really am traumatized.
I need help.
(gulps)
Lis! Lis!
(yawns)
Can it wait till morning?
Sure.
(birds chirping)
Lis! Lis!
-Thanks for waiting till morning.
-No problemo.
I had an actual nightmare
about Kamp Krusty.
There was a body
in a red life vest!
(gasps)
What else do you remember?
We were canoeing.
We were in a storm.
(thunder rumbling)
(gasps)
(metal rumbling)
It's coming back to me, too!
Whatever happened
must have been so horrible
we repressed the memory.
But don't tell, because
they'll make me miss school.
Maybe you should miss school.
I have perfect attendance.
You can't get that back.
Okay, I'll bring your
carriage around.
(imitates hoofbeats)
Uh-oh, looks like snow.
Very funny, Bart.
(imitating farting)
Stop it!
(imitates farting)
(yawns)
(sighs)
Made you breakfast.
I also made reservations
for Mother's Day.
I know it's three months away,
but you can't book too early.
Wow!
(kisses loudly)
Who's that guy?
I don't know.
♪ ♪
Hmm.
D'oh!
Mr. Burns, I noticed no one ever
puts suggestions in the box.
So I took the liberty
of making my own.
Hmm.
Yeah.
(chuckles)
Excellent. Simpson,
I'm giving you a raise.
More money?
But that's more
than I make now!
You've done so well,
Simpson.
I'm giving you
your own trap door button.
Oh, thank you!
(kids chattering excitedly)
(excited screaming)
Excuse me. Coming through.
Working out issues.
Boom-shakalaka.
I was at Kamp Krusty, too.
You don't see me freaking out
every time I see--
(hoarsely)
Red vest! Red vest!
What does it mean?
It means, young lady,
that you're about to go
to the head of the line.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
If everyone has a cut-the-line pass,
no one has a cut-the-line pass.
LISA: Quit your whining!
I'm riding the ride!
While you were pouting,
I did it again!
(humming a tune)
(gasps)
Oh. Maggie's asleep,
and the kids are still having
fun at the park with Grampa.
We're alone.
(moaning)
Marge, no!
I've pledged my abstinence,
like all the most successful
rock stars.
Come on, mister.
I'm too tired
to get my groove back.
It's all on you!
No means no. I looked it up
in the dictionary.
No?! No?!
You've never said "no."
Hmm? Hmm.
Hmm.
Oh!
Honey, I'm really sorry,
but I'm here for you every way.
Except physically.
Also, spiritually and emotionally.
And I've never been good
at zipping up dresses.
What are you saying?
Men have accomplished
unbelievable things
when they've denied
themselves whoopee.
The pointy pyramids of Egypt,
the Duomo,
which I now know is a thing.
You don't name
a company "Microsoft"
when you're getting some.
Oh, boy.
First the kids are screwed up,
and now our marriage is?
We need therapy.
(eerie theremin music plays)
I said "therapy," not "theremin."
Honest mistake.
Or was it?
(eerie music plays)
MASTERS:
Welcome, Marge.
Homer, no need
to take your pants off.
It's not what you think.
I just had a big lunch.
Just a series of questions
for now.
Then the pants come off.
Now, let me be blunt.
Are you happy with
your romantic life?
My problem used to be
too much satisfaction.
We hear that a lot.
But I'm afraid
not so much lately.
Do you self-gratify?
Yes. I do everything
but masturbate.
You know, this all started
with our poor kids traumatized
by a budget summer camp.
So many perfect marriages
ruined by kids.
We tell them
it's not their fault,
when, of course,
it's always their fault.
What you must do is return
your children to this camp
and face down their demons.
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
There's so much more you can do
when you don't think about sex.
That's why nuns
are so successful.
You have to take the kids
back to that camp.
Well, it beats
hanging out with them.
Now, if you'll excuse us,
we have some deviants coming in.
MOE:
Hello? Anybody here?
Yeah, I brought my lady.
She used to be
the helicopter ride
in front of the supermarket.
(rhythmic creaking)
(mechanical clattering,
bell dinging)
(bell dings)
Oh-hooh, uh... just finished.
All right, deviant out.
MARGE: (thinking)
My kids are a mess.
Homer's turned into the man
I've always wanted,
which I don't really want.
And for some reason,
we're going back to Kamp Krusty.
-ALL: Aw!
-(hisses)
(all gasp)
What happened
to this place?
People are wearing
terrycloth bathrobes
like they're ancient Romans.
Actually,
more like Macedonians.
All right, come on,
deer and pig.
It's time for you to mate
and then fight to the death.
What happened
to this place?
Oh, uh, Krusty cut his losses
by partnering with
Caligula's World Family Entertainment.
They redid the whole place
as an adult spa.
Uh-oh.
Did I leave my sash on?
Why don't you kids go in here,
and we'll find someone
who can prove to you
that what you think happened
didn't happen.
So, what do we do now,
get naked?
Ha-ha! I'm joking.
Unless you want to.
In which case,
I've never been more serious.
So, um, uh, which is it?
Don't want to.
Ah, good thing I was joking.
(chuckles nervously)
♪ Who stole the cookie
from the cookie jar? ♪
♪ Tyler stole the cookie from
the cookie jar ♪
♪ What, me? ♪
♪ Yeah, you ♪
♪ Couldn't be ♪
♪ Then who? ♪
♪ Courtney stole the cookie
from the cookie jar... ♪
I've heard enough.
Let's go, Courtney.
You, too, Tyler.
Hey, Bart, Bart, now's our
chance to break out of here.
But I'm four loops away
from finishing my potholder.
Now!
Ugh!
Marge, you know,
it used to be I'd be tempted
by every one of these places.
Now I just want to know
where the business center is.
It's over there.
You can print up all the free
boarding passes you want.
Oh!
We didn't even fly here.
(groans)
(grumbling)
-Oh. Oh.
-(printer whirring)
(playful growl)
Bart, I've seen
that shed before!
Hey, I know your
life is boring,
but you don't have
to advertise it.
(door creaks)
(wind whistles)
(both scream)
I'm remembering now.
We were trying
to escape by canoe.
Come back! Everyone needs
to watch the musical!
We've rehearsed for three hours!
But there was
another kid with us.
LISA: (gasps)
You're right!
BART:
His name was Charlie.
LISA:
(gasps) I forgot
because I was high
on poster paint fumes.
BART: Quiet!
We tipped over in the rapids.
(gasping)
Oh, my God!
Charlie didn't come back up!
Hey, hey!
Look who's back!
Kamp Krusty alumni!
We have reason to believe that
someone was killed in this camp!
Whoa! What happened to hello?
(humming)
Hard to concentrate with waves
gently lapping on the shore.
(kissing grunts)
Ooh! Marge, are you sure
you want to do this?
Mm... I think I still want
the old you.
Everyone, down below the belt!
Move, move, move!
Don't leave anything up here!
We will not be back!
(violin playing
"Adagio for Strings")
Play something
to put him in the mood!
(playing "Boléro")
Faster!
(playing "Call to the Post")
(grunting, kissing)
These children
would like to report
a traumatic incident
on the property.
(grunting)
Poor Charlie.
Charlie?
Did he have a red vest?
-Yes!
Can you kids keep a secret?
I can, but Lisa can't.
I told you that
in confidence!
Charlie! You're alive!
And a man, I might add--
a very short man.
They'd like to be called
"little people."
Yeah, not that much.
I was working undercover as
a spy for Departures magazine.
They are everywhere.
Anyway, when the canoe flipped,
I made my getaway.
LISA: But you didn't have
your life vest.
CHARLIE:
I'm a grown-up! I can swim!
And vote!
(whimpers quietly)
Oh, my God!
It's a miracle.
Whoa, I guess I really
was traumatized.
And now I'm glad
everything's all right.
So many stars.
Ever wonder how many worlds
are out there, Homie?
Pizza. Want pizza.
And you.
That's my man.
♪ ♪
For the fifth time today,
I am not a diving platform!
(snoring)
TV ANNOUNCER:
Next on Fox...
♪ ♪
MALE SOUL SINGER:
Oh, baby, baby.
Tonight's the night
we're not gonna get it on.
And when I say never,
I mean forever.
At my insistence,
I will keep you at a distance.
Because...
♪ My darling, you ♪
♪ Have had enough
of my love, babe ♪
♪ Mm, baby, don't get upset ♪
♪ But your needs
will not be met ♪
♪ Mm, it's like
the more you want ♪
♪ The less I give ♪
♪ Baby, that's no lie ♪
Oh, yeah.
Subtitled by Katie Finegan