♪ The Simpsons ♪
-(chalk screeches)
-(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(tires screeching)
(horn honks)
(tires screech)
D-oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
Hurry, Mom. If we don't get
to the convention soon,
all the good comics
will be gone.
Aw, what do you care
about good comics?
All you ever buy is
Casper "The Wimpy" Ghost.
I think it's sad that you equate
friendliness with wimpiness,
and I hope it will keep you from
ever achieving true popularity.
Well, you wanna know
what I think?
I think Casper is
the ghost of Richie Rich.
LISA:
Hey, they do look alike.
-I wonder how Richie died?
-Perhaps he realized
how hollow the pursuit
of money is,
and took his own life.
Kids, could you
lighten up a little?
Now, Radioactive Man, he rules!
Never punches a bad guy
without saying something cool.
He's no wittier
than the next superhero.
Oh, yeah? Look. He knocks
a guy into the sun and says,
"Hot enough for you?"
Heh, heh, heh...
I stand corrected.
We're here!
Too bad we
didn't come dressed
as popular
cartoon characters.
This looks like
a discount for...
-Bartman!
-(wind gusts)
Who are you supposed to be?
I'm Bartman.
Never heard of him--
full price.
Lousy rip-off.
Is, uh, this on?
(clears throat) Young people
of Springfield, as your mayor,
I'd like to welcome you to our
annual funny book convention
and thank you for pumping almost
$300 into the local economy.
-(scattered applause)
-Your youthful high spirits
have imparted a glow
to this old war-horse.
You might say I feel like
Radiation Man.
-That's "Radioactive Man," jerk.
-(laughing)
I, uh, stand corrected.
Well, have fun and be sure
to clear out by 6
for the Shriners.
Get that punk's name. No one makes
a fool out of Diamond Joe Quimby.
Excuse me, sir.
Has anyone turned in
a left Vulcan ear?
Well, let's see.
We got a utility belt,
a couple of tricorders,
a lightsaber...
Sorry, kid.
Mmm-mm, mmm, mmm, mmm.
Mmm. Mm-mmm.
-Hey, Bart dude.
-Hey, Otto man. Ooh, what's that?
My very own idea
for a comic book, little man.
It's about a dude
who drives a school bus by day
but by night, fights vampires
in a post-apocalyptic war zone.
-Cool!
-Come on, Bart.
We're going to see Buddy Hodges.
-The guy who played Fallout Boy on TV?
-Yep!
Wow! I guess he
wasn't killed in Vietnam.
Ahh, these Laramie cigarettes
give me the steady nerves
I need to combat evil.
Gee willickers,
Radioactive Man.
Wished I was old enough
to smoke Laramies.
Sorry, Fallout Boy.
Not until you're 16.
Look out!
ANNOUNCER:
Will Radioactive Man
act in time to save
the Earth?
(kids cheering)
Well, wasn't that great?
You know kids, I'm sure we'd all like
to remember actor Dirk Richter
for his portrayal
of Radioactive Man
and not the sordid details
of his final years,
so let's keep the questions
tasteful, okay?
Now, how about a big welcome
for Buddy "Fallout Boy" Hodges!
-(kids cheering)
-Any questions?
When Radioactive Man got injected
with shrinking serum in issue 234,
how come his costume
shrinks too?
I'm sure I don't know,
but I did just finish playing
Rum Tum Tugger
in the second national
touring company of Cats.
-Anybody see it?
-Oh, oh, over here!
-Fallout Boy! Me, me me!
-Yes, you. The masked boy.
Do you think the ghost of Dirk Richter
haunts the bordello
where his bullet-riddled body
was found?
(crying) Dirk Richter
was a beautiful man.
Can't you little vultures
leave him alone?!
(sobbing)
Hey! Radioactive Man #72!
It's an imaginary tale
where Radioactive Man
marries Larva Girl.
BART:
Wow, number nine!
That's before Fallout Boy
became his ward.
Tell you what. I'll show you
something very special
if you promise to put your grubby little
hands behind your back and keep 'em there.
-Behold!
-Wow!
Radioactive Man
Number One.
-None other.
-I bet it's worth a million bucks.
It is, my lad. But I'll let you have it
for 100, because you remind me of me.
-Oh, all I got is 30.
-Then you cannot have it.
But I must.
Until this moment,
I never knew why God
put me on this Earth,
but now I know--
to buy that comic book.
Your emotion is
out of place here, son.
(horns honking)
So, did you kids have fun?
Yeah Mom. Guess what? For a dollar,
a man sold me 35 Caspers
and a dozen Lois Lanes.
-Ooh.
-I never knew what Superman saw in her.
Give me Wonder Woman!
(lecherous growl)
And that golden lariat--
she can tie me up anytime.
(barking and howling)
-Homer!
-I was just kidding, Marge.
Hey! What does everyone say
to dinner at Krusty Burgers?
(cheering)
My treat.
Alright Homer!
Woah, you really are a sport, Dad,
taking us out to a fine restaurant
like Krusty Burger.
Alright, what are you
getting at?
I need $100
for a comic book.
100 bucks? For a comic book?
Who drew it, Michael Malangelo?
Oh, please, Dad. I want this more
than anything in the world.
Well, T.S.
-Please, Dad.
-No.
-No. No!
Now look, son.
We all know that,
usually, when you bug me
like this, I give in,
so I'm not mad at you
for trying--
shows you've been
paying attention--
but we all know
I'm not gonna give you $100.
-Now, are you going to stop bugging me?
-No.
-Are you?
-No. No.
Okay!
Hee-hee! I win!
In your face!
Yeah! How do you
like them apples?
-Hoo-hoo! (laughing)
-Don't gloat, Homer.
You know, Bart,
when I was your age,
the one thing I wanted more
than anything in the world
was a child-size,
electric-light bulb oven.
My parents wouldn't
give me the money,
so I went to my sisters,
Patty and Selma.
We'll give you
half our allowance.
Uh-huh, but you have
to be our slave.
-Okay.
-This gives us a lot more free time.
Uh-huh!
Let's take up smoking.
MARGE:
For months I worked and worked
while my sisters
smoked and smoked.
♪ Venus ♪
♪ Oh, Venus... ♪
We want those dress shields
hand-washed
and drip dried.
But the big day finally came,
and because I'd worked for it,
all those lightbulb-warmed treats
always tasted extra good.
So maybe a part-time job
is the answer.
Oh, Mom, I couldn't ask you
to do that.
You're already taking care of Maggie,
and Lisa is such a handful.
LISA: She means you should
get a job, stupid.
Me?
"THE WONDER YEARS" NARRATOR:
Get a job? Were they serious?
♪♪ (The Byrds'
"Turn, Turn, Turn" playing)
I didn't realize it
at the time,
but a little piece
of my childhood
had slipped away forever.
-Bart! What are you staring at?
-Uh... nothing.
He didn't say it, and neither did I,
but at that moment,
my Dad and I were closer
than we've ever--
-Bart! Stop it.
-Sorry.
♪ To everything... ♪
♪ I need some money... ♪
♪ A lot of money... ♪
Ah!
Empty bottles, empty bottles.
Hmm. Well, it's practically
empty.
Here you go, Apu.
Very good.
Would you like the deposit
defrayed from the cost
of a jumbo cherry squishy?
No, not today.
I need the dime.
Oh, it is good to see you
are learning a trade.
Ching, ching, ching!
Aha!
Americanize this,
my good man.
Okey-dokey.
All those coins were only
worth three lousy cents?
Let the good times roll.
This is so humiliating.
I feel like such a geek.
-How's it going, Bart?
-Terrible.
Cars slow down to laugh at me,
but no one's buying.
Maybe you need to play on their
sympathies more. Let's see...
Ha, now you look pathetic.
Ha-ha!
Aw, lemonade sucks!
I need a new product.
Let's see... Ah!
Form a line.
No crowding.
Cheap beer and a sympathetic ear.
Step right up.
Hey, Bart, can you give me one on credit?
I'm a little short this week.
Beat it.
Hey, you got a liquor license here,
young fella?
Uh... my dog ate it.
Got to have a license
to sell beer.
Hey! Writing all those tickets
must make you guys thirsty.
How about a couple
on the house?
Seeing how it's
a first offense...
I guess we can overlook this.
-Mm-hmm.
-(both chuckle)
So long, officers.
Uh-oh.
Hey, what's all the--
(screams)
My beer! My beer!
My beautiful beer!
MARGE:
The poor boy is so desperate.
He wants to earn money
to buy a comic book.
A comic book?
Oh, my.
Boys never change.
Which one is it,
Nazi Smasher?
I don't think so.
Send him over to my house.
I got a few chores
he could do.
He knows how to mix whitewash,
don't he?
-(crows cawing)
-Mrs. Glick?
You must be Bert Simpson.
Well, you look like you got
a strong, young back.
Would you like something
to eat?
I got dried apricots,
almond paste,
sauerkraut candy.
No, thanks.
Who's that?
Oh, that's my brother Esa.
He was killed
in the Great War.
Held a grenade too long.
This one's for you, Kaiser Bill.
Special delivery from Uncle Sam
and all the boys in "D" company--
Yeah, Johnny, Harrison,
Brooklyn Bob and Reggie.
Yeah, even Reggie.
He ain't so stuck up
once you get to--
(explosion)
(gulp)
Here, have some ribbon candy.
-Boys love candy.
-No, thanks.
-Boys love candy!
-Eww!
I think I'd rather
just get to work, ma'am.
We'll start with a little
light yard work,
and when you're done,
you can have a nice barley pop.
I want you to clear out
all the weeds.
You do know
which ones are weeds?
-All of them?
-Good boy.
Now be careful with these.
I'll be inside watching
my stories.
(sighs)
(grunting)
Ow!
Ow! Ooh!
Jack, please.
I'm married.
That must be
what's turning me on.
Oh, stop it. Some more.
Filthy...
but genuinely arousing.
-Finished.
-Merciful heavens!
You're bleeding.
I'll get the iodine.
(mumbling)
Now, let's see....
bunion pad... liver...
iodine.
Now don't fidget.
Listen, lady,
you don't have--
(long scream)
MRS. GLICK:
They never improved on iodine.
Hi, Mom.
Did you make any money?
Not yet, but at least
I'm in a lot of pain.
Well, I think what you're doing
for Mrs. Glick is very nice.
Poor old thing
doesn't have anybody.
There's a reason.
The sludge certainly collects
around those downspouts,
don't it?
I'll sludge you, you old bat.
Today, we wash Beulah.
You know what that is?
Some old lady thing nobody's
heard about for fifty years?
No.
It was my wedding dress.
But then I dyed it black
and it became my mourning dress.
Great story, lady.
Last night I dreamed
I held you in my arms.
(cat growling)
(yowling)
No, no, not the iodine!
Burn the germs off
with a torch
amputate my arm,
but not the...
(screaming)
Well, it's payday.
I'll wager you've been
looking forward to this.
Oh, yes, ma'am.
Here we are-- two quarters.
Two quarters?
You deserve every penny.
You know, I've told a lot
of my girlfriends about you
and they have chores too.
Two quarters?
Bart, you didn't say thank you.
Listen, lady,
I can leave without screaming,
and I can leave
without saying a bad word.
But there is no way
that I am saying thank you.
You're welcome.
All right then, off you go
to spend it on penny whistles
and Moon Pies.
(door slams)
BART:
Moon Pies, my butt.
Somebody ought
to Moon-Pie her.
What's the problem, boy?
I been bustin' my hump all week
for that withered old clam
and all I got was 50¢.
Hey, when I was your age,
50¢ was a lot of money.
-Really?
-Nah.
Dad, I've done
everything I could
and I've only got 35 bucks.
(groans)
I am through with working.
-Working is for chumps.
-Son, I'm proud of you.
I was twice your age
before I figured that out.
(gasps)
Can you let me have it for $40?
40 bucks? Forget it.
You made me get off my stool for that?
It's all I've got.
I sold seeds.
I visited my aunt
in the nursing home.
I fished a dime out
of the sewer, for God's sake!
No way.
What do you want?
Can I have it for 35?
No! No. Freaking kids.
I do not need this.
I've got a Masters degree
in Folklore and Mythology.
Do you have the Carl Yastrzemski
baseball card from 1973,
when he had big sideburns?
Show me the 30 bucks,
because if you ain't got it,
I ain't getting off the stool.
Okay.
Wait a minute.
Martin, if you, Milhouse
and I went in together
we could buy a copy
of Radioactive Man #1 right now.
-Wow!
-Here you go. Muttonchop Yaz.
-I don't want it.
-Freaking kids.
-Look pal, we got 100 bucks
and we'd like to buy
Radioactive Man #1.
So why don't you just
waddle over there
-and get it!
-Yes, sir!
Wow!
-Breathe it in, boys.
-(sniffing)
This is the stuff
dreams are made of.
It smells like my grandpa.
-(thunder rumbles)
-Uh-oh, looks like rain.
We better get this baby home.
Uh-oh.
Looks like you bought more
than you bargained for.
-(fiendish laughter)
-(thunderclap)
MAN'S VOICE: My pants--
(straining)
...caught on barbed wire!
Good Lord! Choke!
An A-bomb!
-Yaarrgh!
-(explosion)
(grunts)
Becoming radioactive.
(deep, powerful voice) From
this day forward I shall call myself...
-Radioactive Man!
-So that's how it happened.
I would have thought being hit by
an atomic bomb would've killed him.
-Now you know better.
-Turn the page, Bart.
BART:
Careful, careful. Ah.
Listen, you guys
are welcome to come over
and read it any time you like.
Why can't we keep it
at my house?
Your house?
That's crazy talk.
Well the comic's ours as much
as it is yours.
How about this, guys?
Bart can have it
Mondays and Thursdays,
Milhouse will get it
Tuesdays and Fridays,
and yours truly will take it
Wednesdays and Saturdays.
-Perfect.
-Wait a minute.
-What about Sunday?
-Yeah. What about Sunday?
Well, Sunday possession will be determined
by a random number generator.
I will pick the digits one through three,
Milhouse, four through six,
-and Bart will have seven through nine.
-Perfect.
Wait a minute.
What about zero?
-Yeah. What about zero?
-Yeah.
Well, in the unlikely event
of a zero,
possession will be determined by rock,
scissors, paper competition.
Best three out of five,
how's that?
-All right.
-That's cool.
Excellent.
Well, today being Saturday,
gentlemen, I guess I'll be
taking my comic and...
-Uh-uh-uh.
-Nice try, Martin.
It almost worked,
but tonight this comic book
stays right here.
If the comic stays right here,
then so do I.
Me too.
Fine. We're all going to stay
here with the comic book.
It will be like a sleep-over.
Yeah, a sleep-over.
That's what pals do, right?
Real friendly-like.
(wind blowing)
I want to read it again.
Nice try, mister.
Milhouse,
The acids in your hand
could damage the newsprint.
We want to keep
this comic forever
so the last one alive
will have the honor
of being buried with it.
What do you mean,
"The last one alive"?
-I meant years from now.
-Yeah, sure you did.
Bart, don't push him.
I knew it--
you're both against me.
Nobody makes a sap
out of Bartholomew J. Simpson.
-Quit it!
-You quit it.
No, you quit it.
(all choking)
I thought you boys
might like some milk
and microwave s'mores.
-(gasping) Thank you, Mrs. Simpson.
-Thanks, Mom.
Sweet dreams, boys.
(all crunching )
(thunder)
One more step,
and you're a dead man.
I have to go
to the bathroom, Bart.
Yeah right, so do I,
-but you don't see me getting up.
-What's going on?
Our dear friend Martin was trying
to steal the comic book.
Let's tie him up!
(thunder)
Bart, is this how you treat
all your guests?
Quiet, Piggy, or we'll stick an
apple in your mouth.
We can't take any chances.
We'll have to take turns watching him.
Okay. I'll go first.
Ah! So that's your little game.
Let old Bart get nice and drowsy
then when his back
is turned, wham!
-Well, it will not happen, see?
-You're going crazy, Bart.
I'm telling your Mom.
Hey, Martin, tell him
what we do with squealers.
I don't know. Is it worse than
what you do with people
who have to go to the bathroom?
You can't stop me.
The hell I can't.
(both grunting)
MARGE: Homer,
it's really coming down.
Could you check on the boys?
They're fine.
-Whoa!
-Yeow!
Bart! The comic!
Don't let go of me, Bart!
Milhouse, it's not
that far to the ground.
The rain's probably
softened it up a bit.
No, Bart, no!
You know, if you guys
hadn't tied me up,
I could be saving
the comic as we speak.
Shut up... shut up!
Help me, Bart.
I didn't even want the comic.
I wanted Carl Yastrzemski
with the big sideburns.
(grunting)
(ripping)
(sighs)
(growling)
(gasping)
(thunder clap)
(groaning)
Boys, you better
come in the house.
-You don't want to get the sniffles.
-Oh, Mom.
Oh, now, come on.
Hmm. You can play your
little tie-up game inside.
I've got some cocoa
on the stove.
Who wants imitation
marshmallows?
-I do!
I'd raise my hand,
Mrs. Simpson, if I could.
(birds chirping)
(yawning)
D-oh!
It's no use, fellas.
Another comic book
has returned to the Earth
from whence it came.
We worked so hard
and now it's all gone.
We ended up
with nothing
because the three of us
can't share.
What's your point?
Nothing. Just kind of
ticks me off.
RADIOACTIVE MAN:
Well, the world is safe again
but... for how long?
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.