Next item on the agenda.
Principal Duggins.
Well, I see that not one
of your students
was able to meet
the national fitness standards.
A light jog.
Come on, Duggins.
You got to be a role model
for those lazy kids.
Tell them you put in
two hours a day stretching...
your lap band.
Oh, my goodness.
Thank you, Principal Finch.
Well, I guess we can cross
hilarious joke off the agenda.
Oh, I've also got
a funny thing.
Duggins' wife was unfaithful.
Skinner,
learn how to read a room.
- Sorry, Duggins.
- Screw you.
Indeed. Now, as you all know,
this weekend in Cincinnati
is the national
administrator's convention,
or EDU‐CON.
And, well,
I have been invited
to give the keynote address.
Oh, well.
Yes. Sunday.
Main auditorium.
The Proctor & Gamble Room?
Crushed it!
Well, that couldn't
have gone worse.
I agree.
Yes, well, as you all know,
the budget allows
for a plus‐one,
and I was thinking
I would bring
the principal
with the highest test scores.
- Finch.
- Well, that's not fair.
Finch runs the magnet school
for gifted test takers.
Sorry, Seymour,
but I have made my decision.
If it makes you feel any better,
you were never in the running.
Hey, we are gonna
light Cincinnati up.
I got a buddy who used to be the
long snapper for the Bengals.
He co‐owns
this amazing poké place.
Seaweed, furikake,
soakin' in ponzu!
My God, you're cool.
Okay, this is
for all the marbles.
No wonder Chalmers
is taking Finch to Cincinnati.
How'd you hear about that?
It's all over the playground.
Chalmers went to Cincy
Didn't take our princy
How many tears
did Skinner cry?
One, two, three, four, five
Well, as usual,
the double Dutchers
have zeroed in on my pain.
Look, Seymour, are you ready
for some tough love?
Is there any other kind?
Being around you sucks.
No one's ever gonna invite you
to anything.
If there's a party
you want to go to,
you got to crash it,
or you'll spend
the rest of your life
sitting around with your hand
stuck in a pelvis.
It's too late.
The plus‐one has been invoked.
Dude, you're Seymour Skinner.
No matter how badly
you're treated,
you keep coming back for more.
That's your superpower.
Use it!
You're right. I will.
Aw, look at you,
grazing the thumb.
Come on.
Come on, come on, come on.
Finch, where are you?
We're going to miss our flight.
Can't make it, Gary.
I ate some pre‐trip poké
last night,
and it's blitzkrieging
my intestines.
I'm firing salmon eggs
from both ends.
But you're my ride
to the airport.
My car's in the shop
being winterized.
Sorry, dude. Yeah? Cool.
Hop in, sir. We still have time
to make our flight.
Skinner?
What are you doing here?
Well, I saw
on Finch's InstaSnap story
that he's firing salmon eggs
from both ends.
So I rushed over here at once.
You want to come with me
to Cincinnat... No. Thank you.
Very thoughtful, Seymour,
but I wouldn't want to...
You wouldn't want
the school board to find out
you wasted the transferrable
but not refundable
$65 plus‐one registration fee?
No, I would not.
Oh, boy.
Game Night.
Jason Bateman,
your boyish charisma
was made for the low‐res
seatback screen.
Sir, are you all right?
If you must know,
flying makes me
just a little bit nervous.
Where'd you put my carry‐on?
I'm going to pop
an antianxiety pill.
Oh, I gate‐checked your bag.
It's free,
and you don't have to fight
for precious overhead space.
Another classic
Skinner travel hack.
My pills were in that bag,
you idiot!
You... Okay. Okay.
I can do this.
It's just
a short domestic flight.
I'm completely safe, right?
Sure. And if you're stressed,
you can take comfort
in the passengers'
many emotional support animals.
Pig?
I'm going to die
in a flying zoo.
Everyone around you
is taking their shoes off.
Okay, no one is safe.
No one's sa...
That phone
is not in airplane mode.
The pilot
dresses like an alcoholic!
Somebody's yelling!
Who is yelling?!
Where in the name of God
is the air marshal?!
You're banned
from Air Cincinnati forever.
Well, we've got to get
another flight.
We can't, sir.
Air Cincinnati's the only
airline that flies to Cincinnati
since the demise
of Cincin‐Air‐Y.
Well, that's just great.
That's great!
In 36 hours, I have to give
the most important speech
of my life.
Now, how in the name
of Satan's jockstrap
am I supposed to get there?
Please, sir.
If you give me one last chance,
I will think of nothing else
but getting you
to that keynote speech on time.
Nah, I'll just drive myself.
All right, where is your car?
It, too, is being winterized.
But I know where to get one.
Oh, no.
You're not borrowing my Buick.
I just had it winterized.
But, Mother,
this road trip is my last chance
to become friends with the man
I admire most in the world.
Please.
Well, you did do such a nice job
re‐beading my eyeglass chain.
I guess a boy your age
should have friends.
Ah, you, me
and the open road, huh?
Yeah. Maybe some music will make
the time pass more quickly.
Timothy, Timothy...
I hope you like this song,
'cause it's stuck in the player,
and there's no volume knob.
Timothy, Timothy
God, what did we do?
Oh, did you know
that in Cincinnati, they have
four different ways
of preparing chili?
You don't say, huh?
- Four different ways.
- The two‐way...
- Chili with spaghetti.
- How about that.
- Spaghetti?
- The three‐way...
- Chili with spaghetti and cheese.
- Lot of ways.
Please shut up.
- Oh, he's got more.
- And there's two kinds
- of four‐ways.
- I just... I want to die.
Hitchhikers!
Oh, thank the Lord.
Hitchhikers, sir?
Is this safe?
They can bury us
in a shallow grave
as long as they don't talk
about chili.
Thanks for picking us up.
We're on our way to a gig.
Oh, a gig.
Are you musicians?
Oh, no. We do...
Improv Shakespeare!
Improvisers?
In the style of Shakespeare?
That seems impossible.
Methinks this noble lord
doth doubt our wit.
We must perform
or else be deemed unfit!
A word, a word.
My kingdom for a word.
- No, no, don't give them a suggestion.
- Cupholders.
To grasp a cup
would seem a great ordeal.
When one must keep both hands
upon the wheel.
The pentameter checks out.
Your parents must be so proud.
They're not.
Toupee or not toupee,
that is the question.
You are the only ones
having fun!
Just you!
Oh, beware the ides of...
Truck!
Well, well, well,
what have we got here?
Don't worry, Officer.
It's minor damage.
Nothing serious.
Alas, poor Buick.
I knew it well.
Dear Lord. Our car,
our wallets, our luggage,
they're all blown to shreds.
But the keynote. Your speech.
It's all on the cards
right here.
But what good will it be
when some backwoods judge
throws the book at us, huh?
All rise for the Honorable
Judge J.T. Winchester.
Who dragged me in here
on a Saturday
in the middle
of my Lifetime movies?
I'm missing my Lifetimes!
An old woman who's enraged
by my very existence.
Don't worry, sir. I got this.
Your Honor,
permission to observe
that your poor cuticles
are raw and torn.
Thanks to my idiot son.
He made my manicure appointment
with Tanya P.
instead of Tanya G.
Oh, well, that boy's
as useless as a shaved frog.
Now, Mother...
Hush up and empty the spittoons,
Fennimore.
You know, I always travel
with cuticle scissors
and jojoba oil.
Let's get these ladies ready
for their close‐up.
Now, you have fun
at the convention, boys.
You just bring it back whenever.
Mother, you never let me
drive the Cutlass.
My car is for good boys!
Timothy, Timothy
God, what did we do?
Well, we're only a half hour
behind schedule.
Should we brainstorm
on a code
for the hotel room safe?
Seymour, you charmed the Depends
off that lady.
I believe I owe you a beer.
A biker bar?
Are you sure it's safe?
All right, stop quivering
like a quince jelly.
You're with me.
Sir, this isn't a biker bar.
It's a cyclist bar.
Don't be a ninny, Seymour.
Barkeep!
A beer for me
and my coworker here.
We just serve energy gels
and oxygen.
You don't like it, get out.
You two oil burners
might want to skedaddle
before my resting heart rate
elevates to 60 bpm.
That's beats per minute,
oil burner!
Why don't you calm down
there, Slim?
What did you call me?
The bike computers!
All our stats were on there!
They hadn't synced yet!
Yeah, but you still got
the exercise, right?
It's as if
the rules of the road
don't apply to them.
Are you pedestrians
or vehicles?!
Make a choice!
Never!
Skinner, what do we do?
Seymour! Well, don't go!
Skinner?
Step away
from my superintendent.
What's he gonna do?
He's just one guy.
You're never alone
when you're a veteran
of the U.S. Armed Forces.
And I do mean armed.
Para‐athletes like us are the
natural enemy of cycling clubs.
Their biceps are bigger
than my quads!
To the support van!
Seymour, how did you...
I keep abreast
of local veterans' events.
Luckily, the Wheel Team Six
para‐marathoners
were racing nearby.
Seymour, you have earned this.
You know, there was a time
I would have mocked you
for collecting bed‐and‐breakfast
travel points with your mother,
but, I'll tell ya,
today those points have paid
for this sweet,
thick elderberry wine.
Well, nothing is as sweet
as your kind words.
Oh, yeah. That's good stuff.
Ernest, I've never felt
more independent and strong.
Can I use your phone
to call Mother?
There she is.
Just make sure no one's using
the upstairs extension.
You're back
in the office already?
Principal Finch,
your gut biome is a wonder.
So, how's Sad Sack Seymour and
the Cincinnati Snooze Cruise?
Yeah, vintage Finch.
But believe it or not,
Skinner has shown,
bursts of utility.
You better not be getting
cold feet, Gary.
We made an agreement.
Skinner gets canned,
and I leave my tiny little
magnet school for the big time,
Springfield Elementary.
I'm pumped!
Yes, I know, I know.
The plan was to fire Skinner,
and...
I am a man of my word.
Fire Skinner?
Chalmers!
Oh, dear.
Fire me?!
You bald‐pated son of a bitch.
I you two gentlemen
could please...
Stay out of this, Trudy!
For years,
this man belittled me.
Humiliated me.
And in exchange
for my unwavering loyalty,
what was my reward?
To be pushed out by
some scheming magnet school...
keister kisser!
The brochures nobody takes!
I'm the one who deserved this
trip to Cincinnati, not Finch.
That's why I put black mold
in his poké.
You did what?
The Rocking Chair Museum.
I've heard good things.
Skinner...!
You know why I was gonna
fire you, Seymour?
Because your neediness,
it sucks the life out of me!
After all these years of trying
to spare your feelings,
I'm just gonna say it now.
I... don't... like you!
And the man in the back said,
everyone attack
And it turned
into a ballroom blitz
And the girl in the corner said,
boy, I wanna warn you
It'll turn
into a ballroom blitz
Ballroom blitz
Ooh, Terry Bradshaw stayed here.
Not the one you're thinking of.
You know, I'm not gonna give you
the pleasure of firing me,
because I quit!
Good riddance!
Well, well, well.
If it isn't the Cuticle Kid.
You racing to give a mani‐pedi?
Just give me the ticket,
Fennimore.
License and my mother's
registration.
Superintendent,
you're on in five.
Great, great.
I'll just ensure my notecards
are in the correct order.
Road trip
conversation starters?
We switched jackets.
Seymour has my speech!
It's often been said
that one speech
can make or break
a man's career.
Together, we now face
such a moment.
Our keynote speaker,
Superintendent
Garibaldi Chalmers.
Well, it's an honor
to be here
in Cleveland.
It's Cincinnati!
Look at the skyline!
You just... You won't believe
what's happened.
I'm...
Well, maybe you will!
You've all got
that one principal,
that one that gets you
into such ridiculous situations,
maybe even on the way here.
Yes. Quite.
This guy, Skinner,
he screws everything up.
He took my jacket and my speech!
He left me with the
useless garbage in his pockets.
A mommy manicure kit.
A VFW event calendar.
A B&B rewards card.
Calico Level.
And conversation starters
like...
How can I make
your job easier?
He sounds like a good guy,
you jackass!
Well, I...
I suppose he is.
He's loyal
and resourceful and...
Oh, God, help me.
I respect Seymour Skinner.
In fact, I like him.
Ditto, Gary.
Aw, Skinner.
I've got something
that belongs to you.
Now go give the greatest
keynote speech of your life.
Well, maybe I already have, huh?
But if I must.
Educational Infrastructure.
Ability Grouping
versus Blended Learning.
Now, a survey
of public administrators
over a 15‐trimester period
showed clearly,
within the standard deviation,
of course...
Well, you did it, dude.
How does it feel to get
what you've always wanted?
Chalmers loves Skinner
Bought him chili dinner
How many ways
did Skinner try?
One, two, three, four, five
It feels just like this.
Maybe you and me were never
meant to be
Just maybe think of me
once in a while
So, guys,
what have you been up to?
Oh, went on a field trip
to the fire station,
but nobody told
the firemen we were coming.
Practiced my sax,
went to school.
Oh, we learned about Peru.
I went to work.
Lenny had a cold,
so he wasn't there.
Carl was there though.
Well, have I got a treat
for you all.
Tonight, we're going to see
Improv Shakespeare!
Washing machine!
Out, damned stain!
For there is a Tide Pod
in the affairs of laundry.
Can you imagine
Shakespeare using a Tide Pod?
No.
Mad tooth bar chin‐up
Boxing out of her hair now
Still do the modern‐day
whack‐a‐mole ditto‐o‐o
What's that?
Good bartender
I had better head out
I said I wouldn't do it
if a poodle had a lid on
Mad tooth bar chin‐up
Boxing out of her hair now
Still do the modern‐day
whack‐a‐mole ditto‐o‐o
What's that?