-CHOIR: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
-(breathing heavily)
(exclaiming)
(school bell ringing)
(Barney belches)
(whistle blows)
(yells)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
(grunts)
(chuckles)
Diddily...
diddily, diddily, diddily...
Asterisk, pound sign,
at sign, exclamation point!
Don't worry, the Holy Rollers
are still up by one on the Pin Pals.
MOE: Gentlemen, prepare to meet
your various makers, there.
'Cause we got one last frame by
our new anchorman, Dan Gillick.
Thank God Otto had that psychotic break
and quit the team.
Is this the Bridge to Terabithia?
-(thuds)
-It's beautiful.
The day my Frisbee landed in your yard
was the luckiest day of my life.
And when you threw your son after it,
-I enjoyed meeting him, too.
-He's a good boy.
(phone rings)
(groans)
Sorry, guys. Emergency meeting at work.
Oh, please, I am missing
eight birthday parties for this!
Just granny-throw it!
Keep my ball.
Well, looks like
the faithful have defeated
a hedonist, a Hindu and a...
What are you?
You know when your dog's
having a bad dream?
That's who I pray to.
Boys, I'm afraid the government
has finally caught up with me
and my appeals are exhausted.
Tomorrow, I begin serving jury duty.
That's a tough break, boss.
Don't sign petitions
outside the grocery store no more!
I felt bad for the guy,
sitting there at his little card table.
Anyway, I must name
a temporary replacement.
Your temporary don is...
our accountant, Dan.
(all groaning)
Fat Tony, a word?
-How about "meringue"?
-That's a great word, but...
(whispering) I'm just a numbers guy,
and the only reason,
I say "numbers guy"
instead of "Wharton MBA"
is 'cause I want to blend in.
I know what I'm doing.
We are bleeding red ink,
which is the only thing
we should not be bleeding.
(all exclaim and mutter)
(clears throat)
Hey, listen, everyone,
I know a good ice-breaking exercise.
Let's all say something
that we are afraid of.
For me, it's you guys. (quiet laugh)
I'm afraid I might
kill this guy right now.
Ring, ring. Is that my phone?
I think it is. Hello?
Yes, sweetie, it's Daddy.
Listen, how would you feel
if I just disappeared?
Sad, right? Sad?
Okay, you know what? I'll tell the guys.
She's crying, guys. Cassidy is crying.
Well, I hope you feel proud of yourself.
Cassidy is a girl's name now?
(dramatic orchestral music playing)
I know this music.
It was a Bugs Bunny!
Oh, what I wouldn't give
for an anvil to fall on me.
D'oh!
Shh! Here comes Lisa's solo.
(music stops)
(playing lively blues)
This is why I'm a season subscriber.
(exhales weakly)
-(all gasp)
-Lisa!
When I prayed for this concert
to be over,
I didn't mean like this!
-I did.
-Where's the school nurse?
Here I am.
Budget cuts.
Lisa, I suspect you fainted
because you thought
Justin Bieber was in the audience.
(chuckles)
Well, once again,
laughter is the worst medicine.
Young lady,
you're not getting enough iron.
Please say it's the vegetarianism.
It's not the vegetarianism.
It's a little bit the vegetarianism.
Lisa, if you must forgo meat,
I advise you to take
these iron supplements.
(clanging)
It's like swallowing dollhouse furniture.
(chuckles)
Gentlemen, look at what we are spending
every month just on olive oil.
We love our bread-dipping.
Okay, can't touch the bread-dipping.
Here's what Joey the Arsonist
thinks of your spreadsheet. Heh?
-(laughter)
-Ha-ha-ha! This is fun.
But you know what?
There is a cost-cutting measure
I'd like to propose-- if you put
a horse's head in someone's bed,
don't let the rest
of the animal go to waste.
For the next guy, use the horse's leg.
Or... a couple of hooves.
Believe me, there is
no part of a dead horse
that's not gonna scare someone.
Okay, good stopping point.
Aah!
Okay... (grunts) Was that real?
(hacks)
A kid's never lonely when he has bologna.
Except me.
(bell rings)
(hacks)
(sobbing)
-You're that Simpson kid, Bart, right?
-Lisa.
I just see mouths.
Can't handle the iron pills?
All day I have vitamin burps.
Try this-- it's what keeps me young.
Mmm, tasty. Love the texture.
-What is it?
-Beetle mush.
(muffled gasp) But I'm a vegetarian!
So am I. Lots of committed
vegetarians eat insects.
-Really?
-Get real.
There's bug parts in peanut butter.
And every year, the average American eats
eight spiders in his sleep.
It's all here in this book.
(mouth full) This is such a big step.
Better decide soon, kid.
The union said I can't talk
to a student this long.
Mmm, that is good grub.
But I promised Paul McCartney
I wouldn't eat meat.
And I promised Paul McCartney
I wouldn't sleep with John.
So, you're saying you'd rather
do the prettiest dude
in the world than the ugliest broad?
Absolutely. But how did we get here
from discussing Aristotle's Poetics?
MOE: Well, well,
if it isn't Mr. Work
Comes Before Bowling.
I am turning my back
because I can't stand
to look you in the face.
(screams) Ooh!
(screams) You.
-(screams)
-Part of my new rice wine promotion.
So, now you think you can
just waltz in here
and buy everybody a beer?
I didn't say that I...
Too late. I already poured.
Oh, sorry, guys.
I got the kind of job that
you just can't play hooky from.
Well, I have no idea what
you do or who you work with,
but I am sure if you put
your foot down on their throats
and grind until you hear a crunch,
they'll sit up straight.
Really? You're sure about this?
Oh, hey, listen, I learned
a lot about human nature
by watching things
through secret cameras.
Uh-huh. All right, then. Okay.
We'll see about that bread-dipping.
Thank you. Thank you
for giving me an attitude.
Thank you for giving me an edge.
Or maybe it's groveling that works.
Hmm. Eh, six of one.
FRINK: Attention, Gourmands
of All Things Creepy and Crawly.
Please welcome long-time
squisher, first-time eater,
Lisa Simpson. (chuckles) Delighted.
Hey, waiter, there's no fly in my soup.
Sorry.
Little more. Little more.
Perfect.
Just-a once, why can't
they go to Applebee's?
Okay, fellas.
This time, why don't I do the cutting?
What are you doing?
I talk with that hand.
Well, you're gonna lose it
if you keep
charging your manicures to us.
If you don't like it, tough tortellini!
And while we're at it,
no more tortellini!
I'm dominating you!
Anyone got a problem? Huh?!
-Kenny the Problem?
-I'm good.
What's this I hear
about no more tortellini?
Only for Christmas and funerals.
No, please, please, I need-a the money.
She's-a pay for my-- how you say?
English lessons.
My name-a Luigi.
I live at a-one, a-two,
a-three, Main-a Street.
(humming)
So, if I'm growing grasshoppers to eat,
am I farmer or a rancher?
There are going to be a lot
of heated blogs on this topic.
MARGE: Lisa, dinnertime!
(meows)
(singsongy) Lisa eats bugs!
Bart! This is America.
Anyone can eat what they want
as long as they eat too much.
Lisa, would you like some shrimp?
Hmm.
You know... shrimp aren't all
that removed from grasshoppers.
They're both arthropods.
Oh, you did that to help me out.
(grunts)
Not sure what your motivation
for that is.
Lunch break.
Make this quick.
I finally got a chair by the window.
I'm afraid the little
Bulgarian lady will take it.
Bottom line, Tone,
I cut expenses 12%.
As my more ruthless cousin
on Wall Street would say,
cut another 12.
But the only other cuts left
are personnel.
There are redundancies.
Like Shotgun Pete, Shotgun Mike,
Ronnie the Rifle, Shotgun the Rifle...
All good men, but some must go.
I agree.
I will announce the layoffs.
Welcome to the dole, boys.
(chuckles)
You jadrool, in our business,
you don't lay them off,
you lay them out.
Right. What?
Oh, boy. Oh, boy.
(whispering)
Oh, boy, you mean, kill them?
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to shout.
Damn, she eats a quick lunch.
Got to go.
Nice breeze, huh?
You have breasts like woman,
but cannot give suck.
Quit saying that!
Get along, little buggies.
If I may, just one question.
Why are you eating us?
You don't feel any pain.
Wha...?! Who told you that?
Um... I just assumed.
This is what you've
been dipping in chocolate.
(Lisa gasps)
Nooo!
I'm afraid sooo!
-Nooo!
-Sooo!
(gasps) Oh, thank God.
Just a dream. (chuckles)
(gasps) I've been meat-walking.
Bart, I can't eat bugs anymore.
Please, please take my grasshoppers
as far away as you can
and release them into the wild.
Okay, but when I grow up
and I'm living on your couch,
and I drink all your booze,
and sell your jewelry,
you got to be cool.
I'll be cool.
But I will not be sharing
my mini-fridge with Homer.
He's there too?
(grunting)
Almost...
(grunts)
Eh, free is free.
(whistling jaunty tune)
He wants me to kill them!
-(shrieks)
-Sorry, sorry.
-First of all, hi.
-Hi, Dan.
Secondly, remember when
you asked who I worked for
and I wouldn't say?
(whispering) I'm a mob boss.
I'm running Fat Tony's gang
while he's on jury duty.
(chuckles) Doodie.
-Homer, that's not the shocking part.
-Oh?
He wants me to kill a bunch of guys.
I've got a gun. Look.
(gasps) Oh, my God!
-You want me to help you escape?
-No!
I want you to stop me from doing it.
-You wha...?!
-I want to do it, Homer.
It's the ultimate business model.
In my business, I try not to be seen.
I'm scary good at it.
-Homer!
-Mmm.
Everything's led to this.
I remember, the first time
I fired someone face-to-face, I cried.
I cried. Saved the tear.
Please stop. I just want
my Frisbee back from your yard.
They fired me for not being tough.
I had learned that in order to succeed,
you must disregard
the dangerous distraction
of being human.
And it brought me here.
You scratch a businessman and
you get a coldblooded killer.
Well, I've been scratched!
This is how I get out
of doing the dishes.
Come on, buddy, why would
you want to be a murderer?
I don't know.
My training,
this opportunity, it's like...
A perfect storm?
I hate that expression!
So overused!
Okay, I don't... I don't
know why I said it.
I was scared. I needed a response.
It was a perfect storm!
Say something original!
(nervously babbling)
Uh, Greek thing, uh, grand b-banana of...
far-na... of f-forever
thing, bleeks blah-blah,
a comma... a com...
a commonality beret burrito.
Oh, it looks like
a kidnapping in progress, Chief.
(groans) You always frame everything
in the worst possible light.
Chief, can I ask-- why do you
want to be a policeman?
Adrenaline junkie.
My dad used to tie me up when
the ice cream truck went by.
And now there's no amount of ice cream
that will make me feel full,
so this should work.
Yeah. That's right. Tie them tighter.
Mmm!
Oh, that's good. Oh, that burns.
Could you please not sound
like you like it so much?
Sorry.
I'm into a lot of weird stuff.
Now stay down here and I'll be back
every hour with food.
And every six hours with food for you.
Thanks, man. 'Preciate it!
Ah, look. I have company.
Hello.
Hello to you and your friend.
It's a party.
(chittering)
I'm going to call you Buggy,
and I'll call you--
please don't go in my mouth.
All right, you can go in my mouth.
Just don't lay egg...
(gargling)
ANNOUNCER:
We now return to AFI Presents
The 100 Greatest Movie Screams.
Number 60, from Teen Wolf Too...
(woman screaming)
-Classic.
-(Dan screaming)
Someone must be watching on another TV.
DAN (screaming):
The bugs!
I really think that's
coming from our house.
Will you stop saying things
that'll make me have to do something?
ANNOUNCER:
Next, we've got three screams
from Scream 3.
(three rapid screams)
(Dan screaming)
That was four screams. Stupid AFI.
Boy, never go into their
directors training program.
How about the Disney Minority Program?
Now, how would you qualify for that?
I'm the son of an oaf.
(scoffs) Have fun getting coffee
for Roy Disney the Third.
-Dinnertime.
-(chirping)
I know you're hungry.
I can hear you rubbing
your legs together and...
Oh, my God!
I never thought Homer Simpson
would be a part of the Day of the Locust.
Thanks.
Now, turn around and get on your knees.
Are you gonna shoot me
in the back of the head?
No, I just know it takes you
so long to get up
I'll have plenty of time to escape.
(grunting)
(sighs)
I'll fix that later.
(ominous organ music playing)
Your Honor, we have reached a verdict.
(gunshot)
Johnny Tightlips.
Give me one reason
why I shouldn't kill you right now.
There's a great one, but you'll
never get it out of me.
On vacation, he digs wells in Darfur!
Damn it!
We find the defendant...
And now it's time for Final Jeopardy.
Pay attention, players.
The category is...
You think you're so smart, Alex Trebek.
I remember when you
were Alphonse Trebagoogoo.
HOMER: Stop!
Make me!
(Bart grunts)
Come on!
You said we were gonna
see somebody get shot.
...not guilty.
I'll have your money in an hour.
(ominous organ music playing)
Dan!
How do you keep finding me?
You really should tweet less.
But everyone deserves to know
what I'm thinking all the time.
Just listen, if you kill those guys,
you'll be as bad as they are.
I don't think so.
They've killed a lot of people,
and they tell their wives
they're working,
but they're really just hanging out.
Look, just give me the gun
before you hurt somebody.
Give it to me.
Oh, I can't kill you.
I knew you were weak.
If you think I'm so weak,
give me back the gun.
-You are weak, but no.
-Let's see how weak I am with the gun.
-No, I don't want to.
-Give me the gun.
I don't want to see it.
You're making my mad and
I want to shoot you now.
I don't have to see it. Huh?!
-Give it to me!
-I can imagine it.
-Give me the gun.
-No.
Come on, weakling, get it from me.
I'm not... You want...
I'm not weak with the gun.
Yeah, well, yeah,
but see who's got it now.
-When I have a gun, I'm not weak at all.
-Yeah, well, you ain't so...
(glass breaks)
(grunts)
Clean-up on aisle me.
(groans)
Okay, Mom, I think that's far enough.
Finally, a place where you
can spread your wings and hop.
(chirping)
We're free!
No, no, I'm still gonna figure this out.
There was a corner here.
David...
Damn it, Judy, let me have this!
So, Tone, you're sure you didn't
order those fiduciary-related whacks?
The important thing is
we have severely cut costs
by reducing
the number of our guns to one.
And I have it.
Any further questions?
-Can I have the gun?
-No.
What happened to our friend Mr. Gillick?
I don't know. But once your finger
has felt the itch of a trigger,
there is no relief till
said trigger has been squeezed.
Sometimes late in life
you find your calling.
The heft of the gun,
the trigger in your hand...
Can you hurry this up, please?
My daughter's got cheerleading practice.
Oh, I-I can go fast.
Ba-da boom!
Could you please not do that?
Is there some kind of problem here?
And if not, can you do my belly button?
Need some place to hang
my badge at the sauna.
Shh!
Subtitled by A. Vandelay