[dramatic theme music plays]
[thunder rumbles]
[trolls grunting]
[troll] No!
[pants]
Finally. A galaxy without trolls.
Huh?
[shouts]
[grunting]
[grunts] Your reign of muscly
heroism ends here, Flexulon.
[horse whinnies]
[shouts]
- [whinnies]
- [shouts]
Soar high, my golden friend.
For today, we die another day.
[laughing]
[Otto laughing]
[laughs]
Next stop, the dank,
sticky jungles of Bong-ulon Five!
- [tires squeal]
- [Otto laughs]
Dude, you shouldn't have let him eat
that whole pan of acid brownies.
In my defense, I-I thought it'd be cool,
and I was right!
So, since Otto has disappeared
with our bus and our brownie pans,
parents will have to drive
their own children to school.
- [Chief Wiggum] Come on.
- [Dr. Hibbert] I'm not doing that though.
Well, fewer of you would have to drive
if you sat down
and arranged a carpool schedule.
[all shouting]
[parent] I'll kill you!
Or your children could walk to school
so none of you have to do anything.
- [Kirk] I like that option.
- [Chief Wiggum] Yeah.
Walking it is.
However, we do need one parent volunteer
to complete our team
of noble crossing guards.
[Moleman grunts]
Just, uh, one engaged parent
is all we need.
- [murmuring]
- [Dr. Hibbert] I'm too busy right now.
Hell yeah. You know I'm in.
I've been waiting for this my whole life.
Homer Simpson. Wonderful.
Hmm? What did he say?
I was watching the trailer
for the Revenge of the Nerds reboot.
John Cena is playing Booger.
Homer, you just volunteered.
Dear God!
No! Stop! Yield!
Well, he's got the lingo down.
This guy's a natural.
[bird squawks]
Now I gotta wake up
at the butt crack of dawn
to walk loser kids
across some loser street.
[sighs] Never have children, Lenny.
[chuckles] You don't have to worry
about that. See, I was born without...
- [beeping]
- [alarm blaring]
What the... We've got a code blue in 7-G.
Repeat, code blue.
[blaring continues]
[groans] Anyhoo, you notice there's
an apple for sale in the vending machine?
[chuckles] I mean, who would buy that?
Double the coolant levels. Now!
I'm on it.
Backup pumps on standby.
Carlson, decrease the steam valve by 60P.
Leonard, the control rods.
You, Glasses, pray for all our souls.
Now, switch generators on my count.
Five. Four.
Three. Two.
Implement.
[machinery powers down]
[all laughing]
- We did it!
- Boola, boola.
[clears throat] Um, fellas,
I'm the nuclear safety guy, right?
Shouldn't my console
have been doing all that beepy stuff?
- [Lenny] Yeah, um... Uh. Uh.
- Um. Mmm. Uh. You see...
We kinda made it so that
just my console does that now.
We just figured we'd lighten your load,
buddy. Since you already do so much.
Like the March Madness brackets.
And you're the go-getter
who implemented jean-short Wednesdays.
Are you guys saying
I've never kept anyone safe?
Oh, sure you have, Homer.
Just by not doing anything.
[groans]
My console isn't even plugged in.
I opened it, and it's full of cleaning
supplies and unsold Mr. Burns Funkos.
Aw. This whole time I thought I mattered,
but I don't, and I never did.
Well, you matter to me,
especially since it's Wednesday night.
- Oh. Right. Scheduled sex.
- [Marge] Mmm.
- [kissing]
- [Marge moaning]
[Homer] Okay. Here we go.
[kissing]
Just give me a second here.
Come on. Come on. Just... Almost.
[Homer grunting]
Uh, sweetie? It seems like your lightsaber
doesn't wanna go "shwoom."
Did you go Han Solo earlier tonight?
Aw. I guess I'm useless everywhere.
I'm just gonna stay in bed tomorrow
and suck my nightstand ketchup packets.
Actually, you have to wake up at 6:00
to be a crossing guard.
D'oh!
- What do you guys think happened to Otto?
- Jail.
Maybe he just got tired of
always running from the darkness.
Oh, God. There's Dad.
Please don't let him embarrass us.
Well, well, time to help
the baby brigade cross the road.
[laughing]
- [Lisa] Oh, no.
- [Bart groans]
I deserve your respect, you little jerks!
Stupid kids.
Without me, they'd be stuck on one side
of the street for the rest of their lives.
Ha-ha!
[singsongy] Got your octagonal sign.
Hey! Give me that.
I need it to tell cars what to do. Stop!
No, you stop. [laughs]
D'oh!
[laughing]
I'm a streetwalker.
Oh, no. I'm late for my AA meeting.
[engine revving]
Hey there, gorgeous!
[Homer] Hmm?
[Homer grunts]
- Whoa.
My whole life just flashed
through my pants.
Way to go, Homer! You just saved
this balding little scamp's life.
- All right, Homer!
- You did it, Dad!
How about one for the paper, Mr. S?
I saved someone's life.
You hear that, world?
Homer Simpson matters!
- [Milhouse] No, wait! No!
- [Nelson] Whoa! No!
Oh. Right. How about one of these?
- [Homer] Whoo!
- [Ralph] Whee!
[Homer grunting]
[Ralph] Whee!
The last two endangered pandas
on Earth died today
in what zoo investigators are calling
a grisly murder-suicide.
Adios, pandas.
We'll see you at the crossroads.
We wrap up tonight's
nightly reading of horrors
with a new optimistic segment I like
to call, "Chicken Soup for the News."
The small-town crossing guard... [chuckles]
...a job most Americans consider
as charming as it is pointless,
until last week,
when local hero Homer Simpson
risked his life to save
one pumpkin-headed little boy.
And now Simpson has become something
of a curbside celebrity.
What can Springfield do to show
its love and appreciation
for local crossing guards?
I don't know.
I guess we could use some new equipment.
These lawn chairs aren't very comfy,
and these old sashes
don't exactly lift and support.
But you know what, Kent?
Keeping kids safe is its own reward.
God bless that saintly dough ball.
That's it. I'm giving Springfield's
crossing guards an actual budget.
Not for self-serving political reasons,
but because I'm a man of principle
who wants to do good in the world.
Joseph, your turn on the sex chessboard.
We can't very well play without our king.
Though the bishop may try.
[Learned Pervert grunting]
Wow. Look at all this orange swag.
And that's just the beginning.
Now you'll be getting a full-time salary.
Sweet Cellophane Sally!
First, I get paid to be the timer
at a chess-themed sex orgy, and now this!
Homer, as the fella
whose heroism got us here,
I nominate you as crossing guard captain.
- [Marge] Ooh.
- [Lisa] Whoa.
Look at my handsome man in uniform.
I don't know, Homer.
The only people that wear badges
are power-hungry chumps
who want to keep the little guy down.
Are you talking about that security guard
at the supermarket?
I wasn't trying to break
the gumball machine.
I was just trying to shake out a purple.
Well, I'm proud of you, Dad.
Volunteering to serve the community
is the highest calling there is.
You know what's even better?
Volunteering for money!
We're getting paid now.
I even got a budget for ten more guards,
and I'm only gonna hire the best
and the brightest.
All right, rookies.
Not all of you are going to
make it through training.
Look to your left. Now look to your right.
That's how you know if a car is coming.
That concludes your training.
Hey, uh, Homer. I-I can't thank you enough
for saving my Ralphie's life.
Of course, Chief. Just doing my job.
You ever need a parking ticket thrown out
or someone else's DNA left somewhere,
you just let me know.
Hmm. [humming]
Arr, Captain, he didn't seek your
permission to cross the seven stripes.
Crossing Guard Stu
thinks he's undermining you.
[Homer] Mmm.
- Where's the fire, buddy?
- [shouts]
Do you know how jay
you were walking there, sir?
I-I-I don't know what that means.
All right, wise guy.
I'm gonna have to ask you
to step out of the curb
and keep your feet where I can see them.
I can't even see 'em.
Sir, calm down.
Look, I can let you off
with a warning this time,
but just so you know, I run these streets.
I... Wha... No, you d... I do!
Well, I run all the parts
between the curbs. Got it?
Ooh. These are nice.
I'm gonna hold on to them,
unless you have a problem with that.
Yeah, no. No problem at all, um, uh,
"Cross-ifer." Just h-have a nice day.
Stupid crossing guards think they're
so tough with their cool orange vests.
Another curb kept safe
by Captain Homer J. Simpson.
Boys.
["Ali; Funky Thing" playing]
[laughing]
[music fades out]
Uh, h-here's that pitcher you asked for,
Squeaky Voice.
That's Mr. Teen to you, rookie.
These new guys got no respect.
It ain't like when we started
three weeks ago.
Homer, I've been trying to reach you.
Whoa there, Skinner.
This bar is crossing guards only now.
I don't even let Lenny
and Carl in here no more.
Y-Yeah, but did you read my urgent memo?
Tomorrow is the science fair,
bake sale and picture day.
Morning drop-off will be very challenging.
Now, uh, I'm not telling you
how to do your job...
Are you telling me how to do my job?
No, I specifically said
I'm not telling you how to do your job.
That's enough, Principal What's-Your-Face.
No pedestrians allowed.
But, Homer, if we don't get this right,
it could be pandemonium.
[scoffs] Pandemonium.
It's pandemonium, folks.
This is Arnie Pye reporting live,
high above
an elementary school traffic jam
turned all-out scholastic fracas.
Surely, this town's handsomely paid
crossing guards
can bring order
to this Monday morning mayhem.
Oh. Oh.
Guys, stop it!
[whimpers]
[shouting]
The punching is making things worse.
Don't make me blow my whistle at you.
Captain Simpson!
The shaking of my car
is dangerously close to mixing
the hydrogen peroxide,
yeast and dish soap within.
So?
Those ingredients create a fascinating
yet volatile substance known as...
elephant toothpaste.
This was the most expensive, destructive
and disgusting riot
since the Isotopes won the pennant.
Go, Topes!
Crossing Guard Captain Homer Simpson,
what do you have to say for yourself?
- Yeah, what?
- You suck!
Um, um.
W-What can I do? Who can I blame?
Coastal elites? Avocado socialists?
The boy? [gasps] I got it!
Mr. Mayor, the blame falls squarely
on the shoulders
of the crossing guards' inadequate budget.
We need more money!
More money?
More money for training, for equipment,
for overtime.
So that your children can cross the street
safely at 3:00 a.m. if they want to.
[murmuring]
Throwing money at a deeply flawed
institution is bound to work!
Um. Have you all been
huffing evidence powder?
Homer Simpson and his chair jockeys
royally screwed the pooch on this one.
And now you want to give him more money?
That makes absolutely no sense.
Listen up, "wokester."
Guys like me are the last line of defense
between your schoolkids
and guys like me who text when they drive!
And if you don't like it,
you can jaywalk your ass back to Portland.
[cheering]
Wha...
All in favor of me pulling
a political 180 on this issue
and giving the crossing guards
a blank check, say aye.
- [all] Aye!
- Nay!
Somebody get my enormous checkbook.
[cheering]
It worked.
Maybe I should have asked them
for more just in case.
And, uh, here's some more just in case.
Ooh! These Bean Bag Bazookas
can shatter a minivan windshield.
[gasps] And it comes with
a Bean Bag Bandolier.
Look at you and your huge budget.
My big strong leader in the streets
and in the sheets.
The bedsheets.
I like that we kept our sunglasses
on last night.
I couldn't see a thing.
Wow, look at all this cool stuff.
You are an all-powerful crossing god.
I thought you said badges were lame.
Hey, like everyone who comes
into a ton of cash,
I flip-flop to the side of authority.
Oh. You're charging me, Francine?
Even though I keep your kids safe
every morning?
Aiden, Charlotte, nearsighted Nicholas.
Oh, I'm sorry. It's on the house.
Thank you for your service, hero.
[sighs] I don't even have kids,
but this guy scares me.
Um, Dad,
I worry that this massive increase in
money and power is subtly corrupting you.
- [chuckles]
- Oh, honey, relax.
There's nothing subtle about it.
["Won't Get Fooled Again" playing]
[music ends]
- [tires screech]
- Move, move, move!
[pedestrians shouting, panting]
Nice job, Squeaks.
Moleman, you got a couple of SJWs...
suspected jaywalkers... at three o'clock.
Engage with extreme hostility.
[Moleman] Copy.
Gun safety and body cam off.
[gunshots]
Mmm. Simpson and his orange shirts
are harassing citizens
with complete disregard
for their civil rights.
I'm up to my eyeballs in angry emails
and nine-figure lawsuits.
Well, you could always, uh,
decrease their budget a bit.
Defund us?
[both yelp]
My department
does not have too much money.
How did you know
what we were talking about?
Uh. Surveillance satellite.
[beeping]
Aw, geez. We wanted one of those!
Uh, Captain Simpson,
your crossing guards now take up
the vast majority of this town's budget.
We have no choice
but to trim your budget by 1.5%.
[stammers] One point... [stammers]
Sir, you're about to learn
the crossing guards are uncrossable.
[rat squeaking]
Where is the nice man who helps us cross?
I heard he lost his funding.
Let's just go by ourselves.
[engine revving]
[screaming]
[Homer] Welcome to
Mayor Quimby's Springfield.
Population: two less kids.
Quimby and his fat cop cronies
wanna flood the streets with DoorDashers,
rolling stoppers
and yellow light speeder-uppers.
Joe Quimby:
bad for Springfield, worse for America.
Paid for by the money we got from Quimby.
A smear ad?
It's not even an election year.
Is it?
Homer Simpson can bully this town,
its citizens and their young children,
but he cannot bully me.
Clancy, shut him down.
With pleasure.
[gasps]
My anti-Quimby ad got a million likes
on my Thin Orange Line Facebook page.
Look at all these supportive comments.
"Murder Quimby"? "Dismember Quimby"?
"Go back in time and kill baby Quimby"?
Ah, the Internet:
the marketplace of ideas.
You're endangering the lives
of public officials.
Oh, come on.
I'm just slinging a little mud.
- What's the worst that could happen?
- [glass shatters]
[gasps] Dear God.
That chair was my best friend
on the force.
Who would dare do this?
[Chief Wiggum] Me would dare.
When you mess with the pig,
you get the snout.
This is a chair too far, Wiggum.
My crossing guards and your cops
need to settle this once and for all
at the most dangerous place in town.
What, that Brunchausen by Loxy place
that's been poisoning
everyone for attention?
No, the six-way intersection.
Well, well.
I thought cops only showed up
after something bad happens.
[laughing]
We are sick of you crossing guards
and your unaccountable, super macho, hypersensitive,
crazily militarized malarkey.
That's our thing, damn it.
No, that's our thing.
Who the hell are you?
We're ICE, keeping this country safe from
cleaning ladies and college-age Dreamers.
We're America's heroes.
You wish, kid cagers.
It's the TSA.
We keep this country safe,
one confiscated shampoo bottle at a time.
Think again, shoe sniffers.
The only force holding society together
is America's meter maids.
And meter butlers.
No, it's us.
Overzealous neighborhood watch guys
in right-to-carry states.
- [shouts, groans]
- Whoops. Sorry, Clem.
[all shouting]
[air horn blares]
You all think you keep America safe?
Pfft. How? By hassling grandmas
and wrecking quinceañeras?
By grazing my junk with your wand?
Or arresting bank robbers who rob banks?
Unlike all of you,
I've earned the right to feel godlike.
I've actually saved a life.
[person]
Um. We save lives every day, bruh.
Shut up, lifeguards.
This is a land argument.
But if the rest of you wanna get nuts,
then come on.
Let's get nuts.
But mark my words,
before you cross the crossing guards,
you better look both wa...
[grunts]
Hey, everybody. I'm back. I...
Uh-oh.
[Homer groaning]
Am I gonna go to jail now?
I wouldn't dream of it.
[cheering]
Well, I hope you learned
a valuable lesson, Dad.
Absolute power cor...
Is the best kind of power there is?
Is a warm Bean Bag Bazooka?
Does bad things to society
and does strange things to me.
No.
Once you militarized the crossing guards,
they became an army in search of an enemy.
And if the only tool you have is a hammer,
then everything
starts to look like a nail.
Perhaps. But on the other hand...
[belches, laughs]
- [groans] Mom.
- [chuckling] Gotcha.
Bart, say, "Excuse me."
I don't care if he says, "Excuse me."
I want him not to burp in my face!
- Lighten up, Lis.
- [Lisa] Is it so much to ask?
- [Bart] I'm not gonna apologize.
- [Lisa] He always does this.
- [Homer] Must hammer nails.
- [Lisa] Have you smelled that burp?
♪ If I had a hammer ♪
♪ I'd hammer in the morning ♪
[music continues]
Shh!