(choir singing)
Yee-haw!
(exclaiming)
(school bell ringing)
(Barney belches)
(whistle blows)
(yells)
(beeps)
(playing the blues)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-(tires screeching)
-(grunts)
♪♪
(thunder crashing)
(eerie music plays)
(muttering)
(maniacal laughter)
Burns, you're
coming with us.
No, no, let me go.
(Burns narrating): Surprised?
Me, C. Montgomery Burns,
locked up like an animal?
What caused this puzzling turn
of events?
Well, I'll tell you my tale...
by thinking about it to myself.
And so our Employee of the Month
is the late Roger Ducette,
who tragically died
from complications
due to union organizing.
Moving on.
The power plant's first annual
Fourth of July picnic
is this coming Saturday.
Whoo-hoo!
Oh, I'm afraid
you misunderstand.
This picnic is for me.
You will all be spending your
Independence Day slaving away
in the hot summer sun without
pay, lotion or gratitude.
D'oh!
Yes, "duh-ohhh," indeed.
♪ 'Cause it's summer ♪
♪ Summertime is here ♪
(Burns laughing)
-(dogs snarling)
-♪ Yes, it's summer ♪
♪ My time of... ♪
Sir, your spareribs, cooked
just the way you like 'em.
Spareribs, eh?
I've played a round of tenpins
or two in my life,
and to me, the word "spare"
reeks of second best.
Give me ten full frames
of strike ribs.
And you, find my doctor
and ask him why I'd
ask for something
-as insane as strike ribs.
-(glumly): Yes, sir.
You know, sir,
these people have been working
since your 6:00 a.m.
parade of the flags.
Maybe you could give them
the rest of the day off
to spend with their families?
Yes, they should go.
Just as soon as they perform
this musical I've written
in celebration
of our nation's birth.
Grab your scripts, people.
We open in 20 minutes.
Break a leg.
I said break a leg.
For God's sake, man,
it's a figure of speech.
You're fired.
(to the tune of "Battle Hymn")
♪ We love America ♪
(fireworks whistling)
(music continues playing)
Meh. Smithers, take my hands
and clap them sarcastically.
More sarcastic.
Burns-- what
an ungrateful jerk.
We hoofed our hearts out for him
with no rehearsal.
I say Burns owes us
a party.
Let's have one
right now... with his wine.
(eerie music plays)
I don't know.
Technically,
this is trespassing.
(scoffs): What's the worst
thing he could do?
-(Homer humming)
-Hey, Lenny,
you care for some Chateau
La Mondotte Saint-Emilion?
That's a regular-sized bottle.
I'm drinking Jeroboams.
I'm pounding
Melchizedeks.
(grunting)
Homer, that's
a $60,000 bottle.
Whoo-hoo.
I'm drinking my salary.
Yeah, but don't some of that go
to income tax?
Yeah, you're right.
The government...
taking my hard-earned
stolen wine
and spending it on
that no-good floor.
I hear that.
-(Homer yelling)
-LENNY: I'm getting radioactive
right now.
(grunting)
(deep breathing)
(Homer laughing)
Smithers, sound the alarum.
Summon the shire reeve.
Wake the beadle.
(sirens wailing)
(tires screeching)
Okay, left hand:
Rembrandt.
(grunting)
(guns cocking)
All right, step away
from the old masters
and kick 'em over here.
Come on.
Whoa, wait a minute, Chief.
-This is The Concert by Vermeer.
-Huh?
Which was stolen in 1990
from Boston's Isabella
Stewart Gardner Museum?
So, Burns,
do you want to explain
how this miracle of measure
and harmony got into
your collection?
Well, I... you-you see...
It's just...
Is it a crime
to want nice things,
and then to steal them
from a public museum
where any gum-chewing monkey
in a Tufts University jacket
can gawk at them?
I think not!
Cuff him, Lou.
MR. BURNS: The entire town turned
out to jeer me.
Me, whose velvet breeches
their lizard lips
had so often
joylessly smooched.
(crowd jeering)
Throwin' stuff.
Get yer throwin' stuff.
Turn a protest into a riot.
How much
for a tomato?
Fresh is a dollar,
rotten's two bucks.
Son, do you really need
the rotten?
I mean, it's not like
you're actually gonna hit him.
Oh... since it's your birthday.
Mom, I'm gonna go hurl
rotten fruit.
No one in this
family is hurling
rotten anything
at anyone.
(Homer laughing)
And just what
might that be?
Uh... this is my lunch.
Really?
Okay, eat your lunch.
But...
You said it's
your lunch.
-Eat it.
-Eat my lunch?
Yes. Enjoy.
-Okay, I will.
-Bon appétit.
MR. BURNS:
They continued for some time
in this vein, until...
You don't think
I'm going to?
I don't see any chewing.
Okay.
(makes chewing sound)
Not air bites,
real bites.
Oh...
-Where are you going?
-Shopping.
Every time this town riots,
the malls are deserted.
You stay here.
(groans):
I hate being stuck at home.
Play with Lisa.
Mom, you don't
play with Lisa.
You play
despite her.
Bart, I'm not
thrilled either,
but one day we might
need each other
for organ transplants,
so we'd better keep
the lines of communication open.
Want to help me
with my ant farm?
You plant the ants,
and then they grow?
No, the ants are the farmers.
Really? What are
they growing?
Nothing. Look, do you want
to do it or not?
-No!
-Fine.
So ironic.
After all my years
of stock jobbing,
gun running,
attempted murder,
successful murder,
and tom peepery,
they get me on a petty
multimillion dollar art theft.
(sobs):
It's so unfair.
Smithers, until I am released,
you shall be running
the nuclear plant.
Me?
Be strong, Smithers.
Be strong for the plant.
She needs you.
(metallic creaking)
MR. BURNS:
This would have been a perfect
time for it to start raining.
Oh, what the hell.
I'm telling this story.
(thunder crashing)
Hmm. Not dramatic enough.
Frostbite took his nose.
(Burns laughs):
Excellent.
MR. BURNS: That prison
was like a prison to me.
Not a prison of bricks
and iron,
but one of steel and cement.
They took everything from me.
One movie stub from
Tillie's Punctured Romance,
envelope marked "bribe."
Empty.
Social Security card.
That's just an S.S. card,
you Dummkopf.
My only hope lay
in befriending the warden.
(with Southern accent):
Now you looky here, Burns.
All your money and influence
don't mean nothin'
on the inside.
Yes, but a wealthy man
can buy information,
information that can be highly
damaging to a certain warden.
Well, uh, what information
we talkin' 'bout?
Well, I'm sure the boys
at the city desk
would be interested to learn
that you're addicted to...
to...
(chuckles)
Can't read my own writing.
But I'll tell you this, Warden,
it starts with an "H."
Ham?
It's clearly more
than three letters.
Get him out of my sight.
Ain't nobody gonna take my H
from me.
(inhales)
(high-pitched):
Damn, that gas is noble.
(blues music playing)
♪ Early one morning ♪
♪ The blues came fallin' down ♪
♪ The blues came-- ♪
(music stops abruptly)
Time for a cavity search.
(laughing):
Oh.
I haven't had a cavity
in over 40 years.
I wasn't talking
about your teeth.
Nor was I.
Meet your roommate.
Hiya, pal.
They put two harmless
white collar criminals
in the same cell.
What luck, huh?
(chuckling)
I was afraid you'd be
some tattooed bruiser.
Well, they don't turn out
too many of those at Dartmouth.
Dartmouth? Get me away from
this hideous brute at once.
At once! Do you hear me?
Got my master's from the
University of Virginia,
the public Ivy.
Guard!
Such an intricate formicarium.
I'm the proudest myrmecologist
on the block.
Hey, they're not eating.
Don't worry.
I gave 'em a Pop-Tart.
The healthy kind--
strawberry-frosted.
Bart, that Pop-Tart wasn't
locally farmed or sourced.
Oh, Lisa, you take the fun
out of everything.
(scoffs):
I am so glad
I am not your kid.
Well, I'm so glad
I'm not your mom.
You should be.
If I was in your tummy,
I'd poo in your throat.
Ew. Ew. Ew. I'll never get
that image out of my head.
Oh, no. You are not
taking the children.
If they're anybody's children,
they're mine.
(grunting)
(gasps):
Quick, we gotta get them back.
There's only one ant left.
I will
never forgive you.
Aw...
Well, I will
never forgive you, Bart.
That only angers me more!
-I know.
-(growls)
Okay, Waylon,
you never wanted this job,
but you got it.
Damn it!
(sighs)
You know, this is my chance.
A chance to be the kind of
boss I want to be.
A little more...
employee-friendly.
Mmm. That was
a wild Christmas party.
In the next few weeks,
we'll be introducing
a medical plan
that covers illness,
and a suggestion box
that is no longer
a guillotine for the hand.
(clanging)
Yeah!
Well, I agree things
are a lot nicer around here,
but I think I speak
for many of us when I say...
what's the catch?
(chuckles)
Well, the catch is,
happy workers
are productive workers.
(quietly):
There's always a catch!
Can I come in?
You're not going
anywhere near Annie.
Annie?
As in "Little Orphan"?
It was an accident--
I didn't mean to kill our ants.
(gasps):
Patty and Selma
are dead?
Whoo-hoo!
A double funeral!
(Homer singing lively tune)
Dad, before you
jump to conclusions...
Oh, please,
tell me they suffered.
(gasps)
Gh-gh-gh... hags!
(both groaning)
MR. BURNS:
Looks like it's Pledge Day.
Which jailhouse fraternity
shall I join?
The Shriners?
The ROTC?
The Sunday Funnies?
Or one of these other
dining clubs?
Look at them circling me
like I'm Cinderella,
belle of the ball.
MAN:
Back off!
He's mine.
Warden, help me!
(high-pitched):
No can do, baby.
I'm not coming down for days!
Mr. Smithers, our lives
are awesome, thanks to you.
And because I know you...
like your loafers light,
I want to give something back.
Wip!
Use that image
any way you want.
Three cheers
for Mr. Smithers!
To Mr. Smithers!
Hooray!
(chuckles)
Uh, listen,
uh, can I leave
a little early tomorrow?
My kid has a thing.
Ooh, yeah, can I
leave early, too?
I wanna take a nap so I'm
awake for the meteor shower.
Well, I'm flexible. Go ahead.
You know, I used
to think you was
just as bad as Mr. Burns.
Now, I think you're
just as good as me.
Oh, that is a
huge compliment.
(phone rings)
Uh, excuse me.
Yes, the service on my car
was excellent.
Five out of five.
Four out of five.
Uh, excuse me, can I go back
and change that four out of five
to five out of five?
I'm wasting your time?
Smithers, what
a marshmallow.
I don't have
a thing with my
kid tomorrow.
You told me you did.
I do, but I'm not
going to it.
To Smithers,
the world's dumbest loser.
There's nothing
sweeter than being nice
to a guy's face and then
stabbing him in the back
the minute
he walks away.
All right, that's it.
-(gasping)
-You know,
I used to wonder
why Mr. Burns
hated humanity.
Now I know.
You open your heart
and they mock your very decency.
(mocking):
Ooh, we mock
your very decency.
(whimpers)
Man, Smithers is working us
like dogs.
Well, at least we got
the best brand
ceiling insulation.
(shrieks)
Well, at least we got
the best asbestos.
(groaning)
(buzzer rings)
I've told you,
you're mine.
And you can't escape the word
of Jesus Christ.
Burns, you shall
reject Satan.
Why can't you
reject your guy?
Because when I
was at my lowest
facing 50 years to life,
someone handed me a book.
I couldn't read a lick,
but that picture of Jesus
gave me a comfort
I've never known.
So I promised the Lord
I'd put that 50 years to use
reclaiming
lost souls like you.
Come to Jesus!
-Shan't.
-(thunder rumbles)
Feel his power!
I've died and come back--
it's overrated.
-Open your heart!
-(groaning)
(thunder rumbling)
I will suck out your evil.
(groaning)
(yelling)
And now, your evil is gone!
(chuckles) I'm afraid that
was just my pre-evil.
(thunder crashing)
I feel it.
I feel the love
coursing through my vein.
(chuckles)
Welcome to the Lord,
brother.
MR. BURNS:
So, that hellhole
became a Heavenhole.
I joined the prison choir.
And the prison
Beatles' tribute band.
I raked a Zen garden
in the courtyard
and found a peace and serenity
I'd never known.
(chuckles)
Who's carrying
50 times her weight?
-Ooh, you are.
-LISA: Bart?
She's only carrying
30 times her weight.
Our girl is slowing down.
Oh, my God.
That is so sad.
It's the natural
order of things.
I'm afraid she's
got another two,
maybe three days, tops.
Do we let her spend the rest
of her life in the wild?
Or let her die in captivity,
like Grampa?
Hey, in my mind
I'm free.
No you're not, ya idjit!
(groans)
It's official.
Smithers is now
worse than Mr. Burns.
Instead of releasing hounds,
he releases wolverines.
(snarling)
I never thought
I'd say this,
but I wish Mr. Burns
was back.
Hey, if wishes were
horses, I'd be eatin'
wish-meat every night.
What does that mean?
It means, it's not like you're
gonna break into the prison
and bust him out or anything.
Oh, hey, come on.
You can't really
be serious about
breaking him out.
It's too late
to turn back, Moe.
We've exchanged
meaningful looks.
No, you can still turn back.
The point of no return
is the whispered huddle.
(whispering)
Oh, God. Oh, God!
(thunder crashing)
-Burns, you're
coming with us.
-No.
No, let me go.
Why would I want
to leave the place
where my soul was saved?
And that's where we came in.
Now, without further ado,
here's what happened next.
But first, I'll daydream
about a sport utility vehicle,
a crispy chicken sandwich
and a wonderful blue pill.
MAN:
Hold it right there!
You're not leaving
with that man.
He's born again.
Been baptized in a toilet sink.
(quietly):
Everyone doesn't
have to know that part.
It's the specific
detail that shows
the humbling
you've undergone.
-You don't have
a "whisper" voice, do you?
-What?
Good-bye, Annie,
my eight-legged friend.
Ants have six legs, Bart.
Oh, thank God.
I thought I broke two off.
You're just a tiny ant,
but you were strong enough
to pull my brother
and me together.
Now go and be free.
Look, if I leave with you,
they're just going
to throw me back in.
The world has changed
since you went in.
Men of wealth
can beat the system now.
Yeah, and they've replaced
parking meters
with this thing you stick
your credit card into.
The war is over
and the future won.
The past never
had a chance, man.
Do you really want to
leave with these idiots?
I'm afraid so.
But I cleansed you
of your evil.
I had a little left
between my toes.
It quickly multiplied, and now
I'm a bigger bastard than ever.
But I must know,
what was it about me
that made you try?
Because I've killed
so many rich white men,
I thought I'd do right
by at least one.
We're not so different,
you and I.
(both chuckling)
Get your skinny
ass out of here.
Lollygags,
slackabouts,
Captain Happys--
you're all fired.
I'll do the firing
around here.
Mr. Burns!
You're even more beautiful
than I remembered.
All of you,
out of my office.
(sighs)
Farewell, friend.
Maybe you'll find another
lost lamb for your flock.
Tell me, brother, have you heard
the story of Jesus Christ?
Well, I am Italian, but no.
MR. BURNS:
♪ Oh, I live me in a mansion ♪
♪ Full of those Grecian urns ♪
♪ But I'm lonely
all the livelong day ♪
♪ That's the blues
of Monty Burns ♪
FEMALE CHORUS:
♪ He's got the blues ♪
♪ The I-got-no-problems blues ♪
MR. BURNS:
♪ Oh, my tapestry's medieval ♪
♪ My heart, it's evil, too ♪
♪ But that don't mean
I don't need love ♪
♪ From lesser types like you ♪
FEMALE CHORUS:
♪ He's got the blues ♪
♪ The old-and-privileged
white man blues ♪
Shh!
Enhanced by Fotokem