CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screeching)
D’oh!
(screams)
♪♪
HOMER:
Hmm.
♪♪
(Homer snoring)
Hmm.
(sighs)
What’s the matter,
sweetie?
Tomorrow’s Multicultural Day
at school.
Now what do they want?
(snoring)
I’ve got to give a presentation
about our family’s heritage,
but ours is so boring.
Yep. The Simpsons
have never married,
or even shook hands,
with anyone interesting.
In a world of 31 flavors,
we’re the cup of water
they rinse the scoops in.
Grampa out.
Aw, Grampa.
We should take lots of pictures
of him while we still can.
Camera’s broken!
(snoring)
(sad music)
(chuckling)
Hey, Lis, check it out.
With some
clever scissor work,
I can make the Lake Land Butter
Indian maiden show me her boobs.
Clean, dirty.
(laughs)
(laughs):
Clean, dirty.
(laughs)
Bart, stop that!
Native Americans
are a proud people
with a noble heritage.
A noble heritage
that anyone can claim.
Cool!
Look what Snap’s
doing to Pop
while Crackle watches!
(laughing)
"My great-great-great-
great... great-grandmother
was a Native American.
She was a member of the..."
(music swells)
"...Hitachee tribe."
♪♪
Wait. Is it wrong for me
to appropriate the culture
of a long-suffering people?
I’ll tell you
what’s wrong:
You getting a "C"
on this project
and winding up at
a third-rate college.
Lisa, the world needs you
to go to Wellesley!
You’re right.
I’ll just need to find
traditional garb.
(Native American music)
And so, my proud people
were nearly destroyed
by the warfare, disease,
and greed of
the invading Europeans.
I didn’t come here
to be insulted.
Guten tag!
(dog panting)
Today, the Hitachees
have dwindled to a handful,
and our detailed
genealogical records
were cruelly destroyed
by the white man.
So, any attempts
to research my tribe
would be the ultimate insult.
(clapping)
Splendid, Lisa.
By far, the best
presentation of the day.
I’m still proud of what I am.
And you should be.
The city’s
Multicultural Council
has invited one lucky student
to perform at City Hall.
Lisa, you’ll be
representing us
and the noble
Hitachee people.
Oh... great!
I’d... love to.
Mm-hmm.
Why did I have to lie
about my heritage?
By speaking with forked tongue,
I am in heap big trouble.
(gasps)
And now I’m thinking
in stereotypes!
That’s even worse!
(screaming)
Must be the war cry
of her tribe.
Probably.
Now, get me some coffee.
(chicken clucking)
Daddy, I got
me a C-minus
on my Multicultural
project.
A C-minus, huh?
Well, let’s celebrate.
Hey, Brandine,
empty out the tub!
We’s makin’ rum!
BRANDINE:
Can’t use the tub!
I’m drownin’
rats in it!
Still?! Are you drownin’ ’em
or makin’ love to ’em?
(bellows)
(chicken clucks)
(busy music playing)
(chirps)
(screech)
(shrieks)
(music continues)
Oh!
(bellows)
(dramatic music)
(screaming)
Mr. Burns, help me!
Why? You’re
not helping me.
But, sir, I’m flaming!
(screaming)
My God, Willie, that fire
is headed right for
the tetherball pole.
Put it out!
I cannot!
All the extinguishers
are gone!
Then I’m afraid
these Wet Ones
will have to do the job.
Gah! These are drier
than a Charles Grodin quip.
(foreboding music)
What monster,
or pair of monsters,
would steal
our extinguishers?
If this works, I’ll go faster
than any ten-year-old
has ever gone.
Whoa!
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa!
(dramatic music)
Oh, the flames are heading
straight for the Flammable
District!
That’s where
our mom works!
(screaming)
My last words are "Lisa sucks!"
(heroic brass music)
That boy is a hero!
Let’s get hoisting!
ALL:
Bart! Bart! Bart!
(pleased chuckle)
Young man,
to show our gratitude,
the City of Springfield
will grant you one wish.
Really? Hmm.
(joyful music)
(satisfied sigh)
(cool jazz music)
(crowd cheering)
That’s it!
I want a license!
To kill?
No. To drive.
Suit yourself.
Do you wish
to be an organ donor?
No way! I don’t want my guts
touching some sick guy.
Well, you make a good point.
-ALL: Oh, yeah.
-I agree.
Oh, this is a bad time for me
to have massive organ failure.
(chuckling)
Where do you
think you’re going?
(nervous screeching)
(cool jazz music)
Oh, I can’t believe
this day is already here.
Me taking you for your
first driving lesson.
Hey! That jerk
cut us off.
Pull alongside.
Eat Marshall Tucker,
idiot!
(grunting)
MARGE:
Homer? Is that you?
(yelps):
Floor it!
("Jessica" by The Allman
Brothers playing)
(school bell ringing)
♪♪
(tires screeching)
(panicked shrieks and yells)
(groaning)
(shrieks)
The Hitachees
invented women’s lacrosse...
soft luggage...
(interested murmuring)
And that thing
where you’re walking
and someone’s
walking towards you
and you each try to step aside
but you both go the same way
and you do it again and again
until one of you
just scoots around?
They had seven names for that.
Whoa, you just
blew my mind!
Uh, thank you and good night.
AUDIENCE:
Yay!
Show’s over.
Let’s go.
What’s your hurry?
Well, some of my report...
um... wasn’t thoroughly
fact-checked.
(nervous giggle)
(laughs)
My little girl’s
just like CBS News.
Lisa, it was
wonderful!
I am such a proud
Hitachee mother.
Lisa, hi, my name is
John Squawking Bear.
I’m a reporter for
The Chippewa Bugle.
I happen to have today’s.
You know, uh, I thought I
knew all the lost tribes.
I’ve never heard
of the Hitachee.
(giggles nervously)
Yes, we’re among the lostest.
Uh-huh. Where
were you centered?
Centered. Centered...
You know where the four
states come together?
Oh, quite well.
Not there.
Not even close.
In the name of the Great Turtle,
will you answer the question?
We were south... west of...
North Dakota-lahoma.
Hmm.
Very good.
Well, I better
get to my office
before my boss,
Screaming Editor, gets mad.
I kid, but he’s
a real jerk.
(gulps)
Hey, guys. See you in a bit.
I entered a thousand-mile
Baja Road race.
Hold on there, boy.
If you wanna keep
using that car,
you’d better start
pullin’ your weight.
This cell phone is
so I can call you
whenever I need your
driving services.
I put in my
own ringtone!
("Fur Elise" blaring)
Hello, Bart?
Now, listen. I need you
to go the gas station.
Tell them you need
to inflate your tires,
but actually you inflate
these volleyballs.
Then, throw them over
the wall of the prison
to create chaos
and confusion.
("Fur Elise" blaring)
H-Hello?
HOMER (drunk):
Bart! Buddy!
It’s your dad!
I need a ride.
I think I’m in Chinatown.
Not our Chinatown.
LISA:
Slow down!
You’re too close
to that car.
Your hands should be at ten and
two, not three and nothing!
You know, it’d
be a real shame
if someone started
investigating your
"Indian heritage."
I’ll be good.
("Fur Elise" blaring)
Oh, man.
What now?
Boy, I don’t want
to freak you out,
but I’m calling
from inside the trunk.
(thumping)
That was me.
Some very un-cool people
put me in here.
(motor revving)
This sucks.
I can’t do anything fun
’cause I’m doing so many
stupid errands.
("Fur Elise" blaring)
Shut up, shut up, shut up!
HOMER:
Ah! It’s dark in here!
Oh, I gotta get outta
this town for a while.
Time to put the pedal
to the metal.
(War’s "Lowrider" plays)
Ooh, North Haverbrook.
The very name conjures up
romance and intrigue.
(bell rings)
Wow, a mint condition
Hippie Hulk from 1968!
Tune in, turn on, Hulk out!
Oh, man, this town’s
got everything!
Hey, hey, LBJ, how many pants
you rip today?
(growl)
♪ Gonna rock around
the clock tonight ♪
♪ Gonna rock, rock, rock
till broad daylight ♪
♪ Gonna rock, gonna rock
around the clock tonight ♪
♪♪
Any of you ladies
like stereo music?
I do.
You look kinda young.
Uh... Yeah.
I have that disease that
makes you look like an old man,
but they gave me medicine
for it and I took too much.
That’s cool.
I’m Darcy.
I’m Bart Simpson,
who the hell are you?
Oh, right. (chuckles)
Darcy.
(romantic accordion music)
(both laughing)
("Fur Elise" blaring)
HOMER: Bart! This is a matter
of life and death.
What is the difference
between ketchup and catsup?
They’re gonna cut
my head off...
(both laughing)
Kyle, are you sure we
should be making out
in this abandoned
sawmill?
Lighten up, baby.
There hasn’t been a murder
here in ten years.
Ten years tonight.
(chainsaw buzzing)
GIRL:
It’s the kid we locked
in the cemetery
in the first grade!
BOY:
Hey, what are you gonna do
with that chainsaw, dork?
(chainsaw buzzing,
couple screaming)
(screaming)
I really like you, Bart.
That is such a girl
thing to say.
(smooching)
So, Doctor, was
it all a dream.
(buzzing, screaming)
(romantic French music playing)
Bart, let’s get married.
(gulps):
What?!
Why not?
We’ve made out.
It’s not right to make
out with somebody
if you have no intention
of marrying them.
I mean, you’re not
a jerk, right?
(gulps): No, I’m not, but...
Then it’s settled.
(smooches)
Oh, man, I must be
the first guy
who was ever pressured
into marriage.
(foreboding music)
Look, Darcy,
I like you.
I really do.
It’s just...
I’m only ten years old.
Wha?!
I’m really sorry.
Bart, I’ve been keeping
a secret from you, too.
I’m pregnant.
(engine grinding)
(groans)
(engine grinds)
I’m going to be a father?!
What?! No!
You couldn’t be
the father.
We never
got close to that.
Really?
We didn’t?
But we kissed and held
hands at the same time.
Wow, you really
are ten.
I thought you were just
kind of stupid.
I’m ten and stupid.
Look, if I’m not the
father, then who is?
A Norwegian
exchange student.
He’s long gone,
back to Norwegia.
I wanted you to marry me
so my baby would have a dad.
I’m very religious
that way.
How religious can you be
if you’re pregnant?
Good answer.
(sobs)
Marrying you
was my only hope.
When my parents find out,
they’re gonna kill me.
(sobbing)
Look, Darcy, maybe there’s
still a way we can get married.
How?
You’re just a kid!
Maybe I shouldn’t be
telling you this,
but there is a state
where the marriage laws
are a little looser.
Utah.
Utah?
Home of America’s
most powerful weirdos?
Our lives could be
so wonderful there.
(serene music)
(gargling)
Oh, Bart.
You are an extreme husband
and an extreme father.
Awesome!
(tense Native American music)
The people of my tribe lived
in harmony with the land.
Eating mock buffalo steaks
made from
peaceful turnip roots,
uh, they...
Environment...
uh, dignity...
Corn god...
(groans):
I’m sorry, I can’t do this!
I made it all up!
There is no Hitachee tribe.
I took the name
from my microwave.
(crowd murmuring)
But surely you can forgive
a little girl who...
(screams)
Wait, wait.
Although she is not
one of our people,
this young lady
has shown the courage
we Native Americans cherish.
And who can blame her
for wanting to be one of us?
We have a noble heritage
and cheekbones to die for.
(cheering)
I’m not Native American, either.
I just ski a lot.
(crowd gasps)
I’m Japanese.
Well, I’m an Aborigine.
I’m two midgets
in a costume.
What?
Not you, Fibbing Bear?!
(clamoring)
You know, my great-great
grandmother was an Indian.
I guess I should’ve
mentioned that before, huh?
Yes, you should have!
(screams)
Bart, sweetie.
I need some
strawberries.
Mm-hmm. I bet they
sell them in Utah.
Bart, I need
some strawberries.
Right now.
We’re in the middle
of the desert.
I need strawberries!
BART:
Take my wife...
please.
Hey, I finally get that joke.
-(smack)
-Ow!
I just found this note
in Bart’s room.
"Dear Mom and Dad,
me and my girlfriend Darcy
have gone to Utah
to get married.
FYI: she’s pregnant."
(chuckling):
Oh.
Simpson men get the job done.
(groans)
It’s a tragedy,
a real tragedy.
I mean, what kind of tramp
gets knocked up
before she’s even married?
I did.
I mean in this day and age,
when the link between sex
and pregnancy has been proven
so... conclusively...
in Scientific American,
where...
Okay, we can trace
where the kids are
by the charges
they made on your card.
In Colorado, they charged
$200 worth of bubble gum.
Actually,
that was me.
"Dingle’s Berries"
in Provo, Utah?
Why would I go to Utah?
I love booze,
caffeine and monogamy.
Then that must be it.
Our daughter says she’s
run off with your son.
Did she mention
she was knocked up?
-No!
-Oops! Sorry for the spoiler.
So how many brides will you
be marrying today, Mr. Simpson?
Just one.
(scoffs):
What are you, gay?
Stop the wedding!
Bart, you’re too young
to get married.
You still make me check
the closet for the boogeyman.
Well, maybe I found
someone else to do it for me.
Someone who will do
a more thorough job.
I don’t care
how young he is,
he took advantage of a girl
five years older than him.
Utah karate!
(intense drum music)
(grunts)
(groans)
Dad, lay off
the Bartman.
He’s not the father.
I just wanted to marry him,
so you and Mom
wouldn’t be ashamed of me.
Ashamed?
I’m thrilled...
because I’m gonna
have a baby, too!
CROWD:
Aw...
We can lie to the neighbors
and tell them they’re twins.
Awesome idea, Dad.
I guess this is
the end for us, Bart.
Thanks for everything.
Darcy, in 50 years,
you might see me
walking down the street
and you’ll wonder,
"Is that Bart?"
And I’ll go...
(armpit farts)
and you’ll know.
BOTH: (giggling)
You know,
I thought Darcy and I
would be like
a real married couple.
Instead we just ended up
fighting all the time.
Uh yeah, how ’bout that?
You know, for a while,
I was kind of looking
forward to being a dad.
Son, one day you’re going
to be a great father.
Aw...
And someday
you’ll be one, too.
Thanks, boy.
(chuckles jovially)
Hey, for old time’s sake,
you want to drive me around
while I sing public domain songs
out the window?
You got it.
♪ Twinkle, twinkle ♪
♪ Little star ♪
♪ How I wonder what you are ♪
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
♪♪
Shh!
Enhanced by Fotokem