CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(panting, gunfire, yelps)
(exclaiming)
(school bell ringing)
(Barney belches)
(whistle blows)
(yells)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
D'oh!
(tires screeching)
(grunts)
♪ The Szyslaks ♪
Already cancelled.
(sighs)
♪♪
Everything I know about women
can be summed up by a jump-rope rhyme:
"Girls go to Mars to buy candy bars,
boys go to Jupiter to get more stupider."
Except I didn't have to go
to Jupiter to get stupider.
(clears throat) I had a bigger ball
of gas I could study.
FEMALE GPS: In three-tenths
of a mile, make a right turn.
Homer, listen to the GPS.
-GPS: Turn right...
-Homer, watch the road!
-onto First Street, head east.
-Not this road, the other road!
Ladies, please!
You can boss me around,
just one at a time!
-On Main Street, turn right now...
-Our Sunday drive is ruined!
Hands at ten and two!
MARGE: What are you doing?
It said turn left, not right.
(screaming)
-BART: Huh?
-HOMER: Huh?
-Hmm.
-What the...?
GPS: Switching to male voice...
MALE GPS: ...so you will obey.
Finally! A supervisor!
Oh...
So the closest thing I had
to an adult male role model
were the schoolyard bullies.
Hey, Simpson!
I dare you to stick this caterpillar
down that girl's dress.
Can't I just stick it
in Skinner's sloppy joe?
It would actually be
the only meat in said joe.
Not everything can be solved
with Skinner pranks, Bart.
Yeah, think outside the Skinner box.
(laughing)
Hey, look,
that movie we were in
got short-listed for an Oscar.
-KEARNEY: Awesome!
-(gasps, bullies laugh)
Who's that stickin'
a fuzzy-wuzzy down my back?
Mary Spuckler!
♪ Lady ♪
♪ I'm your knight in shining armor ♪
♪ And I love you ♪
I thought you left home to be a star.
There's a lot of 13-year-olds out there
with a voice and a dream.
I only got work as a hand model.
Whoa.
That's your hand?
Just the thumb. Did you miss me?
(moaning)
Get out of my face, cootie breath!
I did miss you.
You stink! Come over Saturday.
I'm gonna have to push you
in the mud now.
Don't you pig-waller me, mister!
Do what you must, darlin'.
-(grunts)
-(laughing)
That sure makes up for my dad
beating me last night.
And for my dyslexia.
(bullies laughing)
(doorbell rings)
(yawns)
Mary?
(shrieks)
Thank God I wore the underwear
with the hole on the side.
(humming)
It's 8:00 in the morning.
I'm a farm girl.
I already milked the cows,
overcame a bout of prairie madness,
and made you some sausage and biscuits.
Rain is so romantic, don't you think?
You get the picture.
Perfect girl.
(imitating Woody Allen)
So, like a schmuck,
I treat her like day-old matzo.
(coughs)
(ominous music plays
on video game, gunfire)
(screams)
BART: Doctors Without Borders,
you're now doctors without faces!
(monkeys hooting)
(laughs)
Bart, when are we gonna do girl things,
like catch a frog or leg wrastle?
Soon, baby, soon.
Let me just kill Milhouse's character.
He thinks we're on the same team.
MILHOUSE: Betrayed again!
Mary, could I steal Bart for a minute?
Ask his girlfriend, the game.
Oh, Mary, you know you're the coolest
person I've ever hung out with.
MILHOUSE: Another betrayal!
Bart Simpson, I don't know what
the future holds for you...
If you're lucky, me, then this.
...but, Bart, I do know this:
you will not do better
than Mary Spuckler,
so don't ignore her
for a stupid video game!
Hey, relax.
She knows she's the apple
of the corner of my eye.
-Bart, do you mind if I call my mother?
-Not at all.
Mama! Come pick me up, I'm bored!
BRANDINE: You'll have to wait!
The mule's takin' a nap!
We hope it's a nap.
(video game gunfire)
-(clanging)
-Dinnertime!
♪♪
Now, let's enjoy the granola bars
that city fella gave us
in exchange for lettin' him go.
That'll teach him to try to preserve
our folk singing for posterity.
(scatting)
Just wait till my dad hears this
at 3:00 a.m. on NPR.
It'll prove I'm not wasting my life.
You realize you just ruined the recording.
(scatting continues)
A lot of musical talent in this house.
But no one blows
on a blade of grass like you.
(playing "Flight of the Bumblebee")
Eight more payments and I own this.
But are you sure there ain't no video game
you'd rather be playin'?
All eyes on you, baby.
Well, tell your eye-ears
to watch-listen to this!
♪ I used to think I wanted to roam ♪
♪ But there ain't not never no place ♪
♪ None better than home ♪
Count the negatives, it all works out.
♪ They say that home
is where the heart is ♪
♪ But for me it's where the Bart is... ♪
Now what are you doing?
(piglets squealing)
I wrote a whole song
for you, Bart Simpson.
Least you could do is pay me full mind.
I was gonna enter it in a competition.
Ay, caramba!
Well, you're gonna win,
'cause you've got star quality.
Like the Hulk in movies
other than The Hulk.
You know what?
Every now and then
you say the perfect thing.
(knocking on door)
Mary, it's our turn
to use the boyfriend room.
Y'all don't have boyfriends.
We's gonna practice kissing
with this French-Canadian
mountain man.
Pourquoi m'avez-vous amené ici?
He's still wearing leg shackles.
All men is unpolished stones.
Ou est le whisky que vous m'avez promis?
And then I ran right home to you.
You did everything great, Bart.
Then you told me all about it
like a true gentleman.
I can't wait to use your moves on Lisa.
Ew! On every level, ew!
Bart, you have to treat girls
like they matter,
not like they're a bunch of Milhice.
What? It's the plural of Milhouse.
Look it up.
Listen to your sister, boy.
What I'm saying
applies to you, too, Dad.
What are you talkin' about?
Marge and I are goin' great.
Homer Simpson!
Did you take Maggie to Moe's?
It was during Happy Hour.
Don't you want our baby to be happy?
Don't you see?
You're taking women for granted.
And aside from being lumped
together and generalized about,
it's the one thing all women hate.
(scoffs) How can something
that applies to Bart apply to me?
I'm so much older and wiser.
More like balder and wider.
Why you little... I'll teach you
to say something that sounds similar!
♪♪
-(applauding)
-Thank you, last contestant.
Tomorrow we will feature
the no-longer racist country comedy
of Barry the Satellite TV Guy.
Isn't it funny how all people
are of equal worth?
Please do not boycott
my line of power tools.
(laughs)
Now all Barry's jokes
are about his ex-wife.
No, they ain't. We're back together.
Then you got no act.
(chuckles)
And now, the winner is...
(drumroll)
Devon Peacock!
I can finally get my suspender buckled!
(cheering)
Looks like we got a feud
with the Peacocks now.
Uh-huh.
All I care is what you think, Bart.
(whispers) Compliment her.
BART:
I don't know what she wants.
What would my heroes say?
Slash her face now, Bart.
Slash it while she least expects it.
Bart, tell Mary to play the drums...
the only thing anyone
listens to in any band.
It's hard to pick just one of those.
Bart, you'd better get your act together.
And me, too.
I've gotta get these shirts
to the dry cleaners.
They close at 6:00.
Bart Simpson, you get out of that
gosh-darned fugue state this instant.
Lift my spirits!
Um... lifting people's spirits
is an interesting topic.
For centuries, Neanderthal
and astronaut alike
have enjoyed lifting spirits.
You're givin' me book report talk.
Excuse me, I am
a Brazilian record producer.
I concentrate in the rapidly-growing
jug band-samba fusion market.
Oh, my God! Do you know
Billy-Bobaloo Skeeter-Rodriguez?
Know him? Before he was famous,
he kidnapped my mother!
Mary, would you like
to have dinner with me
and my handsome, girl-crazy son tonight?
I am the first boy
to get my own liquor ad.
(Latin guitar music plays)
Bart, you want to come with us?
I need you.
Mary, we've just been through
three hours of music.
Usually, I only have music
one hour a week,
and the teacher spends it reading
real estate listings for Fire Island.
I'll see you later, Bart.
Mary, are you okay?
Sure. Everything's fine.
At that moment, I had a vision
of every time in my life
an angry woman would say
"Everything's fine."
I guess it's just me and the dog.
(groans)
Everything's fine.
Now.
(whistling)
Melvis? Where's Mary?
I brung you regrets from my sister.
She has been de-avoidably untained.
(groans) Am I getting dumped?
Okay, Bart, maybe you blew it
by taking Mary for granted.
Woman are life's great mystery, along with
why do they give you salt and
pepper at a Chinese restaurant?
But if you want one more shot,
I know a date that will turn
this mighty Aphrodite
into your purple rose of Cairo.
Those are movies I made.
It's my oeuvre.
It sounds dirty, but it's not.
(speaking in French)
(snoring)
Everyone's fast asleep.
It's like my second wedding night,
except more walkouts
and there were no refunds.
Gee...
(couples moaning)
Can I see you tomorrow night?
Sure, I'll be here
with my other boyfriend.
He's watching us now.
BOY: Oh, boy.
Okay, Luann, it's all settled.
We're gonna ditch Milhouse.
Bart, I think it's best
if we take a break.
Good idea, I can chuck
eggs at the other couples.
Just hug me, dummy.
Back pats?
This is a breakup.
You'll be fine.
There's a pot for every possum.
Give me another chance.
I'll be way more attentive
to your needs on the seesaw.
I'll stay down there
for as long as you want.
Sorry, Bart, I'm a hillbilly girl of 13.
If I'm not married
in the next few months,
nobody's gonna want me.
Not even old Joe Clabby.
Hey, you're a pretty
little thing, you are,
but ticktock, ticktock.
Good-bye, Bart.
Aw, sweetie.
I told you this would happen
if you dated outside the family.
Mm-mm-mm.
-(groans)
-Move along, relationship's over.
(groans)
Sure do like forcing
people to leave areas.
Yeah.
MARGE:
I was the only one without a date
at Patty's new lady friend's
travel bookstore soft opening.
You told me it was up to me
if I wanted to go.
You should know that me saying
I don't care
means I couldn't care more.
I am sick and tired of trying
to decode you like you're some
kind of human being separate from myself.
Bart, would you go to your room
while your father and I
finish our little talk?
Little talk?
You guys are having a big fight.
This is the problem with women--
they don't say
what they mean until it's too late!
All right, fine.
If you boys want it,
I'll tell you what I really think.
Finally, we're getting somewhere.
You're both in the doghouse,
which is misleading
'cause I still like the dog.
(sighs)
Hand me my suitcase, boy.
When do I get a Krusty suitcase?
When you're older.
So this is where you go
when Mom kicks you out?
You're saying it
like it happens all the time.
And by the way,
the paint's a little faded
on my parking spot.
You call this a platinum club experience?
We'll get right on it, Mr. Simpson.
I told you a thousand times,
call me Homer!
Oh, what's this notice on the wall?
Standard hotel boilerplate.
It just says somebody died
in this room in the last 72 hours.
Aw, man, we just missed it.
(laughs) Oh, it'll happen again, son.
Um, I've got to make a phone call.
Eh, knock yourself out.
D'oh!
Not again.
(touch tones beeping)
Mary? Ooh, that's odd.
I thought I was calling
the Suicide Not Line,
because I'm doing great.
So, um, how are you
handling taking a break?
Great. Turns out Adele was right.
Ain't nothing better for songwriting
than when your relationship
takes a bolt to the brain.
Tell me what you think.
♪ I broke up with a fella ♪
(samba rhythm plays)
♪ But I ain't grieving ♪
♪ He was much too proud ♪
♪ Of underachieving ♪
♪ I can't believe I liked him ♪
♪ I must have been blind ♪
♪ He wasn't so smart or handsome ♪
♪ Or kind ♪
♪ Every moment with that boy ♪
♪ Was totally horrid ♪
♪ And I can't even tell where
his hair meets his forehead ♪
Why did I buy her that rhyming dictionary?
♪ My eyes are wide open ♪
♪ Now I see his warts ♪
♪ I wish him well, down in hell ♪
♪ Where he'll eat his own shorts ♪
It just poured out of me
like venom from a snake.
(groans)
I had this idea years ago,
but your mother wouldn't let me do it.
shows how much she... (muffled yelling)
It's hurting my eyes!
(gasps)
It's so great here--
no wife to get mad at you
for closing your laptop whenever
they walk into the room.
Or getting your kid hooked on pot.
She's my kid, too, you know.
You know what we need?
A classic "kicked out of the house" party.
Now, who's got a rocking CD?
I've got the audio book
of Robert Caro's The Passage of Power.
That's it?
Well, then let's "power" this party up.
ROBERT CARO (on tape):
Air Force One,
the president's plane, is divided behind
the crew's cockpit
into three compartments.
In the first of them,
just behind the cockpit,
women sat weeping
and Secret Service agents
were trying to hold back tears.
"You've heard of strong men crying?
Well, we had it there that day,"
recalls a reporter.
As the pilot lifted the big jet
off the Dallas runway,
in a climb so steep that to a man...
I miss Mary.
I miss Roxie.
That's the club where I used
to smoke pot with my kid.
This calls for decisive action.
Like LBJ's use of the period
of mourning following
the assassination
to push through the Civil Rights Act.
But how do we figure out what to do?
The same way Hollywood does.
By watching British movies.
(people clamoring on video)
-(gavel bangs)
-The Prime Minister,
that is to say, I, would like
to make an emergency declaration
of love to my poor but cheeky secretary.
What, me? Eliza Commonbottom?
I... that is to say...
Flibberty-gibberty.
-♪ Ah ♪
-(Parliament cheering)
-♪ All the young dudes ♪
-♪ Hey, dudes ♪
-♪ Carry the news ♪
-♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ Boogaloo dudes... ♪
Love is more powerful than all my magic.
Hard to believe that country used
to rule anything.
Agreed, but to win back our women,
we need to make
a grand romantic gesture.
OTHERS: Hear, hear.
After we finish watching the movie.
♪ Carry the news ♪
♪ All the young dudes ♪
♪ Let's hear the news, come on ♪
Hmm, cursive.
"You are invited to
a grand gesture"?
Ooh.
(orchestra playing "Ode to Joy")
♪ I wrote this song to say I'm sorry ♪
♪ Dad, don't be a credit hog ♪
♪ The melody is by Beethoven ♪
♪ Not bad for a movie dog ♪
♪ I'll stop eating from the garbage ♪
♪ Marge, you will get the last pork chop ♪
Oh...
(all giggling, cooing)
A completed chore list.
And I promise to do the things
I checked off within a year.
(swooning sigh)
♪ Spuckler Mary, please forgive me ♪
♪ All I ask is one more chance ♪
Bart, you're a good duck,
but we wouldn't last.
But I'm the main guy in this story.
Things are supposed to work out for me.
Everyone is the main guy
in their own story.
My friend, welcome to my story.
♪♪
And that's when I learned
Cupid was just a fat, naked jerk
with an arrow.
But surely you didn't give up
on love after just one setback?
Love is our only defense
against the abyss
in this meaningless universe.
Love-- what is it?
What does it mean? How do you spell it?
No one knows.
Fortunately there is a cure.
Any video game ever made.
FEMALE COMPUTER VOICE: Remember,
this game is for age 14 or under.
If you are older than that,
please get help.
Get help, get help.
Married?
(groans)
(gasps)
MALE COMPUTER VOICE:
One message received from...
The widow Mary Spuckler.
Whoo-hoo!
Well done, Bart.
You played that like a combination
of Willie Mays and Paul Cézanne.
Who are you?
I... you know, I-I played the ant
in Antz, the lesser known
of the ant movies.
Oh, yeah.
(Brandine and Cletus scatting)
Subtitled by A. Vandelay