-(laughs)
-CHOIR: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(theme music playing)
(exclaims)
(school bell ringing)
(Barney belches)
-(whistle blows)
-(yells)
♪ ♪
(playing melodic harp)
D'oh!
-(tires screech)
-(grunts)
(wind whistling)
-(tires screech)
-(Milhouse grunting)
(bird squawks)
(Selma and Patty grunt)
Ow.
(squawking)
(Homer yelling, grunting)
(playing the blues)
-(wind gusts)
-(explosion)
-Hola.
-(duck quacks)
♪ Simpsons Time ♪
-♪ Run, don't walk ♪
-(sniffing)
♪ You might even hear ♪
♪ Maggie talk ♪
♪ Bart the Boy and a dog named Homer ♪
♪ And jokes written on signs ♪
-♪ It's Simpsons Time ♪
-Yay!
(Homer grunts, yells)
What a beautiful day for a family stroll.
Tell that to my aching back!
(groans)
It's not a family stroll--
Homer forgot where he parked
his car last night,
and now we have to find it.
What a beautiful day to be in denial.
Yeah, Bart. Who cares?
The sun is shining, birds are singing...
people are staring up
at the sky in terror?
(Simpsons shriek)
Do you see it, Lisa?
There's... nothing... there.
And that's where Lard Lad used to be!
Oh, looks like we better file a report
with the Bureau of Missing Statues.
Yeah. Be like that time
that Rodin statue got stolen.
What was the name
of that statue again? Eh...
Ah, let me think. Um...
Thinkin'. Yeah, still thinkin'.
Still thinkin'.
Uh, either we can fan out and search,
or bunch up and riot.
Oh, balderdash and poppycock.
I say we do not riot.
-ALL: Riot!
-ALL: Don't!
-Riot!
-Don't!
Riot!
(all yelling)
(indistinct chatter)
(grunts)
And thanks to the equal number
of non-rioters,
the total cost of the damage
is zero dollars.
-Homer, were you in that riot?
-Marge, please.
I'm a leader in this community.
BROCKMAN:
In response to the outcry...
-(alarm ringing)
-...Lard Lad's parent company,
Tianjin Mining
and Smelting and Donuts,
has issued the following statement--
"We are rebranding Lard Lad
with an updated statue."
Ooh, rebranding.
That just means admitting failure, Dad.
Ooh, admitting failure.
People of Springfield,
please welcome Mr.--
I know I'm gonna mangle this--
Lee Fong.
Uh, actually,
it's pronounced Robert Chan.
(moans)
And now, please welcome the model
for the original Lard Lad,
Mr. Laird Lad.
A lot of crazy names today.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I give you Lard Lad's bold,
focus-grouped, new look!
(mechanical whirring)
(statue squeaking)
That doesn't say donuts!
That says management overthink!
The Thinker!
That statue's called The Thinker.
(laughs) What?
What are we on now? What?
People,
let's give the new statue a chance.
When the Eiffel Tower was first built,
many said it was a steel monstrosity.
It still is.
Fine, but maybe this will grow on you.
-Aw, this thing sucks.
-I don't think so.
(overlapping disapproval)
-Well, at-at-at a certain angle...
-It's beautiful.
-We love it.
-That's beautiful.
(all cheer)
(wind whistling)
♪ ♪
You fools! You've erected a massive
concave reflective surface.
It will focus the sun's beam
in a deadly ray.
(people scream)
(growls)
(cheering)
(all groan)
(all gasp)
-Oh.
-Uh.
Hey!
(groans)
(gun hammer clicks)
QUIMBY: First off,
I'd like to thank the good people
at Tianjin Smelting and Mining
and Donuts and Tarps
for neutralizing our wonderful,
deadly, new Lard Lad.
Yeah, that's great.
They'll grow back.
The time for mourning
and blaming our mayors has passed.
We will rebuild.
ALL: We will rebuild.
We will rebuild!
(strained) We will rebuild.
We will rebuild.
I guess there's only one man
we can turn to.
Supergirl?!
(ominous organ music plays)
So... you'd like me to save the town.
Well, you've got gumption,
I'll give you that.
(laughing)
And such an adorable baby,
it really restores my...
my faith in... in the, uh...
Smithers,
where is the damn trapdoor button?
Mr. Burns,
you already trap-doored us
from your upstairs office.
(laughs) Yes.
And how was your fall?
Painful? Unexpected?
-Oh, yeah.
-Worst I've ever had.
-Oh! Really...
-Really...
-Pulled something.
-Totally painful. Did not see it coming.
(chuckles) Excellent.
So... remind me
what I was saying no to.
Funding repairs to the town.
But if you could do
even one little project.
Re-ducking the duck pond
or fixing up the Springfield Bowl.
The Springfield Bowl.
Very well.
I will rebuild this town
on one condition.
Forget it.
Our desperate plea is nonnegotiable.
I want to put on
a variety show at the Bowl.
A celebration of everything
wonderful about... um,
-what's the name of this town again?
-Springfield, sir.
Yes, I will destroy Springfield.
-Celebrate, sir.
-Fine, we'll try it your way first.
Springfield has risen
from the ashes like a phoenix.
That's phoenix, the mythical bird,
not Phoenix, the cultureless,
Mars-scape of the Southwest.
(chuckles)
Our unlikely angel, the Devil himself,
C. Montgomery Burns.
Thank you, Kent. (groans)
And don't forget the open auditions
for my Springfield Follies.
This year women may audition, too,
with permission of husband,
father, and pastor in writing.
BURNS: Next.
(cat yowls)
-(gentle melody plays on piano)
-(clears throat, coughs)
(beautiful soprano voice)
♪ Un bel di ♪
♪ Vedremo ♪
♪ Levarsi un fil ♪
♪ Di fumo... ♪
Puccini's a little well-trod,
don't you think?
(yells incoherently)
This isn't right.
This isn't how it was at all.
I remember that night so vividly.
Monty, time to go on stage.
Yes, Mama.
Your little butterscotch drop
won't let you down.
Aw, who's candy? You's candy.
Oh, I'm gonna lick you,
my sweet little lolly.
Who likes Mommy's licks?
Monty likes Mommy's licks.
Lickity, lickity, lick.
-(laughing)
-Oh, oh, oh.
-(giggling)
-Oh, ho, ho, ho.
Oh. Oh, ho, ho.
But the butterscotch
soon turned to bitter squelch.
I want everything
just as it was back then.
The stage filled with children
like those from 1913.
High-spirited, snaggletoothed,
and willing to work 18 hours a day.
SKINNER (over P.A.): Attention.
An old man is prowling the school,
looking for young children.
Please, perform for him.
Watch me make this nerd disappear.
(grunts) Ta-da!
Also, haw haw!
Excellent villain.
And my cast is complete.
I'll just save the list and...
(groans)
Samson himself
could not pry open these jaws.
Can I help you, sir?
Oh, women aren't meant for clasp opening.
Young lady, if there's one thing I know
about show business,
it's that there are a lot of clipboards.
How would you like to be
my assistant director?
Hmm.
(thinking) And
I'll be perfectly positioned
to find out exactly
what Mr. Burns is really up to.
I'm in.
And if you need another act,
I also play this.
There's no room in my show for
Adolphe Sax's vile-sounding o-phone.
Do you ever say anything in a simple way?
-Shut up.
-Well, that was clear.
(bird caws)
Hey, Homer, are you sure we haven't let
the plant slip with Mr. Burns gone?
Smitty, as a wise, old man once said,
"Out with the old...
and in with the brew."
♪ ♪
(slurps)
(indistinct chatter)
(alarm blaring)
(alarm stops)
♪ ♪
(hums)
(vocalizing)
-That's enough.
-But I haven't started my act.
-Muntz, what have you got?
-A rabbit in a bag.
Ooh, a promising magic trick.
No, it's my lunch.
Bah! You're all incompetent.
I won't go through this a second time.
"Second time"?
Is there something you're not telling us?
A vast amount.
And what part of
"What I've never told you"
don't you understand?
♪ ♪
(laughter)
Mother, what is that sound
they're making?
Well, it's called laughter.
You're a laughingstock, Charles.
(whimpering) Oh, oh, it's awful.
This show isn't good enough.
No show could be good enough.
(muffled) It's not?
(bird chirping)
(liquid pouring)
(cheerful scatting)
-What are you doing?
-Da-da-do-doo!
Getting ready for Monday.
I'm gonna fill a Super Soaker
full of lemonade,
Carl's gonna fill one with iced tea,
and we're gonna Arnold Palmer
Lenny when he walks in.
(laughing)
Arnold Palmer Lenny.
You're going to Arnold Palmer Lenny.
Yeah, you see,
Arnold Palmer was a golfer,
and he made up this drink
where it's not a full glass of lemonade
or a full glass of iced tea.
Instead...
Homie, I'm worried about
all this silliness at work.
You're the safety inspector.
I'm "a" safety inspector. Not "the."
I've never seen another.
What-- Wait, one safety inspector?
For the whole nuclear plant?
That's insane.
(giggles)
Put everything in the car
and get out of town.
I'll find you if there are still roads!
Sweetie, sweetie,
all you've got to do is be responsible.
Your friends consider you the leader
because you're a little taller.
Hmm. Wow.
Wow!
With above-average height
comes above-average responsibility.
Marge, thank you for setting me straight.
You're welcome.
Okay, I want to open this show
with someone being shot into a cannon.
(laughs)
You're joking, right?
Well, because, see, that's impossible.
(chuckles nervously)
(audience laughing)
(sputters)
Gah! Oh.
Everyone,
Little Miss Nitpick hates the show,
so I'm shutting it down.
("Sabre Dance"
by Aram Khachaturian plays)
This was an act.
Now it's just bullying.
(lights shatter)
(bellows)
Thanks a lot, Lisa.
We were getting out of school for this.
(shoes tapping)
(doorbell rings)
Well, if it isn't the little girl
that made a billionaire cry.
-May I please speak with Mr. Burns?
-No, he's very busy.
Won't you please come back
and do the show?
Shan't.
(bike bell ringing)
Oh, that bell has quite the recoil.
-(bell continues ringing)
-Oh, what is bothering him?
And what were those weird lines
around his eyes?
I know.
It's such a tragedy
on that beautiful face.
Come here.
Well, there's only one explanation
for those lines, Lisa.
He's been watching something
on the Mutoscope.
So, if I play this,
I'll know the answer.
Mm-hmm. It, uh, costs a nickel.
(coin drops into slot)
(film winding and sputtering)
(Lisa gasps)
(film continues sputtering)
So this is what made Mr. Burns
the monster he is.
(giggles)
Within days, half of America
was cranking to my bottom.
I think you're trying to make up
for what happened to you then
by putting on a perfect Bowl show now.
(scoffs)
Spare me you amateur psychology.
"Ooh, I saw my father decapitated
by a grain harvester,
and now I can't enjoy wheat. Boohoo."
Mr. Burns,
I want you to listen to that crowd.
(film winding and sputtering)
Do you really want to let those happy,
joyous people win?
(film continues winding and sputtering)
Smithers, locate my dickey.
We've got a show to do.
♪ I was gonna clean my room ♪
-(laughter and cheering)
-♪ Until I got high ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh ♪
♪ I was gonna get up
and find the broom ♪
-(phone rings, record scratches)
-♪ But then... ♪
Springfield Nuclear.
Yes. Yes, sir, I'll alert the workers...
that the pizzas are here!
(cheering, party music playing)
Oh, yeah, here he comes.
The life of this party!
Who wants to get back to work?
-(record scratches, music stops)
-MAN: What?
(balloons squeak)
We are a public trust.
We bring power to people's homes.
Lightbulbs, toasters,
and that's all I can think of.
Now let's buckle down!
Okay, Homer, just let us get
our microwave popcorn out of the core.
You're only supposed to do that when
we're watching a movie in the core.
(crickets chirping)
(indistinct conversations)
(ragtime piano music playing)
(cheering and whooping)
Thank you, thank you.
Well, that's the easiest time anyone's
had parking at the Springfield Bowl.
(laughter)
-Don't you laugh at me!
-(laughter dies down)
Now, enjoy the show.
God always liked you best.
No, God loves everyone equally.
That's wonderful news.
(chuckles)
Enough of your tomfoolery, Todd.
Let's sing.
BOTH: ♪ Michael, row your boat ashore ♪
♪ Hallelujah ♪
♪ Michael, row your boat ashore ♪
♪ Hallelu... ♪
Say, Sockie, who was that lady
I saw you with last night?
(high-pitched) That was no lady.
That was your mother.
(normal voice) Oh, she'll date anyone.
Why won't she give me a stable home?
(high-pitched) Haw haw!
(bells ringing melodically)
(bells stop, xylophone plays)
-(drumroll)
-(hatch creaks)
-(cymbal crash)
-(audience applauds)
Um, this is just a simple twins trick.
They pulled the other twin
out of the tank behind the curtain.
(applause)
-(fireworks exploding)
-(audience cheering and whooping)
Wait, that wasn't part of the show.
-(screaming)
-(alarm blaring)
No. No, it's not fair!
-I was good!
-Arnold.
-Palmer!
-(grunting)
(both laughing)
(sighs) Fantastic.
What a finale, eh, Mr. Burns?
Childhood trauma cured, huh, huh?
That wasn't the finale.
(audience laughing)
Maestro, "Golden Slippers,"
if you please.
Ooh, boy.
(shudders)
We can't let him
make a fool of himself again.
LISA:
No, no, Mr. Burns needs to do this.
♪ Oh, dem golden slippers ♪
♪ Oh, dem gold... ♪
(stammers)
Ow, the burn. Ooh!
Mr. Burns can't take the impact
of that many photons.
Those light-shining fools!
(muttering)
Ow! Ah!
(laughter)
Oh, for a murder of crows
to pluck out mine eyes!
You. This show was your fault.
Well, you'd better know this, mister.
This town has my back.
And... hey. Where did they go?
How did 15,000 people leave so fast?
Um... hey!
Want to see me do a cartwheel?
(chuckles nervously, then grunts)
(sighs)
Always had trouble with those.
Oh, I can't stay mad at you.
At my age,
I can't stay anything at anybody.
Oh, and you know what?
The laughter in my head is gone.
Go ahead, blow your German kazoo.
Yes, sir!
(playing "Golden Slippers")
Smithers, tap my foot for me.
With impatience.
Now, lift my arm
so I can check my watch.
Oh, you really should start doing
some of these things yourself.
♪ ♪
(slurps)
Dad, why do Simpsons always fail?
Oh, sweetie pie,
it's a terrible curse
that goes back centuries.
(knocking on door)
No, no! Don't answer that.
MAN: We just need a place
to stay for the night.
Oh, shouldn't we help them?
Hey, in Zero B.C.,
you can't trust anybody.
-Curse them, Mary!
-You curse them.
-My water just broke!
-Please?
You're telling me that really happened?
They looked just like us, didn't they?
(ragtime band playing)
Tha-tha-tha-tha-tha-that's all, folks!
-(crowd murmuring)
-Shh!
Subtitled by Jimmy Boots