CHORUS SINGS:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(Krusty laughing)
(exclaims)
(school bell ringing)
BARNEY:
Hello.
(whistle blows)
(yells)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
(grunts)
Hah!
-Ooh!
-(gunfire)
(tires screeching)
(horn honking, Grampa shouts)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
(tires screeching)
(grunts)
Draw me some beer.
♪♪
People of Springfield,
this town is in the worst
financial meltdown
we've ever seen.
No longer can we cook the books
and fudge the numbers.
Mmm. (drools)
This is serious.
Pay attention.
(giddy laughter)
Oh, yeah...
And so, it is with regret
I announce the following
cost-cutting measures:
eliminating
dead animal pickup...
(Krusty grunts)
...dramatic cutbacks
in our education budget...
Good morning, children.
Today, we are instituting
shortened school hours.
How shortened?
Take 'em home, Otto.
(children cheering)
...and we have released
all low-level criminals
from our prisons.
(snickers)
(gun cocks)
Spit the grapes back in
with the others.
Homie, slow down.
Why should I?
The city's broke.
They can't afford to enforce
their precious laws.
(horn honking)
(Homer laughing)
How fast
were they going, Lou?
I don't know, Chief.
We can't afford
a radar gun,
so we're just
using a thermos
on top of a hose handle.
Well, it's better
than my pistol.
Hey, hey, uh,
that Ralphie's
getting to be
a pretty fine artist.
I drew it.
-Hmm.
-Mm-hm.
Another Springfield family
moves to Detroit
to find a better life.
Now that it's empty, who's
gonna buy their house?
What if someone moves
in with two Barts?
Or four teenage Barts?
(engines revving)
Eh, at least they're learning
their fractions.
(worried groan)
(sniffs) What's that
delicious smell?
Cookies!
(sniffs)
Mmm.
Stop that sniffing.
It's not for you.
They're making the house
next door smell like cookies
so people will subconsciously
want to buy it.
Oh, come on.
What kind of big, fat moron
would fall for...
(sniffs)
Cookies!
So delicious.
Must buy house.
Homer, no!
Marge, get loan
preapproved.
Offer over asking.
Waive inspections.
Two-day escrow!
Initial the radon disclosure.
And done.
Sorry. Someone else
has bought the house.
But my loan has already been
sold in pieces to banks,
hedge funds and municipalities
across the globe.
Death to Homer!
At least we'll
always have Beowulf.
That's not us.
Oh, no!
A credenza?
Credenza?
Lowboy? Sideboard?
Portmanteau?
Mom, it's so superficial
to judge
our new neighbor
based on his furniture.
(gasps)
He drives a hybrid!
LISA:
He's got koi!
(sighs happily)
And where there's
exotic fish,
there's got
to be a...
BOTH:
Water feature.
Dames. (groans)
Well, I'm gonna go introduce
myself Bart Simpson-style.
(hawks and spits)
Yo. Bart Simpson.
No doubt you
read about me
in your nuisance
neighbor disclosure.
SIDESHOW BOB VOICE:
Hello, Bart.
Huh? Say that again.
Hello, Bart!
Hello, Bart.
Hello, BART.
(screams)
Sideshow Bob!
Side what whom?
(screaming)
(hammering)
Man, you're good with
the tools when you
want to be.
Why on earth
do you think
that harmless-looking man
is Sideshow Bob?
BART:
I know he doesn't
look like him,
but I'll never forget
that voice.
A lot of people sound
like Sideshow Bob.
Like Frasier on Cheers.
Or Frasier on Frasier.
Or Lieutenant Commander
Tom Dodge in Down Periscope.
Look, I'm telling you,
no matter who he says he is,
he's really Sideshow Bob.
Honey, his name
is Walt Warren,
and he's a very nice man.
He stopped me from driving away
with my coffee cup
on top of the car.
Ah.
Really? Hmm.
Maybe I...
(screams) Sideshow Bob!
(sighs)
(chuckles)
Stupid kid,
fooled by a silhouette.
(gasps) Ooh.
Eh... (gasps)
Ice cream?
Oh, nothing is ever boobs
or ice cream.
I'll prove
I'm not crazy.
Sideshow Bob could never
resist singing along
to a Gilbert and
Sullivan operetta.
Who am I again?
Yum Yum.
I'm Peep-bo.
Mom, Dad, I got the lead!
And a one,
and a two, and a...
♪ Three little maids
from school are we ♪
♪ Pert as a schoolgirl,
well can be ♪
♪ Filled to the brim
with a girlish glee ♪
♪ Three little maids
from school. ♪
Uh-oh, Bart.
Who will sing
the next verse?
We need a third maid.
Maybe someone
will step in and help.
♪ One little maid
is a bride, Yum Yum ♪
♪ Two little maids
in attendance come ♪
♪ Three little maids ♪
♪ Three little maids... ♪
Sorry, gentlemen.
I'm not a fan of that
particular style of music.
My radio dial never strays
from 89.4 "The Spur."
It is a good
station, Bart,
what with the
Morning Cattle Drive
and Armadillo Mike
in the afternoon.
And nothing
keeps me informed
like Rodeo Rick's
News Roundup,
every hour on the...
Shut up.
I just want to say, I've
not only found new neighbors,
but gained new friends.
And from now on, Wi-Fi
in this neighborhood is on me.
(all gasp)
Ooh, that book I ordered
is gonna be delayed.
(grunts)
All right, Walt Warren.
Let's see who you really are.
Harmless World,
Mild Manners,
Not Mad Magazine,
Nap Fancy,
Calm, Comfortable,
a "Cuddly Puppies" calendar.
Aw, little guy can't get out
of the pumpkin.
(grumbles)
There must be something here.
Something, something, something.
-MARGE: Bart?
-(startled shout)
What are you doing?
You're indoors at
an outdoor party.
Walt is Sideshow Bob,
and I'm gonna prove it.
Look.
Who needs a knife this big?
It's probably a deboner.
(chuckles) Boner.
-Mom, I'm scared.
-(groans)
I can see there's only one way
to settle this once and for all.
Okay ma'am, Sideshow Bob's cell
is all the way
at the end.
Walk fast and don't call
attention to yourself.
Pretty lady in a strapless dress
coming through!
-Oh, yeah!
-Come here, woman!
If you were my wife,
I never would've killed you!
Thank you.
You're very sweet.
Nothing is holding up
the dress!
Only her melons!
And here we are.
Sideshow Bob.
(gasps)
(grunts)
I can't see.
Oh, here you go.
Huh?
BART: That is Bob.
Guess I was wrong.
(gibbering)
We better go.
Pretty lady coming back!
Aw, yeah... yeah!
-Come here, baby.
-Walkin'...
Guys, guys, I'm married.
-You are?
-So sorry.
(gagging)
(gasps)
(electrical buzzing)
(siren wailing)
(dogs barking)
(snoring, muttering)
Great day to be alive.
Ah, the paper's here.
-Morning, Marge.
-(screams)
Hope I didn't interrupt
your petite dejeuner.
Look, I feel terrible
that Bart and I
got off on the
wrong foot,
and I have an extra ticket
to today's baseball game.
Bart, care to come?
They're playing
Spokane.
The Cascades?
They totally stole the
Federal Cup from us last year.
Can I go, Mom? Can I?
-Is your room clean?
-No.
Good. That'll give me
something to do
while you're at the game.
Marge, the bathroom
scale is lying again.
(screaming)
All right, buddy,
I'm gonna do to you
what you should have done
to my son a long time ago.
(high-pitched voice):
I'm not Sideshow Bob.
I'm the real Walt Warren.
But that's impossible.
If you're the
real Walt Warren,
who's taking our son to the
baseball game right now?
Uh, you missed the turn-off,
Mr. Warren.
You don't have to call
me Mr. Warren anymore.
You see, Bart,
you were right all along.
I am... Sideshow Bob.
-(screaming)
-(evil laughter)
And now I am free to sing
all the Gilbert and Sullivan
I damn well please.
♪ Behold the lord
high executioner ♪
♪ A personage of noble rank
and title... ♪
(humming tune)
Hmm...
Hmm...?
I'll prove I'm
telling the truth.
Bob has huge feet, right?
Well, look...
You see?
(all gasping)
It's like you're
a Chinese empress.
You see, I was Bob's cellmate.
My new cellmate, Walt Warren,
was the perfect
candidate for my plan.
He had the same build as me--
lacking only my regal
bearing and leonine grace.
As a minor offender, he was
scheduled for early release.
Say, Bob, why do you
keep measuring my face?
Just passing the time, bunky.
Well, I guess it beats
what the last guy did.
Well, nighty-night.
And nighty-night to you.
(grunts)
(thunder crashing)
SIDESHOW BOB:
I began by removing
Walt's face.
(blows)
Five-second rule.
That was the easy part.
The hard part was
removing my own face.
Luckily, as Krusty's sidekick,
I'd been hit with so many pies
that my face had lost
all sensation.
(screams in pain)
Or so I thought.
(screaming)
(thunder crashing)
The final reattachment
was a mere bagatelle.
Or so I thought.
(sighs)
They returned Walt's
possessions to me.
Keys, cell phone,
$143,000.
Oh!
It was only $27,000
when you came in,
but, uh, we invested it well.
-Would you like a commission?
-Not allowed.
And I walked out
free as a bird.
I bought the house next
to you, and here we are.
So I just have to kill
you, then sell the house.
Selling the house
will be murder.
You could just rent it
till the market recovers...
which'll be never.
(evil laughter)
Walt, why didn't you tell
your story to the guards?
Well, I tried to, but I had
trouble moving my new lips.
They heard me babbling,
thought I was crazy,
and threw me into a padded cell.
I tried to warn you by writing
"Bart Simpson will die"
on the walls,
but you ignored me.
You have to admit,
"Bart Simpson Will Die"
was kind of open
to interpretation.
I'm not a writer.
And I'm not a locksmith.
Man, that dude
does not like Bart.
(gasps) I know where
Bob's taking Bart.
(muffled yelling)
Another cup of
coffee, handsome?
It's on the house.
Well, that's kind of you, Joyce,
but caffeine makes me jittery,
and I have a task ahead of me
which requires a firm hand.
Ooh, I like a man
with a firm hand.
Hey, looks like you've got a
loose thread on your collar.
No, don't.
(screams)
My face. My beautiful,
borrowed face.
Come back!
I don't care
if you don't have a face.
I just need something warm
to cuddle at night!
Excuse me.
Have you seen this man?
Yeah, I've seen him.
He, uh, said
he was driving down to Mexico.
Mexico?
Ándale! Ándale!
Arriba!
I don't believe her.
I think she fell in love
with my face,
and she's trying
to throw us off the scent.
Walt, it's a nice face,
but I don't think it would drive
a professional waitress to lie.
Well, fine. You go to Mexico.
I'm going to Five Corners.
Hey, handsome.
Is that a loose
thread on your collar?
(groaning)
All the good men are either gay
or have no face.
Welcome to the
Five Corners,
the only geographic
location in the U.S.
where five states meet,
and where
you will meet your doom.
Come on, Bob.
You don't need
to kill me.
I'll probably
kill myself pretty soon
with all
the stupid things I do.
Oh, no!
I swallowed my tongue!
(gagging)
Yes, I would
be a fool.
Unless I did it here,
where your murder
will be unprosecutable.
You know, the great ones
can kill without explaining.
I can stand in one state,
fire a gun in a second state.
The bullet will travel through
the third, hitting you
in the fourth
so you fall dead in the fifth.
No single act
is against any law.
But their sum total
is the greatest murder
since Snape killed Dumbledore.
Oh, I haven't gotten
to that part yet.
It's a four-year-old book.
I'm a slow reader.
A fitting epitaph.
(sighs)
It means last words.
Are you here
to teach me, or to kill me?
What in the name of Malcolm
Muggeridge are you doing?
Ruining your plan.
If you shoot me
while we're in the same state,
you go to jail.
(grunting
with each step)
Oh! (mutters)
Fine. I'll just shoot you,
and tell people I did the plan.
(grunts)
Not today, Bob.
See, Bob, even you
hate to see you.
Now Bob, you take my face off
nice and easy
and kick it over here.
Oh! There's a bee
under my cheek!
Hey! Hey, no!
Help us! Help us!
For the love of God,
won't somebody help us?
-Sí.
-Uh, yes,
I'd like... um...
-How do you say taco
in Mexican?
-Taco.
-Yes, that's exactly the word
I want to translate.
-Taco.
-Homer, can we please find Bart?
-Oh, yeah, yeah, right.
Uh, just give me one of those
crispy shells with meat in it.
-Taco?
-Oh!
Walt, because
I like your face,
I'll let you decide
which state I kill you in.
Okay, uh... Hawaii.
Choosing privilege revoked.
Hold it right there,
Switches of Eastface.
Switches
of Eastface?
I don't want
to censor myself.
That's how creativity dies.
Aah! Blasted Wiggum!
How did you find us?
You see, Bob, Bart was never
convinced you were Walt.
So before he left for the game,
he called us and warned us
to track you.
Which we were able to do
through the dashboard of
your car, which, like all
hybrids, is secretly monitored
by the government.
Bravo, Chief.
Or should I say, Clancy?
Yeah, thanks...
Wait a minute--
why so familiar?
Because I'm afraid you don't
have jurisdiction in this state.
(in Southern accent):
Welcome to my jurisdiction.
(with Minnesota accent):
You just, uh, go ahead
and put your hands
up there, mister.
(with New Jersey accent):
Oh. You got the right
to remain silent over here. Oh.
We're takin' you in.
But first, we're gonna make
a stop at the shore
for some Skee-Ball
and funnel cakes. Oh!
Oh, Bart, I am so glad
everything's okay.
Well, not
everything.
Apparently someone switched
your face with a butt.
(laughs)
(groans)
Well, whoever moves in,
it can't be worse than having
a murderer next door.
Howdilly-dowdilly,
next-door-oonies.
Howdy, Cousin Ted.
Howdy do to you, Cousin Ned.
How are Roddy and Toddy?
Flantastic times two.
How are Connie and Bonnie?
Dandy as candy,
like every good Flandy.
Glad to hear it,
thank the Holy Spirit.
Glad to say it, and now
the girls will "yay" it.
-GIRLS: Yay.
-Stop! Stop! Stop!
(chattering)
Shh!
Enhanced by Fotokem