CHORUS: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(theme music playing)
(bell ringing)
(whistle blowing)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
(honking horn)
(tires screeching)
D'oh! (screams)
Now, whose calculator can tell me what
seven times eight is?
Oh! Oh! Oh! Low battery?
(groans) Whatever.
Attention, children.
Uh, over here.
Oh, for the love of-- The doorway.
-KIDS: Oh!
-We have a very special visitor today.
But he's no ordinary visitor.
In fact, uh, you might say--
-He's a robot. We saw him on the way in.
-Thank you, Bart.
All right. Come in. They know.
Kids, this is Robby the Automaton.
Greetings, Earth children.
Where are you from?
Earth.
Anyway, have you ever wondered
what it feels like to touch a star?
-(screams)
-Cool!
Or which of the Three Stooges
had the heaviest brain?
Hmm. Larry-- Three point two kilograms.
Fascinating!
Ah.
The answers to these and similar questions
can be found at
the Springfield Knowledgeum...
a hands-on learning environment...
opening this Saturday.
-No, kid! Don't!
-(grunts)
-(screams)
-ROBBY: Command link severed.
Default setting. Crush. Kill. Destroy.
(gasping) D- Don't!
Children, help! He's killing me!
(cheering)
What a whimsical building.
Who says science can't be fun?
Me. I smell a museum.
Yeah, good things don't end with "eum."
They end with "mania" or "teria."
Will there be beer?
(over speakers) Welcome to
the Knowledgeum. I'm Troy McClure.
You may remember me from such automated
information kiosks
as "Welcome to Springfield Airport"
and "Where's Nordstrom?"
While you're enjoying
our Hall of Wonders...
your car will, unfortunately,
be subject to repeated break-ins-
What'd he say? What about my car?
ALL: Wow!
KIDS: (shouting) (grunting)
(shouting)
It says the ceiling was donated
by the Velcro company.
(gasping)
And the floor was donated
by American SuperBall.
Hey, I'm gonna go toss the Virtual Salad.
I want to read the Giant Book.
I'm gonna try the Sex
Education Computer. (gasps)
Come on, Maggie.
Let's try and find the Enormous Pendulum.
Whoa! Wait there!
(clears throat) The section now
illuminated is the floating point unit...
one of my personal favorite units.
-Oh, I see!
-(exclaiming)
Oh. Well. (chuckles)
How do you get this thing
to play blackjack?
Stop that. You're hurting it.
-So how's it supposed to work?
-Well--
-Boring! Am I on the Internet?
-No, you can only access the--
Boring! What's that fire for?
The hard drive is crashing
at an alarming speed!
No more pictures!
(grunting)
Ovulate, damn you. Ovulate!
(woman's voice) You are out of sperm.
(whimpers)
Hey, baby. Remember me?
Whoa! This whole planet
is like one big skate park!
Look out, Ralph! (screams) (grunts)
I found a moon rock in my nose.
(imitates static)
Houston, we have a booger.
Hey, loser, this planet's for space studs.
Yeah, blast off.
I know you. My daddy took your beer.
Whoa! The baby can talk.
I am not a baby.
-Tell it to The Ear, baby.
-(muffled talking)
(chuckling) Good one, guys.
-Simpson, go kiss the Virtual Ass.
-Yes, sir.
(whimpers, grunts)
-You poor little boy!
-Ah, no. He'll be fine.
He's always gettin' himself
stuffed into this or that.
(yipping, roaring)
-Is that normal?
-Yeah, he's just playing Wiggle Puppy.
That's a dog he made up
who flies by waggin' his tail.
I tell you, that dog has had
some amazing adventures.
Well, Ralph certainly has
a lot of imagination.
Ah, yeah, the kid's incredible.
I mean, the special schools
are all over him.
Maybe he needs some real friends.
Sure, we'd all love
some real friends, Marge...
but what are the odds of that happening?
-(panting)
-Hello, Ralph.
When I was little,
I used to play by myself too.
Your hair is tall and pretty.
Well, thank you, Ralph.
You're such a fine, young gentleman.
Help! She's touching my special area!
Then me and my friend
were about to press it,
but the man said not to press it.
But we pressed it anyway!
And we ran and we hid in the Giant Tire.
Oh, yeah. And my other friend
was already there.
All right. All right now.
You're overstimulated.
Let's get some beer in you,
and then it's right to bed.
Whoo-hoo! Beer, beer, beer! Bed, bed, bed!
Firecrackers, stink bombs,
maps to teachers' homes.
-You know who's nice?
-No. Who?
That Ralph Wiggum boy.
-He's a real winner.
-You would know.
Bart, you don't have to go anywhere today.
I've got a surprise for you.
-What?
-I scheduled a playdate.
(doorbell rings)
A what? With who?
-(gasps)
-Hi, Bart. We're gonna be friends.
I have a finger trap.
Whoa. Get him off. Get him off!
Fighting only makes it tighter.
(grunting)
You want me to hang out with Ralph Wiggum?
-Not hang out. Playdate!
-Stop saying that!
Now, why don't you show off
your new friend around the neighborhood?
You two make an adorable pair.
Someone will be right with you.
Mom, school has changed a lot
since you were a kid.
Popularity is very important now.
-But--
-Don't talk. Listen.
The social order of elementary
school is densely layered.
The coolest kids are at the top--
Oh, you mean like the "A" students?
Mom, I don't want to play with Ralph.
He's just a misunderstood
little boy who needs a friend.
And if he hangs around with you...
well, everyone will think he's cool.
Well, I don't know about that.
-Might help him a little.
-OK! Great!
-You kids have fun.
-Hey, wait! I didn't agree to-
(humming)
-(humming continues)
-Mom, I am not--
MARGE: I can't hear you! (humming)
(electronic whirring)
Your toys are fun to touch.
Mine are all sticky.
Ralph, I just got through sorting those.
I dropped my "Popsticle"
in your toy chest.
-Ralph, would you just--
-Look! A rocket ship!
That's not a toy!
Hey! Do you know how
to play hide-and-seek?
(gasps)
Shh! I been here two hours,
and Bart still hasn't finded me.
These syrup stains are the worst.
Bart, it's too nice a day
to leave Ralph in a closet.
You boys should go play outside.
But people will see me
paired up with a doofus.
You have no idea what that's like.
-Uh-oh.
-I'm going.
Slow down, Bart. My legs don't know
how to be as long as yours.
Well, that is your problem, Ralph.
This is how I always walk.
KIDS: (shouting) All right!
-Whoa!
-Check this out!
-Yeah!
-All right!
Videotaping this crime spree
is the best idea we ever had!
-Quick, Ralph. In the bushes.
-(grunts)
Whoo!
-Hi, guys. Hot enough for you?
-Shut up.
(shouting)
(sighs) That was too close.
We gotta stay off the streets.
Bushes are nice 'cause
they don't have prickers.
Unless they do. This one did. Ouch.
This is my swing set. This is my sandbox.
I'm not allowed to go in the deep end.
That's where I saw the leprechaun.
Right. A leprechaun.
He told me to burn things.
Uh-huh.
-Wanna play stuffed animal parade?
-Maybe later.
Come on, Ralph. Your dad's a cop.
There must be some cool stuff around here-
bullets, dead body photos, what have you.
He keeps that stuff in his closet,
but he says I'm not allowed in there.
-Did he say I'm not allowed in there?
-Yes.
Well, I'm goin' in anyway.
(grunts)
Oh, Lord, I thank you for this bounty
I'm about to receive.
Hmm.
(shuddering) Huh!
Wow! Dad's been in jail six times!
Aw, Mom's only been in twice.
-(door opens)
-Hello! Sarah! Ralphie!
-It's me, Chief Wiggum!
-Oh. We better hide.
-(grunting)
-(gasping)
Quick! In here!
(sighs) Oh! Man, we have got
to get an escalator.
(gasps) A 341 in my own bedroom.
All right, crookie. Let's dance.
(grunts) Oh! God, my back!
Oh! Officer down! Officer down!
-(grunting)
-Hi, Daddy.
Oh, oh. It's just you.
Well, help Daddy up.
(grunts)
You know you're not
supposed to go in there.
What is your fascination with
my forbidden closet of mystery?
Sorry, Chief. Um, we were just playing.
Ralphie, you got a friend?
Hey, that's fantastic!
Here, here. Have some riot gear.
It's on the house.
(both grunting)
(laughing)
Ah, that takes me back to the '60s.
What's that weird key for?
That's Daddy's magic key.
It opens every door in town.
The police master key?
Oh, Ralph.
Do you realize what we can do with--
(smacking, gulping) Get me a towel.
"Hi. This is Jerry Maguire.
Show me the message.
Show me the message!"
No, that stinks. Let me try one.
"This is Geraldine, and the devil made me
miss your call...
so here come the beep.
Here come the beep!" (chuckling)
"Do the message!" (humming)
So long. I'm gonna sleep over
at Ralph's.
Oh! See, I knew you'd find
something you liked about him.
Oh, I found something, all right.
(moans)
(humming continues)
-After the beep.
-(beeps)
Uh, Ralph's a little afraid
of the dark, Bart.
-Is it OK to sleep with a night-light?
-Absolutely.
Good night, guys.
-I'm scared.
-Ow!
MAN (on TV): We now return to
The Return of the Pink Panther Returns...
starring Ken Wahl as Inspector Clouseau.
(snores) Ow.
-Ow.
-RALPH: (whimpers)
(snoring)
Ooh.
Son of a-- (snoring)
The world is our toy store.
Toy store, toy store, toy store! Whee!
Oh, to be eight again.
Whee!
-Whoa! Whoa!
-Whee! Whee!
(laughing) Whoa! (both grunt)
Ah, I can't believe
we ate a whole wedding cake.
And an entire pan of funeral fudge.
(gasps)
Check it out, guys. It's dork and dorker.
What you doin' there, Simpson,
babysittin'?
We're on a playdate.
-(laughing)
-Isn't that adorable?
Ah, the girls are on a playdate!
Uh, I'll take it from here, Ralph.
Um, we're just hangin',
chillin', little bit of illin'.
I don't get you, Simpson.
Sometimes you seem kind of righteous,
but then we see you
fraternizing with lameoids.
Which makes you a lame wad!
Oh, yeah? Would a lame wad
have the police master key?
-Whoa! Useful, dude!
-Very handy!
Hey, maybe you are cool enough
to hang out with us.
Really? You think so?
I don't know what to say.
This is all happening so fast.
Let's use this thing to rob the school.
Let's go to the zoo and tease the dingo.
Let's use it to key some cars.
Those are all moderately cool ideas...
but if you really want to
walk on the wild side...
I know just the place.
Here she is, the big house.
The stony lonesome.
The thug jug. The mobster trap.
-Penn State. The old crook--
-Shut up!
Let's just open the gate.
-(dog howling)
-I'm scared, Bart. I wanna go home.
Come on, Ralph. Don't embarrass me.
It's just an abandoned prison.
All the murderers are long dead.
And I'm sure their ghosts
are probably in hell.
-(whimpering)
-Let's go, Simpson! Ditch the baby.
(whimpers, gasps)
(sniffling)
-My key!
-Sorry, Ralph.
I thought we were friends.
(laughing) Wait. I missed that.
Get him to say it again.
Go on home, Ralph.
(sobs) I can't, without
Daddy's key! (gasps)
I can't bail on a friend,
even if it is Ralph.
-Ah, you wuss.
-Hey! Give it back!
-(grunts)
-Hey! Keep away!
Hey, come on! I thought we were friends.
Yeah, well, I hope the irony's
not lost on you, Simpson.
(grunts, groans)
(grunts)
(laughing)
This sucks. Let's do somethin' else.
I know. Let's go pick some huckleberries!
-Yeah!
-Huckleberries! All right!
Daddy's key went in there.
Hey, Ralph, you're braver
than you thought.
-(owl hooting)
-Wait for me!
(gasps)
Wow! Look at all these toilets.
And just inches from your bed.
Talk about luxury.
There's the key!
-(squeaking)
-(gasps)
The pointy kitty took it!
Oh.
Danger, eh?
(key turning in lock)
-(door creaking)
-(both gasping)
Whoa, mama! The electric chair!
(sniffs) Smell that, Ralph?
That's the smell of justice.
Smells like hot dogs.
Hmm. Maybe it still works.
Give me the newlyweds from that cake.
Stand back.
(grunting, sighs) What a gyp.
Maybe our key fits in here.
(crackling)
(sinister chuckling)
Till death do you part.
-MAN: Somebody down there?
-(gasps) Uh-oh. Let's get outta here.
(panting)
Why do I always shout first?
Just gives them a chance to run away.
Well, I'm an idiot.
-Got any threes?
-Go fish.
Oh! See, here's the problem, Ralph.
-You have several threes.
-Go fish!
Why don't we watch cartoons?
The Justice League is moving
into their new building today.
Kent Brockman reporting live
from Mayor Quimby's press conference...
at the abandoned penitentiary.
Huh?
I have ordered the reopening
of this prison
to send a message to
the criminals of Springfield.
If you commit
a violent crime in my town...
you are going to end up here.
Hey, that's our play chair!
To demonstrate what you're in for...
I will now strap myself
into this electric chair
which was deactivated over 30 years ago,
and, I can only assume, still is.
Uh-oh. We didn't reset the safety switch.
He's gonna smell like hot dogs.
(beeps)
Operator, get me Morningwood Penitentiary.
-It's an emergency.
-(busy tone)
(groans)
Now, Martha, we've been
over this and over this.
We're too old to start having children.
If you're looking for something to do,
why don't you start a new twine ball?
Come on. A man's life is at stake.
We need to get a message to the prison.
Think. Think!
Lisa's a good thinker.
That's it. Ralph, you're a genius!
Now, as I mime the convulsions
of a condemned criminal,
I remind my staff
not to come to my assistance
no matter how realistic
my performance may be.
BART: They're getting ready
to throw the switch!
Come on, Lisa. Hurry!
Let's just pray this hits the prison.
(whistling)
-(gasps) Huh?
-(gasps)
Smithers, there's a rocket in my pocket.
You don't have to tell me, sir.
(grunting) Turn off the chair.
-Turn off the chair.
-(all gasping)
"Electric chair is on," eh?
Then the old prison has been
getting free electricity for 30 years.
I'll put a stop to that.
(grunting) (groaning)
-Yea! Yeah.
-Wow! That was really entertaining.
-How did you make that smoke?
-(groans)
-Yeah! All right! Whoo!
-All right!
-Way to go, Ralph!
-Ralph?
But the rocket was my idea.
-But asking you was Ralph's idea.
-You're the man, Ralph!
But surely I deserve some credit for--
BART AND HOMER: Ralph! Ralph! Ralph!
Ah, let him have this one, Lise.
After all, it's Ralph.
Ralph! Ralph! Ralph! Ralph!
Ah, you've done grand, laddie.
Now you know what you have to do-
burn the house down!
Burn 'em all!
(theme music playing)
Shh!
Captioned by Visual Data Media Services