-CHOIR: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
-Hey.
-(yelling)
-(laughing)
Is there any
better feeling
than waiting for a live
Krusty show to start?
Maybe watching your bride
coming down the aisle.
Hmm.
(organ plays discordant music)
(grunting)
(sobbing)
Why does she get to eat
before the reception?
(sobbing)
Seltzer bottle connected
and pressurized?
Check.
Roll-up dicky set to six?
-Nope. 11.
-(gasps)
My comedy comes
from taking risks.
Or avoiding them.
I can't remember.
Krusty, we need to talk.
Make it fast.
I've got a coiled-up spring
ready to boi-oi-oi-oi-oing.
Oh, why can't I be funny
with just my words?
Bill Maher doesn't put dangerous
things near his crotch,
except when he's off work.
(laughs)
Yeah.
It's about your vodka,
Absolut Krusty.
We're having trouble
persuading people
it's hip to drink a vodka
made by a clown,
in a bottle shaped
like a clown,
that does this
when you open it.
-(ooga horn sounds)
-(laughs)
Always gets me.
Yeah, plus, that TV special
where you drank another brand
of vodka didn't help.
I used up my stuff
poisoning deer.
If we're ever gonna
sell your vodka,
we need to do something
completely unorthodox--
a viral marketing campaign.
(metallic creaking)
Get to the point!
Unless you want a face
full of clown chunks!
People are more likely
to drink your vodka
if they think all their
coolest friends are drinking it.
So, we pay for a big party
at the home of a
Springfield trendsetter.
Your Brockman,
your Bumblebee Man...
He invites his cool friends,
we serve free cocktails,
made with your vodka,
generating buzz.
We got buzz.
Positive buzz.
That exists? Wow.
So, all you have to do is find
one of your loyal fans
whose house we can trash
and friends you can exploit.
(metallic creaking)
(gasps, grunts)
I need a drink.
Not that!
Never that!
-(theme music plays)
-Hey, hey, kids!
Who wants to host
a viral marketing event?
ALL: Yay!
All you have to do
is write me a letter
about how hip and influential
your parents are.
Milhouse, I'm gonna
win that thing.
How do you know, Bart?
Maybe for once I'll win.
Children of troubled marriages
not eligible.
Oh!
(birds singing)
So, uh,
why are you here?
Is it about that unauthorized
Krusty look-alike
I hired for Lisa's
first communion?
What was his name?
Krappy the Klunk. See?
Homer, we're here
to throw the most redonkulous
marketing outreach
this town's ever seen.
All you have to do is invite
every cool person you know.
Hey, I wrote the application.
Do any of my friends get
to come?
One friend.
He can listen to music
with headphones on,
he gets one slice
of cheese pizza,
and if the party
gets slow,
he has to pretend to let
Krusty save him from drowning.
-Redonkulous!
-Off the dilge!
(dance music playing)
(tires screech)
(crowd chatter)
This party is so much better
than the crummy ones we plan.
(laughs)
I hope Bart's having fun.
And that's why John Gielgud
is more of a father to me
than my own father.
Where's the nachos
you promised?
There'll be time enough
for nachos!
Why can't I go to
the grown-up room?
You said the clown scared you.
Well, he did a little.
(crowd chatter and laughter)
Boy, everyone from the
nuclear plant is here.
Except the bosses,
of course.
Yeah, even Homer's not dumb
enough to invite...
BURNS:
So, this is the famous party.
Feh. Guh.
Pffoy.
(crowd chatter)
He's destroying
our youthful demographic!
Oh, God, I need a drink!
So the car in front of us
forgot to validate his... uh...
(laughs)
I was in an anecdote once.
Um, I have surgery
in the morning.
Yeah, and I'm the one
having the surgery.
(sighs)
Homer, you're the nominal host.
Do something!
Oh! Uh! Oh!
Mr. Burns,
so glad you're here.
Finally, the party
can get started.
Your cotillion seems
to be in full promenade.
(laughs)
Good one.
Uh, Mr. Burns, everyone is dying
to hear you sing karaoke.
Come on,
just pick a popular song.
Do you have anything
by Prince...
Wilhelm of Prussia?
I have 16 million songs,
but, uh, no.
Just play the oldest,
stupidest thing in your catalog.
Uh, let me check
my beeswax cylinders.
Uh, here we are.
♪ Come, Josephine,
in my flying machine! ♪
♪ Going up she goes,
up she goes ♪
♪ Balance yourself
like a bird on a beam ♪
ALL: ♪ In the air she goes,
there she goes ♪
-(applause and cheering)
-(Mr. Burns chuckles)
May you all fly
in an aeroplane someday.
You certainly seem to be
enjoying yourself, sir.
Indeed.
That Homer Simpson
is the beating baboon heart
of this party.
So he says, "Bigamy is having
one too many wives."
To which I replied,
"So's monogamy."
-(laughter)
-Oh, yeah!
I may have a use for
this Simpson character
higher up in the organization.
Really?
Well, as safety inspector,
he hasn't exactly
set the world on fire,
although he came close
several times.
(crow caws)
Simpson, you're probably
wondering why you're here.
It's never good. I always wind up
being chased by hounds,
or falling
through a trapdoor,
or being a peg in your game
of human croquet.
When I made you a hoop,
you split your pants.
Now, here at the plant,
there's no position more important
than our accounts man,
who's responsible
for glad-handing our
customers and suppliers.
I'd like you to take over
that position.
The last thing I understood
in that was "pants."
Just give me your answer,
and make it quick!
Our current account man,
Robert Marlowe here,
is retiring at the
end of the month.
In two weeks, the only tie
I'll be wearing is
for autoerotic pleasure.
Yes. Simpson,
only you have the bonhomie
and rotund charm
to replace him.
It means a hefty expense account
and a corner office.
Well, in that case...
Before you say yes, Simpson,
I feel it's my duty to warn you,
account men lose their soul.
Woo-hoo!
No more church!
(door squeaks open and shut)
So long, Sector 7-G.
Hello, Sector 22-F!
(elevator bell dings)
(gasps)
(sizzling)
(giggling)
(moans)
The higher they rise,
the further they fall!
You know,
you're kind of a downer.
I thought you were retiring.
Why are you still here?
Hey, you're a baby
account man.
Still on the bottle.
So, for my last good deed
before I retire,
I'm going to help you
persuade Mayor Quimby
to sign off on
a nuclear rate hike.
Uh-oh, a meeting
with the mayor.
How do I prepare for that?
(chuckles)
I see.
Now, how do I prepare
for the meeting with the mayor?
I am really enjoying this,
but, um...
Hello!
Meeting with the mayor?
(glass breaking)
Aw. Bourbon go bye-bye.
There ain't enough bourbon
in Kentucky for you, big guy.
Yeah, the governor wrote me
a letter to that effect.
Wow, I can't believe I'm eating
steak with the mayor.
The next time I vote for you,
it's gonna be on purpose.
Much obliged.
Now, uh, where would you like
to discuss
your proposed tax breaks?
(laughing)
Mmm.
Hey, Homer!
Look at you, man!
(loud whisper)
I've outgrown you!
Oh, Mr. Mayor,
more "peanut nore"?
(knocking on window)
(glass squeaking)
(both grunt)
Say what you will, man.
He's pretty resourceful.
-(cheering)
-HOMER: Wow.
These seats are amazing.
And if you don't like the score,
you can change it yourself.
(click)
HOMER:
Boring!
(click)
God, what a great game!
And you, too, can be on
the winning team, Mr. Mayor.
The Springfield Nuclear Team.
I have never heard an analogy
involving sports!
I love it!
I can't believe
that was work!
Yeah, but work is over now.
Want to drink with me
till I fall asleep?
Oh, well...
Mm, I really should look
at this picture a little longer.
Hmm.
Okay, let's go.
Great. Now, in honor of my
last day on the hamster wheel,
I have a little
gift for you.
This set of bar tools
has been passed down
from account man to account man
since the dawn of history.
1956.
Can you be my dad?
If your mom was a secretary,
there's a good chance I am.
(tires squealing)
(sighs)
Welcome home, handsome!
(both moan)
(laughs)
It's a rat race,
but it looks like I won.
-Oh, to the victor go the spoils.
-Mmm.
Dad, you were supposed
to read me a bedtime story.
Oh, sorry, sweetie.
Bart can read it to you.
(Homer and Marge laugh)
Read to Lisa? Why don't you
just ask me to kiss her?
If you kissed her,
that would be lovely.
-I'll read! I'll read!
-And kiss.
Does anyone want
my opinion?
Please, Lisa.
I had 18 martinis today.
MARGE:
Hello.
All right, Lis, let's get this stupid
bedtime story over with.
Proceed to the page with
the butterfly bookmark
as I cuddle up
with Madam Bunny.
(clears throat)
"If genn-i-oos..."
Genius.
"...is eternal pati...
pat-eh...
pa-tie..."
Patience. Patience!
Get on with it!
Shut up! Shut up!
I'm a bad reader, okay?!
-Well, I could help you.
-I don't want your help!
I'll get one of those jobs
where you don't need to read,
like French fry maker
or general.
-Well, you're getting my help.
-Forget it.
Don't you want to be able
to read the things
people carve into your chest
in prison?
I guess.
♪♪
Close enough.
(sighs)
"But when the helpful voice
was silent,
the daily lesson over,
the beloved presence gone,
and nothing remained
but loneliness and grief,
then Jo found her promise
very hard to keep."
We did it, Bart.
-(groans)
-I'm a mentor.
Big deal, you taught me
to read one book.
No, Bart, you can read
other books, too.
What?!
Homie,
what are you doing?
My work is
so meaningless.
You make electricity.
It runs the hospital.
You can't touch
electricity, Marge,
you can't feel it.
That's because
it would kill you.
It already is killing me,
Marge.
You're the only one
I can talk to.
My wife just
doesn't get it.
I'm your wife.
My job is my wife,
loneliness-- my mistress,
despair-- my sex buddy.
Angst is a chick
I met online,
but then it turned out
it was really a guy.
I'm going to bed.
You don't understand me.
Only she understands me.
Another round, kid?
(squeaks)
Hey, uh...
I got here after you did.
I'm sorry to bother you at home,
Mr. Marlowe,
but my husband's
acting pretty odd--
coming home late,
drinking in the morning.
-Wake me when you get to "odd."
-Hmm.
I don't suppose you'd consider
taking your old job back
so Homie can go back
to his old job?
Sorry, Marge,
that account job hollowed me out
like a cheap chocolate bunny.
I've been divorced three times,
I've got a cocktail addiction,
a shrimp cocktail addiction,
and I can't stop bending women
to my sexual will.
Well, you certainly
won't be bending me...
Wait, how did I end up
in your bedroom?
Lady, I am smoother than
an Eisenhower-era freeway.
Look, I came to talk
about my husband, and...
How did we get in here?
I think better
in the shower.
There's room in here for two.
I'm a happily married woman.
Wow, no woman's ever done
that to me before.
Your husband
is a lucky man.
I know,
and I don't want him to stray
from anything except his diet,
and I don't really
want him to do that.
Marge, I made
a big mistake years ago.
I gave up on my family.
Then I gave up on my
secret other family.
I missed my son's graduation,
my father's funeral,
and my dog's
best in show.
Don't let Homer make
the mistakes I did.
Luann?
It's not what you think.
It's much weirder.
You're reading
a chapter book.
For fun!
Bullies, to me.
(both grunt)
Let's see the name
of this wedgie ticket.
-(gulps)
-Little Women?
Are you aware that's another way
of saying "girls"?
Look, I had to read it
to my sister.
Well, maybe
we should hear a little.
And then maybe you'll be hearing
from my sisters.
Your fists are sisters?
Yeah, Poke-ahontas
and Sock-ajawea!
-Nice save.
-Get reading.
"And Amy and Jo hugged
one another close,
and everything was forgotten
in one hearty kiss."
End of chapter eight.
You can't stop now.
I want to know if their father
comes home.
Does Jo learn to handle
her hasty temper?
Does Amy get over
her conceitedness?
Aw, come on, guys,
it's getting dark.
Okay, but you better be here
tomorrow after school.
'Cause we're going to
keep making you read us
a lame ol' girl's book.
(laughter)
Bart needs to work
on differentiating
the character voices
a little better.
I know, I keep going,
"Why is Meg saying that?"
and then I realize it's Beth.
-(all agreeing)
-That's right.
(Homer grunting)
(intercom buzzes)
RECEPTIONIST:
Your wife is here, Mr. S.
(whispering loudly)
Tell her I'm at a meeting, not drinking.
This is a whisper-amplifying
intercom.
-(screams)
-Homer, I want you to come
with me and the kids
on a family vacation.
Of course, of course.
Family is everything
to us company men.
Now, where shall we go
on your vacation?
The farthest thing from
this office I know:
rafting down Rattler River Canyon.
(Homer whimpers)
That's great--
let me run the numbers
'cause I really want
the Simpson account.
And give these cigars
to your children.
Don't talk to me
like I'm a client.
You're not a client,
you're the client.
(groans)
Simpson, put on your
charm-their-pants-off pants.
The mumpish oafs
in Washington are sending
their sternest band
of nuclear regulators,
handpicked to resist
all blandishment.
I'll handle it, I always do.
Rafting, eh?
It's a perfect way
to entertain them.
Finally, humanity has found
a use for water.
Mr. Burns, I can't go
rafting with you because--
wait a minute,
could this all work?
HOMER:
Oh, no, you don't.
Coggily-doggily.
It all fits.
Mr. Burns, rafting it is.
Excellent.
But Mr. S.,
you just promised this week
to Mrs. S., Master B.,
and Mamselles L. and M.
Now, relax, Dottie.
Leave everything to me.
(grunts)
Oh, Marge, this is
the most romantic trip
you ever nagged me into.
And maybe
when we get home,
we can ride down
something else.
Not sure what you're
going for, but...
(lusty growl)
(gasps)
Uh, Marge, why don't I
catch us some salmon?
(grunting)
D'oh!
It's about time.
We've been making small talk
about Mussolini for 15 minutes.
Well, I, uh, found
that contact lens I was missing.
Let me just screw her back in.
(pained grunting)
So, everybody good?
Why did you get us...
Diversity Kittens
on Meltingpot Mountain?
It's more fun to play
with a ball of yarn
if it has all the colors in it.
And yarn should be allowed
to marry dental floss.
If you've got that, then...
Are you sure
you're Martin Scorsese?
(Homer grunts)
Enjoy the outdoors,
you stupid kid.
(worried grunting)
This family time is so precious.
Got to go.
(panting)
(murmurs suspiciously)
(grunting)
(unzips, hums)
(zips up)
(grunting)
(grunts wearily)
Homer, I want
a Long Island ice tea,
America's most
complicated cocktail.
Homer,
are you schmoozing those men?
(alarmed shriek)
Huh?
Um, I think we're supposed
to get off here.
Take us out first.
Anyone can start a family.
These days
no one can find a job.
Let's see, my family
gives me love and sex.
My work gives me
money and sleep.
Hurry, we're heading
for the falls!
My coworkers are like a family,
but in some ways
my family is like a family, too.
For God's sakes, Homer,
I've given you three children.
Whose side are you on?
Yours, Homie,
I'm always on yours.
How ironic.
I survived the Titanic
by making a raft
out of steerage passengers,
and now this.
MARLOWE:
Mr. Burns, your heart will go on.
(all screaming)
Marlowe, I thought
you retired.
I can't-- Treasury bills
are paying nothing. Nothing!
Well, Simpson,
you were willing
to let me go
over a waterfall,
but you cut operating expenses
by six percent,
-so you're forgiven.
-Thanks.
Now if you'll
excuse me,
I don't really like bourbon
or business talk,
just good old
Simpson family fun.
Hey, kids, I'm it.
(laughter)
(grunting)
Aah!
(screams)
I'm okay,
and I found some gold!
See, luckiest man
in the world.
Oh, I'm so glad
you're not an accounts man anymore.
Yep, your worries
are over.
I'm back to being
a boring old safety inspector
at a nuclear power plant.
(both moaning)
-(murmuring)
-Shh!
Subtitled by A. Vandelay