CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(humming)
D'oh!
(tires screeching)
(grunts)
(screams)
(grunting)
Huh?
Ay, caramba!
(chuckles)
I haven't ridden a bike
since Lance Armstrong
was a good guy.
Geez, Lis, you're riding
the girliest bike in the world.
Ooh, I stand corrected.
(hums)
Hey, dipwad, bikes only.
I need to pay my water bill.
Not on motorized transport, you don't.
What you need to get
is out of our way.
Yeah, bikes win again!
Trains win again!
When will you people give up
your dependence on handlebars?
Quite a Schwinn-dig, eh?
Shut up, biking Flanders.
(bicycle bell dings)
Chief, no, don't go
in the doughnut shop!
Your pants are too tight!
Oh, I'm just gonna eat one little...
Drinkers, if you go on the wagon,
make sure
it's the Duff Beer Wagon.
Oh, yeah!
Duffman,
how about a 21-thrust salute
to America's military?
My hips are proud
to honor our endless war.
One, two, three...
-(cracking)
-Ow, God!
Something's wrong with Barry.
Never use...
my mortal name in public.
I have very troubling news.
(chuckles)
Duffman is undergoing
hip replacement surgery.
Now, Barry will be fine,
but as of this moment
there is no Duffman.
(gasping)
They came for Joe Camel,
and I said nothing.
They came for the Frito Bandito,
and still I said nothing.
So what are you saying now?
About what?
(humming)
(groans)
KENT BROCKMAN:
Duffman, the man, has retired.
But Duffman, the idea, endures.
Authorities are unsure
whether the empty bottles
are a beautiful tribute
or just drunks too lazy
to find a trash can.
Either way,
the Duff Corporation announces
an open televised competition
to find out who will be
the next Duffman.
In other news,
the Chinese land on Mars.
Also, no more elephants.
Now, for more cool,
refreshing news...
Marge, what would you think
if I tried out to be Duffman?
I know why you want
to be Duffman.
It's so you can drink free beer
and get shnockered all day.
Sure, I admit I get "shnockered"
once in a while.
I might have been "lacquered"
from time to time.
I may have, how you say,
had a subconjunctival hemorrhage.
(chuckles)
But this isn't about that.
Then what is this about?
Marge, if I died today,
the obituary would read,
"H. Simpson, father of three,
extra pallbearers needed."
Being Duffman would give me
another line.
Okay, sweetie, you can try.
Great, but it won't be easy.
I got to start practicing now.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah. Ow!
(theme music playing)
ANNOUNCER:
Ladies and gentlemen,
your hostess,
the inescapable Cat Deeley.
Are you ready to find out
who will be America's
next Duffman?
Yes, Cat, yes!
A million times, yes!
America's next Duffman
will be selected
by the planet's foremost experts
in the field of party starting--
best-selling electronica artist,
Der Zip Zorp.
Former Duff Girl and current
senator from Oklahoma,
the Honorable Missy LeBeau.
I look reasonable, but I'm not.
And billionaire Mumbai entrepreneur,
Rajneesh Superstar.
Bottle service, ballers!
(audience cheers)
Now let's welcome the Chairman
of Duff Industries,
Mr. H.K. Duff VII.
Thank you, Cat.
I just want to say,
if we can't find ourselves
a Duffman out of this group,
then maybe we'll just give up
on the concept.
Brilliant!
Now, let's find our Duffman.
♪ I'm... coming up ♪
♪ So you better
get this party started ♪
♪ I'm... coming up... ♪
Oh, yeah!
My two favorite words
aside from "Seacrest passed,"
can I get an "Oh, yeah"?
Oh... ja.
(crowd jeering)
Oh, yes.
(jeering)
Ach.
NELSON:
Haw-haw.
♪ Vo-de-oh-doh-doh ♪
(jeering)
Oh, yeah!
(crowd cheering)
♪ I'm... coming up ♪
♪ So you better
get this party started ♪
♪ I'm... coming up ♪
♪ So you better get... ♪
Did you miss me?
Like Mexico misses California.
It's down to two.
And before revealing
our results,
former Duffman, Barry Huffman,
is here to wish you luck.
I was told there would be morphine.
Oh, yeah.
Homer, any last thoughts
on what Duff means to you?
Without Duff,
I wouldn't have brought
three beautiful children
into the world.
That's right, man.
We're beer babies.
AUDIENCE:
Aw...
(groans)
The judges are conferring.
(discussing)
We have our decision.
Karma is in the house, dawg!
Homer,
your words were beautiful.
That is exactly why
you're America's Next Top Duffman...
runner-up!
(cheers)
(groans)
The real winner
is America's new hero--
contestant number 12!
(dance music playing)
(making alarmed computer noises)
What is it, Der Zip Zorp?
Olde Ogdenville Ale?
He drinks a competitor.
Reverse the confetti.
And check the fat guy
for tattoos.
Just one that says
"Marge Madness."
These reality shows really
leave you no privacy.
Well, I guess that
makes this guy Duffman.
Ooh, ooh, ooh,
do I get the confetti?!
One confettus.
Ow! I mean... Whoo-hoo!
I mean, oh, yeah!
("Game of Thrones" theme playing)
♪ ♪
(squawking)
(squawks)
That's how we'll tell the trades
you got the job.
Seems awfully overproduced.
Just take the oath.
♪ ♪
Night gathers,
and now my Duff watch begins.
It shall not end until my death.
Or my 13-week option
is not picked up.
I shall take no wife,
hold no lands, and father no children,
except for the wife and house
and kids I'm already stuck with.
I shall wear
no other beer's crowns.
I am the six-pack hidden
in Daddy's secret cabinet.
I put the "fest" in Oktoberfest
and sell for eight bucks
at ballparks,
though I have nothing to offer
but my suds, head and beers,
and promotional cozies,
for this night
and all the nights to come.
MAN:
When life looks hopeless, it's not.
♪ Duff Beer, feeling no pain ♪
♪ Made from Canadian rain ♪
♪ Tastes like nickel champagne ♪
♪ It will tickle your brain ♪
♪ Duff Beer, feeling no pain ♪
♪ Made from Canadian rain ♪
And here's a painting
of my ancestor, Ichabod Duff,
crossing the Duffaware River.
Ah, hell, this is all BS.
Duffman was a fascist icon
my grandfather repurposed
'cause he couldn't get the damn rights
to Woody Woodpecker.
Mr. Duff,
can I ask what's in this safe?
Little lady, inside that safe
is the formula for Duff itself,
known only to three people--
me, Condoleezza Rice,
and my brother-in-law Terry.
And the combination
is not known to any human...
Uh, what the...?
"Schlitz plus water."
Why don't you kids run off
and play in the bottle cap pit?
Don't cut yourselves!
Mr. Duff,
I want to say something.
I'm proud of my husband,
but I'm not sure if this is something
Homie should be doing.
Just what do you mean?
Well,
aren't you making him a superhero
so that beer looks cool to kids?
(laughs)
Uh, Marge,
let me tell you a little
something about beer.
Do you know why man stopped
running around,
lassoing mastodons,
and became civilized?
No.
So he could grow hops
and make beer.
-It's true.
-Oh.
Our beer has helped people
celebrate weddings.
Enjoy a good game.
Ease the pain
of a lost loved one.
That's the tradition
your husband will inherit.
Geez, now you make me
want to drink it.
Attagirl, have a designer bag.
Now, Homer, there is one thing
we needed to do in private.
Okay, what...?
Ow!
Hey, that's not my butt!
We've injected a chip in you
that detects the slightest presence
of alcohol in your blood.
You see, Duffman cannot drink.
(laughing)
What? That's funny.
I thought you just said
that Duffman can't drink.
(laughs)
But that would be crazy.
They all fight it at first.
(laughs)
You wouldn't tell Batman
he couldn't eat bats.
When you're Duffman,
you're at work, Homer.
You wouldn't go to the nuclear plant
drunk, would you?
Uh...
Well, uh...
My husband won't have
any problem not drinking.
Yeah...
The only reason he wanted
to become Duffman
was to be respected and beloved.
Uh...
And what better way to do that
than to be stone-cold sober?
(moans)
When my husband
put on that costume,
he didn't just
put on a sleeveless shirt
that says "Duff" on it
and a cape for some reason,
he put on responsibility.
And boots that I don't think
will hold up in the rain.
But the point is--
it's not about being drunk,
it's about being someone.
You're right, Marge.
I will do something no one has
ever done-- be fun sober.
What a crisp
and refreshing attitude.
Hey, this stuff is pretty good.
Mmm, foamy Marge.
(babbling)
Uh, that's the chip.
No drinking.
I was licking my wife.
Can you believe they
put a chip in my arm,
and I can't drink beer?
-Ah.
-Ah, gee, tough break.
Maybe Moe could dig it out
with a corkscrew.
Yeah.
Oh, I would love that,
Homer, I really would.
But then Duff might take away
my neon sign,
and, uh, it's the only thing
lighting the bar.
BARNEY:
Whoa, creepy.
(Bart and Lisa laugh
mischievously)
Stop shooting those at each other.
Relax, honey, no one's ever
been killed by a T-shirt cannon.
Oh, no, it's the 5:00 blahs.
CLOCKS:
Blah, blah, blah, blah.
Help us, Duffman!
(laughs heroically)
(screams)
Drink Duff!
(crowd cheers)
Care to team up with Fruit Batman?
I'm thinking of dumping
Kid Sourpuss here.
I'm a hero.
Oh, I can see my obituary now.
Wow. Wow!
COMMENTATOR: Watkins putting
for the championship.
It's breaking towards the hole.
Time to move from the links
to the drinks!
(cheering)
♪ ♪
Well, if you guys like commercials,
you're gonna love this.
Wait, we never said
we liked commercials.
♪ Drink, drink ♪
♪ Let the toast start ♪
♪ May young hearts never part ♪
♪ Drink, drink, drink ♪
♪ Let every true lover
salute his sweetheart... ♪
♪ Drink, drink, drink to... ♪
H.K., this new Duffman
is driving sales straight up.
Turns out, men like men
who look worse than them
selling them beer.
Why did it take us 142 years
to discover this?
Because executives are
incompetent, sir?
Well, then why do I have so many?
Studies show when a decision
is made by a group,
everyone feels more confident,
even though the decision
could be incredibly stupid.
-Is this true?
-(affirming)
Can't argue with that.
What do you guys think?
(affirming)
Did I hear a no
from section C-72?
Oh, uh, no,
that was a, uh, "whoa!"
(chuckling)
Oh.
Give the whole
lower bowl a raise.
Uh, welcome aboard, Duffman.
Fair warning now-- at the end,
I just might ask
for an autograph for my son.
Here you go-- they're all pre-signed.
With nicknames.
Buddy, Sport, Tiger, Red.
Uh, give me a "Red."
I'll start calling him that now,
and then give it to him
on his birthday.
Now, where to, sir?
Oh, this is a romantic night.
How about everywhere?
All right.
Navigator,
set a course for everywhere.
Where the hell is that?
I said everywhere!
Now, Homer,
look through the beeriscope,
and gaze upon the wonderful world
that you and Duff have created.
Captain, it never dawned on me
beer could have such a dark side.
You must be talking about
new Duff Stout.
Take us down.
I have to think.
To be honest, you said
you wanted to go everywhere.
So we ran out of fuel
an hour ago,
but I didn't want
to disappoint you,
so I will toss down a tow rope.
Hey, come here. Man...
Uh... this is not good.
(sighs)
Marge, do you ever worry
that you made
a giant mistake in your life?
Oh, um...
I need a little context.
Not drinking beer has given me
the clearness of mind
to realize drinking beer is bad.
I've got to undo what I've done.
Hey, how you doing?
(dance music playing)
Is this the most outrageous party
you've ever been to?
(cheering, affirming)
Well, guess what.
You've all been served nothing
but nonalcoholic Duff.
(spectators gasping)
BARNEY:
Then why am I throwing up right now?
As Duffman, I had the power
to switch the beer trucks
working this race.
(screams)
So you see, you don't need beer
to have a good time.
Join Duffman today in saying,
"I've had enough
of that life-ruining Duff!"
Why the hell did you do this?
Because Duffman is a hero.
And with great taste
comes great responsibility.
Well, "hero," here come your fans.
(shouting indistinctly)
(yelps)
-(engine starts)
-So long, suckers!
(laughing maniacally)
What the...?!
So long, suckers!
(Homer laughing maniacally)
What the...?!
It's a circle.
So the answer is--
go in reverse.
So long, suckers.
(Homer laughing maniacally)
What the...?!
I'm not sure
how many more times
we can watch Dad chased down
by an angry crowd
before it affects us psychologically.
As a family therapist,
I can assure you
that you have
all the coping skills you need.
Why is Lisa talking to an empty seat?
See you next Tuesday, Dr. Schulman.
Oh, right.
You're in Maui.
(whimpers)
Hey, my beer.
(screams)
(panting frantically)
(gargling)
Get him back in uniform.
Hmm.
Homer, now, listen to me.
You're in a stadium
surrounded by people
who want to kill you.
They don't have the guts.
Ow.
Now, there's one way
out of your hell.
Prove you still love beer.
Drink this with gusto.
B-But the chip.
There never was a chip.
It was all the power of suggestion.
You tricked me!
And I trusted you
after you snuck up
and injected me
without my consent.
Just drink the beer, pretty boy.
Whatever you do,
you'll be my hero.
Now you're pushing it.
Homie, it's time to go.
Come on, come on.
Give me the beer inside you!
Oi.
This place seems
even sadder than before.
Uh, yeah, well,
I kind of gloomed it up a little
while you were gone.
Nothing to see here, sunshine.
(sighs)
(slurring)
H-Hey, y-you used to be Duffman.
Can I get a picture with you?
(gasps)
I finally made it.
I'm a has-been.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Ah, let's make it official, eh?
Aw...
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
Sir, may I interest you
in a French hazelnut latte
and an Iggy Azalea CD?
I'm not here for three-buck coffee.
I'm here to ask you
to be Duffman again.
And to use the bathroom.
I don't know what you're
talking about, sir.
Fine, can you tell me
where your travel mugs are?
Yeah, over there.
Come on, Barry, I know it's you.
Sorry, H.K.,
I traded in my beer goggles
for coffee-grinding pince-nez.
Are you telling me
you don't miss the big time?
The girls on the side,
the corporate jet?
There's talk of an animated series.
Duffman would like a job
where he could phone it in.
You just called yourself Duffman.
Duffman never took off his tights!
Let's go, girls!
But we're managers here.
They learned the register
better than me! Oh, yeah!
Oh, yeah!
Subtitled by Jimmy Boots