(SINGING) The Simpsons
(TIRES SCREECHING)
D'oh!
(EXCLAIMING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(ALL GRUNTING)
ANNOUNCER (ON TV):
And with time running out,
the Seminoles
are on the warpath!
Go, Seminoles!
Cover the point spread!
(SNIFFS) Mmm.
(GULPS)
ANNOUNCER: Here's the play
that will determine the game.
(CROWD CHEERING ON TV)
(GASPS)
ANNOUNCER:
Stay tuned for "Sitcom Sunday."
(MUTTERING)
Where's the remote?
(GROANS)
(CLANKING)
This is not
a drill, people!
(WHIMPERING)
(STRAINS)
Huh?
Oh.
(CLANKING)
(BARKS)
(FEEDBACK)
(AUDIENCE SPEAKING
SPANISH ON TV)
Hmm. The TV
changes channels
every time
the dog barks.
(BARKS)
ANNOUNCER:
We return to Mel Gibson's
"The Salad of the Christ"
on Christian Carrot Theater.
I think he swallowed
the remote.
(GRUNTS)
Bark for your master.
(WHIMPERING)
(ITCHY GIGGLING)
(BARKING)
(WHIMPERING)
Lousy American-made dog!
(BARKING)
(GRUNTS)
(STRAINING)
Oh! Why must
I be so voluptuous?
(WHIMPERS)
Oh!
Oh. Time
to make you pretty!
(BOTH GRUNT)
(WHIMPERS)
PATTY: Oh, yes.
A little more color.
How do I look?
(GRUNTING)
HOMER: Ow!
Oh, after my makeover,
I'm gonna get you, boy!
Yo, yo, yo.
Here now the nizzews.
The top artists of hip-hop
are coming to Springfield.
This all-star concert dubbed
"Murder 4 Life" features,
Da Glock Pointaz, Romeo Smoov,
Queen Booty Shaykah,
MC Champagne Millionaire,
and Assault "Weapons
Magazine's" Man of the Year,
Alcatraaaz.
Alcatraaaz
is wide-spread!
I'm talkin' da junk!
Just what we need.
Another lame suburban
kid who loves rap.
So? You like the blues.
Yes. But the blues
are unpopular.
Man, are you illin'.
Rappers stopped
saying "illin"'
12 years ago.
I'm keepin' it real!
They stopped saying
"keepin' it real"
three years ago.
Mom, Lisa's dissin' me!
Dissin'?
Do rappers
still say that?
Oh!
Hmm.
Dad, can I go
to a rap concert?
Tickets are $50.
Go to hell.
Okay.
What if I pay
for it myself?
Fine. Go nuts.
I love you, Dad.
I love you, too, Jerry.
Baggy britches?
Loose-laced gym shoes?
Are you going
to a rap performance?
Hell, yeah.
I'm representin'
at Murder 4 Life.
Know what I'm sayin'?
All too well.
Rap music belongs
in the rubbish bin.
It encourages punching,
boastfulness,
and rudeness to hos!
Step off, Mom.
Rap is the poetry
of the streets.
Well, you are not
going to any concert
that promulgates stink talk.
But Dad already
said I could go.
Oh, did he?
Homer, you tell
your son
a rap show
is not a safe place
for a 10-year-old.
Son, your mother
makes a very loud point.
But you said I could go
if I paid for the ticket.
Boy, let me explain
the situation in terms
you'll understand.
(SUCKING RHYTHMICALLY)
(RAPPING) You did it
on the straight
Got your dad's permission
But your mom dropped a bomb
So I flipped my position
Don't argue with Marge
I know what's best
The only wrap in this crib
Keeps sandwiches fresh
Fresh, fr-fresh
for Mommy's baby boy
Baby boy. Baby boy.
Ba-ba-ba-baby boy
(SCREAMS)
Dad, you completely
sold me out.
Well, I paid for this ticket.
That makes me an adult.
I'm going.
(GRUNTS)
I love you,
Krusty-wusty.
(RAP MUSIC PLAYING)
(RAPPING)
Every miner, forty-niner
And stone cold conniver
Stakes a claim on my tongue
To pan my saliva
Make the hos
drop they clothes
Like they Lady Godiva
(CROWD CHEERING)
Whoa.
(FEEDBACK)
(RAPPING) Yo, cuz!
Put down my mike
'Less you know how to use it
This is old school
not preschool
So don't Dr. Seuss it
(CROWD LAUGHING)
(GULPS)
(RAPPING) Don't critique
my technique
I'm no geek
I make the principal nervous
My friends can confirm this
I'll bust a spit wad
in your epidermis
Oh, no, he didn't!
(CROWD CHEERING)
You can trace my remorse
To its supersized source
A hungry, hungry hypocrite
Named Homer, of course
My old man's pathetic
Damn is his head thick
The gas from his ass
is carcinogenic
Every day I pray
his DNA ain't genetic
(ALL CHEERING)
Damn, this ride
is pimped out.
Yo, downstairs
I got a wax museum
of famous movie monsters.
Check it out,
if you want to get
your fright on.
(CAR REVVING)
Jeepers! It's 50 Cent.
Yo, B. I heard you
throw down on stage.
Wanna join
my world tour?
Sorry, Fitty.
I have school tomorrow.
You're right.
The more you know,
the further you go.
And that's one to grow on.
Does that count
as community service?
No.
All right.
Take me to the park.
We'll pick up
some dog poop.
Yes, sir!
Here you go,
you little yellow cracker.
Now let's go murder
our enemies. Peace.
(TIRES SQUEALING)
Mmm!
Bart's gone!
I checked everywhere!
That little sneak
disobeyed us
and went to that
hip-hop festival!
If that's true,
he's gonna be like NWA.
Not Without Ass-welts.
Well, time to face
my punishment like a man
or lie my way out
of it like a kid!
(GRUNTS)
(BOTH WHIMPER)
A flying rock!
Call a geologist!
Hmm.
"We have kidnapped your son.
"Follow instructions and
Bart will not be harmed."
Follow instructions?
He's doomed!
(WAILING)
This'll be the worst
Thanksgiving dinner ever!
Thanksgiving's not
for months!
The bad news
keeps on coming!
(WAILING)
Tragedy climbed
a ladder last night
as 10-year-old Bart Simpson
was snatched from his bed,
his chocolate
milk dreams cut short
by kidnapping fiends.
Mrs. Simpson,
is the pain
so unbearable
you wish your son
had never been born?
Ooh! What a horrible thing
to say to a mother. (CRYING)
Perhaps reading
this message aloud
will comfort you.
It's
win-a-Hawaiian-getaway-week
on Channel 6."
(CRYING)
So, mail in those
pineapple stickers today.
Aloha means one
entry per person.
(WAILING)
I will find Bart Simpson.
Clancy Wiggum is on the case.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Chief, seriously,
shouldn't we just
plan for the funeral?
Hey, I crack
cases all the time.
Like the case
of the symphony conductor
who murdered
his star cellist.
That was an episode
of Columbo, Chief.
They show you
who the bad guy is
at the beginning of each one.
Yeah. But you have
to remember.
(GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
This is no fun
without Bart. (SIGHS)
He used to watch me
while I did this.
BART: I still do.
(GASPS) Bart!
Are the kidnappers
after you?
Well, some kidnappers
might be after me.
It's a big world.
But in this case,
I faked the whole thing.
Why? Are you mad at me?
No. It's not about you.
Oh. It's never
about me! (GRUNTS)
OFFICER (ON RADIO):
10-23, you seen anything?
Look, I need
a place to hide out
until the heat is off.
In my dad's apartment,
the heat is always off.
He made a coat
out of all
my stuffed animals.
(BART SHUDDERS)
You can hide out
in my room.
My dad won't know
because he's at work.
Shoo! Get outta here!
(CROWS CAWING)
These aren't your soybeans!
Wow. I should've
read these headlines
a long time ago.
Together, they really
paint a picture
of failure.
And now my only
friend is the bottle.
BARNEY FIFE (ON TV):
Rise and shine, Chief Wiggum!
This pity party is over.
What...
Officer down! Huh?
Hmm.
Barney Fife!
Y-E-S spells
"You got it, buster!"
And I'm here to tell you
the feelings you're having
are common for every (SNIFFS)
brother of the badge.
Well, my fat grew
over my badge.
Oh, sour mash.
It's time for you
to roll up your sleeves
and get the ol' (SNIFFS)
crime sniffer
out on the street.
You're right.
I gotta buckle down
and do some police work.
Now that's the can-do attitude
that puts dudes in the can.
(LAUGHS)
Well, I'm wanted
back on the set.
Set? Are you the character
or the actor who plays him?
(EERILY) Now I must go.
Wait a minute.
Now you're a ghost?
(EERILY) Avenge me.
(PHONE RINGING)
Hello?
BART (IN DIFFERENT VOICE):
This is the kidnapper!
Do what I say and
Bart won't get hurt.
Oh, yeah? Send a finger
wrapped in today's paper
to prove you have him.
Homer!
I know what
I'm doing.
You can use any
section of the paper,
except Metro.
It's a big snooze.
(GRUNTS)
Please give me back my boy.
I just want to
tell him I love him
one more time.
(CRYING)
Mom, it's me.
Don't cry. I'm okay.
The kidnappers say
if you worry too much,
(IGNITES ELEMENT)
they'll kill me.
(WAILING)
Uh... No, no. I mean...
(POPCORN POPPING)
(DOOR OPENING)
Okay, you made
your point!
(CAWING)
Gotta go!
All right, boys.
Let's get this tape
back to the lab
for analysis.
We have a lab?
Yeah. It's that room we keep
the Christmas decorations in.
BART (RECORDING):
Uh... No, no. I mean...
(POPCORN POPPING)
What is that noise
in the background?
Maybe I can isolate it.
(REWINDING)
(POPCORN POPPING)
(SIGHS) I know I've heard
that noise before.
Think, Clancy. Think.
Hail falling
on a tin roof?
No. That's it!
(SNAPS FINGERS)
Stovetop popcorn!
And it sounds like
my favorite brand!
Chintzy Pop!
Eddie, Lou!
We're going to
the Kwik-E-Mart!
You already sent us
there twice today.
No. That was for snacks.
This time,
it's not personal.
I need the name of everyone
who buys Chintzy Pop popcorn.
Oof. Chintzy Pop
is the worst
legal popcorn.
Many of the kernels
are baby teeth.
There are only
two idiots cheap enough
to buy this crap.
You and...
Oh, baby.
(BEEPING)
ls there anything
better than video poker
and Chintzy Pop?
Whoa! I'm looking at
an inside straight!
(BEEPING)
Oh.
Someday I'll hear
the winning music.
Someday.
(GUNS COCKING)
(GASPS)
Drop the corn,
tighty-whitey!
What? I didn't do anything!
We'll let a judge
be the judge of that!
Yo, Chief,
we found the kid!
Wow. For once
I did everything right.
What's going on?
I didn't know
he was here! I swear!
Uh, Chief?
Is Milhouse's dad
gonna be in trouble?
He's not really a bad guy.
Now, now.
There's no need for you
to defend your captor,
Bratty Hearst. (GRUNTS)
We're putting you
in a dirty little cell.
Not as small and dirty
as this apartment,
but you know,
it's still pretty bad.
(SMOOCHING)
Oh, Bart, I'm so glad
you're okay!
Oh, son!
Taking your tombstone
back to the store
will be the happiest
thing I've ever done.
BART: Ay, caramba!
Chief, we're sorry
we didn't have
faith in you.
And I'm sorry I wrote
those letters to the editor
calling for your ouster.
You're "Worried in
West Springfield"?
Not anymore, Chief.
Not anymore.
(MARCHING BAND PLAYING)
Keep those rose petals coming!
I almost stepped
on regular ground
back there.
(CROWD CHEERING)
(GUNS COCKING)
Bart, two, three, four.
You put my dad in jail,
flip, spin, twirl.
Milhouse, if you tell anyone,
I'll tell the world
you wet your pants
watching Harry Potter.
I wasn't scared.
I was just peeing!
Look, if you tell
what I did,
I'll get in trouble.
You gotta do something!
I want my dad back!
(GRUNTING)
(CROWD CHEEERING)
You've got the perfect
build for a suit,
44 regular.
(WHISPERING) 56 huge.
Boys, even though
I've been made
Police Commissioner,
Don't think
I've forgotten you.
Lou, you're promoted
to Chief of Police.
Sweet.
And Eddie,
you're promoted to Lou.
Nice.
And, uh,
who's gonna be Eddie?
We don't need an Eddie.
Commissioner Wiggum,
I need to confess something.
Is it that
you're proud of me?
I lied about
being kidnapped.
The whole thing
was a hoax.
A hoax? A hoax?
Oh!
Bart, please.
You can't take
this away from me.
How would I explain it
to Ralphie?
That kid can't understand
where the world goes
when you close the drapes.
But what about
Milhouse's dad?
Hey, this is
the best thing that
ever happened to that loser.
Women love famous felons.
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
Kirk, you are so dangerous
and misunderstood.
You've kidnapped
my heart.
I love the way
I've heard of you.
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
So Bart, as you can see,
from what I just said,
everyone is a winner here.
(BIRDS SQUAWKING)
Huh?
(GASPS)
A shirt from
that rap concert.
Bart must've gone
to the show.
But that means...
Bart was never kidnapped?
Lisa, I'm very glad
you brought me this.
I'll see that it gets to
the proper authorities.
Dad!
Why did you do that?
Hollywood producers
have paid me a fortune,
which I've already lost,
for the rights
to Bart's story.
So I have to destroy
anything that proves
that story's not true.
Why did you
burn up your shirt?
What shirt?
I don't see any shirt.
(GRUNTS)
Burn the truth.
(SIGHS)
So you see,
Principal Skinner, that's
why I had to come to you.
Wait. Why did
your father
burn his pants?
It doesn't matter.
The point is
only with your help
can I expose Bart's lies.
A chance to bring
down Bart Simpson,
our school's second
most wanted criminal
after the mysterious
El Barto.
Hmm.
Sign me up.
Boys, let me tell ya.
Now that I'm Commissioner,
the shaves are hotter,
the steaks are thicker,
and I got my own
private bathroom.
So Lou here won't be
using my sonic toothbrush
on his rotten choppers.
Yeah.
Uh, listen, Commissioner.
Lisa Simpson
came by the office today
asking questions about
her brother's kidnapping.
Questions?
Yes.
As if she were trying
to unravel a tapestry
of deceit.
(CAMERA CLICKING)
All right, people.
We got a situation here.
Your daughter's gonna blow
our whole deal sky high.
You leave Maggie to me.
No, Lisa.
Not her. She'll hunt
us down relentlessly.
Like a bloodhound
mixed with a student
loan officer.
Hey, I can't leave this place.
I get three square meals a day
and trailer time
with Springfield's
craziest chicks.
(ALL SCREAMING)
Hey, I got the most
to lose here.
I just printed up
10,000 business cards.
How am I gonna pass
all these out before
she catches me?
Give me a call sometime!
Give me a call some...
(GROANS)
Here comes the panic!
People, please,
the only way
Lisa can bust me
is if she finds someone
who can prove I was
at that rap show.
(SNAPS FINGERS)
And I know just where
she can find that someone.
Let's go
cover our asses!
Wait. Before we go,
I took the liberty
of making these
embroidered conspiracy
jackets for all of us.
Wow. Those jackets
are beautiful!
We must never wear them.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
(ALL GROWLING)
Mr. Alcatraaaz,
my name is Lisa Simpson.
And this is Principal Skinner.
Hi.
Would you mind showing us
video footage of
your last concert?
No problem.
I got 200-inch plasma TV
in my shoe closet.
(ALL GUFFAWING)
(CHUCKLES)
I'm sharing a laugh
with my new friends.
(RAPPING) Homer is a fat load
AUDIENCE: (RAPPING)
Homer is a fat load
This proves Bart lied
about being kidnapped.
Not yet.
Can we verify
exactly what time
Bart was at the show?
(TAPE REWINDING)
If only we had
the exact date.
(TAPE REWINDING)
Bingo! Thank you,
Mr. Alcatraaaz.
Ain't nothin'.
Uh-uh-uh.
It is nothing.
It's idiomatic, biatch.
(GRUNTS) All right,
(GUN COCKING)
hand over the tape
and nobody gets hurt.
(GUNS COCKING)
Oh, this is hopeless.
My gun isn't even loaded.
Nuts. They're gonna release
that tape and our hoax
will be exposed.
(SIGHS) Well, I guess
I'll go back to Baltimore
and sell ribbon with my daddy.
"Ribbon, get your ribbon!
Great for presents!" (SIGHS)
Wait a minute. Why do
we have to come clean?
Nobody's been hurt.
Everyone's happier
with the lie.
The lie is love.
Wait just a minute!
Love the lie.
The way I was raised, by Mom,
I learned the truth
can't be swept
under the rug.
That's a very
noble sentiment, Lisa.
But for once in your life,
can't you just be cool?
Yeah.
Be cool like us.
Coolee. Coolee cool.
Come on, fool.
Be coolee coolee cool.
(CREAKING)
(GRUNTS)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
(GUNS COCKING)
(GASPS)
Yo, put away
your Glocks, man.
Yes.
Share with us the wisdom
of the street,
O mighty Alcatraaaz.
There are times in life,
when the truth
ain't black nor white,
but a subtler
shade of gray, yo.
And when the path
for justice is obscured
by the fog of uncertainty,
there is only one solution.
House party!
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING)
(PEOPLE CHEERING)
(ALL CHEERING)
I don't understand.
After all the corruption
and deceit we witnessed,
how can everyone
just party?
Lisa, the world
is a very complicated place.
And when you get
right down to it...
Cannonball!
(ALL CHEERING)
Do you think
there's a place
in the hip-hop world,
for a 40-something
elementary school
administrator?
Hell, yes.
Hmm.
But I'm already paying
a guy for that.
Skinner! I order you
to step off, dawg.
(ALL LAUGHING)
I think they're
making fun of me
but my wife is very sick.
Whoo!
(SHUSHING)