(SlNGlNG) The Simpsons
(TlRES SCREECHlNG)
D'oh !
(SCREAMlNG)
(TlRES SCREECHlNG)
(MlCROWAVE DlNGS)
How's the ice cream, kids?
BOTH: Great!
Who's ready for a kitten?
l am !
Make mine calico!
Here you go.
(MEWlNG)
This whole morning
has been wonderful. . .
(KlTTEN PURRlNG)
Too wonderful.
You're right. This is it!
They're selling us to be
crash test dummies.
Oh, please let it be Volvo.
Oh, you children
are too suspicious.
(QUlETLY) lt's go time.
(CHUCKLlNG)
lt's shot day!
(ALL SHRlEKlNG)
Welcome to Hell. . .man
Avenue Medical Plaza.
(WHlMPERlNG)
Children,
you should be grateful
you live in a country
where childhood diseases
have been practically. . .
Karate!
Ow!
(CHUCKLlNG)
(GRUNTS)
Bart! That hobo skeleton
is not a toy!
This is ridiculous.
Only babies and ex-junkies
are afraid of needles.
Stick me, Chuckles!
(WHlMPERlNG)
Can l have a lollipop?
Well, that just leaves Bart.
Don't forget Maggie.
Oh, l got her when
your heads were turned.
Got her good !
Now, Bart,
just look out the window.
lt'll take your
mind off the pain.
And when you're done,
l've got more lollies.
No, thanks.
l already helped myself.
See you later, inoculator.
(CAR SPEEDlNG AWAY)
He can run, but nobody
escapes the needle.
Charlene,
cancel all my appointments.
But, l need that kidney now.
(SlNGlNG) One way or another
I'm gonna find ya
I'm gonna getcha
getcha getcha getcha
One way or another
I'm gonna win ya
I'm gonna getcha
getcha getcha getcha
One way or another
I'm gonna see ya
I'm gonna meetcha
meetcha meetcha meetcha
One day, maybe next week
I'm gonna meetcha,
I'm gonna meetcha
l'll meetcha
Black-on-black
violence must end.
That was for Dr. King.
(CHUCKLlNG)
Don't feel bad, Doc.
l won't even let my
mom clip my toenails.
(LAUGHS MlSCHlEVOUSLY)
BARNEY: l guess
you're just too
smart for me, Bart.
What?
Ha-ha!
Huh?
(STRUGGLlNG)
Thanks, Barney.
Moe, we won't need you now.
Oh.
Okay. Well,
l really enjoyed being you,
Dr. Hibbert.
Oh, by the way,
you're not welcome in
the library no more.
l'm sorry.
Now, that wasn't so bad,
was it, Bart?
You know
sometimes the fear of. . .
(STATlC CRACKLlNG)
Whoa. Something's wrong !
l can't hear!
Doctor, perform a diagnosis!
Hmm. . .
l'm afraid the inoculation
has swollen his
ear holes shut.
Maybe this
would be a good time
to talk about
the side effects.
The boy's hearing
should clear up in a day.
lf it doesn't,
call me in the Bahamas.
For now,
he can express himself
with this complimentary pen.
Cool.
Oh, it's a good pen.
Try it out.
All right.
That was
a malpractice waiver, fool !
(CHUCKLlNG)
Ha-ha!
(AlR HORN BLOWlNG)
Stop it, Homer!
Oh. . .
Gimme your wallet, kid !
We're gonna identity theft
your ass.
(STATlC CRACKLlNG)
(lNAUDlBLE)
He's just standing
his ground !
He knows that deep down,
all bullies are cowards!
We're undone!
(ALL EXCLAlMlNG lN FEAR)
l know what
you're hiding, lad.
Willie's been deaf
since the boiler
explosion of '88.
But l taught
myself to read lips.
Morning, Willie!
What did you say
about me mother?
For your information,
her feet stink
because she works
in manure all day!
But it's still
the best damn
Starbucks in Glasgow!
Bart, pass the ketchup.
(YELLlNG) Bart,
pass the ketchup!
Dad, he's deaf.
Oh, sorry, right.
Bart, pass the corn !
(YELLlNG)
(SlGHS)
l think you should stay home
from school tomorrow.
But, Mom, tomorrow's
the big donkey
basketball game.
The kids are gonna
play the teachers!
Donkey basketball?
Now l've heard everything,
unlike you !
(LAUGHlNG)
Oh. . .
Everyone remember that
for when his
hearing comes back.
Swish !
(CROWD LAUGHlNG)
WeIcome, everyone,
to the AnnuaI Donkey
Basketball Classic.
l'm sure that "mule"
enjoy it.
Hmm. Tough crowd.
WouId everyone just rise
for our national anthem?
(BAND PLAYlNG NATlONAL ANTHEM)
Hey, donkey, want a carrot?
Psych ! (LAUGHS)
Good Lord !
Bart's mooning the flag !
Don't look, Buttermilk!
(CROWD JEERlNG)
How dare he?
That's the flag
my grandpappy
rebelled against!
When you insult the flag,
you insult my flag tattoo!
Uh-oh.
(MUTTERlNG NERVOUSLY)
(DONKEY BRAYlNG)
What did you say
about my mother!
(YELLlNG)
You'll fry up
nice tonight!
Your child's
behavior appalls me
not just as a principal,
but as a veteran of
America's only losing war.
To date!
l swear, Bart didn't know
what he was doing.
He was deaf.
Oh, sure, Marge.
Just like Blind Bart,
Wheelchair Bart,
Pregnant Bart,
and my personal favorite,
Railroad
Spike-Through-Head Bart.
(LAUGHlNG)
Kids love trains.
Hey, fellas,
my hearing's back.
Congratulations, traitor!
Thank you. And let me say
l missed your sweet,
sweet voices.
Cram it, lraqi !
(GRUNTS)
Why'd you dis the flag?
lt partied on the moon !
Weren't we afraid of him
just a few days ago?
We're complex.
All right,
who can take a story
and blow it way
out of proportion?
l'm your man, boss!
l want you to
over-hype this story
so much,
it makes the New York Post
look like The New York Times.
Or The New York Times
look like the New York Post.
l forget which one
the good one is.
l did not come to
this country illegally
to see it mocked.
There's the boy
who bared his bottom
to Old Glory
and the family
that applauds
his every moonery!
They hate our country
but they love our
soapy water.
Huh?
Hey, Benedict Arnold,
our cups don't want
your colorful balls!
No one calls me unpatriotic!
(EXCLAlMS) Uh-oh.
(GROANS NERVOUSLY)
Hey, guys!
Oh, cold shoulder, huh?
Well, l'll just talk
to myself.
"Hey, how you doing, Homer?"
"Oh, not too bad.
How about you?"
"Oh, l'm fine.
Your wife was great
in bed last night."
"You keep your
hands off my wife!"
"Oh, yeah? Well,
l give her what she needs.
And she like. . ."
(CHOKlNG)
"Homer, stop it!"
Homer! This bar's
only for real Americans
and people on
permanent visas like me.
What? What are
you all looking at?
l'm Dutch.
Ah, forget all of you.
(CLOMPlNG)
l'm leaving, too.
l'm gonna go listen to
the President's
weekly radio address.
And not the rebuttal.
Goodbye, Homer.
l can't get drunk
and vomit next to a guy
l don't respect.
(SOBBlNG) Even my
best friends have left me.
l'm all alone!
LlSA: We've become pariahs!
ln the last two hours,
l've gotten 1 000 hate spams.
(RlNGlNG)
Y'ello?
Appear on your TV show?
Tell our side of the story?
You'll see us there?
Goodbye? Dial tone?
MARGE:
lf there's one way to get
the truth out,
it's on a cable
news channel.
When we explain
our side of the story,
the hate calls will end.
l won't have to hear
"Suck my such and such"
or "hell this"
and "bitch that."
We get it, Mom !
Oh, no, no, let her finish.
Look, what should l say
to make people not hate me?
Son, l've learned
one thing in this life.
To stay out of trouble
just say nothing.
Don't rock the boat.
Don't even get in the boat!
Just buy some ice cream
and walk around the pier.
But don't go
in the bathrooms,
they're filthy.
Dad,
l am going on a talk show,
l have to say something.
Talk about boats.
Then, when he asks you
if you hate this country,
you just start crying
and pretend you don't.
But l don't hate
this country.
There, there.
Save your lies for
the American public.
l'm Nash Castor
and it's time to butt heads!
Bart Simpson,
what do you hate most
about this country?
ls it the freedom?
Nash, l've realized
something.
l'm the worst kid
in the world
and the last thing
l deserve is forgiveness.
But with
a little help from Jesus
and our fighting
men and women overseas. . .
All right.
So if l hear you correctly,
you're saying America
is better than Jesus.
Do you agree?
Before he can answer, do you?
Well, America's not perfect.
So America isn't perfect.
ls that why you
and your son hate us?
lf by "us" you mean
loud mouth talk show hosts,
which everyone seems to be
in this country,
then, yes,
l do hate Americans.
(GASPS) What did she say?
Well, Marge, l'm surprised
you haven't been
run out of town.
l'll have you know
l am very well-liked
in Springfield !
Well, there you have it.
Springfield hates America.
Now coming up
after this commercial, l will
be talking even louder!
Don't miss it!
AII over the country tonight,
patriotic Americans
are denouncing Springfield
and its officiaI spokesmen,
the Simpsons.
I decIare today,
December 25th,
We Hate Springfield Day.
(ALL CHEERlNG)
TOM: Overseas,
the reaction tonight
is decidedIy different.
Simpsons be praised!
Praise be to Springfield!
(ULULATlNG)
But not everyone is
uIuIating tonight.
The President announced today
he is pointing warheads at...
Turn that off.
This could destroy our town.
Look what happened to
Hitler City, North Carolina.
lf they hadn't
changed their name
to Charlotte, they'd be sunk.
Sir, conventions are
pulling out of Springfield
left and right.
The Paprika Festival,
Bandana Days!
Sir, we just lost
the Adult Video Awards.
Not the Boneys!
l am honored to announce
that we are changing
the name of our town
to Libertyville!
"$1 7.76"?
l can't afford to sell
a West Side home for that!
But what a fantastical year
for pizza by the slice!
(HUMMlNG)
(SlNGlNG)
Charge a-money for a pizza
Buy myseIf a big-a new car
l'm as patriotic
as the next person,
but changing
the traffic lights
to red, white, and blue
just seems dangerous.
Come on, kid, go!
You got the red !
TEENAGER: Oh, no!
Okay, Mr. Teeny,
before the cops come,
swallow all
these illegal pills,
then run to the vet.
(TEENY CHATTERlNG)
(MUTTERlNG)
"Homeland Noodles
with Uncle Sam Balls."
Apu, aren't you going
a bit overboard
with the patriotism?
l don't think so.
lt is a heartfelt
expression of my true desire
to protect my mahogany noggin.
Uh-oh. Poonam and Uma
are fighting.
No, no.
Those are their
pre-witch hunt names.
Their new names
are Freedom, Lincoln,
Condoleezza, Coke, Pepsi,
Manifest Destiny,
Apple Pie and Superman.
And together,
we are the MacGillicuddys.
(ORGAN MUSlC PLAYlNG)
Lord, give us the courage
to worship the American flag,
be it on a car, a belt buckle,
or on your holy person.
BART: Ay, caramba!
l'd like to say
something about
the current climate
of repression and fear.
Oh, put a cork in it.
Sit down, Saddam !
"Congress shall make no law
"abridging
the freedom of speech
or of the press."
That's from
the First Amendment
to the Constitution.
Thank you.
Thank you, Lisa.
l'm sure your opinion
will not go unnoticed.
(HELlCOPTER WHlRRlNG)
(GUNS COCKlNG)
Simpsons, you are
under arrest
for the violation of the
Government Knows Best Act.
Martha, play something
to lighten the mood.
(PLAYlNG TAKE ME OUT
TO THE BALL GAME)
(SlNGlNG) Buy me some peanuts
and Cracker Jacks
l don't care...
Ow!
l can't believe
they put us in jail !
lt's not a jail.
lt's a reeducation center.
Well, where do you
think we are?
Well, let's see.
After they blindfolded us,
it was left-right-left,
then a three-hour plane ride.
Do you get time off
for snitching on
your cellmates?
You were right, Homie.
We shouldn't have
rocked the boat.
Then none of this
would have ever happened.
Well, we're not the only ones
to be unjustly imprisoned.
Check out all
the left-wing celebrities.
Elmo go to wrong fundraiser.
Bill Clinton?
What are you doing here?
l called the Republican
tax cuts unwise.
And l stand by it.
They're unwise.
I want my Washington Post!
Here's your Washington Post!
You like that, Clinton?
You traitors pipe down !
You're all here
because you hate freedom !
l'm here because
l said imported wines
are better than Napa Valley!
Yeah? Well, why don't you
take a "napa"?
(GRUNTS)
My only crime was driving
a truck full of explosives
in from Canada.
Oh. . . l don't know
why they put
the real ones in
with the joke ones.
(LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
(FLUTE PLAYlNG)
Hello,
l'm the U. S. Constitution.
And I'm over 200 years oId.
But I'm feeIing fine.
I wish I couId say the same
for my crazy cousin,
Bill O'Rights.
(SLURRlNG)
What did l do?
(BOTH LAUGHlNG)
Lisa, that's not funny.
You believe in
the Bill of Rights.
l don't know whether
it's the lack of sleep,
the sodium pentothal,
or that it's
the only cartoon l've seen
in two months.
But this is what
l believe in now.
Oh, Homer, we've gotta
get out of here.
Yeah, yeah. Next commercial.
l know a way out.
Who are you?
l'm the last
registered Democrat.
Tax and spend ! Tax and spend !
(LAUGHS CRAZlLY)
Now, if you want to escape,
you can do it during
the prison talent show
tomorrow night.
l don't want to be
in any stupid talent show.
Not without my
Tennessee walking horses.
Well, you got no choice.
lt's the only way
you'll achieve your goal.
Goal !
Sweet, sweet goal !
Ninety-seven, 98, 99, 1 00!
(CHEERlNG)
Thank you. Vote for me
for best in show.
You guys are on
after Al Franken.
So the guards
would have used up
most of their bullets.
Make your break at
the end of your act.
Now, people have
accused this family
of not loving our country,
but you can't spell
USA without "us," hey?
(ORCHESTRAL MUSlC STARTlNG)
(SlNGlNG) Oh, beautifuI
for spacious skies
For amber waves of grain
(FAST MUSlC PLAYlNG)
Fifty stars and 1 3 stripes
Okay, kids,
show off your pipes
Americans are
brave and IoyaI
So come on jerks,
give us your oiI
My card here says ACLU
Now look what
I'm going to do
To Iove our country
is no chore
Wait right here
for our encore
(CROWD CHEERlNG)
We mean it, don't move!
(ALL LAUGHlNG)
They've escaped !
Okay, kids,
show off your pipes
Dad, why are
you still singing
that stupid song?
Because if they catch us,
we may have to do it again.
And this time
l want it tight.
D'oh !
What genius put a prison
on the middle of an island?
Does everyone remember
their swimming lessons?
Yes.
No.
Great. Dive in !
(COCKS GUN)
Hold your fire.
That walrus will eat them.
No, that's the dad.
But he's eating a seal.
Swim toward San Francisco!
l'm not made of money!
We'll swim to Oakland.
(FOGHORN BLOWlNG)
There's a ship! We're saved !
Oh, what's the use?
Even if they pick us up,
we'll go back to jail
because they think
we hate America.
l don't want to
end up like Elmo,
hanging himself in prison.
Mes amis,
we hate America, too!
Come to France
and we shall mock the country
that saved us
twice from the Germans!
l've always
wanted to go to France.
Your women don't age.
Like Catherine Deneuve.
Eh, you wait till
you see her up close,
then you tell me.
Maman,
please pass the baguette.
The food is so
delicious here.
And these Chanel suits
are five for a dollar.
l'm using
a jacket as a napkin !
And here no one
calls me a fat jerk!
l'm a gourmand !
And yet l miss America.
l miss America, too.
The United States
has its grandeur
and its follies,
but mostly,
it's the place
where all our stuff is.
l wish we could go back.
But l don't think
we're welcome there.
No, Marge,
there's one group that's
always welcome in America,
immigrants without lDs!
(SHlP'S HORN BLASTlNG)
Well, kids,
this is the first chapter
of our brand new
lives in America.
Name?
Simpson.
From now on,
you're the Simps.
That'll save time.
Now kids, it'll take us
a while to assimilate.
l'll start out as a cop,
and with time,
become a dirty cop.
l think l'm going
to like this America.
(SlNGlNG)
Everywhere around the worId
They're coming to America
Every time
that fIag's unfurIed
They're coming to America
Got a dream
to take them there
They're coming to America
English - US - PSDH