♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
All right, I raise a quarter.
-I'm out.
I'm out.
(groans)
Homer, you want
any cards? Homer!
(gagging)
(grunts)
Whoo.
Don't try to eat
these so-called "chips."
Do you want another
card or not?
Huh? Oh okay.
I'll take three.
D'oh! D'oh! D'oh!
Uh, I mean, whoo-hoo.
I'm in.
Let's see your cards.
-Oh, I was bluffing.
-(laughs)
Come to papa!
Wait a minute.
You have
a straight flush, homer!
G'oh! You do this every time, ya--
Oh, you--
(gagging)
Chokin' on my own rage, here.
Hey, don't yell at Homer
just 'cause he's a little slow.
(gasps)
Something was said. Not good.
What was it?
"Don't yell at Homer"!
No, that's okay.
What was it?
"Slow."
They called you "Slow"!
How dare you call me that?
I-- Huh?
Hey, Homer, you still here?
Boy, you are slow.
(gasps)
Something said. Not good.
Get the hell out of here.
-(kick lands)
-(door slams)
(all chewing loudly)
So anyhoo, last night
we're playin' poker, right?
As usual, I'm winning
and not realizing it.
And Lenny says that
I'm, uh-- (chuckles)
Get this--
(laughing)
"A little slow"!
(laughing loudly)
How come you're not laughing?
Do you think I'm slow?
-Buh.
-Snuh.
(groans)
We don't think you're slow,
but on the other hand,
it's not like you go to museums
or read books or anything.
You think I don't want to?
It's those TV networks, Marge.
They won't let me.
One quality show
after another,
each one fresher and more
brilliant than the last.
If they only stumbled once,
just gave us 30 minutes
to ourselves.
But they won't!
They won't let me live!
(sobbing)
Oh, who am I kidding?
-I am slow.
-Oh, Homey.
If you feel so bad
about yourself,
there's always things
you can do to feel better.
Take another bath
in malt liquor?
There's that.
Or you could take
an adult education course.
Oh, and how is "education"
supposed to make
me feel smarter?
Besides, every time I learn
something new,
it pushes some old stuff
out of my brain.
Remember when I took that home wine-making
course and I forgot how to drive?
That's because
you were drunk!
And how.
One way to drive
your man wild
is to wear tight,
revealing clothes.
ALL: Eww!
At this point
I'd like to remind you,
there are no refunds.
All right,
here's the 411, folks.
Say some gangsta
is dissin' your fly girl.
Ya just give' em
one of these.
(hip-hop plays)
♪ Ooh, eh, ah, ooh ♪
(students
protesting)
(chewing, humming, spits)
(pings)
You see, that ping sound
means the spit was on target.
-Now you try.
-(spitting)
-(moans)
-Gettin' better.
Wait a minute.
Even Lenny is teaching a class.
Look at the way they admire
and adore him.
(simpering sounds)
That's it. If he can teach a class,
he can teach a class!
I mean, I can teach a class!
What is your area
of expertise?
Well, I can tell
the difference between butter
and "I Can't Believe
it's Not Butter."
No, you can't, Mr. Simpson.
No one can.
Oh, I failed again.
Everybody can teach
a class but me.
I'm an idiot. What am I gonna
tell my wife and kids?
-Oh, you're married?
-That depends.
Is there another way
to get this job?
No. Mr. Simpson,
what I mean is we may have
a job for you after all.
We need someone to teach a course on
how to build a successful marriage.
I'll do it!
Anything to get me
out of that house,
away from all
that nagging and noise,
uh, of a family of love.
♪ Sha-la-la-la ♪
(children chewing loudly)
Look, everyone.
Now that I'm a teacher, I've
sewed patches on my elbows.
Homer, that's supposed
to be leather patches
on a tweed blazer,
not the other way around.
You've ruined
a perfectly good jacket.
Ah, incorrect, Marge--
Two perfectly good jackets.
I think it's great
you're a teacher, Dad.
So, will you be lecturing
from a standardized text
or using the more
Socratic method
of interactive
class participation?
Yes, Lisa.
Daddy's a teacher.
(doorbell rings)
(chuckles) Oh, Homer.
What a pleasant--
Can't talk now, Flanders.
I've got a class to teach.
But you rang my--
BOY:
Can I take your order?
Nothing for me today.
I've got a class to teach.
Sir, it's a felony
to tease the order box.
-(tires squealing)
-It's all right. I'm a teacher!
(gasps) I didn't know
we could do that.
-(tires squealing)
-(clamoring)
(scraping on blackboard,
students protesting)
All right. The first thing
they told me to do
was to make sure everyone here
is in the right class.
(sputters)
Down the hall, room 12.
MAN (with mouth full):
Thank you.
Ew.
Okay. Let's get started.
Uh, um...
uh-h-h-m...
hmm--
(whispers)
No talking.
(clears throat)
Uh--
Hmm.
Hmm. Oh.
Hmm. No.
Uh--
(smacks lips)
Hmm.
Um, how about if we tell you
our problems
with relationships.
Yeah. Yeah!
That'll eat up some time.
Um, how about you, Otto?
Oh, my standards
are just too high, you know?
I feel like nobody's
good enough for me.
Whoa. You think
you got 'em all,
but you forget about the eggs.
My problem is
I'm a real user of women.
I move in right away and
stay until the money's gone.
Well, I'm a smart woman,
but I make bad choices.
-(whispering)
-(giggling)
Okay. Here's a set of house keys
and my A.T.M. Card.
Um, I was married once,
but, uh,
I just didn't know
how to keep it together.
(sobs)
Come on, Waylon.
Make love to me
the way you used to.
No.
It's that horrible
Mr. Burns, isn't it?
You leave Mr. Burns
out of this!
(yells)
BURNS: Smithers!
Smithers!
Mmm.
Ooh, Mr. Simpson,
are you listening?
-(chewing loudly)
-Simpson!
Huh? Yeah, I was listening.
Very funny.
Oh, ya were not.
You were just eatin' a damn orange.
Oh, yes, yes.
To the untrained eye,
I'm eating an orange,
but to the eye that has brains,
I'm making a point
about marriage.
For you see, marriage
is a lot like an orange.
First you have the skin,
then the sweet,
sweet innards.
(chewing loudly)
I don't understand.
If I wanted to see
a man eat an orange,
I would have taken
the orange-eating class.
The eating of an orange is
a lot like a good marriage.
Just eat the damn oranges!
(students muttering)
This is terrible.
MRS. KRABAPPEL:
Ah! We're leaving.
Ach, let's get out of here.
This is a terrible excuse
for education.
Oh, I told Marge this wouldn't
work the other night in bed.
-In bed? Well.
-What?
So somethin' wasn't workin' in bed, huh?
Heh, heh, heh.
No, that's not what I meant.
Marge and I always
talk things over in bed.
Like the other night,
we were fighting about money.
Ooh, a fight.
Trouble in paradise, huh?
Heh, heh, heh.
I was telling Marge
that we could save some money
if she only dyed her hair
once a month.
-(gasps) Marge dyes her hair?
-Oh, yeah.
She's been as gray as a mule
since she was 17.
Ooh.
Come on. Tell us more.
WILLIE: Tell us about it.
I went on for hours, and they
were hanging on my every word.
-I really think I was born to teach.
-(tires screech)
All right, Simpson.
You were warned about teasing the box.
(screams)
BOY: Wait! I need closure
on that anecdote.
(cash register beeping)
Oh, Mrs. Simpson,
it may interest you to know,
we are having a sale
on blue dye number 52.
It is your hair color,
I believe.
Whatever do you mean?
I don't dye my hair.
(forced laughing)
Nah, nah, nah.
You got it wrong, 'Pu.
She's blue 56.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
We just love
your husband's class.
-That's nice.
-(vehicle speeds away)
Homer, I really don't like you telling
personal secrets in your class.
Marge, I didn't tell 'em
personal stuff.
Today at the Kwik-e-Mart
everybody knew I dyed my hair.
Oh. You mean about you.
All right, maybe I said some things,
some personal things.
But you should've
seen 'em, Marge.
They really wanted to hear
what I had to say.
Mmm. I'm happy about that.
But I think you
can be a good teacher
and still respect our privacy.
Look, Marge.
You don't know what it's like.
I'm the one out there every day
putting his ass on the line.
And I'm not out of order.
You're out of order!
The whole freakin' system
is out of order.
You want the truth?
You can't handle the truth!
'Cause when you reach over
and put your hand into a pile of goo
that was your best friend's face,
you'll know what to do!
Forget it, Marge.
It's Chinatown!
Homer, don't ever tell them
personal stuff about me again!
(quietly) Yes, ma'am.
Now, what is a wedding?
Well, Webster's Dictionary
describes a wedding as
"The process of removing
weeds from one's garden."
(all groan)
Tell us more
about you and Marge.
This is a place of learning,
not a house of...
hearing about things.
-(students groan)
-Guess he's run out of stories.
What a rip-off.
I can't believe I paid $10,000
for this course.
What the heck
was that lab fee for?
No. Wait. Uh, um--
Wait. I-- Yes.
(clears throat)
I do have a story about
two other young marrieds.
(students murmuring)
Now, the wife of this couple
has an interesting quirk in the bedroom.
It seems she goes wild with desire
if her husband nibbles on her elbow.
-We need names!
-Well, let's just call 'em, uh,
Mr. "X" And Mrs. "Y."
So, anyway, Mr. "X" would say,
"Marge, if this doesn't
get your motor running,
my name isn't
Homer J. Simpson ."
(all gasping, murmuring)
-Huh?
-Ooh, Homer.
Don't you have to get to class?
Not tonight, Marge.
Tonight we can eat a nice,
leisurely dinner at home.
Oh. Well, that will be l--
(gasps)
What the darn?
Marge, you'll
never guess what.
My whole class is here.
They're going to observe
the human peep show
that is our lives.
Apparently, that disturbing odor
was the food.
So, little Lisa,
apple of my eye,
how are things down
at the old schoolhouse?
I find this demeaning and embarrassing
beyond my worst nightmares.
(chuckling)
And how's my little
major leaguer?
Catch any june bugs today?
Well, me and Milhouse took
some mail from a mail truck
and threw it down the sewer.
Son, I know you meant well,
but that wasn't
the right thing to do.
What the hell are you
talkin' about?
You're the one
who double-dared us.
Why, you little--
-(choking)
-CLASS: Ooh.
Homer!
-I'm outta here.
-Me too.
(students murmuring quietly)
(forced laughing)
Well, now that the little ones
have toddled off to bed--
I want this to end now.
Hey, Homer.
Why don't you just nibble her elbow?
That always melts her butter, right?
Heh, heh, heh.
(gasps)
All right.
Okay.
Everybody out!
Ooh,
she's gotta have it.
Get out! Get out! Get out! Get out!
Get out-out-out-out-out-out-out!
All right, we're breaking early
tonight, class.
For tomorrow, you should read
pages seven through 18
in Lisa's diary.
-You too.
-Huh?
Get out!
But I'm not
in the cla--
Is any of this gonna
be on the test?
'Cause I wasn't
payin' attention.
Come on, Marge. Let me in!
There's crickets out here.
Okay, Marge. Things were said.
Mistakes were made.
Let's end this madness
and get on with our lives.
You just don't get it,
do you, Homer?
You told personal things
about our lives,
even after
you promised you wouldn't.
-I can't trust you anymore.
-But I learned my lesson.
It'll never happen again.
Hey, Homer.
What's the big brouhaha-ha?
Ah, Marge is throwin' me out
-for blabbin' about her elbow thing.
-(groans)
Honey, the door blew shut.
Oh. Fine.
If that's what you want,
you've got it.
This scene is gettin' old, man.
I'm hittin' the road.
Maybe I'll drop you a line
someday from wherever I wind up
in this crazy old world.
Kids, your father and I are going
through a really tough time right now,
and I don't know
what's going to happen.
But just remember that both your mom
and your dad love you very, very much.
Wow, I've never seen Mom
so mad at Homer before.
I'll tell you
a secret, Bart.
Every time I'm worried
about Mom and Dad,
I go to the attic and add
to my ball of string.
(screeches)
Earth base, this is
commander Bart McCool.
We are under attack by
the Zorrinid brain changers.
Quickly, into
the safety dome, Milbot.
(in monotone)
Affirmative, humanoid.
BOTH: Ew!
Don't mind me, boys.
Just scrubbin' my undies.
Sorry, Bart.
Your dad kinda blew the fantasy.
I only like it
when I'm pretend-scared.
Keep up the roughhousing, son.
Without a strong male
presence in the house,
you could turn
sissy overnight.
Oh, these stubborn
grass stains.
Oh, good.
Reverend Lovejoy will
make Marge take me back.
He has to push
the sanctity of marriage,
or his god will punish him.
-Get a divorce.
-Mm-hmm.
But isn't that a sin?
Marge, just about
everything is a sin.
You ever sat down
and read this thing?
Technically, we're not
allowed to go to the bathroom.
(sighs)
(moans softly)
Good night, Marge.
(kisses)
Oh, why didn't I take
a picture?
I had ten years
to take a picture.
Hmm. Funny the way everything
reminds me of Homer.
HOMER'S VOICE:
I love you.
Will you marry me, Marge?
You mean,
I'm gonna be a daddy?
I hope we'll always be
together, together, together--
-Together?
-(tires screech)
(screams, grunting)
Ooh.
Here, Dad. I brought you some nice--
(yelps)
Good news, Lisa. I don't need
your mother anymore.
I've created a replacement that's
superior to her in almost every way.
Dad, that's just a plant.
Lisa! You will respect
your new mother.
Now, give her a kiss.
Kiss her!
(yelps)
Oh-my-God! Oh-my-God!
Oh-my-God! (panting)
All right.
Let's get our stories straight.
She tripped, right?
Look. I brought you
some nice pudding.
Ah, your flesh mother
used to bring me pudding.
Oh, I miss Marge.
Lisa, you're smart.
Help me trick her into taking me back.
Dad, you can't trick somebody
into loving you.
There's a reason two people
come together and stay together.
There's something
they give each other
that nobody else can give them.
If you want to get Mom back,
you just have to remember
what you give her
that nobody else can.
I'll pay you $40
if you think of it for me.
-No.
-Okay. 30.
Good luck, Dad.
All right, brain.
It's all up to you.
If you don't think of what it is,
we'll lose Marge forever.
Eat the pudding. Eat the pudding.
Eat the pudding.
Okay, but then
we gotta get to work.
(eating loudly)
(moans softly)
(doorbell chimes)
(exhales)
(clears throat)
Oh. H-hi, Marge.
I heard you and Homer broke up,
so I'm declarin' my intentions
to move in on his territory.
Here, I, uh,
brung ya some posies.
Oh, my.
I'm very flattered, but
I'm not really interested.
Sheesh. I come here,
I get dressed up all nice-like,
put my heart on the line,
and I make a fool of myself.
Oh, boy. Oh, I'm gonna
start bawlin' here.
Hmm, why don't you come inside
for a drink of water?
'Kay.
Hmm. Clean house,
no silverfish.
Could've been very happy here.
(knocking)
-Homer.
-Moe.
-What are you doin' here?
-I, um-- Well, I--
I never touched her, Homer.
Homer, I swear,
I never touched her.
MARGE:
Here's your water, Moe.
I didn't ask her
for no water.
She's lyin', Homer,
she's lyin'.
She told me you were dead.
That's the only reason I--
I didn't do nothin'!
(glass breaking, Moe shouts)
Bye, Moe.
Homer,
what happened to you?
Marge, I figured out what
I can give you that no one else can:
A bouquet of po-- Ohhh.
I give up. I don't deserve
to live with you.
-Hmm.
-(table bumps against wall)
Oh. My tattered rags
are caught on
your coffee table.
Oh, here.
Let me help you.
(muttering softy)
Wait a minute.
Wait, that's it.
I know now what I can offer you
that no one else can:
Complete and utter dependence.
Homer, that's not a good thing.
Are you kidding?
It's a wondrous, marvelous thing.
Marge, I need you more than
anyone else on this entire planet
could possibly
ever need you.
I need you to take care of me,
to put up with me
and most of all,
I need you to love me,
because I love you.
(sad grunt)
But how do I know
I can trust you?
Marge, look at me.
We've been separated for a day,
and I'm as dirty as a Frenchman.
In another few hours
I'll be dead.
I can't afford
to lose your trust again.
I must admit,
you really do make a gal feel needed.
Wait till my class
hears about this.
Kidding!
(sighs) Oh, it's great to be
indoors with my family.
I'm really glad
you're back, Dad.
I knew you could do it.
Now don't screw it up.
Look, Dad.
I missed you so much,
I couldn't concentrate in
school and I got an "F."
Hey, this is dated
two weeks ago.
Oh. Sorry.
Here's a fresh one.
And I have a special
present for you,
but I'll give it
to you later tonight.
Special present? I don't
wanna wait. I want it now!
I want the children to see.
Ooh.
Oh, right.
Later.
(chuckling)
So, Marge, are you
really happy? Really?
-Hey, Moe.
-(yelps)
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.