♪ The Simpsons ♪
(chalk screeches)
(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(tires screeching)
(horn honks)
(tires screech)
Ahh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
♪♪
Gah!
(barking)
Uh-oh.
I, uh, I think
the boy's hurt.
Oh, for crying out loud.
Just give him a nickel,
and let's get going.
-(horn honks)
-I think we should call an ambulance, sir.
(muttering)
Hey, cool.
I'm dead.
MAN: Please hold on
to the handrail.
Do not spit over the side.
Por favor, aguantese
en la baranda.
No escupa...
Aunt Hortense...
Great Grampa Simpson.
Please hold on
to the handrail.
-Snowball.
-Do not spit over the side.
-Aah!
-We told you to hold on to the handrail.
We asked you not to
spit over the side.
Howdy, stranger.
I'm Bart Simpson.
Who the hell are you?
Please allow me
to introduce myself.
I'm the devil.
(evil laugh) And you've earned
eternal damnation
for your lifetime
of evil deeds, Bart.
Spitting off the escalator
just clinched it.
Hey, I'm innocent, man.
(laughing)
Innocent, huh?
Everybody's innocent.
Okay.
Let's just pull up
your file here.
Hmm. Seems to be a mistake.
According to this,
you're not due to arrive here
until the next time
the Yankees win the pennant.
That's nearly
a century from now.
(chuckles)
Boy, is my face red.
Bart? Bart?
Um, say, is there
anything I can do
to avoid
coming back here?
Oh, sure, yeah,
but you wouldn't like it.
Okay. See you later, then.
Good-bye, Bart.
Remember...
lie, cheat, steal
and listen
to heavy metal music.
Yes, sir.
Intercom: Doctor Warner, you're
wanted in radiology, please.
-He's awake!
-Oh, Bart, we thought for a minute
-you'd gone away from us.
-I did go away, Mom.
I was miles and miles
and miles away,
writhing in agony
in the pits of hell,
and you were there.
And you and you and you...
You I've never seen before.
Hey, yeah, who are you?
I saw you chasing Bart's ambulance.
Hutz is the name, Mr. Simpson.
Lionel Hutz, attorney at law.
Here's my card. It turns into a sponge
when you put it in water.
Ooh, classy.
I'd like to talk to you about
bringing legal action
against the fiend
who did this to your boy.
Well, the fiend who did this
to my boy is my boss.
And besides, the doctor says
it's just a bump on the head
and a broken toe. Nothing serious.
Doctors. Doctors are idiots.
There's no telling what kind
of permanent injuries he might have.
You might have to wait on him
hand and foot
for the rest
of his natural life.
That's the downside.
Now here's the good part.
You can ching, ching, ching,
-cash in on this tragedy.
-Wow.
Excuse me, Mr. Hutz.
Are you a shyster?
How does a nice little girl
like you, know a big word like that?
Mr. Hutz, this is hardly
the time or place
to discuss this.
You're right, you're right.
When you feel up to it
come over to my office
and we'll talk about it.
Lionel Hutz,
attorney at law.
What's that, a broken neck?
Great!
-Hello, Dr. Hibbert.
-Hello, Lisa.
Well, we've got a nasty bump
on our head, haven't we?
-Ow! Quit it.
-And a little tiny broken toe.
Ow. quit it.
Is he well enough for me
to mother him unbearably, Doctor?
Mmm, better let him
rest up a while first.
Hey, Simpson, I heard
Mr. Burns crushed your boy.
Yeah. If I wasn't so spineless,
I'd march into Mr. Burns'
office right now and...
-Simpson.
-(screams, chokes)
Mr. Burns wants you to march
into his office right now.
Uh-oh.
Ah, Simpson, at last we meet.
Nice to meet you too, sir.
Yes. My attorneys
have advised me
to pay you for running
over your child,
-so I'm cutting you a check.
-Really? Great.
(straining)
$100. Of course,
you'll have to sign a waiver
relinquishing your right to sue
and so forth. Merely a formality.
A hundred bucks?
It's a very generous offer,
sir, but medical bills alone--
Oh, so extortion is the name
of your little game, is it Simpson?
Very well.
Then you get nothing.
I have the finest lawyers
in Springfield, Simpson.
Tangle with me, and
I'll crush you like a paper cup.
(straining)
Throw him out, Smithers.
You don't have
to do that, Mr. Burns.
I can throw myself out.
(door slams)
Ooh... Lionel Hutz.
Right in here,
Mr. Simpson.
Any calls, Della?
Calls? Oh, calls.
Yes, uh, the Supreme Court
called again.
They need your help
on some freedom thing.
Tell them to sit tight.
I'll get back to them.
This way, Mr. Simpson.
You sure have got
some education, Mr. Hutz.
Yes, Harvard, Yale,
M.I.T., Oxford,
The Sorbonne, The Louvre...
-(siren begins wailing)
-Oh. Oh, well.
Mr. Simpson,
the state bar forbids me
from promising you
a big cash settlement,
but just between you and me,
I promise you
a big cash settlement.
My fee is 50%.
50%?
You'll be getting more
than just a lawyer, Mr. Simpson.
You'll also be getting
this exquisite fauxpearl
necklace-- a $99 value--
as our gift to you.
Well, I don't know.
You and I might have
different ideas
about just how big
a big cash settlement is.
A million dollars?
Whoo-hoo! Oh!
I stand corrected.
A million bucks is a-okay.
(wolf whistle)
Now we'll get
a real doctor's opinion.
-Bad news.
-Oh?
Your son is a very sick boy.
Just look at the x-rays.
You see that dark spot there?
Whiplash.
Whiplash? Oh, no.
And this smudge here
that looks like my fingerprint?
No, that's trauma.
-Mmm.
-Am I gonna die?
-Yes, son.
-Homer!
No, of course you're not
going to die.
Everything's fine.
Will I ever
play baseball again?
No!
(sobbing)
But I played baseball
this morning.
That's right, he did.
Excuse me,
but Dr. Hibbert has been
our family physician
for years
and he thought Bart was fine.
Oh, Dr. Hibbert
(sarcastically)
from Johns Hopkins Medical School.
With all due respect, Mrs. Simpson,
you're not a doctor.
The boy's not a doctor.
I'm not a doctor.
The only person in this room
who even comes close is this man.
Stop, you're embarrassing me.
Doctor, are you sure there isn't
a little soft tissue trauma
in the facial area?
Oh, yeah, tons of it.
Just say when.
A million dollars? Smithers!
I want this Homer J. Simpson fired.
Uh, do you think that's
wise, Mr. Burns?
I mean,
think of the headlines.
BURNS: Hmm?
Hmm?
Ooh.
What about the headlines?
Well, the press might
be critical of you
for firing the crippled boy's
father so soon after the accident.
Well, all right then.
I don't want
to seem like an ogre.
I'll bide my time.
Let him twist in
the wind slowly, slowly.
And then, when the papers have found
their new flavor of the month,
they'll find out
this cat has claws!
Good thinking, sir.
Now let's pretend
you're on the witness stand.
-How are you, Bart?
-Fine.
(pleasantly) Oh fine, isn't that nice?
Bart says he's fine.
Wrong! You are not fine!
You're in constant pain!
I am in constant pain.
Dad, may I please make
an observation?
-What is it?
-I think this is all a charade
to make Bart look more injured
than he really is.
Maybe Lisa does have a point.
I don't mind you boys
doing this in the living room,
but in court, doesn't Bart
have to tell the truth?
Yeah, but what is truth,
if you follow me?
Now, Bart, can you roll your eyes
back in your head like this?
Oh, you mean like I'm dead?
Yeah, sure.
The kid's a pro.
Springfield Municipal Court
is now in session,
Judge Multon presiding.
Your Honor, my client
has instructed me
to remind the court how rich
and important he is,
that he is not like
other men.
I should be able to run over
as many kids as I want!
(gasping)
Mr. Burns, I must warn you
that if you continue to disrupt
the court in this way,
I will have to cite you
for contempt.
You wouldn't dare.
Well, no, I guess I wouldn't.
Calling Bartholomew J. Simpson
to the stand.
(crowd groans)
Oh, please.
Hello, Bart.
Now you know the difference
between telling the truth
and telling a lie,
don't you, son?
-Maybe.
-Uh-huh.
Well, you wouldn't lie
to the United States,
would you, Bart?
-No.
-Good.
-Proceed, Mr. Hutz.
-Thank you, Your Honor.
Now, Bart, I want you
to tell the jury,
in your own words,
exactly what happened
on the day of the accident.
Yes, sir.
It was a beautiful
Sunday afternoon.
I was playing in
my wholesome, childlike way,
little realizing that I was
about to be struck down
by the luxury car of death.
(children screaming)
Defenseless child at 3:00.
(evil laughter)
Luckily, I was not killed
that day,
although sometimes,
I wish I had been.
Oh, he's lying.
Now that's
believable testimony.
-Hmm.
Now, Mr. Burns, would you please
relate in your own words
exactly what really happened
on the day of the accident?
Certainly.
Oh, it was a beautiful day.
The sun was shining. I was driving
to the orphanage to pass out toys.
Suddenly, that
incorrigible Simpson boy
-darted in front of me.
-(Burns stammering)
(laughing)
Ahh!
Oh, my goodness.
Look what's happened.
Oh, it's not important, sir.
Let's drive on.
Why, you despicable,
cold-blooded monster.
Regardless of what you think, we will
summon help and comfort the dear boy
until an ambulance arrives.
No!
Take me!
I'm old!
And that's what happened.
What are you looking at me
like that for?
You believed
his cock-and-bull story.
It's looking good,
Mr. Simpson.
It's looking very, very good.
They hate me?
What trial were you watching?
Maybe a settlement--
Oh, yes, settlements, fine.
Hang your heads in shame,
you over-priced, under-brained,
glorified notary publics!
BURNS: Just get that big ape
to my house tonight,
and we'll buy him off
with a banana or two.
...and that ugly customer
was the last Indonesian
rhino on Earth.
Hmm. I didn't know
you liked animals.
Oh, I don't like
everything about them,
-just their heads.
-(both snicker)
Wwll, would you care
for some wine, old buddy?
-Don't mind if I do.
-Go, go.
Bottoms up, Simpson.
There's plenty more where that came from.
Mr. Burns, are you trying
to get me drunk?
Yes. Now then Homer,
old chum,
I'm sure you'll agree
with me that this trial
is an affront to our
collective dignity.
What do you say we
settle this man-to-man?
-You mean duke it out?
-Oh, no.
I mean I'm prepared
to offer you
a most generous
cash settlement.
A princely sum--
Well, a handsome sum that
can end this little imbroglio
once and for all.
$500,000.
-Goodness.
-Bup-bup-bup!
Don't answer me now.
Relax, talk it over
with the missus.
Soak in the opulence
of your surroundings,
and dream of what might be.
Smithers, let's go
powder my nose.
Well, Marge,
what do you think?
Well, I don't know.
Maybe we should take his money
and put all this ugliness
behind us.
Hmm. The fish is in the pan.
MARGE:
What do you think, Homer?
I'll tell you what I think.
I think he thinks
I'm an idiot!
The only reason
he's offering us this
is because he knows
he's gonna lose at trial
and have to pay us
a cool million.
Oh! I feel faint.
$500,000!
I spit on his $500,000!
-Hmm.
-Homer, what's happened to you?
All this greediness and lying
and shifty lawyers
and phony doctors...
Phony doctors? Hello.
Do you know what I'd settle for,
if it was up to me?
Bart's medical bills
and an apology.
And you won't even get that.
Sorry. Offer's expired.
I guess we'll just have to let the jury
decide. Twelve good men and true.
Good day.
Smithers, release the hounds.
(snarling, barking)
-(gavel bangs)
-Your Honor,
I would like to call
to the stand
Mrs. Homer J. Simpson.
(gasping, murmuring)
Do you swear to tell
the truth, the whole truth
and nothing but the truth,
so help you God?
Mmm... Yes, I do.
She sounded like
she was taking that
-awful seriously.
-Oh, the truth.
Mrs. Simpson, does
the name Julius Hibbert
mean anything to you?
Yes, he's been our family
physician and trusted friend
ever since the day
I became a mother.
He's seen us through everything,
from colds to impetigo,
with competence
and loving care.
But wait a minute.
I'm confused.
This court heard
expert testimony
from one Dr. Nick Riviera.
-What is your opinion of him?
-Mmm.
-Mrs. Simpson?
-I'm sorry,
but my mother always said
if you can't say anything nice,
don't say anything at all.
Will that hold up in court?
No, I've tried it before.
Mrs. Simpson, what is
your opinion of Dr. Riviera?
And let me remind you
that you're under oath.
Hmm. Well, to be honest,
he seemed a lot
more concerned
about wrapping Bart in bandages
than in making him feel better.
And he mispronounced words
that even I know, like abdomen.
And his office was dirty.
Now that I think about it,
I'm not sure he's even a doctor.
D'oh!
And Mrs. Simpson,
could you describe for us
in your own words
Bart's intense mental
anguish and suffering?
-Well, I don't know how intense it was.
-Uh-huh.
But, well, I guess he did
miss three days of school.
-Oh, three days.
-Although he doesn't really like school
-all that much.
-No.
So I guess that may not
count as anguish.
-No, it doesn't, Mrs. Simpson.
-It was a little hard on me
having him around the house
all that time.
Could you put a dollar amount
on all these hardships?
Well, we pay Bart five dollars
a week to take out the trash.
I suppose if he'd been able
to do it that week,
we might have
given him the $5.
Five dollars?
But your lawyer,
assuming he is a lawyer,
is asking for a million.
Well, we can't blame them
for trying, can we? Heh heh.
Thank you very much,
Mrs. Simpson.
(sobbing)
Oh, Marge!
(sinister laughing)
I'm going to write a figure
on this piece of paper.
It's not quite as large
as the last one,
-but I think you'll find it fair.
-(Smithers chuckles)
-I think we should take it.
-(shuddering)
HOMER (thinking):
A million dollars.
My wife cost me
a million dollars.
Homer, would you like some
more macaroni and cheese?
Yeah, a million dollars worth,
you treacherous snake woman.
-No, thank you.
-Some string beans?
No, I don't want any string beans either,
you two-timing back-stabbing...
Uh-oh, better answer.
No, thank you.
Some celery with
cream cheese on it?
Just mouth polite nothings.
No, thank you.
You know what would have
really been cool?
If we got that million bucks.
-Bart, please.
-What?
We could have bought tons
of great stuff, Mom.
Maids, a pool, fancy sweaters--
-Stop me if I'm wrong.
-Marge, dear,
would it be alright if
I went over to Moe's
-for a drink?
-Why, sure.
HOMER (thinking): I don't know
if I'll ever come back here.
Good night.
(thinking) Hmm. My woman's intuition
is telling me something.
-I wonder what--
-(door closes)
Oh, my God.
Well, that's it.
I guess this is the glass
I'm gonna die in.
Ah, you're better off.
Rich people aren't happy.
From the day they're born
till the day they die,
they think they're happy,
but trust me, they ain't.
Moe. I wish he'd shut up.
Hey. Hubba-hubba.
-Yow!
-Look, a chick!
And it's not even
ladies night.
Hey, hey, guys.
Knock it off.
HOMER: It's just my wife.
-Well, hello.
-Va-va-voom.
My name is Marge.
Homer, I'd like you
to forgive me
for doing the right thing.
Oh, Marge.
We've squabbled over money
before. Never this much.
I mean, I know this is
different than that time
I washed your pants with the 20 in
the pocket, but I--
No, no, no.
You think this is about money?
Well, it's not.
It's worse, Marge.
I'm afraid that from now on,
when I look at you,
I'm not gonna see
the wife by my side
or the mother of my children.
I'm just gonna see the dame
who blew my one big chance.
-What are you saying, Homer?
-I'm saying...
(thinking) She's been your wife
for ten years.
You've had
three children together.
It's time to be honest
with her.
I'm not sure
I love you anymore.
-(gasps)
-But don't worry.
I'll never let on.
I'll still do all the bed stuff.
-Maybe it won't be so bad.
-Oh, my Lord!
Well, I don't want to wait
another minute to find out
whether you
love me anymore.
I think that you should look me
in the eyes and find out.
-No.
-Homer, look at me.
All right, all right, look at her
if it'll shut her up.
Start with the feet.
Still angry.
Good. Good, Homer. Good.
This is tough.
Need refreshment.
Ah, good old
trustworthy beer.
My love for you
will never die.
All right, all right,
got to look at the wife
straight in the eyes
and tell her...
Oh, who am I kidding?
I love you more than ever.
I love you too.
Sorry to scare you
like that, babe.
(crowd cheers)
Okay, everybody.
For the next 15 minutes,
one-third off on every pitcher.
(cheering)
MOE: Hey, one per customer.
Domestic beer only.
Hey, no sharing.
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.