(exclaims anxiously)
(exclaiming)
(school bell ringing)
(Barney belches)
(playing glissandos on harp)
(playing random melody)
(strums strings)
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
(grunts)
(cowboy melody plays
on harmonica)
(ethereal chord chimes)
(strumming guitar)
(whale singing)
(eerie melody plays)
(jaunty circus music playing)
(hoarse barking)
(electric guitar
plays surf riff)
(footsteps thudding)
(various melodies and
sounds shifting rapidly)
(melodies and sounds
shifting faster)
(remote shattering)
♪ The Simpsons 25x10 ♪
Married to the Blob
Original Air Date on January 12, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
NARRATOR:
High above Zenith City,
Radioactive Man keeps
a lonely vigil!
RADIOACTIVE MAN:
All seems quiet.
Maybe I'll fly to China
and get some takeout.
(gasps)
A sky tweet from
Commissioner Sweeney!
This looks like a job for:
@radioactivemanó01.
(whooshing)
Leaping Leptons! It's
the Fossil Fuel Four!
Old King Coal...
Patroleus Rex...
French Femme Fatale
Charcoal Briquette...
...and the enemy of
drinking water everywhere,
the Fracker.
(grunting with effort)
Stop attacking the
nuclear plant...
this country's safest
energy source!
Studies show, I'm America's best hope
for energy independence. (laughs)
Those studies were
industry financed.
You lie!
Holy Hedrons!
I need backup!
Calling Citizen Solar, and
his sidekick Wind Lad.
(French accent): I believe you
will find them lacking in energy.
It's too cloudy.
People don't like
the noise I make.
Ehhh...
Petroleus Rex, please
remember when you used to be
Environmental Scientist
Rex Bernstein.
I have become my destiny.
(grunts, groans)
I'll crush you like
a gnat, King Coal.
(shouting in pain)
(grunting with effort)
(shouting)
Half life.
Quar... ter life.
Eighth life.
Gone.
Frack-cellent!
(laughs sinisterly)
They killed off
Radioactive Man?
I did not see that coming.
Die-carumba!
They'll just reboot Radioactive Man
in an overpriced new origin issue
and get clueless fanboys like you
to line up at midnight to buy them.
Clueless fanboys in costume.
(text alert chimes)
MILHOUSE:
Wow!
Midnight.
I won't know which day
to write in my diary.
- Homer.
- What?
Will you take me to buy a comic
book Tuesday at midnight?
And miss the back
half of Jimmy Kimmel?
That's when
he experiments, boy.
You never watched an episode
of Jimmy Kimmel in your life.
Yes, I have. After the
Oscars, when he forces you.
(Ralph Wiggum singing
random melody)
(door bell dings,
all cheering, clapping)
Quiet. Quiet!
And attention please,
valued customers.
You will each be allowed to enter
the store, and buy one copy.
Swallow your gum, now.
(all gulp)
MILTON: Oh. Oh. Mr. Book Guy.
Can I go first?
I was once cast to play
Fallout Boy in a movie.
Tell it to Harlan Ellison.
I think, you
over-privileged kids
with your electronic tablets
and your talking phones,
wouldn't know a good piece of fiction
if your iPod read it to your ass.
I wish someone would have
come from the future,
and warned me
not to talk to you.
That's my idea!
You're stealing my idea!
Sorry.
C-B-G. What's the happs, my man?
Well, well, well.
If it isn't Milo,
the owner of my main
competitor, Coolsville.
Or should I say,
"Foolsville."
That is some tasty
cashish, my friend.
Indeed.
And how did you
spend your evening?
Um... Let's see.
I wrote a Lost
fan fiction finale
that also answers all the
questions from Twin Peaks.
Reranked all the Doctor Whos
by puffiness of the hair.
Oh, and I also got married
to my actual, non-imaginary,
comic-tolerating
girlfriend, Strawberry.
Now when Milo talks to
himself, it won't seem crazy.
So, Milo talks to himself.
We will treasure
that information.
Yes... we will.
Now, if you'll excuse me, I'm gonna share
this primo origin ish with my bride.
Even the mintiest comic
is just acidifying pulp,
if you have no one to
read it with, right?
Nerds don't get girls.
These days they do, man.
Comic-Con is now
eight percent women.
STRAWBERRY:
Burn!
Wrong... Wrong!
Wro... Where is he?
Come on, buddy, I gotta get home and
climb into bed with my loving wife.
Oh, right. You have
a loving wife.
Oh. Marge and I
get along perfect.
We're like George Burns
and John Denver.
Oh, man!
Carrying these kids
is hard on my back.
Oh...!
Oh, yeah!
- And now to Moe's.
- Look at him. Look.
He's got family... friends.
What do I have?
Oof. Jimmy Olsen
vs. Matter Eater Lad.
Hm. This is better than
I remembered, actually.
No...! No it isn't!
It-It's horrible!
(moans)
The only thing that could make
this moment more cliched,
is if I started to sing
about my feelings.
And... here I go.
(slow, melancholy intro)
♪ I've always been happy
♪ To call myself single
♪ No Mary Jane
♪ Or Lois Lane
♪ With whom I'd co-mingle
♪ You could say that I was
♪ An unstackable Pringle
♪ I've got originals signed
♪ By Siegel and Shuster
♪ But they don't satisfy
♪ In the way that
they used-ter ♪
♪ It really don't matter if
you've got a Cap Anson ♪
♪ If you spend your nights
in your underwear prancin' ♪
♪ With your cardboard stand
♪ Of Scarlett Johansson!
(yelling, grunting)
♪ Guess I've always
been lonely ♪
♪ But I've never revealed it
♪ Dropped my heart into Mylar
♪ And then... (sobs)
♪ Vacuum sealed... it.
(quiet sigh)
Stan Lee!
Or, is it my imagination?
I'm your imagination.
The real Stan Lee's over there.
Excelsior!
But listen, as comic
book guys go,
you're trim, friendly,
and, quite a catch.
(laughs)
But now... your
opportunity is knocking.
Huh...?!
Don't let it slip by.
- Can you help me?
- I can only watch.
I cannot interfere.
New Radioactive Man
number one, please.
Come on, nudnik.
Ask her out.
- You're interfering.
- Hey, I'm 90 years old.
I can do what I want.
Um... Er...
Stammer. Eh...
C-Can I sign you up for our
frequent buyer's club?
The Just Us League?
You would be member number 003.
I... I am the first two.
Sure. I am Kumiko
Nakamura from Osaka.
I am visiting America's
saddest cities,
as research for my
autobiographical manga.
Volume Six, Springfield.
Land of Angry Tears.
That's you.
The man with sparkling
eyes, and zigzag beard.
- You have seen me before?
- Yes. Through window.
But you don't see me.
You're either looking down in
disgust, or up in disdain.
I think you have great soul.
Would you permit me to go in the
back, and do a brief inventory?
(muffled):
She tolerates me!
Ah... Is it too soon to give
you flowers in a Hulk hand?
It is the perfect time.
(doorbell rings)
(humming happily)
Hmm?
(yelling): Bart! Your
comic vendor's here.
Uh, actually, it is you
that I am here to see.
I, um, I need your help.
I am getting ready for a date.
(stammers)
The closest thing I have to a father
is the Obi-Wan doll in my store.
And he comes from a race
of celibate knights.
- So...
- I will help you.
As long as our bellies never touch
again like they are right now.
BOTH:
Ew!
Oh...!
Why pick me?
Because you are the only
fat man in real life
who ever got a hot woman.
- Hey.
- Ooh... (laughs)
Well, come in.
I'll explain how it all works.
Okay. It helps if she's got a
mother she's trying to get back at.
MARGE:
Aw...
No woman will be able to
resist you, dressed like this.
Now, remember, don't be
the way you normally are
and sustain that for
the rest of your life.
Kumiko, uh, meet my dear friends
uh, Homer and Marge Simpson.
I-In my country,
it is a tradition
to bring a much older
couple on a first date.
It is not in any way,
weird, or-or sad.
Does anyone tell you that you look
like the man on a box of Mr. Sparkle?
Aka ni taishte burei da!
Yogore o yaburu!
In Japan, drinking your detergent
is a popular method of suicide.
(gasps)
Honki da yo?!
Kumiko, for you, we chose the
coolest restaurant in town.
But the walls are
covered with garbage.
MARGE:
Oh...
Not garbage, Americana.
Here's some more Americana,
that bubbled up in the swamp.
Here you go: Your All-American
Fifty State Potato Skin Sampler.
Okay: Wisconsin, cheddar.
Maryland, blue crab.
They're neither in alphabetical,
nor geographical order.
What-What madness is this?
Please, sir. Ask your questions
after all 50 "tates."
I cannot hide the snide inside.
Oh. I don't mind.
If you think it's stupid,
say it's stupid.
Really?
In Japan, no one ever
says what they think.
We know our game
shows are degrading
and our baseball
fences are too close.
But no one says anything.
(gasps)
Attention, restaurateurs!
(diners murmuring)
You should've spent
less on the kitsch,
and more on
the kitch-en.
With this bowl of
Chuck's Cherokee Salsa,
I baptize you mediocre, at best.
(laughs)
American nerd snark is
the finest in the world.
Let's go walking and
mocking in the rain.
I'm in love!
And, yet, still
a little bitter.
It-It's surprising.
(Japanese pop song
"Ponponpon" playing)
JIM-JAM BONKS: Father,
why-sa you-sa forsake-a me-sa?
♪
(applause)
Marge, Homer, you have
nurtured our love
like Steven Speilberg nurtured the
careers of Zemeckis and Gale.
(sympathetically):
Oh...
So, we want you to know, I
have decided to move in
to the basement
under his store.
At last, we'll be
in the same bed.
Just like Batman and Robin.
- HOMER: Ohh...
- MARGE: Hmm...
Homer, I want you
to take Kumiko
and Comic Book Guy a
housewarming present,
and maybe check in on them?
We talked about this, Marge.
The hammock is a
chore-free zone.
Apparently, including tying
the knots on the hammock.
And getting the termites
out of the trees.
(squeaking)
Not a word.
(Japanese accent):
Excuse me, sir.
I am looking for my daughter.
I thought this was her residence, but
all I see is a store full of, uh,
non-pornographic manga.
(gasps)
You're Kumiko's father?
Welcome, sensei.
I am not a Kung fu instructor.
I am a humble salary man
who could kick your ass.
Say, has anyone told
you you look like...
I know. Mr. Sparkle.
I was going to say, like
you're going to have a stroke.
(laughs)
I get that a lot too.
Now, please,
where is my daughter?
Okay. She moved in
with her boyfriend.
Well, he's not a boy. He's immature.
But, fat and old.
So, an obese nerd has stolen my
daughter to live in his basement?
- I didn't tell you about the basement.
- It was an obvious guess!
(bell dings)
(crying)
Daughter! You are
coming back to Japan!
There are 87 old people who
need you to take care of them.
No. Please... Please. I
was becoming cuddly.
I deleted rants from my blog.
You can retrieve rants if you
did not empty your trash.
Goodbye!
Now I know I've got a heart...
because it's breaking.
Wizard of Oz reference!
Did I do that?
Urkle reference!
(panting)
Help me.
Fire reference!
(panting): I can't stop.
I can't stop.
Homer Simpson, this was your
doing. And I want you to fix it.
I have a bad feeling about this!
Every action movie
ever made reference!
Now!
Yeah, Homer. We have
much in common.
We both love our daughters,
and discipline our sons.
No... discipline would imply,
I'm trying to make him better.
So... are you married?
(sighs)
My dear Michiko
has passed away.
But she's always with me.
You promise double suicide.
You hear what you want to hear.
Always with me.
Another drink!
Something stronger!
(creaks)
JAPANESE BARTENDER (dramatically):
Snake rice wine.
Now, that's disgusting.
Wine made of rice?
Try some.
Hai.
(hissing)
(Homer slurring drunkenly)
(Mr. Nakamura drunkenly laughs)
(slurring): Why didn't I
stop with the snake wine?
Why did I drink the fish wine?
That was the aquarium.
(quiet, gentle melody plays)
(engine humming)
(tires screeching)
You didn't see nothin'. Scram.
♪
(clanking)
Uh! I am ruined
by whimsy.
MILHOUSE'S VOICE: The good thing
is, soon I'll be a beautiful swan.
(cackling)
Aw...
(whimpers)
What's going on here?
BART & LISA:
We'll explain it.
The rice wine has penetrated
to the essence of your souls.
- Yeah, listen to my tail.
- You're the tail!
No... You're
the tail.
(yelling): Dad! Bart's feet
are on my half of the shell!
(screaming):
Why, you slimey little...
Ow!
(both grunting)
- (grunting)
- Ooh.
Hey, that actually feels good.
- (grunting)
- Oh, yeah. More. A little bit more.
- (shouting)
- Right there. Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
That's the stuff.
Enough nonsense! I came
here for my daughter!
♪ I-I am a golden bird
♪ And I love the comic nerd
♪ Of this, I won't be cured
♪ Papa-san, Papa-san.
The monster is me.
Who... 'da thunk it?
(weeping)
(thunder rumbling)
(sighs)
Homer, drinking
that snake wine,
and going to White
Castle afterwards,
really opened my eyes.
Mr. Nakamura, I have used
my hitherto unmentioned
chemical engineering
degree to get a real job
at the Springfield
Phosphate Works.
They're giant polluters.
But... the CEO
is a woman.
It's very vexing.
Now, have I proven myself
worthy of your daughter?
(firmly):
No.
Please, take your time.
You were worthy!
The way you were.
I... I was?
But I rented the store.
I eBayed my stool.
Cancel the sale.
But then my seller
rating will go down...
- Stop being nerd!
- Yes, Papa-san.
Geekly beloved,
we are gathered here
in the eyes of me,
King of the Cameos, Stan Lee.
To celebrate the wedding
of, Comic Book Guy,
and Kumiko Nakamura.
Does anyone wish to offer any
thoughts, on this blessed occasion?
Yes. (clears throat) I-I-I
would like to say something.
Um, since I met Kumiko,
strangely, comic books no
longer seem so important.
I will also be selling
greeting cards.
And, every day, I will give one to
Kumiko in commemoration of today,
with the salutation,
"Best... Day... Ever."
Ghost Wife, are you happy?
Kind of!
(traditional Japanese
music playing)
MILHOUSE: How long am I
gonna stay this way?
As long as we
keep drinkin' this.
(clink)
DOLPH: Give us
your eggs.
I'm a boy.
KEARNEY:
We said eggs.
(all laughing)
Yes!
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
Shh!