♪ The Simpsons ♪
D'oh!
(screams)
(horse neighs)
You sure look stupid
in that green dress, Lis.
That's funny.
I don't feel stupid.
Hey, everybody's
wearing green.
Oh, no.
ALL: Pinch! Pinch!
Pinch!
Happy St. Patrick's day, loser.
Ow! Quit it!
It's the wearin'
of the green, Bart.
Pinch! Pinch! Pinch!
No one's pinching his legs.
Oh...
(groans)
It's been St. Patrick's Day
for hours,
and I'm still not drunk yet.
Oh, it's never
gonna be 9:00.
Moe! Thank God,
you're here.
We'd like to come in
and drink, please.
We kicked down
the back door
but then,
there was a metal door.
Yeah, all right, listen up.
This is the busiest
drinking day of the year.
Where are
the designated drivers?
Beat it.
I got no room for cheapskates.
Top o' the morning to ye
on this gray, drizzly afternoon.
Kent O'Brockman
live on Main Street
where today, everyone
is a little bit Irish,
except, of course,
for the gays and the Italians.
All right, then, move along.
Nothing to see here.
Show's over, folks.
Parades just bring out
so many emotions in me--
joy, excitement, looking...
Mom, can I go buy one
of those long, plastic horns?
Oh, Bart, we've bought
those before,
and you always just
throw them out the car window
on the ride home.
I get bored with them.
But that won't happen
this time.
(groans)
Beep! Beep! Coming through!
Hey, Notre Dame,
move it or lose it.
(blowing horn)
Will the owner
of the great big butt
please move it out of my face?
Hey, Ma, I'm on TV.
Hey, where's that
weather chick?
This is some
wicked party, huh?
Hey, have you seen Sully?
Get away from there.
Hey! I need that pencil!
Ladies and gentlemen,
what you're seeing
is a total disregard
for the things
St. Patrick's Day stands for.
All this drinking, violence,
destruction of property--
are these the things we think of
when we think of the Irish?
(cheering)
BART:
Hey, give me some room.
Watch your elbow, Seamus.
Hey, look, everybody,
free beer.
Open your yaps, boyos.
(gulping)
Hey, what the--
(groans)
Everybody...
everybody get naked.
Come on,
don't be stuck-up.
It's going to be great.
Well, why not?
This party's
just getting started!
Stop the celebration.
That small boy is drunk.
(laughing and hiccupping)
(all gasping)
That's not right.
Look at that.
(murmuring)
ALL: Yay, Bart!
Look at me.
I'm the prime minister
of Ireland.
(laughing)
Hey, Homer,
ain't that your kid on TV?
What are you looking at?
(hiccups)
"What are you looking at?"
The innocent words
of a drunken child.
Well, I'll tell you what
we're looking at, young man--
a town gone mad...
a town whose very conscience
was washed away
in a tide of beer
and green vomit.
I'm going down to Moe's
for a couple of beers.
-I'll come with you.
-No! No more drinking.
I'm tired of looking
like the world's worst mother.
Oh, honey, you're not
the world's worst mother.
What about that
freezer lady in Georgia?
(growls)
But what's the solution?
Are we so bereft of ideas
that we must revive
the antiquated notion
of prohibition?
Channel six says yes.
Prohibition. Pfft!
They tried
that in the movies
and it didn't work.
I predict
this is the last
we'll be hearing
about prohibition.
ALL (chanting):
We want prohibition!
You can't seriously
want to ban alcohol.
It tastes great, makes women
appear more attractive,
and makes a person virtually
invulnerable to criticism.
Oh, won't somebody please
think of the children?
What kind of an example
are we setting?
Ladies, please.
All our founding fathers,
astronauts
and world series heroes
have been either drunk
or on cocaine.
Uh, uh, oh, oh, wait.
Lookee here.
(blows)
Seems there's been
a prohibition law
on the books in Springfield
for 200 years.
It's just never been enforced.
Get out of here,
old clerk guy.
There's also a law requiring
ducks to wear long pants.
QUIMBY: Wait a minute,
let me see that.
Well, I'll be darned--
long pants.
Read the other one,
the non-duck one.
"...and spirituous beverages
are hereby prohibited
under penalty of catapult."
(chuckling)
Did you see this, Bernice?
Eh-- Oh, my.
(all cheering)
No, we're not worried.
Our customers buy Duff
for its robust taste,
not its alcoholic content.
I predict our new
alcohol-free Duff Zero
will sell even better
than our previous brand.
(gulping)
Oh, yeah.
Well, that's the end of me.
(whistling)
♪♪ (jazz)
NARRATOR:
Dateline: Springfield.
With prohibition
back in force
sobriety's peaceful slumber
was shattered by its noisy
neighbor, the speakeasy.
Glad you're finally back
in business, Moe.
Yeah, that was
a scary couple of hours.
NARRATOR: The suppliers
of the illegal booze?
Gangsters
running truckloads
of smuggled hooch
all the way from Shelbyville
and John Law was helpless.
You didn't
see nothing.
I don't know why
people are always
bad-mouthing the mafia.
♪♪
(belches)
Wa-hoo!
So!
Ah, geez.
This looks bad.
Better turn
on the old Wiggum charm.
(gasps)
Pervert!
Oh, boy, that sounded bad.
We demand you bring in
a police chief
who will enforce
the prohibition law.
Demand?
Who are you
to demand anything?
I run this town.
You're just a bunch
of low-income nobodies.
Election in November.
What, again?!
This stupid country.
NARRATOR: With rum-running hoodlums
in the catbird's seat,
Springfield sent
for the one man
who could clean up the town
and shoot the gangsters--
Rex Banner.
Ow!
Hey, I was watching that
and I was sitting there.
Rex Banner. I'm running
this department now.
Wiggum, you're out--
suspended indefinitely.
Huh?
Tuck in that shirt!
Get those shoes shined!
Take that badge out
of your mouth!
You're police officers.
What are you
waiting for--
somebody to kiss you
good-bye?
Well...
no, no, no.
I guess not.
NARRATOR:
Wasting no time,
Rex Banner tore into
the bootleggers
like a chippie tearing
into a lobster.
(tires screeching)
(rapid gunfire)
How do you know
you don't like bribes
if you've never
taken one? Here.
Say, this is nice.
No! No bribes!
Okay, you win.
From now on, we'll stick
to smuggling heroin.
See that you do!
At first,
I thought prohibition
was a good thing.
People were drinking more
and having a lot more fun.
But without beer,
prohibition doesn't work.
Hey, hi.
Can I arrest any of you people
for anything?
-No.
-Ah, geez.
I don't have
anything to do anymore.
With Banner around,
alcohol and crime
are history in this town,
and so am I.
Now, don't say that!
Alcohol is a way of life.
Alcohol is my way of life,
and I aim to keep it.
Sounds like
you have a plan.
Maybe I do, chief.
Maybe I do.
Come on, boy.
Think of a plan.
I'm trying, Dad.
Kent Brockman
at the now-closed
Duff bottling plant,
where a mysterious
person in black
keeps a solitary vigil.
(Barney belches)
I've got it!
We're going out, Marge.
If we don't come back,
avenge our deaths.
MARGE: All right.
BART: Whoa, bonanza!
Let's load it up
before the rats regroup.
Right. Now remember:
Don't mention
this to anyone--
not your mother,
not Rex Banner,
not anyone.
(scoffs) Rex Banner--
what a dope.
Yeah. Look at him trying
to aim that stupid gun.
(both scream)
(siren wailing)
Hang on, son!
Dad, knocking over
a gravestone is bad luck.
Really?
I heard good.
What happened
to you, Homer?
And what have
you done to the car?
Nothin'.
I don't think it had
broken axles before.
Before! Before!
You're livin'
in the past, Marge.
Quit livin' in the past.
That's funny.
I used to be able
to go down there.
Going bowling.
Not back, avenge deaths.
Why do you have
so many bowling balls?
Uh...
I'm not gonna lie
to you, Marge.
So long!
(door closes)
(car speeding away)
(growls)
Ah, rats!
Another gutter ball!
Gee, Homer
you sure do suck tonight.
Yeah, suck like a fox!
(both laughing)
Here you go, barn.
That'll be 45 bucks.
45 bucks?!
Well, this better be the
best-tasting beer in the world.
You got lucky.
You see, boy, the real money
is in bootlegging,
not in your
childish vandalism.
Oh, so many
wasted nights.
What's the matter,
chief?
Yeah, you've barely touched
your Banana Kaboom.
This isn't a very
happy birthday for Rex Banner.
(Barney mumbling)
Hello, fishies!
(belches)
(screaming)
Listen, rummy, I'm going
to say it plain and simple:
Where'd you
pinch the hooch?
Is some blind tiger
jerking suds on the side?
Yes?
Wait a minute.
I forgot to make sure
the coast was clear.
Ah, it's probably clear.
Let's go.
(yelps)
Beer!
I can explain, Marge.
Please let me explain.
(wailing) Oh, why won't
let me explain?!
You're the one the papers
have been talking about--
that mysterious "beer baron"
who's been supplying Springfield
with alcohol.
How have you been
getting away with this?
Well... and I can
explain, remember?
I fill the balls with beer
that I found at the dump
and then I bowl them
and some underground pipes
take them into Moe's.
Homer, that's very clever.
-Huh?
-Mom!
Well, it is. I've known your father
since high school,
and this is the cleverest
things he's ever done.
Besides, he's only breaking
a silly, 200-year-old law.
It is silly, Marge.
And look at all the
money I'm making.
Whoo!
Mom! Prohibition
may be unpopular,
but it's the law,
and we still have--
ALL:
Go to your room, Lisa.
(pounding on door)
Open up, curly.
This is a raid.
A raid?!
Curly?!
Um, all right, but, uh...
I don't know what you
expect to find
in a, uh, simple, uh...
neighborhood... pet shop.
Pet shop, eh?
Well, I just have
one question:
What kind of pet shop
is filled with
rambunctious yahoos
and hot jazz music
at 1:00 a.m.?
Um...
uh...
the... best... damn...
pet shop in town!
PATRONS: Yeah!
All right,
but you people remember:
Baby turtles and alligators
may seem like a cute idea
for a pet,
but they grow up.
Let's go, boys.
Ow!
Those gears down there
really hurt.
You're out there somewhere,
beer baron,
and I'll find you.
HOMER (distant):
No, you won't.
Yes, I will.
HOMER: Won't.
NARRATOR:
Dateline Springfield.
The illusive beer baron
continued to thumb his nose
at authorities.
Swaggering about
in a garish new hat
he seemed to say,
"Look at me, Rex Banner.
I have a new hat."
Hey, boy, get cracking.
Moe upped his order
to 20 balls a night.
Uh, Dad--
Call me beer baron.
All the beer from the landfill
is gone, beer baron.
We're out of business.
But I can't be out of beer.
I'm the beer baron.
Homer, my customers
are sobering up,
and they ain't gonna
stick around for the ambiance.
You got to get me more beer.
Sorry. I'm all out.
How about some turpentine
or caulk?
Delicious caulk.
Look, find it, buy it,
make it, I don't care.
Just get me some booze
and fast.
Make it, eh?
Forty-two bathtubs, please.
You know, they're 50
for $3,000 today.
I said 42!
Now you're making
your own alcohol?
That's more illegal than
what you were doing before.
(laughing)
Remember, honey,
we're disobeying
an unjust law here.
We're patriots.
Like...
all those people in jail.
(cheering)
(sniffing)
Who wants a bathtub mint julep?
Are you the beer baron?
If you're talking
about root beer,
I plead guilt-didilly-ilty
as char-didilly-arged.
He's not the baron,
but he sounds drunk.
Take him in.
Are you the beer baron?
Yes, but only by night.
By day,
I'm a mild-mannered reporter
for a major metropolitan
newspaper.
Don't crack wise
with me, tubby.
Tubby?
Oh, yes, tubby.
Hey, Banner,
how's it hanging?
None of your business.
(rumbling)
(both screaming)
What on earth happened
down there?!
One of the stills--
Uh, nothing, Marge.
I think it must have been
that bean I had for dinner.
(explosions)
Ka-boom! Blam!
Oh, excuse me again, dear.
Homer, there's no point
in pretending
you're making those noises.
Your homemade liquor
is exploding again.
What, dear? Ka-blammo!
You made some money
and had the fun of being
a wanted criminal.
Why not quit now
while you're ahead?
-(explosion)
-Boom.
I'll be right back.
(rumbling)
(loud explosion)
(screaming)
It's hot! Oh!
Oh! Oh! Oh!
Whoo.
I've thought about
what you said, honey,
and I've decided to quit.
Oh, well, fun's over.
But I still have
my wonderful money.
Stick 'em up!
Geez, what happened to you,
Wiggum? You look terrible.
Never mind how I look.
You gonna give me
the money or not?
Well, I don't think so.
You don't even have
a trigger on that thing.
Yeah, I had to sell the trigger
and most of the handle
to feed my family.
Come on, give me the dough.
I can throw this pretty hard.
Poor Wiggum.
I'll bet you really hate
Rex Banner, huh?
Um... who?
The guy who took your job.
Oh, yeah.
More than anything in the world.
Hey, how would you
like to show him up
by beating him
at his own game?
(cheering)
I'm happy to report
that the flow of illegal liquor
seems to have dried up.
Public drunkenness has ceased
and those
mysterious liquor clouds
over Evergreen Terrace
are gone.
People, Rex Banner has won
your war against alcohol.
(cheering)
What about
the beer baron?
I suspect he was just
an invention of the media.
The idea that someone like that
could operate under my very nose
is laughable.
(gasping)
(gagging)
Well, you all know
what laughter sounds like.
We now go live
to Evergreen Terrace
where I'm informed
that former police chief Wiggum
has captured the beer baron.
(gasping)
They captured Homer?
Then the liquor-filled
bowling balls traveled
through a network
of underground pipes
finally emerging
at a nearby speakeasy.
You forgot
one thing, Wiggum.
Yeah? What's that?
I filled the balls
with a funnel.
That was a very sweet thing
you did for poor Wiggum.
But what's going
to happen to you?
Oh, probably
just a slap on the wrist.
"And he who shall
violate this law
shall be punished
by catapult."
(grunting)
Last time I help you.
Sorry. I thought
you'd get a fine
or at most,
three, four years in jail.
BANNER: Hold it.
This machine
is two centuries old.
Better test it first.
(yowling)
Okay. Go ahead.
Wait! Wait!
You can't do this!
All my husband did was violate
a law that doesn't make sense.
Now, I'll admit
car crashes and fistfights
have been down recently,
but prohibition
has cost us our freedom--
our freedom to drink.
Now hold on
a minute, missy.
It's not up to us to choose
which laws we want to obey.
If it were, I'd kill everyone
who looked at me cockeyed.
Our laws are in place
for a reason.
Send him back
to mama, boys.
(yelling)
That was unexpected.
Well, reset the catapult,
and let's get this over with.
CLERK: Wait.
I've discovered more lines
on the parchment.
It says that
the prohibition law
which was passed here
200 years ago
was repealed 199 years ago.
Release the prisoner.
On behalf of the city,
I'd like to apologize
and ask how long
it will take for you
to flood this town
with booze again.
Well, sorry.
I'm not in
that business anymore.
Four minutes.
NARRATOR: And so, one town's
brief flirtation with prohibition
ended in a joyous remarriage
to lady liquor.
Congratulations,
Springfield.
We wish you the very best.
To alcohol--
the cause of
and solution to
all of life's problems.
(cheering)
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.