♪ The Simpsons 25x18 ♪
Days of Future Future
Original Air Date on April 13, 20
(bubble wrap popping)
(pop)
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
(yawns)
(moans)
(gasps)
Please let it be a
bear that did this.
(Homer groaning)
How much did I eat?
(groaning)
Homie, you can't keep
doing this to yourself.
(scoffs)
I'm as healthy as a horse.
Horses only live 30 years.
(mimics a neighing horse)
(sighs)
If you could just ease up
on the eating after 3:00 a.m.
That's all I ask.
Marge is right. I'm gonna walk
upstairs, take her in my arms
and tell her my good
health starts now!
Mm-hmm!
Legs pumping.
Blood flowing.
Two at a time.
(grunting)
Heart exploding.
(yelling, grunting)
Ooh. Pepperoni.
(grunting)
(wheezing)
(struggling): All that's left
are clever last words.
(groans, gurgles)
♪
And so we mourn the loss
of Homer J. Simpson.
Beloved husband, father and
poorly informed sports fan.
All he did was yell
"traveling" at the screen.
Major condolences on
your bereavement, dear.
If, uh... you know, after a respectful
period of grief and whatnot, uh...
yous would like to have some
coffee, please give a call.
- Thank you, Moe.
- FRINK: Stop!
Stop with the wailing and
the gnashing and the aye...
Homer is not dead!
I have made a copy.
I'm number two.
(moans in excitement)
You're alive! But how?
Uh, well...
(clears throat, speak gibberish)
I was able to put Homer's
memories in the body of a clone,
identical to the
original in every way.
I wanted to clone a sheep, but I needed
to start with something simpler.
Which he is, because
his brain is fliveck.
Oh... Dad, you're back!
Just in time for
my recital.
Somebody kill me.
Now, Homie. I hope you use this second
chance to live a more sensible life.
Amen, baby. Did you make
potato salad for the wake?
Yes.
That man sure loved
potato salad.
(cracks knuckles)
Ah, hey, Midge. Uh...
here we are again, ah?
Yeah...
(laughs)
And, oh, uh, here,
uh, my new card.
(laughs)
Yeah.
I'm back!
Coming through!
(laughing):
Yeah.
I can die all I want.
Frink's got Homers like the
Tuileries has park benches.
Huh? I wonder where
I picked that up.
Oh. I planted a
Western history chip,
but all you retained were
the places to sit down.
Nice!
♪ Letting the days go by ♪
♪ Let the water hold me down ♪
(grunts)
♪ Letting the days go by ♪
♪ Water flowing underground ♪
♪ Into the blue again ♪
♪ After the money's gone ♪
♪ Once in a lifetime... ♪
Homer, you'll be all right, but,
uh, no solid food for two weeks.
Aw... two weeks?
(continuous beep)
♪ Same as it ever was,
same as it ever was ♪
♪ Same as it ever was... ♪
(groaning)
We are gathered here to mourn the
passing of yet another Homer Simpson.
Beloved father, precious memories,
local character, et cetera.
Okay. We're ready for
the crematorium bot.
(mechanical whirring)
(pounding)
HOMER:
Wait a minute!
(flames ignite)
(grunting)
(beeping)
Don't go far, Cremo.
Oh, Moe, are we
doing this again?
You know what? No. I'm tired
of getting my hopes up here.
You and your immortal husband
can go take a flying leap, huh?
Um, I am so very sorry, but, uh, this time,
I could not bring Homer back to life.
ALL:
Wha...?
(groans)
Stupid Moe.
You just had to act like yourself,
didn't you, you jackass?
All is not lost.
I was able to download Homer's brain
into this flash drive. It'll have to do.
Yo. Where's my body?
Oh, you used up all your clones, you
fat, fat, fat, reckless, fat pig!
From now on, you're just going
to be a face on a monitor.
So, enjoy screen
saver mode!
Bonk. Bonk. Bonk.
Ooh. Corner. Ba-donk.
Let me just say this once.
(screams)
I'm good.
Hey, kids. Want to chase Grandpa
Homer around the house?
- I do!
- Yay!
(Homer and kids giggling)
After 35 years of wifely obedience,
I'm married to a face on a screen.
Not exactly fun and games
for me, either, Marge.
Ooh... Goody Gobble!
(chomping)
(whoops)
Liquid center power-up!
(chomping)
(sighs)
How are you, Milhouse?
Things aren't
great with Lisa.
If it wasn't for that squirrel
that eats our bird food,
we'd have nothing
to talk about.
As I told you when we
talked last month,
"I've been doing a lot of
charity work for the undead."
HOMER:
Uh, Marge, excuse me.
Uh... I think I
need a reboot.
Just stick the tip of your pen in that
little hole and hold it for 15 minutes.
(click)
No. I'm throwing you
out of the house.
You can live with
your no-good son.
- Hey. What did I do?
- Nothing for 30 years.
You're perfect
for each other.
No. No. No. Don't pull me
out before you click eject.
That hurts like
a mother...!
So, Dad, what do you
think of my place?
Son, could you put me
in 3-D for a second?
(click)
Why, you little...! I'll teach
you to emulate my sloppiness!
(click)
Okay, guys. Time for you
to go to your mother's.
Here's your mom's house.
(rings doorbell)
(sighs)
Hi, Jerry.
Hey, Bart. Great to see you, man.
How are you?
Great. Great. So, I guess you and Jenda
are still together? Is she there?
Oh, yeah. She's just
getting out of the shower.
Hey, you're looking
good, man.
- You been working out or what?
- No.
You're lucky, man. I have to
hit the gym like every day,
or I'm like...
(shrieks)
(kiss)
Hey, baby.
Hurry, boys. We're going
camping this weekend.
But our thing was camping.
Living out of a car
is not "camping."
(laughing):
That's right, babe. (kiss)
(groans)
- Bye.
- Good-bye, Daddy!
Take care, Bart.
Hey. Check's due on the first,
whether it's a weekend or not.
Dad, if I ever needed
fatherly wisdom, it's now.
(sighs)
(roars)
Okay, everyone. Jolly did a great
job standing on her hind legs.
What does she get?
ALL:
A goat!
(goat bleats)
(crowd cheering)
Cheer up, Bart. You're
working with dinosaurs.
(sighs)
I miss my kids.
Come on. You're
free and sleazy.
I know some adult dancers
that work with my mom.
Isn't your mom 87?
With social security a thing of the
past, she can't afford to retire.
I don't know how that happened
in a senate with 99 Democrats.
That one Republican is
great at getting his way.
(zombies moaning)
Brains.
Actually, Terrance, this
is a synthetic substance.
Devised for zombie vegans.
Or "zegans."
Meh.
What are you doing here?
You weren't answering
your phone.
I was worried you might
have been bitten.
Oh. Zombies not able
to control selves.
All we do bite, bite, bite.
You, sir, am racist.
I'm sure you're one
of the good ones.
Not to imply that there are
any bad ones, of course,
but all stereotypes
come from a place of...
- (groans)
- Ow!
(moans)
Still meh.
(upbeat techno music blares)
I don't think I'm
ready for this, man.
Dude, it's been two years
since the divorce.
Ooh. I love your perfume.
Can I smell you later?
Why don't you
smell me now?
Haw haw.
Well, that didn't
look so hard.
You know, at my job, I satisfy
ladies even bigger than you.
- Um, I feed dinosaurs.
- Sir, you have to leave.
You're bumming out
everybody,
and you have, like, a goat
beard stuck to your shoe.
Huh?
(groans)
One, please.
Mm-hmm.
Huh? Man, that's some
targeted advertising.
After this procedure, you will have
total closure from your divorce.
- How long does this take?
- It'll be over before I finish this...
(electrical buzzing)
- ...sentence.
- Wow. It works.
I'm completely
over my ex-wife.
Do you take
wedding bands as tips?
Put it in the jar.
One more injection in two
weeks, and you're cured.
But until then, you may
experience some zombie-ism.
(chuckles)
Brains.
No. Those are just
teaching brains.
They're like the plastic sushi in
front of a Japanese restaurant.
Window sushi fake?
Window sushi fake.
Ay, caramba.
I have moved on.
Hey, passable-looking.
Sorry. I'm just a little creeped
out by that screen saver.
Nothing to worry about.
He's been frozen
like that for days.
(moaning)
(whistling)
♪ Girls ♪
♪ All I really
want is girls ♪
♪ And in the morning
it's girls... ♪
Wow. Now I see why they
call you Miss Hoover.
You must have been
vacuuming for an hour.
Anything to please my man.
So, was it good for you?
"Good" is not a concept
in my culture!
Oh, my God. We went
home with you?
Not just me.
There's Beppo, Boppo,
Emmett Kelly the Ninth,
Frenchy, Insane Clown Polly
and Commodore Tee-hee.
(horn toots)
Brains? Brains?
Garden brains.
(Milhouse grunts)
Spicy Mexican
garden brains?
- Too much sodium.
- (grunts)
Give me your wallet!
(grunts)
(whirring)
(imitating siren):
Whoo! Whoo! Whoo! Whoo!
What seems to be
the oopsie here?
(growling)
Yay! I'm fighting crime!
(grunts)
Officer needs backup.
There, back up.
(grunts)
Oh?
The old Milhouse would have been
helpless with an asthma attack.
No breathing, no asthma.
I love how you're dropping
all your definite articles.
Brevity soul wit.
(giggling)
LISA:
Uh, what are you cooking?
Nothing.
You know, Dad
really misses you.
Well, I don't miss
his nonsense.
There's a lot of stuff
he blamed on raccoons
that I'm starting
to suspect was him.
Look, maybe I shouldn't have done
this, but I've got him right here.
Oh.
Sorry, I must have
recorded over Dad.
But admit it. When you thought
it was Dad, you were excited.
It's only natural to miss a
man you buried 127 times.
(classical music playing)
(whooshing)
Hey, Homer, your robot
body finally came.
About time!
(whooshing)
Huh. Huh.
Hmm? Hey, where's my junk?
Oh.
Whew!
(doorbell rings)
Hello?
(laughter, whirring)
- Oh, you boys look happy.
- Yeah, but Mom's sad.
Jerry moved out.
(Jenda cries)
I thought he was
the one, Bart.
I just put in a saltwater tank where
he could shed his exoskeleton.
And now when I walk by
it, I feel like a fool.
He's the fool.
You're great.
You're just saying that
because you have to.
I don't have to
say anything.
Believe me, no guy wants to see his
ex looking hot or being sweet.
Makes him realize
everything he's lost.
Wow. Wow. You've
really grown.
We should have
dinner sometime.
Hey, Dad, can you
watch the boys?
Sure.
(high-pitched whistling)
Body, to Moe's.
Hey, you're kind of
quiet tonight, Homer.
(belches loudly)
(whirring)
(crowd chatter, gentle
instrumental music plays)
You know, this was
a great evening.
(in squeaky voice):
Please enjoy your desserts.
Man, when is that
voice gonna change?
(whimpering)
Suddenly, I want a
different dessert.
But they brought us
little cakes and...
Oh.
Ay, caramba.
(metallic thudding)
Oop, oop, uh, yeah, open
your stance a little there.
Oh! Yeah, that's it.
Do your worst, kids!
(both gasp)
Come on! Hug your
grandpa, boys!
(whimpering)
Threat perceived.
Terminate! Terminate!
(yelling)
(laughing)
Kids are so afraid
of being terminated.
Looking good, Santa's
Little Hybrid.
Father, what am I?
JENDA: Guys, sit down.
Our lives are gonna
change a little.
- Uh-oh.
- This is never good.
This is good. Your father and I are
gonna try to make it work again.
Like a classic rock band whose
hold-out member finally needs money.
Wow. Everyone's back together
except Gramma and Grampa.
Oh, I think that's
about to change.
(high-pitched mechanical
whirring and hissing)
Aren't you going
to work, Dad?
One of us has to stay
home with you guys.
And your mom can't quit
her job at Google.
They need my help hunting down those
self-driving cars that turned evil.
Oh, you passed
another rest stop!
I am not stopping again.
But I had a large soda!
I said get the small!
It was only 50 cents more!
Let's play The Quiet Game!
(groans)
Now, will somebody hold
up a one dollar bill?
(bellowing screech)
(screaming)
(laughter)
(thunderous footsteps,
audience gasping)
Uh-oh. It looks like we woke
someone up from her nap.
(laughter)
Well, now that you're up,
you can do your juggling act.
(low growl)
(laughter)
(sad growl)
Milhouse, you were supposed
to come see me today
for your final
anti-zombie injection.
- (groans)
- Yes, well, uh...
But I'm supposed to
be in surgery now,
so I guess we're both
playing hooky. (laughs)
But, Lisa, if you want Milhouse
to return to his old self,
then you'd better bring him in
for that shot tomorrow.
But, Doctor...
(whispering): He's so much more
interesting this way.
(growling)
- Ooh.
- I see.
Now enjoy the majesty of
our prehistoric past.
(horn toots)
So, that earring I lost in the
teleport, turns out it's in Florida.
Yes!
That's not a
listening-to-me "yes."
- You're watching something.
- What? Me? Oh, that's crazy.
You know, I knew it. This is supposed to
be us time, and you're lensing a game.
Well, you're not paying attention
to me. You're texting.
Yeah, only to complain about you
not paying any attention to me.
If I wasn't
paying attention,
then how did I notice
you not paying attention
to my not paying
attention? Ha!
Oh, I thought this time things
were gonna be different.
They are. You're
four years older.
Wow. What does that mean?
Uh...
Hey, Bart, what'll it be?
A tall beer and no
judgmental women.
That is so typical of you.
What are you doing here?
I have to decide whether
to make Milhouse...
(sighs)
...human again.
I even prefer the
way he smells now.
Some meat went bad in our freezer,
and my heart skipped a beat.
Phoo! You two don't know
what a rough marriage is.
Mom, I got to know. Once and
for all, what is the secret?
Why did you stay
with Dad so long?
Until I was eight, I thought
he was a magical gorilla.
Look, life's tough.
It's hard to
make it through.
The only way I know is
when you make a decision
that comes from your
heart, you stick with it.
(sighs)
- Like my marriage.
- Or my divorce.
Or my decision to support
Duffman in his old age.
Duffman can still
swing and party.
(wheezy):
Oh, yeah.
Wait, Mom. Does that mean
you're going to take Dad back?
No, I'm going to
join him forever.
(electrical buzzing)
(moaning)
- (gasps)
- (laughs)
Oh.
(electronic beeps,
tune plays)
I can't tell if that was love, suicide
or a... a really boring video game.
Lisa, your husband
is... fine.
(chuckles)
No residual zombie-ism
whatsoever.
Are you sure?
Watch. I'll just wave this
juicy brain in front of him.
I'm gonna faint!
Hooray.
So, Jenda, I don't
know what love is,
but I know what it
isn't, and we're isn't.
Yeah. You're right.
That's why I started seeing Jerry
again without telling you.
Hey, buddy, how,
uh, how you doing?
What?! Oh!
You know what, Jenda?
I'm not even mad,
because I'm finally,
completely over you.
(whooshing)
WOMAN:
...sentence.
Wait. What am I
doing back here?
You never left. Everything
that you experienced
between when I flipped
the switch and now
was just a neural implant
in your temporal lobe.
Uh, you should look
at my profile.
Oh. Uh-huh.
It was all a dream, and
now you can go home.
So, you're sure I'm cured?
No more feelings
for my ex-wife?
I'm positive. We treat a lot
of people for obsessions.
(electrical buzzing,
whooshing)
It's a whole new day
for Nothing Stu!
Wow. I'm free.
Get ready, world.
I've got a whole new set
of mistakes to make.
(whistling)
Uh, ol' Gil could
use a fresh start.
Weren't you just in
here this morning?
I've had a bad day.
After 35 years of marriage,
we've finally gotten it right.
Yes, even my personality
has gotten,
shall we say, an upgrade.
Oh! That's a bit
of a whoo-hoo.
Indeed.
Lis, I hope things work out
with you and Milhouse,
but if they don't, I know
just where you should go.
Thanks, but Milhouse and I
are in a pretty good place.
Even though he's not
a zombie anymore?
No, that's what happened
in your false memories.
- There is no cure for zombie-ism.
- (groaning)
Dead flower from
dead husband.
(sighs dreamily)
And I was a false
memory, too.
- No, you were real.
- Aw, shucks.
ANNOUNCER: Next week on Fox
Television's The Simpsons:
Sit down.
You're not going anywhere.
(gasps)
Release the...
It ain't what you think!
I said no mayo!
Ay, caramba.
(laughs)
ANNOUNCER:
One week from tonight.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
Shh!