Good grief.
This candy's terrible!
Circus peanuts,
raisins, nicotine gum,
a library card?
You got all
the good stuff.
And yet l'm still
not satisfied.
(GRUNTS lN FRUSTRATlON)
You thieving hussy!
(CHOKlNG)
Ow!
(EXCLAlMS lN SHOCK)
You kids have got to
learn that actions
have consequences!
(GRUNTlNG)
Eat fire, punks!
KlDS: Whoa!
What the. . .
l'm still cold.
Will everyone please stop
fighting and burning?
Never!
(SCREAMlNG)
Beat the lumps.
BART: Hey!
BART: Ay, caramba!
Homie, l disagree
with your approach
to the children.
(GRUNTlNG)
(GUNSHOT)
(HOMER SCREAMS)
(MARGE COCKS GUN)
(GUNSHOT)
HOMER: D'oh !
Pathetic humans.
They're showing
a Halloween episode.
ln November!
Who's still thinking
about Halloween?
We've already
got our Christmas
decorations up.
BOTH: Ho, ho, ho!
Merry Christmas!
(CHRlSTMAS MUSlC PLAYlNG)
(SlNlSTER TUNE PLAYlNG)
(BANGlNG ON DOOR)
l am Death.
Death?
We don't want any.
l have come
for Bart Simpson.
Bart, run like the
(MlSPRONOUNClNG) wind !
Mom, it's "wind."
Well, l've only
read it in books.
(UPBEAT TUNE PLAYlNG)
Oh ! Why you little. . .
(OMlNOUS MUSlC PLAYlNG)
Please don't take me.
Take Milhouse.
We all know there's
no happy ending there.
Your time is up.
This is for
Snowball l and JFK!
Ow!
Cool.
Dad, do you realize
what you've done?
You've created
a world without
death.
Does this mean
they'll never cancel
the Jim Belushi Show?
l guess so.
(SCREAMlNG) No!
LISA: A world without death.
(GUNSHOTS)
(GROANlNG)
Frankie the Squealer,
why won't you die?
Ugh ! lf l knew,
l'd tell you, l swear.
l'd better call my wife,
tell her l'll be late.
(SlGHlNG)
lf l knew this would
take so long,
l would've put on a TV.
Pizza!
Your money's on
the counter. No tip.
Oh, you miserable
bastard !
That's why
l'm up here.
Death, Death,
we miss you so much.
You were a busboy in
the restaurant of life
clearing away the oldies,
and the sickies,
and the chokies.
And you made
NASCAR racing exciting.
Homer, it's trash day.
Will you just take
him out to the curb?
l'll curb him. . .
Without enthusiasm.
Ooh !
This robe's pretty soft.
Check it out! l finally
found a dead guy's
clothes that fit me!
(ALL SCREAM)
What? lt's not. . . (YELLS)
My hand ! What's happening?
Dad, you've become
the new Grim Reaper.
No way! Forget it!
l might occasionally kill
out of anger or to
illustrate a point.
But l am not
a Grim Reaper!
Ow! Ow!
l'll reap!
l'll reap already!
(lN SPOOKY TONE)
Jasper, your time
has come!
Where's the regular guy?
Where's Doug?
Never mind.
l'm Death now.
(EXCLAlMS lN DlSAPPOlNTMENT)
l liked Doug.
(GAGS)
"My Dad's Job."
"My dad's job takes him
to all parts of the community.
"He performs a valuable
service but is often
misunderstood
"like a vulture or the
flesh-eating maggot."
Would anyone like to see
Mr. Simpson harvest a soul?
Yeah !
l would !
You said something
about a hot meal?
(CLEARlNG THROAT)
(THUDDlNG)
CHlLDREN: Yeah !
Oh, man.
These seats suck.
Leave everything to me.
Pardon me, comin' through,
rest in peace, you're dead,
take a dirt nap,
feed the worms.
(HOMER EXCLAlMlNG PLAYFULLY)
Oh !
Hmm.
Dad, were all those
people on the list?
l don't know.
Okay. Who am l giving
the finger to today?
(GASPS)
Not this!
Anything but this!
Uh. . .
What was that
first one again?
Oh !
(MARGE SCREAMlNG)
(SCYTHE SLASHlNG)
(SOLEMN MUSlC PLAYlNG)
Okay, God.
l bumped off the love
of my life according
to your divine whim.
Now release me from
this ghastly vocation.
MALE VOlCE: No!
Come on !
All right.
Woo-hoo!
Hey, wait a minute.
This isn't Marge.
This is her fat
sister, Selma.
lt's Patty, chump!
(LAUGHlNG)
MALE VOlCE: Doggone it.
l am too old and
too rich for this.
Thanks for not
killing me, Homie.
Here's an extra
pork chop.
(LAUGHlNG)
l'm gonna not
kill you every week.
(ALL LAUGHlNG)
(SlNlSTER TUNE PLAYlNG)
(RlNGlNG)
Y'ello?
Sir, l'm honored
to inform you
that you've won
the Nobel Prize.
The Nobel Prize?
Finally!
So, it's for what?
My whole deal?
This is Professor
John Frink, isn't it?
lf l say no,
do l still win?
l'll tell
Professor Frink
he's won.
(SPEAKlNG SWEDlSH)
(lN EXAGGERATED
SWEDlSH ACCENT)
Great glayvin
in a glass!
The Nobel Prize!
They must've
awarded it to me
for my invention of a hammer
with a screwdriver
on the other end.
lt's mildly convenient.
Just for that?
lt was a slow year, yes.
l only wish my dear father
were here to see me win.
ls there a problem
with your father?
Well, our relationship
was never great.
Mother used to say
we got along like
positrons and anti-neutrinos.
(LAUGHlNG)
Yes. l'm a geek.
l was always
a disappointment
to him.
You see,
he was one of those
he-man scientists
who worked on
the atom bomb by day,
and slept with
Marilyn Monroe
by night,
and sold secrets to
the Russians at lunch.
The last time l saw him alive,
he was going to study sharks.
l don't want to go on
this oceanographic
expedition, Father.
l get seasick
taking a shower.
Clean but nauseous.
"Clean but nauseous." With
the rolling and the heaving
and the you make me sick!
You've disgraced the name
of John Nerdlebaum Frink.
But, Father, l. . .
(SOBBlNG)
We never spoke again.
Well, where is he now?
Maybe l can help
you two patch up
your differences.
Uh. . . You'll need to
patch up more than that.
Whoa! Did a shark do that?
Yes.
He was testing out a new
blood-based suntan lotion.
You know, now that l have
my hammer-screwdriver,
l could reanimate him
without the needless
switching of tools.
That's always
tedious and annoying.
(CRACKLlNG)
l'm alive! With the breathing
and the tingling and the. . .
What's this radiator
where my pupik should be?
Oh ! Papa,
you're back!
Now we had to replace
several vital organs
with machinery.
But that doesn't make you
any less of a man.
Except you have no penis.
ln the traditional sense.
So what am l?
Some kind of a tin can man
from Planet Tomorrow?
Sir, your son has brought
you into the 21 st century.
lt's a lot like the 20th
except everybody's afraid,
and the stock market
is much lower.
Polly don't
like that cracker.
l'm getting me a real
spleen and then l'm gonna
vent it on you, boychik.
Oi ! Shoving.
lt almost sounded like
he plans to tear organs
out of living people.
Well, that's my dad.
(LAUGHS)
You can't stop him.
(HUMMlNG)
Hey, 700 Club.
You look like
a healthy specimen.
Well, l did finish first
in the Walk for the Cure
of homosexuality.
Say "ah," baby.
Ah. . . (GAGGlNG)
l'm dying !
And there's heaven.
But who's that?
Confucius?
And Milton Berle?
Boy, have l been
barking up the wrong tree.
(HUMMlNG)
Nice posture.
Oh, thank you. Mother
always said a curvy spine
is the devil's roller coaster.
Hey! You can't
have that!
(SCREAMS)
Lost your spine, huh?
You just keep
finding new ways
to disappoint me.
(STAYlN' ALlVE
lNSTRUMENTAL PLAYlNG)
There you are!
Have you stopped to think
about who you're hurting
with this rampage?
The people l've killed?
No! Your son !
On the biggest day of his life
when he accepts
the Nobel Prize,
you're not gonna be there!
Oh, dear God !
l've let my organ lust
come between me and my son.
(WEEPlNG)
Well, it's not too late.
You can still fly
to Stockholm.
Well, it better be
first class.
Comic Book Guy's ass
won't fit in coach.
You may keep
my posterior.
Just please return the
"Jabba the Butt" tattoo.
(BLOWlNG WHlSTLE)
ANNOUNCER:
He explored the behavior
of individual molecules
in a chemical reaction.
She's the sexy
star ofAlias.
Please welcome Nobel laureate
Dr. Dudley Herschbach
and Emmy nominee
Jennifer Garner.
(AUDlENCE APPLAUDlNG)
She blinded me
with science
You know,
Dr. Herschbach, our jobs
are actually not that different.
l disagree.
Winner of the
Nobel Prize in physics
Professor John Frink.
(AUDlENCE APPLAUDlNG)
(CLEARS THROAT) Thank you.
This is a tremendous honor.
However, l can't help being
somewhat disheartened
that my father has become
a marauding ghoul.
Not anymore, Son !
(LAUGHS)
(ALL GASP)
l'm here to accept the
Nobel Prize for stupid.
Can you forgive me?
Well, good glayvin, Dad.
You've made
receiving the Nobel Prize
the happiest day of my life.
Oh, the hug is good.
This is what
the Nobel Prize
is all about.
The science, and the love,
and that physics
we call quantum.
Ain't that right, people?
(ALL CHEERlNG)
What a great crowd.
You all have
such big hearts. . .
And such big brains
with large, juicy,
dripping-with-knowledge
heads!
(ALL GASP)
That's it!
l'm going smorgasbord
on these Poindexters!
(ALL EXCLAlMlNG FEARFULLY)
And l thought Halle Berry
went nuts during her
acceptance speech.
l wish l was
Death again.
That was cool.
Every brain
unlocks more secrets
of the universe.
Muffins are
surprisingly high
in calories.
The pyramids were
actually built by Sears.
He's right!
lt all checks out!
(PEOPLE SCREAMlNG)
(GROANlNG)
This is more violent
than the hip-hop awards.
You've gotta
stop your father!
Yes, but how?
He's 63 years old,
pressure points
here and here,
room temperature is
22 degrees Celsius.
Yes, this should
just about do it.
Ball sack'n !
(GROANS)
Oh, Father.
You're dying again.
But l can bring you
back to life, sir.
Son, it doesn't take
five brains in your head
to know that's a bad idea.
You saw l'd become a monster
and you stopped me like a man.
l'm proud of you.
And now it's time
for me to go to hell.
Ow! Ooh !
Ooh ! Ah ! Oy!
Oy! Ooh ! Ow!
Dead.
(SOBBlNG)
This is most
exciting Nobel Prize
ceremony ever.
l disagree.
lt must be tough to
win the Nobel Prize
and lose your father
on the same day.
Oh, l didn't really
lose my father.
Thanks to my
latest invention,
the soul catcher.
Let's bring it out
and look at it.
I may be a souI,
but I'm hungry.
Can you throw in
a little matzo?
Maybe a nice
piece of fish.
Why, of course, Father.
Allow me to satisfy
your Hebraic desires.
That's a good
shmendele.
Oh, l've waited
so long to hear
you say that.
What does it mean?
ls it dirty?
(TlCKlNG)
(SlNlSTER TUNE PLAYlNG)
Oh ! Baby,
did l find something
to throw out today.
lf you like space
in the attic, are
you gonna be happy.
Cool. Comics
from the '70s.
BART: "Superman
versus Patty Hearst."
"EveI KnieveI Jumps
the Jackson Five."
"Batman and Rhoda."
Check out these ads!
Let's see. X-ray gum.
(GASPS) Cool ! Milhouse,
do you have your change
purse?
MlLHOUSE: Always!
(DOORBELL RlNGS)
Here you go, son.
"To stop time,
click watch."
Wow! She looks like
a background character
in a Hanna-Barbera cartoon !
"To restart time,
click watch again."
What the. . .
Lisa, that's
a filthy habit.
(LAUGHlNG)
lf we're both
touching the watch,
neither of us
will be affected.
Do you realize
what this means?
Yeah, but you
say it first.
We can do
anything we want!
Let's get really
far ahead on
our homework!
Wait till the other kids
see we're already
on the red unit
of "Adventures
in Reading !"
(SlGHS lN EXASPERATlON)
Due to budget cuts,
music class will now have
a two-drink minimum.
Cranapple juice only
counts as one and. . .
(GASPS)
My slacks.
They've descended.
(ALL LAUGHlNG)
(CHUCKLES)
Huh?
What the. . . Hmm.
D'oh !
D'oh ! D'oh !
l can't go on.
(SOBBlNG)
(WAlLlNG LOUDLY)
Ha. . .
Huh?
(LAUGHlNG)
(CLOCK TlCKlNG)
(CLlCK)
People,
Springfield
is in crisis.
Fingers have been
shoved up noses, pants
have been pulled down,
and Mayors have been
repeatedly humiliated.
Damn it!
(ALL TALKlNG lNDlSTlNCTLY)
l thought our
mysterious pranksters
might be here tonight.
So l covered the meeting hall
with ultraviolet powder.
Behold the perpetrators!
(ALL GASPlNG)
lt was those guys!
Come! Let us kill them
before learning of the magical
secret which they possess!
MEN: Get them !
(BART SCREAMlNG)
(ALL YELLlNG ANGRlLY)
Oh ! That was close.
Bart, look at the watch !
Milhouse,
we broke the watch ! Do you
realize what this means?
Yeah, but you
say it first.
(CLlCKlNG REPEATEDLY)
Oh, man. Things are
stuck like this forever.
Well, l couldn't
be happier.
l'm the second
coolest kid on earth !
(GRUNTlNG EXClTEDLY)
Actually, l guess
we can do anything
we want
and no one
will stop us!
l'm gonna play
naked basketball !
No, you're not.
Family looks good.
Thanks.
l just washed 'em.
That keeps happening !
Can l punch
Oscar de la Hoya
for a while?
Just keep it
above the belt.
(GRUNTlNG)
(SlGHS)
You know, Milhouse?
l thought l'd love
eating only frosting
and giving the
pope a wedgie.
But l miss being
a regular kid
in the real world.
Getting a hug
from my mom.
Yeah. l thought
l'd be happy with my
parents back together.
But it's kinda hollow.
All right. lt says here
we can learn watch repair
in eight one-hour lessons.
Boy, that took forever.
Yeah. Well, l work better
in a structured environment.
Here goes nothing.
Wait,
when people see all the stuff
we did, they're gonna kill us.
Yeah !
And l can't run too fast
after 1 5 years of eating
nothing but gummy worms!
l'm gonna quit tomorrow.
l swear.
What we need
is a scapegoat.
Okay.
Acting natural, and. . .
(ALL CONTlNUE YELLlNG)
To repeat what l said
a moment ago,
you are so dead !
Dios mio,
this kid is fun to hit!
(BOTH WHlSTLlNG NONCHALANTLY)
MARGE: Hmm.
Why is Bart so
tall and shaggy?
Just one of
life's mysteries.
Like why is my nose
jammed full of army men?
Oh, come on !
Don't you get it?
Bart stopped time with
his magic stopwatch !
Jealous much?
Why can't l tinker with
the fabric of existence?
Let the baby
have her bottle.
Hmm. What happens
if l press this button?
(HOMER YELPS)
Sorry, sorry, sorry!
(CLlCKlNG)
(EXCLAlMS lN FRUSTRATlON)
Okay, that's good.
Stop there.
...gIad rags on
and join me hon'
We'll have some fun
when the clock strikes one
We're gonna rock
around the cIock tonight
(THEME PLAYlNG
lN SlNlSTER TUNE)
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
(THEME PLAYED
lN SlNlSTER TUNE)
English - US - PSDH