CHORUS:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
(buzzing)
D-oh!
(screams)
REV. LOVEJOY:
...And may we burn
in painful
and foul-smelling fire
forever and ever.
A...men...
...onite minister
will be giving a guest sermon
next Sunday.
Go in peace.
A...
(coughs)
Don't make me come up there.
-...men.
-HOMER: Whoo-hoo!
MOE: Let me outta here.
The guy never stops talking.
-(stomach growling)
-Oh.
I'm starving.
Mom, can we go catholic
so we can get communion wafers
and booze?
No. No one's going catholic.
Three children is enough,
thank you.
Hang in there, son.
I'm taking us out
for our traditional
Sunday brunch.
DRIVER: Idiot!
HOMER: He zinged you, Marge.
(giggling)
-(gasps)
-Brunch is served.
(smacking loudly)
I feel guilty
coming here every Sunday
and never actually
buying anything.
Why? We're following the rules.
If it has
a toothpick in it, it's free.
-Hey.
-(smacking)
Ah, this is my kind of aisle,
soy substitute,
whiz-less cheese...
(gasps)
Oven-roasted cud.
It's packed in its own drool.
Gavin, honey,
help Mommy pick a cereal.
(gasps)
How about alfalfa-bits?
Those suck.
I hate this store.
But, sweetheart, Mommy--
I hate you , too.
I want to live
with one of my dads.
Mmm.
So you say this product
is known as fudge?
Yes, just like it was last week.
If you're going to get snippy,
I'll take my business elsewhere.
Cherry Garcia? Yuck.
Honey Bono?
Desmond Tutti Fruitti?
Ech.
Lisa, help Daddy find
some normal flavors.
(grunts)
Candy Warhol?
Xavier Nougat?
Nah. Nothing made of dead guys.
What's in the back?
-(grunting)
-(shivering)
Hurry up!
My hands are getting cold.
(Lisa sneezes)
Oh, my goodness, Homer,
get her out of there!
Ohh!
Ugh. Sherbet Hoover?
Oh. We've got to get you home
to a warm blanket
and a cold compress.
Whoo!
(grunting)
(man clearing throat)
Those are eight dollars
a pound, sport.
Hmm. Eight dollars a pound times
say, oh, five pounds is, umm...
Let's see.
How many pounds in a gallon?
Oh, I can't afford that.
(gasps)
Unless...
(sneezes)
(laughing)
I told you I'm a financial genius.
I buy an eight-dollar lobster,
fatten it into an $80 lobster
and eat the profits.
Lobsters need saltwater.
I'm way ahead of you.
BART: Dad, the fish.
Son, I'm still fine-tuning.
Eh-eh.
Uh-oh!
Perfect.
(sneezes)
Oh, you don't sound so good.
We'd better get you
some cold medicine.
No problem, I picked
some up at the store!
Oh.
Oh, Homey,
you made breakfast.
Nothing's too good
for my one and only.
Eat, eat. You're nothing
but skin and bones.
(sneezes)
Oh.
Oh, how are you feeling, sweetie?
(nasally voice)
Much better.
(sneezes)
Oh, my. You're burning up.
I'm going to tell the school
you're staying home.
I'm afraid I can't allow that.
Lisa...
Mom, no, wait!
We can make a deal!
You don't have anything I want.
Ohh...
NARRATOR:
The ocean abounds
with fearsome creatures,
but none attacks its prey
with more fury
than the seaweed shark.
The struggle is soon over.
Oh. You shouldn't be
watching the learning channel.
You need to take it easy.
But I'm hardly learning at all.
Why don't you play
with one of Bart's
video games instead?
Hugh Downs says
they're the latest craze.
-(sighs)
-(evil laughter)
Foolish dingo,
you must find and devour
the seven crystal babies,
or spend eternity trapped
in deep didgeri-doo!
(evil laughter)
I am so scared.
All right. I guess you're supposed
to go through this stupid door?
Hmm. I wonder
what's in this glowing barrel.
What? Nunchuks?
Those aren't even australian.
Oh, great. So I'm dead now.
Fine. I'm sick
of this stupid game anyway.
Yes! I am just
four power wands away
from an antigravity lozenge.
(gasps) Hope I don't run
into that weird little troll.
Hi, Lisa.
LISA: No, pause, pause!
I brought your homework.
We have to read this.
LISA: The Wind In The Willows?
It's about a toad
and a badger and a mole.
I drawed on mine.
(chuckles)
Is this my house?
No. You live in a different house.
Choo-choo-choo, whoo, whoo!
Then I shall rule
The Down Underverse!
(evil laughter)
We'll see about that, mate.
HOMER: Okay, together
we weigh 300 pounds.
According to my driver's license,
I weigh 140 pounds.
That means that you weigh, ohh...
160 pounds.
Oh-ho-ho! You're doing great.
No, no!
Yep! That's it! Bite, bite, bite!
-(knock at door)
-MARGE: Lisa?
Oh, sweetie,
you look so much better.
Ready to go back to school?
Uh, I don't know.
(coughing)
I mean, I could risk it, but...
No, no, you just stay put.
Wow. You didn't even feel
her forehead.
How do I get
that kind of credibility?
With eight years
of scrupulous honesty.
Eh. It's not worth it.
Oh, I really need
one more day, mom.
I think the germs are regrouping.
Now, for breakfast,
I'll have hash browns,
coffee and a short stack.
And would it kill you
to heat up the syrup?
(tires screeching)
But I... I might infect the other kids.
That's a risk I'm willing to take.
So long!
Welcome back, Lisa.
I trust you got
the homework I assigned.
The Wind In The Willows?
Oh, yeah, Ralph brought it over.
Perfect. Then I won't need
to excuse you from the test.
(gulps)
Test?
(Taskmaster's voice):
Game over, mate.
Ohh...
Okay, all right.
You can bluff your way
through one test.
"Mr. Toad has a red blank."
Okay, skip that one.
"Mr. blank needs a blank
in order to blank his blank."
Oh, I am in deep blank.
And the lowest grade in the class...
She's going to say my name.
Lisa Simpson, zero.
(gasps)
-SKINNER: Lisa...
-(gasps)
...the president of Harvard
would like a word with you.
Nasty business, that zero.
Naturally Harvard's doors
are now closed to you,
but I'll pass your file along to...
(snickering)
Brown.
Hmm. Heck of a school.
Weren't you at Brown, Otto?
Yep. Almost got tenure, too.
(gasps)
No! Not Brown,
Brown, Brown, Brown...
Lisa, you're saying Brown
an awful lot.
Are you okay?
Well, actually,
I do feel a little feverish.
Ah. Don't worry about the test.
Just get yourself
a nice drink of water.
Then come back and finish the test.
(gulps)
I need a miracle.
-Come on. You owe me.
-What's up, sis?
-Bart, shouldn't you be in class?
-I am.
It's a little something
I whipped up at shop, mostly latex.
What are you doing out here?
We've got a test,
and I didn't read the book.
I'll get a zero for sure, Bart.
What do I do?
Well, if it was me,
I'd just take the zero.
-(growls)
-Uh, but that's not for everyone.
There's one other possibility.
Hey, I can't go in there.
Relax. There's nothing here
you didn't see
when Dad boycotted pants.
NELSON: Hang on. I'll buzz you in.
Buzz!
Teacher and subject?
Miss Hoover, Wind In The Willows.
Hmm-hmm-hmm. Oh.
Here we go.
(gasps)
Oh, my god.
These are the answers to the test.
I don't want to cheat.
Hey, hey, these are study aids.
They're for novelty purposes only.
If a few bad apples
use them for cheating,
I can't be held responsible.
Forget it.
I'd rather get a zero.
Good for you, lass.
I got me a zero once
and my life turned out just fine.
Oh! Whoa!
That's a nasty clog.
Ooh, you've got yourself
a partner, have you?
(grunting)
Keep the change.
WILLIE: Come here,
you slippery rascals.
Good news, my delicious friend.
You're going to be
a free-range lobster.
Come on, boy. Dig in.
They'll give you
a big, strong thorax.
Whoa!
Why, you little... Ah!
Ohh, look at him cower.
Just like the boy.
I can't stay mad
at such a helpless little mammal.
(giggles) I'm gonna get you
for that, you little scamp.
Here! Yeah! Take that, Pinchy.
(giggling)
I graded this morning's test
over lunch
and most of you did quite well.
-I got a B.
-No, Ralph. That's an F.
I must have spilled some kahlua.
Perfect, Lisa.
And you got
all the extra-credit questions.
Even the one that got
cut off by the copy machine.
Oh,well, I guess
I was just on a roll.
(groans)
Don't be so modest, Lisa.
You earned that A+++.
Actually, there are four pluses.
No, that's drambuie.
Mmm.
Ooh, so plump and juicy.
Hmm! He's going to boil up nicely.
(slurps)
Well, I guess this is it, old pal.
This is your big day.
The water's boiling.
Quick. Chuck him in.
-Uh...
-Come on. Chuck him in.
-Okay.
-Let's go! In the pot, in the pot!
Ohh.
-But, Marge, look at the little guy.
-(gasps)
(growling)
He looks like an ordinary...
Ow! Son of a--
Feel that, Marge? He likes you.
And now, for the main course...
Steamed Maine cabbages.
(clears throat)
Pardon me for asking,
but where the hell's
my stupid lobster?
We're not eating Mr. Pinchy.
He's part of the family now.
(grunts)
Pinchy, I made you some risotto.
Dad!
BART:
What, you got to be kidding me.
What's your problem, veggie?
You don't even eat lobster.
No, but I enjoy the smell.
Well, lobster or no lobster,
this is still a very special dinner.
(humming fanfare)
Lisa broke her own record
by two whole pluses.
Mom, where did you get that?
Oh, it just turned up in the course
of my daily rummaging.
By the way, I oiled
the hinge on your diary.
Aren't you proud
of your big sister, Mr. Pinchy?
Hmm? Hmm?
Oh, I am sick of everyone
being so proud of me!
That's my girl!
BART: Ah, cheer up, Lise.
You got a good grade
without even reading the book.
That's win-win.
Can't you see the difference
between earning something
honestly and getting it by fraud?
Hmm, I suppose, maybe if, uh...
No. No, sorry, I thought
I had it there for a sec.
(bell ringing)
Psst, Lisa, check it out.
Tomorrow's fraction quiz.
I'll give you the numerators free,
but the denominators
are going to cost you.
I don't want
your dirty denominators.
-Well, la-dee-da, lady cheaterly.
-(gasps)
Can I at least
keep you in my rolodex?
No!
I never cheated before
and I never will again.
Oh, I almost wish I hadn't
gotten away with it.
SKINNER (over speakers):
Lisa Simpson,
report to the principal's office
to discuss the results
of yesterday's test.
We never met.
SKINNER: I've just received
some rather unusual news
regarding your unprecedented
A triple plus.
To be honest, I'm surprised
and saddened.
Uh, no, not saddened.
What's the word?
Ah, yes. Delighted.
-What?
-I'm delighted to report
that your grade
brought the entire school's G.P.A.
up to our state's
minimum standard.
We now qualify
for a basic assistance grant.
It's the greatest honor
the school has ever received.
And it's all thanks to you.
Your devotion to scholarship
is a shining beacon to all who...
Stop it! I cheated!
Cheated, cheated,
cheated, cheated, cheated!
Lisa, what are you trying to say?
I cheated!!
(gasps)
SKINER: You cheated?
Oh, lordy, lordy, lordy.
Why didn't Miss Hoover tell me?
She doesn't know.
You're the only one I've told.
Well, then...
one could make the argument
that there really is no problem.
But what I did was wrong.
Oh, very much so,
but as long as we handle this
in a mature and above all,
quiet manner,
we'll still get that grant money.
(chuckles)
Oh, you really scared me there.
But we can't accept that money.
It's tainted.
Now, now.
Leave the money out of this.
It's not the money's fault
you cheated.
Besides, I've already
started spending it.
Check out the new scoreboard.
-(fanfare plays)
-CROWD: Charge!
(laughs)
I'm still learning all the buttons.
Well, if you're going
to cover this up,
I'll just have to go
over your head to Super...
-(buzzer sounds)
-...intendent...
-...Chalmers!
(explosion)
Skinner!
I am outraged
that you've kept this from me.
You were supposed to call
as soon as
the new scoreboard was in.
Tell me, does it play
that song "Charge"?
Oh, does it ever!
(grunts)
You can't keep this scoreboard
because there's not going to be
any grant money
because I cheated!
Lisa, let's take a walk.
A little traveling music, Seymour.
(stadium organ music plays)
(grunts)
Good lord, what a dump.
-(dog barking)
-(cat meowing)
It's not surprising this school
was once classified
the most dilapidated
in all of Missouri.
-LISA: Hmm?
-That's why it was shut down
and moved here, brick by brick.
Look around, Lisa.
That grant money
could do a lot of good.
Don't you think those youngsters
deserve a regulation tetherball?
-Ow!
-Ohh!
We can buy real periodic tables
instead of these promotional ones
from Oscar Mayer.
Now who can tell me
the atomic weight of bolgnium?
Oh, delicious?
Correct.
I would also accept
"snacktacular."
And for the first time ever,
our computer lab
actually has a computer in it.
Hi, Lisa.
Hi, Supernintendo Chalmers.
Meow.
I'm learnding.
Ah, way to go, Ralph.
Oh, she's a beaut.
You can't beat a coleco.
How many
can I put you down for? A lot?
Please say a lot.
I need this.
I don't know.
I'm not even sure
we can keep this one.
It's up to Lisa.
What do you say, Lisa?
Will you keep our little secret
for the good of your classmates
and your school?
And let's not forget old Gil, huh?
(chuckles)
The wolf's at old Gil's door.
Uh... I guess
I don't have much choice.
Oh, thank god!
Now let's talk rust-proofing.
These colecos
will rust up on you like that.
Shut up, Gil.
Close the deal, close the deal.
Relax, boy.
We're not going to cook you.
Enjoy your day at the beach.
Ooh, look. Here's a little
playmate for you.
(whimpering)
Hey, you don't have to take that
from no punk-ass crab.
What's wrong with you?
Grr, it's not his fault he's a sissy.
Someone's been coddling him.
Don't look at me.
I wanted to eat him.
Sorry. It's usually the mother.
You know, I run a small academy
for lobsters like this one.
We stress tough love,
daily chores and the like.
No. We're not sending
the lobster away
to some snobby boarding school.
Arr, I understand.
It... It's hard to let go.
Eh, tell me this then.
Do you have any spare change?
SKINNER: And now
to present the grant money,
a legendary figure
in educational disbursement,
State comptroller, Atkins.
Whoo!
Thank you.
I'm here tonight to honor the girl
whose unprecedented test score
has set a new standard
in excellence.
Lisa.
(applause)
Thank you.
I know this giant check
is very important to everyone here.
But what's even more important
is the truth.
(all muttering)
Because, after all,
education is the search for truth.
No. No, it isn't.
Don't listen to her.
She's out of her mind.
And the truth is,
we don't deserve this grant
and I don't deserve your applause.
I cheated on that test.
(audience gasping)
Wait. How dare
you condemn this girl?
Who among you can honestly say
you've never cheated?
On your wives or your husbands?
(all muttering)
What she just did took courage.
And where I come from, Canada,
we reward courage.
So I hereby decree
that you keep the grant
and let's give this brave girl
the ovation she deserves.
(applause)
Oh, honey, I'm so proud of you.
You got the highest grade
in the class.
-But, mom...
-The highest grade.
Okay, Lisa's gone.
Places, people.
Oh, man, acting is tough.
I'll be in my trailer.
Ah, good old predictable Lisa.
I knew her conscience
was a ticking time bomb.
Heads up.
Here comes the real comptroller.
COMPTROLLER:
This grant ensures
a light bulb in every classroom
and a high-definition TV
for the teachers' lounge.
(applause)
Now, where's the little girl
who made this grant possible?
Where's Lisa Simpson?
(applause)
Come on up here, Lisa.
Now how about that?
Smart and modest.
Well, I should be going now.
These giant checks
don't hand themselves out.
Okay, people, let's have
a round of applause
for the real comptroller.
-COMPTROLLER: Hmm.
-(applause)
CHALMERS: Idiot.
I know a liquor store
where we can cash this right now.
(cheering)
LISA: And done.
That's one grade I truly earned.
Ohh, who left
these muddy claw prints
on my clean floor?
Sorry, Marge.
Pinchy got all dirty
in the yard chasing birds.
But don't worry,
I put him in a nice, hot bath.
(sniffs)
Hey, what smells so good?
Yeah...
Pinchy?
Oh, Pinchy!
(crying)
(Homer sobbing)
(sobbing loudly)
Oh, man, that's good.
Pass the butter.
(sobbing loudly)
Are you going to eat that
all by yourself?
Uh-huh.
Pinchy would've wanted it this way.
My dear, sweet Pinchy.
No more pain
where you are now, boy.
(grunts)
(sucks)
Oh, god, that's tasty.
I wish Pinchy were here
to enjoy this.
(smacking)
Oh, Pinchy.
(theme music playing)
Shh.
Captioned by
Visual Data Media Services