♪ The Simpsons ♪
(chalk screeches)
(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(tires screeching)
(horn honks)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
♪ The Monster Mash ♪
♪ And do my
graveyard smash ♪
MARTY:
Doing the "Monster Mash" with you
on this beautiful
Valentine's Day.
BILL: Marty, why did
you play that song today?
There must be thousands
of love songs.
MARTY:
Well, it's-it's kind of a love song.
All the monsters enjoying
each other's company,
you know, dancing.
Holding their evil in check.
BILL: You played
the wrong record, didn't you?
MARTY:
Why are you doing this to me?
Bah! This is just another
Hallmark holiday
cooked up to sell cards.
Oh, a Valentine
from my granddaughter.
Could I have the envelope?
"To Moe,
from your secret admirer."
Yoo-hoo!
Oh, God, no.
(kisses, belches)
And this is
for my huggy bug
in honor
of this special day.
(thinking)
Special day?
Oh, what have
I forgotten now?
Now don't panic.
Is it bacon day?
No, that's crazy talk.
She's getting impatient.
Take a stab at it.
Happy Valentine's Day.
Oh, thank you, dear.
Woo-hoo!
I'll bet you have a lot of
things planned, eh, Dad?
Uh, kind of.
Nobody makes a big deal
out of Valentine's Day.
♪ If you think I'm cuddly ♪
♪ And you want my company ♪
♪ Come on, wifey,
let me know ♪
♪ Ow, ow, ow, oww! ♪
Hey, Dad, why don't you
give Mom her present?
What a nice idea, son.
It's, uh...
upstairs on the second
floor of our house.
I'll just go get it.
(footsteps)
(door slams)
(Homer grunting and groaning)
(screaming)
Apu, you got
to help me.
I need a Valentine's gift
for my wife.
Perhaps this might
be appropriate.
Yes! You saved my life.
How much?
$100.
What?
That's highway robbery.
I won't pay it.
Oh, I think you will.
Forget it, pal.
(humming)
All right! But I'll
never shop here again.
(thinking) If he discovers
the discount supermarket next door,
all is lost.
-Nickel off on expired baby food.
-Sold!
Miss Hoover, can we
exchange our valentines?
Not just yet, Janey.
First, we're going to
construct paper mailboxes
to store the valentines.
Isn't that pointless busywork?
Bull's-eye! Get cracking.
Yes, Ralph?
My parents won't let me
use scissors.
(children giggling)
The children are right
to laugh at you, Ralph.
These things
couldn't cut butter.
Now take out your red crayons.
Miss Hoover?
Yes, Ralph?
I don't have a red crayon.
-Why not?
-I ate it.
Attention, everyone.
This is Principal Skinner.
Some student,
possibly Bart Simpson,
has been circulating
candy hearts
featuring crude,
off-color sentiments.
Well, let me
tell you something.
Valentine's Day is no joke.
Sending your chick
a valentine, huh?
Yep.
(gunfire and screaming)
Johnny.
Johnny!
Johnny!!
Cool.
I broke his brain.
All right, children.
You may now
exchange valentines.
Miss Hoover, I glued
my head to my shoulder.
(chuckling)
(sniffling)
(sobbing)
Poor Ralph.
Here you go, Ralph.
(gasps)
You choo-choo-choose me?
Happy Valentine's.
(sighing)
All right,
special holiday meal.
Where do you want
these beef hearts?
On the floor.
It doesn't look very clean.
Just do your job, heart-boy.
(creaking)
(heart beats)
(moaning)
Bart, what's wrong?
My baboon heart.
Body...
rejecting it.
(screaming)
Mm-hmm.
(school bell rings)
Can I walk you home...
valentine?
Sure, I guess.
That valentine
sure was funny.
(chuckles)
Glad you liked it.
It says,
"Choo-choo-choose me."
And there's a picture
of a train.
Yeah, nice gag.
Uh, so...
do you like... stuff?
The doctor said I wouldn't
have so many nosebleeds
if I kept my finger
out of there.
(nervous chuckle)
Well, here's my house.
♪ ...and fight,
The Itchy & Scratchy show ♪
Hey, kids, don't forget to
watch my 29th anniversary show
featuring clips like
this one of Sideshow Mel
whacked out on wowee sauce.
(drunkenly)
Everyone's always kissing your ass.
Well, I'm not afraid
to tell you,
you're a (bleep).
Oh, I'd give anything
to go to that show.
I'd sell my first-born son.
-Hey!
-You'll do as you're told.
Ralph thinks
I like him,
but I only gave him
a valentine
'cause I felt
sorry for him.
Ah, sweet pity.
Where would my love life
have been without it?
What do you say
to a boy
to let him know
you're not interested?
Well, honey--
Let me handle this, Marge.
I've heard 'em all.
"I like you as a friend."
"I think we should
see other people.
"I no speak English."
I get the idea.
"I'm married to the sea."
"I don't want to kill you,
but I will."
Honey! Honey, I'd tell this boy
that you're very flattered,
but you're not ready
for this kind of thing.
Thanks, Mom.
And if that doesn't work,
six simple words:
"I'm not gay,
but I'll learn."
Ralph, I think you're nice,
but I'm just not ready
for this kind of thing.
Do you understand?
I guess so.
Good.
Dad, how do you get
a girl to like you?
Son, whether you want to win
a girl or crack a nut,
the key is persistence.
Keep at it,
and never lose your cool.
(grunts)
Ah, come on,
you stupid...
Let that be a lesson
to the rest of you... nuts.
Okay, Dad.
I'll be persistent.
Is that how you got Mom?
Well, son,
never underestimate the appeal
of a man in uniform.
Oh, yeah!
(Wiggum chewing)
Oh. Mmm.
Oh, yeah.
Hey, boys and girls,
only four days
till my anniversary show.
29 years,
and when I came on,
they said
I wouldn't last a week.
And you know where
those reviewers are?
All dead.
How you doing down there,
fellas? Huh? Huh?
Anyway, here's a clip.
Now why do they call this
a urine monkey?
Oh... I just found out.
That's funny
for so many reasons.
We have to go
to that show.
Forget it.
To get those tickets,
our parents would
have to be part
of Springfield's
cultural elite.
Can you believe Flanders
threw out a perfectly
good toothbrush?
Ew.
(doorbell ringing)
Oh, no, it's Ralph.
Just make up some excuse.
She's in the can.
Go away.
Yes, sir.
I'd do anything for Lisa.
Really?
Mr. Simpson, the tar fumes
are making me dizzy.
Yeah, they'll do that.
"Dearest Martha,
since boyhood
"I have yearned to be
on the one-dollar bill,
"and with your help,
this, I shall achieve.
Sincerely, George Washington."
(class applauds)
Thank you, Rex.
I've selected the cast
for our Presidents' Day pageant.
Martha Washington
will be played by...
-Lisa Simpson.
-(giggles)
HOOVER: George Washington
will be played by...
(clears throat)
-Ralph Wiggum.
-(gasps)
Hmm.
What? This is a travesty.
Everyone knows
I'm the best actor
in this ridiculous school.
-Sit down, Rex.
-I will not sit down.
Someone's gotten to you,
you deceitful cow.
That's absurd, Rex.
Ralph won the part
fair and square.
That's the signal.
Take the boot
off the car, boys.
(chuckling)
Now Ralph is
in the play with me.
I just know he's going
to embarrass me
in front
of the whole school.
(knocking)
Huh?
Oh, no,
it's a package from Ralph.
Oh, a Malibu Stacy
convertible.
"Look in the tunk."
He must mean "trunk."
(gasps) Tickets to
the Krusty anniversary show!
Oh, he must want me
to go with him.
Oh, it isn't fair.
I'm ten times
the Krusty fan you are.
I even have the Krusty
home pregnancy test.
I'm not sure I should go.
I don't even like him.
You're right, Lis.
You shouldn't go.
It wouldn't be honest.
I'll go, disguised as you.
What if he wants
to hold hands?
I'm prepared to make
that sacrifice.
What if he wants a kiss?
I'm prepared to make
that sacrifice.
What if he--
You don't want to know
how far I'll go.
Dad, is it right
to take things from people
you don't like?
Sure it is, honey.
You do mean stealing,
don't you?
Well, actually,
it's not as bad as stealing,
but my conscience
is bothering me.
Your conscience?
Lisa, don't let
that pushy, little weenie
tell you what to do.
Homer, that's
a terrible thing to say.
Oh, shut up.
Yes, sir.
I am so glad you
cho-cho-choose to come.
Heh. I think you should
give that a rest, Ralph.
Chief Wiggum, how did you
ever get these tickets?
Krusty knows
how to play ball.
Ah... nothing beats
a good porno movie.
Chief Wiggum,
is this a bust?
Uh, yeah.
That's just what it is,
a bust.
That story isn't suitable
for children.
Really? I keep my pants on
in this version.
Ew.
ANNOUNCER:
It's the Krusty the Clown
29th Anniversary Show!
Hey!
(applause and cheering)
Thank you. Thank you.
Hey, Mr. President.
I campaigned
for the other guy,
but I voted for you.
(goofy laughter)
You know, I started this
show so long ago,
the ayatollah only
had a goatee. Ha ha!
(buzzer sounds)
What's the matter,
don't you people
read the papers?
Ah, let's look at some clips.
"He will not see me
stopping here
to watch his woods
fill up with snow..."
Hey, Frosty, you want some
snow, man? Bwah!
We discussed this,
and I said no.
(applause)
Now, here's a clip from 1973.
♪ Try to run, try to hide ♪
♪ Break on through
to the other side ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
Ah!
What was I on?
Lisa, do you want
a bite of my ice cream?
No, thanks.
Send it this way, boy.
-Whoops.
-Aw.
Aw... nothing gets
chocolate out. See?
I've worked with some marvelous
second bananas over the years,
but none more memorable
than Sideshow Raheem.
Uh, the script says
I'm supposed to bonk you with this.
I wouldn't.
Right on.
(queasy groan)
(applause)
Angry, angry young man.
Now for my favorite
part of the show.
What's that say?
"Talk to the audience?"
Oh, God,
this is always death.
All right.
Oh, no, please don't
show me with Ralph.
What's your name, son?
-Ralph.
-(Lisa whimpers)
And is this
your girlfriend, Ralph?
Yes, I love Lisa Simpson.
And when I grow up,
I'm going to marry her.
No!
Now you listen to me.
I don't like you.
I never liked you.
And the only reason I gave
you that stupid valentine
was because
nobody else would!
Watch this, Lis.
You can actually
pinpoint the second when
his heart rips in half.
And... now.
(groans)
At least you guys
are my friends.
(quacking)
(sighing)
Son, I know just
how you feel.
You've got a great little girl,
and the world's your oyster.
No, Dad, she made
a fool out of me.
Hey, come to think of it,
she did.
Well, she didn't reckon
with the awesome power
of the chief of police.
Now, where did I put my badge?
Hey!
That duck's got it.
Oh, come on, come on,
give it back.
I need it.
Ah, keep it.
(police siren)
Something wrong, officer?
Yeah, got a taillight out.
Where?
Right there.
You know, one day honest
citizens are going to stand up
to you crooked cops.
They are? Oh, no.
Have they set a date?
This orange drink
is the only way
to recoup our terrible losses
from "Fire Drill Follies."
I just don't know
what went wrong.
You opened the show
with a fire drill,
and everyone cleared out.
Hmm. So mother was right.
It was my fault.
Go ahead,
water it down some more.
My God, man, I've watered her
down as far as she'll go.
I cannot water no more.
Good evening,
everyone, and welcome
to a wonderful evening
of theater
and picking up
after yourselves.
We begin with a tribute to
our lesser-known presidents.
("Hail to the Chief" playing)
♪ We are the
mediocre presidents ♪
♪ You won't find our faces
on dollars or on cents ♪
♪ There's Taylor,
there's Tyler ♪
♪ There's Fillmore
and there's Hayes ♪
♪ There's William
Henry Harrison ♪
♪ I died in 30 days ♪
♪ We are the adequate,
forgettable ♪
♪ Occasionally regrettable ♪
♪ Caretaker presidents ♪
♪ Of the U.S.A. ♪
Hey girls,
check out this president.
(imitating Nixon)
I am not a butt.
(screaming)
Bart, do you want to
play John Wilkes Booth,
or do you want to
act like a maniac?
I'll be good.
Ralph, I'm sorry I--
Leave me alone.
I'm here to play
George Washington.
Uh... Ralph?
Miss Hoover, this beard's
giving me a rash.
Milhouse, you have one line
and then you're shot.
Now get out there.
I thought that Civil War
would never end.
Now to soothe my head
with an evening
at Ford's Theater.
Oh, no, John Wilkes Booth!
Hasta la vista, Abie.
(Milhouse grunting,
Bart imitating gunshots)
Come on boy, finish him off.
(screaming)
You're next,
Chester A. Arthur.
Unhand me, yankee.
And now our evening
comes to an end.
Woo-hoo!
With a thorough re-telling
of the life
of George Washington.
HOMER:
D'oh!
Dear, dear George Washington.
Can this liberty you dream of
be worth all this bloodshed?
Well, can it?
Dear madam,
would you put a price
on the air we breathe,
or the providence
that sustains us?
But couldn't we just
give in to the British?
Never!
(cheering, applause)
That boy is magnificent.
He makes me want to learn more
about our founding fathers.
To the library.
Yeah!
Dear Martha, I fear
my time is at hand.
Oh, George.
Your broth,
Mr. President.
I asked for no broth.
Away with you, lest my cane
find your backside.
Hmm, yes.
(sobbing)
Please don't leave me,
George.
Dear wife, if I could take
but one treasure
with me
to the next life,
it would be
your tender kiss.
Mmm...
Now that's a man.
I did not cry
when me own father
was hung for stealing a pig,
but I'll cry now.
(sobbing)
♪ From sea to ♪
♪ Shining sea ♪
Thanks for coming.
And don't forget to
purchase some orange drink
for the long ride home.
Ralph! Ralph!
You were so good!
Ralph!
Lisa.
Hi, Ralph.
You were great tonight.
Aw, thanks.
I've got something
for you.
"Let's bee friends!"
It says "Bee,"
and there's a picture
of a bee on it.
(both chuckle)
I thought you'd like it.
Oh, look at that.
Attention, all units.
-Riot in progress at--
-Not tonight.
BILL: Hey, hey! Bill and
Marty here wrapping up
a beautiful President's Day.
MARTY: To George and Abe
and all the rest,
here's a special song
just for you.
♪ I was working in
the lab late one night ♪
MARTY: Doggone it!
♪ When my eyes beheld
an eerie sight ♪
♪ For my monster from
his slab began to rise ♪
♪ And suddenly
to my surprise ♪
♪ He did the mash ♪
♪ He did the Monster Mash ♪
♪ The Monster Mash ♪
♪ It was a graveyard smash ♪
♪ He did the mash ♪
♪ It caught on in a flash ♪
♪ He did the Monster Mash ♪
♪ From my laboratory
in the castle east ♪
♪ To the master bedroom
where the vampires feast ♪
♪ The ghouls all came
from their humble abodes ♪
♪ To catch a jolt
from my electrodes ♪
♪ They did the mash ♪
♪ They did the Monster Mash ♪
♪ The Monster Mash ♪
♪ It was a graveyard smash ♪
♪ They did the mash ♪
♪ It caught on in a flash ♪
♪ They did the Monster Mash ♪
♪ The zombies
were having fun ♪
♪ The party had just begun ♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.