CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screech)
D’oh!
(screams)
(tires screech)
(wind blowing)
(British accent):
Oh, hello.
I’m documentary filmmaker
Declan Desmond.
32 years ago I interviewed
a group of Springfield
schoolchildren.
(laughter, indistinct talking)
(gulping)
DECLAN:
These children
ran the gamut of society:
rich and poor, black and white,
"he’ll grow into his looks"
and "forever hideous."
My dad was a circus freak, but
my mom don’t remember which one.
I like to think it
was a little bit of all of them.
DECLAN:
Every eight years,
I revisited those children,
creating a cinematic chronicle
of their lives.
Join me, won’t you,
to see dreams dissolve
like a muffin
in the rain in...
In (reading):
(fanfare plays)
What does the future hold
for these children?
Will he grow up to work
in a robot factory?
Will she be the receptionist
for a robot businessman?
And will he be a crusader
for robo-sexual rights?
I say, "yes," "no," and "yes."
Whee!
DECLAN:
So, Lenny, what
have we here?
My daddy said I can have
any birthday party I want.
My cake will be a picture
of a dinosaur
and all the guests will say,
"Why, Lenny,
that’s a fine cake!"
Then, "Yes," I’ll say.
DECLAN:
I decided not to waste any more
film on him after that.
I wish for world peace.
I wish for world war.
Oh, yeah, that would
be cooler.
(grunts)
I wish
when I grow up,
I’ll be richer
than everybody!
(laughing)
I will! I will be rich!
I’ll own a football team
and a basketball team
and I’ll make them
play baseball!
But what became
of these wide-eyed naives?
Let’s begin by following the
life of little Clancy Wiggum.
Bang-bang! Bang!
Freeze, robber, freeze!
Bang, bang, bang!
(screaming)
It hurts!
It hurts so bad!
Please, just put
one in my brain!
(sighs)
Okay.
Uh, bang.
(groaning):
Thank you.
As hall monitor,
I am the law.
No running in the hall.
No running
in the hall.
Ah, no running in the hall.
Hey, detention bird!
Thanks for not
running in the hall.
(muffled yelling)
Go, Wildcats.
(gunshots)
DECLAN:
At 24, Clancy Wiggum
was accepted into
the police academy.
(clicking)
Hmm...
Wiggum!
What did I tell you
about pointsy-towardsies?!
You seem a little
cranky, Commandant.
A back rub’ll set you right.
There we go.
Ooh... okay.
Don’t be afraid
to dig in there good!
(gunshot, thump)
Hey, what’s the matter, buddy?
Need a backrub?
DECLAN:
At 32, Officer Wiggum
had found the fast track
to becoming chief.
Oh, yeah, oh,
that’s the stuff.
Thanks for giving me
an 8:30 appointment.
You are a lifesaver.
You know, uh, if I was Chief,
I could give you 8:30 every day.
I don’t have
the authority to...
Oh... oh...
I’ll make it happen.
And here we are in now-times.
As you can see, I’ve gotten
everything I’ve ever wanted.
Except pants
that fit.
I told you that if
I let you in this movie
you couldn’t make
fun of me.
I’m not making fun of you.
I’m making fun of your pants.
Well, how’d you like it if
I made fun of your pants?
Go ahead.
Well, they’re a little, uh...
They-they, uh...
Oh, they’re perfect.
When I grow up,
I’ll have a giant mansion,
my own pinball machine
with infinity quarters,
eight pairs of peanut butter
and jelly pajamas...
How many wishes do I have left?
DECLAN:
None. You never had any.
I’m not a genie.
D’oh!
Homer, your dreams will
take a lot of money.
Don’t look at me.
Look at the camera.
Got it.
I said, look
at the camera.
No problem.
Now you’re looking
at a mud puddle.
That’s your hand.
That’s the production
accountant.
That’s your
other hand.
Do you even know
what a camera is?
Well, of cour... No.
I’m gonna put
this squeaky toy
on top of
the camera.
(squeaking)
(giggles):
Squeaky! Squeaky!
Squeaky, squeaky!
Squeaky, squeaky, squeaky!
DECLAN:
Unsurprisingly, by age 24,
Homer’s dreams of wealth
had not come to fruition.
Manure for sale!
Get your manure!
Loamiest in town!
Hey, the manure dealership
is just one of the things
I got going.
I also have a sweet gig as
an infomercial question-asker.
Um, I know Super Clean cleans,
but does it scrub?
My garage band
is getting so tight.
(guitar solo)
(drum solo)
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
(harmonica solo)
(panting)
The album cover’s
gonna be a naked girl
with stars for boobs.
And I do
open-casket caricatures.
Did he have any hobbies?
Get out of here!
DECLAN:
But Homer had found
a peanut of hope
in his Cracker Jack box
of despair.
Homer is so amazing!
He can chug a beer and
pitch woo at the same time.
The light from your eyes
could guide a ship at sea.
Eh?
DECLAN:
Are you two
considering children?
(scoffs):
Kids? No way!
You’ll never see a couple
of rugrats tying me down!
You better not put this shot
after the one where I said
I won’t have kids.
That would be
a devastating edit.
Homer, your life is
nothing to be ashamed of.
You’ve got
a loving family
and a steady job at
a nuclear power plant.
You’re not
English Breakfast,
but you’re not
Lapsang Soochong either.
(fey laughter)
Oh, yeah?
Check with me
in eight years, Dr. Who.
I’ll be kickin’ your ass
with a solid gold boot!
Hmm... what’s changed for me
since the last time I saw you?
Only... everything!
DECLAN:
I can’t believe it!
Homer Simpson...
a bloody millionaire?!
Why do you sound so shocked?
This is our fifth take.
Whee!
(laughing)
Now that I’m super-wealthy,
I can buy them whatever
their hearts desire.
(chuckles)
That’s why rich kids
turn out so well.
(whooping)
(laughing)
Mine has a cup holder.
Bart, that’s a blowhole.
You’re a blowhole!
(dolphin squealing)
No, boy.
Up, up, up!
DECLAN:
Well, Marge, you must be
proud of your "Homie."
Oh, yes, I’m so proud,
I feel my chest might burst.
Can you edit that? I don’t want
to say "chest" in a movie.
You said it
and it stays.
But I must know: How
did Homer come so far
in eight short years?
(mariachi band playing)
This pays a lot better
than you think.
(speaking Spanish)
You see, Declan,
I made my millions
with a simple invention:
the Condiment Pen!
Just click the
buttons at the top,
and you can choose from ketchup,
mustard, mayo and relish.
♪ Do, do, do, do, do-do-do. ♪
(loud whisper):
I got the idea
from the regular pen.
DECLAN:
Can I use it on
fish and chips?
I don’t know.
You can put horseradish on
your dead mother for all I care.
The point is:
I’m rich, rich, rich!
Just look--
my dog has his own Jacuzzi!
(yelping)
(giggling)
He loves it!
(yelps)
DECLAN:
You win, Homer.
I guess there’s no way I can
embarrass you any further.
(Declan chuckles)
When I, um, grow up,
I’m gonna be a rocket scientist!
To Mars!
Zoom.
(grunts)
(nervous cry)
Ah, bullies approaching.
Activate cloaking device.
DECLAN:
Professor Frink,
you’ve become
one of Springfield’s most
renowned scientific minds.
-You discovered and
cured Frink’s disease,
-Uh-huh.
created the element
Frinkonium,
and invented the
eight-month-after pill.
Yes, yes, all right.
All of that means nothing, sir.
I’ve spent my whole life in the
lab and never talked to a girl.
That’s why I built
this time machine.
I give you the chrono-trike!
Now, I’ll go back in time
to tell myself to choose
a different career,
one where I’ll meet a female
woman of the girl-u-lar variety.
(grunting)
Have to get the speed
going here.
(electrical zapping)
(humming)
Listen to me,
little Frink.
I am here to warn you...
(grunting
and groaning)
That was...
Hey, I’m still going,
but... (groans)
(humming)
Hey... cool!
I want to be a lawyer
and a doctor
because a woman can do anything.
DECLAN:
At 24, Eleanor had graduated
from Harvard Medical
and Yale Law.
Your Honor, I’d like
to request a continuance
so I can go deliver a baby.
I love babies.
I’ll allow it.
I’m a little burnt-out.
So, sometimes-- don’t shoot me--
I have a glass of wine
with Buster here.
(chuckles nervously)
He’s a real comfort.
I might even get a second cat.
(shrieking
and muttering gibberish)
(cats yowling)
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
DECLAN:
Nice kitty.
I like taking pictures.
Whee!
(camera shutter clicks)
Take my picture.
(grunts and groans)
(camera shutter clicks)
Aw, crap, my
first kiss.
You could do a lot worse,
my friend.
DECLAN:
At age 16,
Marge was the star photographer
for her school newspaper.
But her interests soon expanded
beyond shutterbuggery.
The biggest change for me
over the last eight years?
That’s got to be Homer.
Marge, baby!
I got a picture of you
tattooed on my chest.
(chuckling)
They had a sale
on skulls.
(murmurs awkwardly)
DECLAN:
At 24,
Marge’s photojournalistic
dreams were,
shall we say, underdeveloped?
I need one wallet-sized photo
for my captain’s license.
(sighs wearily)
Coming right up.
Mind if I turn on
a little music?
("Disco Inferno" playing)
It’s so danceable.
Nautical Stu
loves disco music.
Ha, ha!
DECLAN:
And the world welcomed
Disco Stu.
Ha, mm, yeah!
(sighs)
I need a full-time job
to support Homer
so he has time to work
on his rock music,
his erotic etchings,
his Play-Doh Theater...
(sighs heavily)
And yet look how
things turned out.
This overnight affluence must
have come as a tremendous shock.
Oh, yes, sir.
As shocks go,
this one’s a real zaparoo.
Listen, something’s been
piquing my curiosity.
Why is your medicine cabinet
full of old man ointments?
Oh... mm-hmm.
-Well, yeah, the
ointments, um..
-(door opens)
(gasps):
What are you people doing
in my summer home?
(stammering):
Uh, oh, uh...
This is Eduardo,
my pool boy.
He thinks he’s an
angry, rich man.
I am an angry, rich man.
(loud whisper):
That’s the pool
chemicals talking.
Homer J. Simpson,
your fabulous millionaire
lifestyle is all a lie.
(a la Katharine Hepburn):
Oh, Father, my pony Buttercup
can jump
ever so high...
(normal voice):
Hoo-boy, it’s Mr. Burns.
Please, Mr. Burns,
pretend you work for me.
You can have the boy.
Just don’t beat him.
(loud whisper):
You can beat him.
Just don’t leave marks.
Shut up, you waste
of skin and fat.
You’ve desecrated
my every possession.
Ugh!
Eww!
(muffled grunting)
(sighs)
(panting and groaning)
Oh, thank you, sir.
For three days
I’ve had nothing to read
but clock-setting instructions:
"Using the suspension spring
above the pendulum leader,
hang the pendulum
on the pendulum guide..."
(angry grunt)
Mr. Burns,
we’re so sorry.
The plan was just
to use your backyard,
and the next thing
we know,
Mr. Smithers is tied up
in a grandfather clock.
Please get me out of here.
It’s 11:59:59.
(clock tolling 12 times
as Smithers moans)
(exasperated grunt)
I’ve heard enough.
Release the hounds.
Uh, sir, your hounds are
still at the winter house.
Well, bring them over
in the Durango.
Shadow and Winston
have been fighting a lot.
Huh, put Winston
in the front.
Winston doesn’t
like the front.
Just do it. Do it.
Do it now!
(sipping)
...and that’s
how I got
the vending machine
contract for the Kremlin.
(polite laughter)
(door opens, growling)
Sorry, sir.
Traffic was
a nightmare.
Then I got caught in some
kind of garlic festival.
(menacing):
Release the hounds.
(barking, screaming)
HOMER:
Stop it, Winston!
In the wake of this deception,
I had two questions for Homer:
"Why lie?" and "Lies... why?"
But he seemed
less than eager to meet.
Homer, I brought
a squeaky!
(squeaking)
(shrieks)
(toy squeaking)
(yelling)
(yells)
(toy squeaking)
(shrieks, grunts)
Ooh! Ah! Ah!
Help!
DECLAN:
I realized that if this bunny
was going to be boiled,
I would have
to turn up the heat.
LENNY:
There you are!
I’m ready
for my segment.
(chuckles):
Lenny...
always exciting
to hear from you.
Did you ever try
that new shampoo?
Nope, never did.
Want to watch me
pay my cable bill?
I got checks with
butterflies on them.
I am interesting.
No, you’re not.
What do you want?
Marge, can you just
let me in for a minute?
We let you in
32 years ago
and it’s brought us
nothing but pain.
Well, if you want, I can
cut you out of the film.
No, no, no, no, no!
Let’s not get crazy.
Then I just want to know why
your husband did what he did.
HOMER:
I’ll tell you why.
It’s been another eight years
and what do I have?
Same job, same house,
same dirty joke book.
(weak laughter)
I just thought for once I could
be the cool guy in your movie.
But all I am is the guy who
makes everyone else look good.
Strong words
from a dumpy man.
And cut.
Wait just a
cotton-swabbing minute!
A good man went to a lot of
trouble just to impress you.
And I went along with it
because I love him to pieces.
And you made him
look like a fool.
Well, I don’t want you
anywhere near my house!
Now you can cut!
What’s the matter, Declan?
Did a cop give you
a ticket
for talking
like a fruit?
It’s the oddest thing.
I actually feel affection
for these knuckle-dragging
sub-monkeys.
I feel sorry
for Homer Simpson.
What, have you been
sipping cuckoo juice?
Homer’s got it made.
He’s married to one
hell of a woman.
All I’ve got
is this porn channel
I’m too cheap
to descramble.
That’s an ad
for shoe inserts.
What the....?
I’ve been writing creepy
letters to that?
But what you said
about Homer, it’s...
it’s given me
a brilliant idea!
An action movie
where I play the Pope
who kills the president?
No, that’s a
terrible idea.
Yeah, I know.
It’s stupid.
I think
it could work, though.
I’ve even got a title:
Pontiff No Return.
I came up with it, but
I don’t really get it.
DECLAN:
The next day, I invited Homer
to my editing bay.
Oh, my God, the view!
This makes it all worth it!
Yeah, it’s not so much
fun when you’re blind.
At least you made it
up the mountain.
No thanks
to you two.
All right,
you lured me to your bay.
Now what sick game
are you playing?
I have some footage
to show you.
O, spirit!
Are you gonna show me my future?
My snow-flecked grave,
mourned by no man?
Well, it’s not too late
for me to change!
You there, boy!
Buy me a Christmas goose!
The biggest one in the shop!
BOY (squeaky-voiced):
And then what?
Homer, come over here
and take a look at this.
I’ve gone over 100,000 hours
of Springfield footage--
twice-- and put together
something you must see.
If I could trade lives with
anybody, I’d pick Homer.
Have you been to Homer’s house?
It’s got a back yard,
a front yard...
The place is like yard city!
I love his laugh.
He picked the perfect time
to lock in his mortgage.
He’s the kindest,
sweetest, most generous man
ever to drive through
my living room.
I’ll pay for most of this!
He may not be perfect,
but he’s my dad.
Homer gave me a kidney.
It wasn’t his, I didn’t need it,
and it came postage due,
but still, a lovely gesture.
I like when
Daddy’s out of work
’cause he can spend
more time with me.
At bedtime, he tucks me in
tighter than anyone else could.
And you know what?
No monsters have gotten me yet.
Wow...
I have a pretty good life
after all.
Homer!
Don’t kill the foreign man!
(chuckling):
Relax, Marge.
I wasn’t
gonna kill him.
All those years I was dreaming
of other things,
I was actually doing
what I really wanted:
hanging out with my family,
drinking with my friends,
making friends with my family
and hanging with my drinking.
Marge, you’re my
real dream come true.
And I get to live you
every day.
Oh, Homie!
You make each eight-year
interval better than the last!
Oh...
So, Homer, are you at peace
with your lot in life?
Absolutely.
Hey, is that
a mixing board?
Uh, no, no.
It’s something else.
Yes, it is.
Look, I need to lay
down some tracks.
I’m making a demo tape.
By the time you come back
in eight years,
I’ll be the world’s
richest rock star!
One, two,
three, four...
♪ Satan, you’re my lady ♪
♪ Stick me
with your pitchfork thing ♪
♪ Satan, you’re my lady ♪
♪ Stick me
with your pitchfork thing ♪
♪ All night long ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, girl ♪
♪ Smother me
with your beezle boobs ♪
♪ ’Cause I’m
a rock ’n’ roll hero ♪
♪ With a motorcycle made of fire
called the Flame Mobile ♪
-♪ Flame Mobile ♪
-(electrical zapping)
♪ Satan, you’re my lady ♪
♪ Stick me
with your pitchfork thing ♪
Come on, Declan.
Join me.
♪ Shoobie-doobie-do-wa ♪
-No!
-♪ Woobie-shoobie-do-wa ♪
-Those aren’t
the lyrics!
-What?
-"Satan,
you’re my lady."
-Oh!
♪ Satan, you’re my lady ♪
♪ Stick me
with your pitchfork thing ♪
-♪ Shoobie-do-wa,
shoobie-do-wa ♪
-I think I’ll keep that in.
Stop.
I don’t really know much about
this rock and roll thing.
Oh, you could
have fooled me!
-I think I can do
one more, though.
-All right.
♪ Satan,
you’re my lady ♪
♪ Stick me with your
pitchfork thing ♪
♪ Shoobie-do-wa,
shoobie-do-wa ♪
-♪ All night long ♪
-♪ Yeah, yeah, girl ♪
-♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
Don’t quit your day job.
All right. That’s it.
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Shh!
Enhanced by Fotokem