♪ The Simpsons ♪
D'oh!
(screams)
(all screaming)
ANNOUNCER: Live from
Springfield Penitentiary's
fabulous big open area
in cell block "D"
it's the Krusty The Clown
Prison Special.
(cheering)
♪ I slugged
some jerk in Tahoe ♪
♪ They gave me
one to three ♪
♪ My high-priced lawyer
sprung me ♪
♪ On a technicality ♪
♪ I'm just visiting
Springfield Prison ♪
♪ I get to sleep
at home tonight ♪
(all grumbling)
Hey, hey, I kid.
I kid 'cause I love.
I tell you, the best folk
in the world
are prison folk.
(all cheering)
Man, those cons
love Krusty.
Inside every
hardened criminal
beats the heart of
a ten-year-old boy.
And vice versa.
Just remember, Bart,
convicts aren't cool.
They're bad people.
Yeah, maybe so,
but they get the job done.
Hey! Now I know where
my tax dollars are going.
-Huh?
-(chuckling)
Hey, hey,
it's my old TV sidekick
Sideshow Bob.
Why, I haven't seen you
in years.
What have you been doing
with yourself, Bob?
Well, Krusty,
as you may remember,
after I tried to frame you
for armed robbery,
I tried to murder
Selma Bouvier.
Let's see-- I rigged
the mayoral elections,
I tried to blow up Springfield
with a nuclear device,
and I tried to kill you.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
And whenever I could find
a spare moment,
I've tried to murder.
Bart Simpson.
(yelling)
He said, "tried."
Someone should
really go up there
and talk to him.
(sighs)
Whew.
Homer!
Oh,
all those stairs...
Oh, you have nothing
to worry about, honey.
Your mother's right,
Bart.
Sure, you're the one
who ruined
all of Sideshow Bob's
criminal schemes--
We're very proud
of you, by the way.
And sure, he's probably
so insane with rage
that he'd butcher you
horribly if he could.
But he's
safely locked away.
In a medium-security prison.
-For life.
-Unless he gets out somehow.
Which is impossible.
Or so you think,
except he's done it
so many times before.
Thanks for trying, guys,
but Sideshow Bob
wants me dead,
and Sideshow Bob
is an unstoppable
killing machine.
♪ I once ♪
♪ Was lost ♪
♪ But now am found ♪
♪ Was blind but now I see ♪
Well, that was
lovely, Robert.
You other cons could benefit
from his shining example.
(all grumbling)
Now, really, Reverend,
your praise is going
to get me beaten up.
Oh, I'm sorry, Bob,
but your transformation
is truly inspiring.
Yes.
I'm a good, good man.
You know, it's hard to believe
this model prisoner
could be the same
monstrous fiend
who once ran for mayor.
It's a pleasure
to have recommended you
for the work-release
program.
Me? I'm touched.
I really am.
But you'll never find
anyone willing to hire
a five-time loser like me.
I already have.
Cecil?
Is it really you?
Hello, brother.
I'm happy to see you.
But it's been ten years.
We haven't spoken
since the...
unpleasantness.
You mean
Arthur Fiedler's wake?
No, no, no.
I mean our falling out.
Oh, that.
That's ancient history.
Let's make a fresh start.
Come work for me.
But this is wonderful.
You do know
I used to have a--
(clears throat)
problem with trying
to kill people?
Goodness, I had no idea.
For, you see, I have been
on Mars for the last decade
in a cave with my eyes shut
and my fingers in my ears.
Touché, Cecil.
I'm aware
of your felonious past,
but you are
still my brother,
and blood is thicker
than bread and water.
You don't have to worry
about me, brother.
I'm all murdered out.
Praise the Lord.
(booing and yelling)
Get back in there!
How can you even think
of releasing Sideshow Bob?
He's just faking it
to get out of jail.
He's a maniac!
Bob is no maniac.
He explained his reasons
for trying to kill us all.
And I assure you,
they were perfectly sane.
Oh, you gotta be kidding!
My friends, please.
I make no secret
of my past.
But isn't our system
of justice
based on the idea
that a man can change?
Have the boys
check into that.
I know I don't deserve
another chance,
but this is America.
And as an American,
aren't I entitled to one?
MAN: Probably!
Can't you find it in your hearts
just to let me
live and work in peace?
(all agreeing)
Don't you see
what you've done?
Sideshow Bob hasn't reformed.
He's pure evil!
Oh, if only you knew
what he was thinking.
I hope they still make
that shampoo I like.
Now, make yourself
at home.
Perhaps a glass
of Bordeaux?
I have the '82
Chateau Latour
and a rather indifferent
Rausan-Segla.
I've been in prison,
Cecil.
I'll be happy just as long
as it doesn't taste
like orange drink
fermented under a radiator.
That would be
the Latour, then.
And God bless Mom and Dad
and Lisa and Maggie
and, please, God,
kill Sideshow Bob.
Bart, no!
It's him or me, o, Lord.
-(grunting)
-Ow!
You can't ask God
to kill someone.
Yeah! You do
your own dirty work.
Well, I suppose I should
ask you what you do
if I'm to be
working with you.
For me, Bob. For me.
I am Springfield's
chief hydrological
and hydrodynamical engineer.
Hydrological
and hydrodynamical--
talk about
running the gamut.
Snigger all you like, Bob.
Thank you.
I believe I shall.
But you'll find
one gets more respect
as a humble civil servant
than as a homicidal maniac
or a clown's sidekick.
Aha! I knew it.
You're still angry that
Krusty picked me instead of you.
I can't imagine
what you mean.
Oh, come now.
You wanted to be Krusty 's
sidekick since you were five!
What about the buffoon lessons,
the four years at clown college?
I'll thank you not to refer
to Princeton that way.
The point is you obviously
still blame me
for what happened
at your audition.
(whimpering)
Thanks for driving me,
big brother.
These giant clown mitts
are extremely hilarious,
but do make it
difficult to shift gears.
That's the title of Erma Bombeck's
latest, isn't it?
KRUSTY: Number 73!
You're next.
Make with the laugh-laugh.
(drum roll, rim shot)
(clearing throat)
(meekly)
Hey, children.
Meet me, Sideshow Cecil.
KRUSTY (imitating buzzer):
Next.
Uh, I have prepared
a pie-in-the-face take.
(groaning)
All right.
Knock yourself out, kid.
Hal?
Ooh.
Free comedy tip, slick:
The pie gag's only funny
when the sap's got dignity,
like that guy.
Hey, Hal, pie job for
Lord Autumnbottom there.
Oh, dear.
(laughing)
(applause, laughter)
That guy's a genius!
He's gonna change the way
we think about
getting hit by pies!
Chumley, you're hired.
When that pie hit your face,
I saw my dreams explode
in a burst of cream and crust.
But I suppose
I should thank you.
After all,
it led me to my true calling.
Cecil, no civilization
in history
has ever considered
chief hydrological engineer
a calling.
(clearing throat)
Yes, yes. The Cappadocians.
Fine.
CECIL: There it is--
the future site
of the Springfield
hydroelectric dam.
Just the thought of all
that raw, surging power
makes me wonder why the hell
I should care.
Because you'll be supervising
the construction crew.
Oh, great.
Whenever a woman
passes by,
I suppose it will be my job
to lead the hooting.
"Oh, yeah!
Shake it, madam.
Capital knockers!"
Come on, Bob.
This is your chance to show
the people of Springfield
you can hold down
an honest job.
He's planning something evil--
I know it.
It must have something to do
with the town's water supply.
Maybe he's gonna pee
in the river!
Mmm. Nah.
That's not his style.
Who is that?
(gasps)
Why...
it's Bart Simpson!
Hello, Bart!
He's just a little shy because
I've tried to kill him so many times.
Oh.
I really must thank you
for this moment
of tranquility, Edna.
You know, I haven't been
on a date in six years.
Oh, the pleasure's
mine, Bob.
It's so exciting
to be dating a killer.
To be fair, I never
successfully killed anyone.
Oh. I see.
I did once try to kill
the world's greatest lover,
but then, I realized there are
laws against suicide.
(giggling)
-You get my drift?
-Oh, you.
Mrs. Krabappel, no!
That's Sideshow Bob!
Well,
that's the last time
I announce my dinner
plans in class.
That was Edna Krabappel.
You only get one chance
with Edna Krabappel.
I hope you're happy.
I won't be happy
until I find out
what you're up to.
Wherever you go
and whatever you do,
I'll be there
watching and waiting.
He says that, but I bet
he gives up pretty quickly.
Hello, brother.
All's well, I trust?
It most certainly is not!
The workmen you've given me
don't know their asses
from the hole in the ground
they accidentally
blew yesterday.
Come now, you speak as if
they were a gaggle
of slack-jawed yokels.
Mr. Terwilliger,
come quick!
There's trouble down to
the "see-ment" mixer, sir!
See, cousin Merl
and me
was playin' fetch
with Geech--
that's our old
smellhound-- and--
Geech gone to heaven,
Mr. Terwilliger.
Oh, cousin Merl, really!
Temper, temper.
You know cousin Merl
ain't been quite right lately.
I'm telling you, Cecil,
I can't take
much more of this--
rustic workmen who've
turned the Sanijohn
into a smokehouse...
coveralls that don't
quite cover all...
and a psychotic little boy
who will not stop
hounding me!
This little boy right here.
Sometimes, I wish
this dam would burst
and bury this cursed town.
Hey, you said we were
going to Dairy Queen.
I lied. Now, help me rummage
through Bob's trash for clues.
Then, I promise
we'll go to the water slide.
Okay.
(both screaming)
You again!
Well, that's it.
I'm going to do what I should
have done a long time ago.
(knocking)
Madam, your children
are no more...
than a pair of
ill-bred troublemakers.
Lisa, too?
Especially Lisa.
But especially Bart.
If he crosses me one more time,
just once more--
Well, I can't be held
responsible for my actions.
Well, I hope
Bob fed you
'cause I ate
your dinners.
I know it's hard to accept,
Bart, but face it--
Sideshow Bob has changed.
No, he hasn't.
He's more the same
than ever,
and I know
where the evidence is.
There's only one place
it could possibly be.
Bob's trailer at the
construction site?
That's even better.
Let's go there.
What were you thinking?
The haunted mine.
Blueprints...
concrete invoices...
construction schedules...
If I didn't know better,
I'd swear Bob
was building a dam.
Oh, yeah?
Then explain this.
(gasping)
Bart! There must be millions
of dollars there!
What is Sideshow Bob
doing with--
(rattling)
(grumbling)
(roaring)
(screaming)
Who left the lights on?
Who's in here?
Cletus? Cousin Merl?
Big Hungry Joe?
I think he may
have spotted us.
Run!
(gasping)
You two.
Be careful.
There's hydroelectricity
in there.
Whoops.
Will you children
stop tormenting me?
I've done nothing wrong.
Give it up, Bob.
We found the money.
Where did that come from?
I've never seen that money
before in my life.
Then you must have
had your eyes closed
when you embezzled it.
I told you, I'm not
a criminal anymore.
You want to know
what I've been up to?
Here's a clue
for you, Jack.
100,000 tons of
reinforced concrete.
My God,
it's completely hollow.
What happened
to all the concrete?
You cut back
on building materials
and kept all the money
for yourself.
That's what happened.
Get him, Lis.
But I wasn't in charge
of the money.
Cecil was.
Now, let's stop bickering
and get out of here.
This dam could collapse
at any minute.
CECIL: One minute past sunrise,
to be precise.
SIDESHOW BOB:
Cecil?
Once I blow up the dam
there will be no evidence
of missing concrete
and I walk away
with 15 million.
But everyone will know
you did this.
Perhaps...
or perhaps they'll blame
the master criminal.
You know, the one
who's been working at the dam
and has a grudge
against Springfield.
I know cousin Merl has had
his troubles with the revenuers
but he's hardly a master crim--
Oh. You're referring to me.
Yes. I'm framing you,
and I'm doing a really
excellent job, too.
Wait a minute.
This is all because I got
to be Krusty's sidekick
instead of you, isn't it?
Off the record, yes,
but officially,
I did it for the money.
Speaking of which
hand it over.
Ta.
I forgot to mention,
I'm planning to blow up the dam
with you inside.
Well, obviously.
(lock clicking)
(grunting)
Oh, it's hopeless--
utterly, utterly hopeless.
Oh, I see.
When it's one of my schemes,
you can't foil it fast enough,
but when Cecil tries
to kill you,
"It's hopeless-- utterly,
utterly hopeless."
Well, if you kids
aren't going to foil him,
I'll have to do it myself.
Come on, quickly now.
Bart, for once,
I'm not trying to kill you.
I know it's an
awkward situation,
and I don't like it
any more than you do,
but you've got
to trust me.
Ah, what the hell.
(gasping)
(screaming)
(coughing)
Let's go again.
No!
Come on, children.
Let's go thwart my brother.
♪ I'm on the top
of the world ♪
♪ Looking down
on creation ♪
♪ And the only explanation
I can find ♪
♪ Boo-boo-boo ♪
Um, do you know
what you're doing?
Lisa, you don't spend
ten years
as a homicidal maniac
without learning
a few things
about dynamite.
Plunger? Check.
Hard hat? Check.
$15 million and a gun?
Checkmate.
Good-bye, Bob.
No!
Guess who?
Maris?
Oh!
Shoot.
Bob, look.
At last, I'm going to do
what Bob never could--
kill Bart Simpson.
By throwing me off a dam?
Isn't that a little crude
for a genius like you?
Ooh, I suppose it is.
If anyone asks, I'll lie.
(screaming)
Bart!
Cecil...
And now, to kill you.
There may be a slight
ringing in your ears.
Fortunately, you'll be
nowhere near them.
I guess this is it.
Thanks, anyway.
You know, I could
snip the wires.
We'd fall to our deaths,
but we'd save the entire town.
Bart, how would you like to do
something incredibly noble?
Do we have to?
Yes.
(screaming)
(gasping)
(grunts)
You-- You saved
my life, Bart.
Yeah.
I guess this means you can't
ever try to kill me again, huh?
Oh, I don't know about that.
Joking. Joking.
(sirens wailing)
You've brought shame
to this family, Cecil.
Oh, I don't relish
having to write
the Christmas letter
this year.
Nor I to read it.
You know, Bob,
all this time
I thought
you were a bungler,
but destroying the city
is far tougher than I thought.
Here's your man, chief.
Cecil? I think not.
This looks like the work
of crazy old Sideshow Bob.
No, chief.
Bob's innocent.
It's the truth.
The truth, huh?
That sounds
like the testimony
of crazy old
Lisa Simpson.
Cecil just voluntarily
confessed, chief.
That's some good work, Lou.
You'll make sergeant
for this.
Uh, I already am
a sergeant, chief.
Perhaps you are,
but I say
Bob goes
back to jail.
But, surely--
I mean, I caught Cecil.
Maybe so,
but Lou here says
you were
resisting arrest.
No, I didn't, chief.
Quiet, Lou, or I will
bust you down to sergeant
so fast, it'll make
your head spin.
Funny, isn't it, Lise?
Those people down there
have no idea
how close they came
to complete destruction.
Marge, I'm going
to look for the kids.
(screams)
I think I wet my bed.
But you can't do this.
I saved
the children's lives!
I'm a hero!
Tell them they'll live
to regret this.
You'll live to regret this.
Oh, thanks a lot.
Now I look crazy.
There they go--
two criminal geniuses
locked away together.
Who knows
what diabolical schemes
they might concoct?
You give me--
I'm older.
I get the top bunk.
Oh, poppycock.
I called it
at the arraignment.
Get back.
So, when do
they bring us the menus?
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.