(SlNGlNG) The Simpsons
(TlRES SCREECHlNG)
D'oh !
(SCREAMlNG)
(BRAKES SCREECHlNG)
(ELECTRlCAL BUZZlNG)
This is Kent Brockman,
live at
Springfield's most beloved
tourist attraction,
the man-shaped mountain crag
known as Geezer Rock.
Carved by
centuries of wind and rain,
Geezer Rock
will soon be more than
just a place for teens
to have sex
and commit suicide.
Why did they cancel Futurama?
(SCREAMS)
You crushed my boyfriend !
You better be good
at making out!
Today, Geezer Rock will be
officially designated
a national landmark.
What's the big deal
about a rock that
looks like a dude?
l've got a dad that
looks like a monkey.
Bart, you promised
you'd stop making
that comparison !
Per our agreement!
(GROANS lN DlSGUST)
Knock-kneed home renters.
Can't we
thin this herd with some
smallpox-infected blankets?
We're already immune,
you jerk!
Gee, l never
noticed that before.
He's got a tree in his eye.
lf that tree gets too big,
it'll ruin the beauty
of that rock!
We'll lose tourists!
And then, who will
buy my roadside corn?
You don't sell
roadside corn.
There's a lot
you don't know
about me, Marge.
A lot that would shock you.
(SlNGlNG) Ride a painted pony
Let the spinnin' wheeI spin
Thank you, BIood and Tears.
Sorry to hear about Sweat.
Now, before
the Undersecretary
of the lnterior
declares Geezer Rock
a national landmark,
we shall hear
a poem written by
honor student, Lisa Simpson.
Thank you.
(HOMER STRUGGLlNG)
Geezer Rock,
An Appreciation in Verse.
(LlGHT APPLAUSE)
(GRUNTlNG)
Now, to do something
l've never done before.
Help out an old man.
"Postcard image,
thing to see. . ."
(RUMBLlNG)
Gotta go, sweetie!
But l didn't read my poem !
Here's a poem.
Run fast or lose your ass!
(ALL SCREAMlNG)
Mr. Burns?
Mr. Burns is gone.
And tonight was the night
l was gonna
show him my tattoo.
(SOBBlNG)
l can't believe that
historic rock is gone.
My poem has become an elegy.
An elegy no one
will ever hear.
Well, at least
some good came out of today.
Bart, you're grounded
for a year!
l'll just pay the fine.
Okay. Three bucks.
Why don't you
publish your poem?
Publish it myself?
Why not?
l could put out
a whole newspaper
dedicated to the rock!
l'd be a publisher,
just like Katharine Graham !
Or that lady who wheels
Larry Flynt around.
Mr. Burns, perhaps it's best
you were snatched away
before time could
diminish your beauty.
Stop your wailing, Waylon !
l'm alive!
MR. BURNS: Oops!
That stays in.
Sir, you're alive! But how?
Because of my svelte physique,
l was able to fit in
a narrow air pocket.
l survived on
whatever sustenance
came my way.
ThankfuIIy, a mother moIe
nursed me as her own
untiI I was strong
enough to continue.
Now, let's see how
the common folk
are grieving for
their fallen god, me.
And so,
a day after the tragedy,
the town still mourns
the loss of its
venerable old man.
Here it comes.
BeIoved by chiIdren.
Yes, the little ones.
Thought to be
thousands of years oId...
l have been 89
for a while now.
We'll miss you, Geezer Rock.
(SPlTS)
(GASPlNG)
Quickly, Smithers,
re-hydrate me.
But one old man
we certainIy don't miss
is the late
C. Montgomery Burns.
As owner of the Springfield
Nuclear Power Plant,
he generated both
eIectricity and contempt.
Thank you, Geezer Rock,
for doing what none of us
had the courage to do,
smush Mr. Burns.
This town cared more
for a soulless piece of
granite than for me.
l don't have
a friend in the world.
You have me, sir.
Don't be so needy!
Well, l'm going
to change this town's
accurate impression of me.
Sir, you could
improve your image
with various good deeds.
Don't l already give out
turkey slices to the poor?
You eliminated that program
in the '30s, sir.
They were getting
too grabby!
Oh, all right.
l know how to change the way
the public thinks of me.
l'll buy every
media outlet in town !
Bring me a checkbook
and a mother mole!
(SUCKlNG)
l really got
hooked on this stuff.
Thanks for helping me deliver
the first edition of
The Red Dress Press, Dad.
l'm always happy
to help you, sweetie.
Extree! Extree!
Man driving erratically
throws papers out window!
LISA: "Elegy for Geezer Rock.
"Postcard image,
thing to see,
"to think of Springfield
is to think of thee.
"What thoughts
be-pass a'hind thy mien?
"Why sky art bIue,
why trees art green?
"And what, pray teII,
did thine eyes see?
"Perchance, old friend,
they gazed at me.
"Brought Iow by
nature's oafish hand,
"thou crush-ed
our reviewing stand
"and twixt thy stones
gIimpsed I the truth.
"AII things must pass,
thy face, my youth."
Oh, wow.
l haven't cried like this
since the third
Mr. Teeny died.
You couldn't hold
a candle to him.
(WEEPlNG)
Neither could you !
You're okay,
you got me broads.
Oh, this is one
dilly of a daily, Lisa.
Can't wait for tomorrow's.
"Tomorrow's"?
l hadn't thought
about publishing more.
You better.
l've already sold
a bunch of subscriptions.
How do you think l
got these swell prizes?
All right, Nelson,
what kind of journalism
skills do you have?
l don't know.
Making nerds cry?
Perfect.
You're our TV critic.
Ralph, what about you?
l want to be a fire truck.
How about
a feature columnist?
Yeah,
l'm a feature columnist!
(lMlTATlNG SlREN BLARlNG)
Good day.
Hello.
Great glayvin's ghost!
He's alive!
Yes, that's right.
l pulled a Jesus.
Have a nickel.
(EXCLAlMS lN SURPRlSE)
Burns is alive?
Then whose skull am
l drinking beer out of?
Boy, l can't wait to
dance on his grave!
Mmm-hmm.
Oh, yeah.
(ALL EXCLAlM)
Whose grave?
Uh, the unknown soldier?
Carry on.
(SHOES TAPPlNG)
Okay, it's time
to win the love of these
hateful morons.
Step one,
amass a vast media empire.
The station's not
for sale, Burns.
lt's been in the same family
for generations.
Look, l assure you,
no sack of money
is big enough to
change my mind.
Now, if. . .
There's more to life
than being rich, you know?
Very tempting,
but l assure you,
l'm still not sold.
Want to split
an ice cream sundae?
Done and done!
BART: Check it out.
Principal Skinrash.
Nice work, Bart,
but give him a runny nose.
l want the readers to gag
on their morning cup of joe.
Snot a problem, chief.
Don't call me chief.
Sure thing, jerk.
Chief is fine.
You're on the Morning Zoo
with BiII and Marty!
What's your Wednesday whine?
MR. BURNS:
Well, first of all,
I agree with you two,
it's sheer humbuggery
that pretty girIs
can fIirt their way
out of speeding tickets.
No support for
the naughty hotties!
(HONKlNG HORN)
Secondly, l want you to
pack up and get out.
l just bought this station,
and you're fired.
And pIay that
deIightfuI fIush sound
on your way out.
Yes, sir.
(TOlLET FLUSHlNG)
lndoor plumbing.
The lack of it
killed my mother.
l've done it, Smithers!
l've bought every
media outlet in town.
TV, radio,
even the skywriters.
Cletus, what does that say?
That? That says,
"l loves you, Brandine."
Oh, Cletus.
Tonight, you can
knock me up again.
Excellent. But put a little
more apple in my cheek.
lt's apple-ing now, sir.
Splendid !
Now, let's see how l'm faring
on the jumping box.
You mean
the television, sir?
Television,
jumping box, picto-cube,
just crank it up!
In tonight's face-off,
I wiII be debating
Channel 6 movie
ghouIie BoobereIIa
on the subject
of our new boss,
C. Montgomery Burns.
My view, he's a great Ieader
and a gaIIant American.
He's got a heart
as big as my boobs!
I guess we'II have to agree
to agree on this one.
Boobs!
Smithers, do you know
Bill from Accounting?
That's his daughter.
Hmm.
Let me show you
why you and aII
protesters are wrong.
AII right.
NucIear power heIps
heat that orphanage
and keeps that
hospitaI humming.
But what about wind power?
It's cheap and safe.
ls it?
(YELLS)
Remember, children,
nucIear power is your friend,
and so is Monty Burns.
Don't end up Iike me.
Vote RepubIican.
God bless America.
This cartoon
was made in Korea.
Burns owns everything !
l've got to speak out
before it's too late!
D'oh !
"Dear readers,
you hold in your hands
"the last paper not controlled
by the Burns Media empire.
"We are not afraid to say
"Montgomery Burns
is a monopolistic,
self-aggrandizing
"stinky pants."
Hmm. Maybe Burns
ain't so great.
This little girl has
given us a lot to mull.
Hey, you mugs,
thinking ain't drinking !
Hey! Ow! Okay.
Bring that girl to me.
l'm sorry, Mr. Burns,
but my paper is not for sale.
Maybe a little gift
will change your mind.
Send in Sugarbell.
She's very pretty.
But the answer is still no.
Honeysuckle, Dewdrop.
(MUSlC BOX CHlMlNG)
Oh, no!
(NlCKERlNG)
They're so beautiful.
And their breath
smells like peppermint.
No! No! l won't
take your blood ponies!
Go on, sweeties. Go on.
Shoo.
(HlSSlNG)
Very well.
You had your chance.
l am going to shred you
like a Christmas card !
Now get out!
l can't!
My mom's not picking
me up for an hour!
(SlGHS)
So, what do
you think of today's
popular music scene?
l think
it distracts people from more
important social issues.
My God, are you always on?
(SCREAMlNG)
Stupid women drivers!
Stupid women
helicopter pilots!
(SCREAMlNG)
Everyone okay?
(ALL GROANlNG)
(RATTLlNG)
Uh-oh.
You can't leave now.
We're the only thing
stopping Mr. Burns!
Sorry, Lisa.
And by the way,
that story l filed
from Baghdad was all made up.
l was actually in Basra.
(GROANlNG)
Everyone chickened out.
Except Ralph.
He got poached by
the Chicago Tribune.
l guess we're down
to just me.
Take the sob sister
act somewhere else.
You're standing in my light.
Bart, you're staying !
Lise, l've learned
a valuable lesson here,
the pen is mightier
than the flaming bag of poop.
Oh, it's beautiful !
This is an outrage!
Since when
are public figures
fair game for satire?
Your goons did run
her off the road, sir.
l can't be held responsible
for what my goons
were ordered to do!
Perhaps there's
a non-violent way
to silence this girl?
Non-violence
never solved anything.
Fine, curtsy boy.
l'll try it your way.
What the. . .
Dad, Mr. Burns cut our power!
Now, l can't print my paper!
These batteries have to power
everything in our house!
(SlNGlNG) Yo,
I'II teII you what I want
what I reaIIy, reaIIy want
What l want, what l want
I'II teII you what I want
l want...
(TAPE SLOWS DOWN AND STOPS)
That was totally worth it.
Stupid Burns!
Cuts off my power,
lowers my credit rating.
Lisa, l think l can help you.
You're not mad about
Principal Skinrash?
Are you kidding? l love it!
l once had
a principal like that!
Now, come with me.
What's that?
This, young lady,
is a mimeo machine.
A hand-operated
duplicating device.
No electricity needed.
(SNlFFS)
That smell takes me back.
(GUNS FlRlNG)
(YELLS lN VlETNAMESE)
Finally in 1 992,
l was reunited
with that chair.
lt wasn't quite the same.
Good God. l'm at war
with a little girl.
And l'm losing !
Smithers, this calls
for the League of Evil !
My league!
My beautiful league!
All dead.
Even monsters
need air, sir.
Blast!
Well, gather their watches.
l must find another way
to vanquish the girl.
So, has your
daughter always been
such a righteous
little rabble-rouser?
Oh, yeah.
She's always trying
to improve mankind.
Fascinating ! Do go on.
Wait a minute.
Are you trying to
get dirt on Lisa?
Oh, you saw right through me.
Well done.
Have some
congratulatory drugs.
Well, if that's your custom.
Now, tell me more
about your daughter.
And speak into the lamp.
Okay.
Well, she's into Buddhism,
whistle-blowing,
totally against pollution,
no matter what l say.
Liberal wacko, eh?
Any young beaux?
Well, that loser Milhouse
has always had
a thing for her.
Don't you love it
when nerds don't
know they're nerds?
Yes.
There's nothing more pathetic
than self-delusion, eh?
Hello, Beefcake Charlie.
(CHUCKLES)
Dad, how could you
say these things?
l'm so sorry, honey.
l said good things
about you, too.
Check out
the Lifestyle section.
"Plastic Pearls
Make the Girl."
Well, at least
there's nothing else
Burns can do to me.
Oh ! (GASPS)
LlSA: No!
Way to go, Moon Milhouse!
lt's as easy as
crushing an ant.
You know the. . .
(GRUNTlNG)
Whoa!
Take my wallet
and leave me alone!
lt's not fair.
(SOBBlNG)
l can't stand seeing
one of my children like this.
(MUFFLED SOBBlNG)
Oh, l can still hear her!
l better do something !
Look at you go!
Typety-type-type-type!
Marge,
l'm pulling an all-nighter
for my little girl !
Put on a pot of coffee,
drink it and start
making burgers!
Some anniversary this is.
"The Homer Times"?
HOMER:
"AII my daughter ever did
"was teII peopIe to
think for themselves.
"I may be her father,
but when I grow up,
"I want to be just Iike her,
except stiII a dude!"
Oh, Dad, this is so sweet.
But l've learned
one little paper
can't make
a difference in this world.
"The Barney BugIe"?
Lisa, you've made me realize
the importance of
free and independent media.
So l printed my own paper!
Although, it's mostly culled
from wire services.
(BELCHES)
Hey, who wants a copy of
The Lenny Saver?
You have a newspaper, too?
Well, l was reading
in The Homer Times
about what you did for us.
And l got to thinking
maybe l should start
asking my own questions.
You know, find out
the truth about things.
lt had to be told.
Check out
The Willie World News.
l reviewed the new tractors.
They're all shite!
See, Lisa?
lnstead of one big shot
controlling all the media,
now there's a thousand freaks
xeroxing their
worthless opinions.
l couldn't be prouder.
Are you a Patty or a Selma?
Take our quiz.
Well, blow me down.
l'm a Selma.
Well, l guess it's impossible
to control all the media.
Unless of course
you're Rupert Murdoch.
He is one beautiful man.
l couldn't agree more.
Smithers, l'm a proud fellow,
and it's not easy
for me to admit defeat.
But l know just the thing
to make me feel better.
Shopping.
(JOYFUL MUSlC PLAYlNG)
English - US - PSDH