The Simpsons
D'oh!
Bill, bill...
Bill.
Homer, you got a letter.
Hmm. It's from the library.
Overdue book?
This is the biggest
frame-up since O.J.
Wait a minute.
Blood in the Bronco,
the cuts on his hands,
those Jay Leno monologues!
Oh, my God! He did it!
Here's the book.
"Classics for Children"?
Yeah. I checked that out
when Bart was born.
I was gonna read
to him every day.
What happened?
Stuff kept coming up.
Mostly car-related.
Piece of crap.
Why don't you
read to us now?
I decide who reads and when!
How about now?
Mmm.
Homer's Odyssey.
Is this about that
minivan I rented once?
No, Dad.
It's an epic tale
from ancient Greece.
That minivan had
the biggest cup holders.
And change slots
for every coin,
from penny to quarter.
Dad, I loved it, too,
but it was seven years ago.
Fine.
"It was the end
of the Trojan War.
"Clever Odysseus had
come up with a plan
"to destroy the Trojans
once and for all. "
Hi, odiddily-Odysseus!
Stupid king of Troy.
I think I speak
for all the Greeks
when I say
this war has gone
on for too long.
I'll say.
I'd really like to go
out and get the mail.
Anyway, over torture,
one of your soldiers
mentioned
that you collect
giant wooden animals.
We hope you
don't have a horse.
Well, I don't have
one from you.
Bring it in!
Now throughout history,
when people get wood,
they'll think of Trojans.
Trojans.
What are you
laughing at, Dad?
If I'm laughing at
what I think I am,
it's very funny.
Anyway, "As night fell,
the Greek soldiers crept
from the wooden horse. "
Aw, look at them.
Sleeping like little angels.
Spare no one.
Remember, just 'cause
their heads are off,
it don't mean they're dead.
Now I can return to Ithaca
and my sweet wife, Penelope.
Odysseus, do not forget
to thank the gods
for our victory
with an appropriate
animal sacrifice.
Forget it!
Sacrificing animals
is barbaric.
Now have the slaves
kill the wounded.
No sacrifice?
We'll teach that mortal
to trifle with the gods.
I got it.
You fat lush.
You just destroyed Atlantis.
You used to be fun.
Where's the Zeus
who used to turn into a cow
and pick up chicks?
He grew up.
Maybe you should, too.
Poseidon,
you take care of Odysseus.
Yarr. I'll send him far.
Off course.
"Greece"
is the word.
Is it "vase" or "vase"?
You gonna be asking
that the whole trip?
Gentlemen,
I must be wasted,
'cause it looks like
that cloud is mad at me.
Yarr!
On the island
Island of Sirens
Our hot sex
Will leave you perspiring
Hey, that's kind of catchy.
It's coming from that island.
Let's steer heedlessly
towards it.
Heedlessly it is.
The feta is cheesy
The Sirens are easy
Boy, if they kiss
as good as they lure, wow!
On the island
We'll sex you up
Island of Sirens
Oh, God!
They're hideous!
Someone gouge my eyes!
Save me
from the ladies!
It's been so many years
since I've seen your father.
I hope he's
still the magnificent
physical specimen
he was when he left.
Mom, maybe it's time
to choose a suitor.
Discus Stu has
ouzo for twozo.
I'll leave you guys alone.
Discus Stu was
talking to you.
Oh, where could
your father be?
Almost home.
Ain't I a stinker?
Welcome to my island.
I am Circe, the sorceress.
Boy, who decided
to give every
weirdo an island?
You must be thirsty.
Drink from my cauldron.
Well, I was in the mood
for something bubbling.
Out of the way, slim.
Thanks for your help
with the anchor, guys.
Guys?
That pig looks like Lenny.
Hey!
Mmm. That's the next best
thing to eating Lenny.
I'm still hungry.
Didn't you eat
enough of your friends?
Those were my friends?
Yes. I've been
saying that for hours.
That's it! I'm going home!
Which way to Ithaca?
It's not so easy.
You must go through Hades,
crossing the River Styx.
You're my lady
Of the morning
Oh, this truly is hell!
Okay. It has been 20 years,
and you suitors
have been very patient.
We've been beyond patient!
When we came here,
Helen of Troy was hot!
Now look at her!
This is the face
that launched
a thousand ships,
the other way.
Honey, I'm home.
Well, look who
the fates dragged in.
Oh, I'm sorry
I was gone so long,
but I'm gonna do
something I haven't
done for 20 years.
Take out the trash!
Sweet Penelope,
you're just as beautiful
as you were when I left.
Oh, I can't stay mad at you.
Aw.
Brave Odysseus,
it's been 20 long years.
Regale me with tales
of your adventures.
Quit suffocating me.
I'm going to Moe's.
Oh, here's the story
of Joan of Arc.
Ooh! Did you say
Joan Van Ark?
No, Mom. Joan of Arc.
It's never Joan Van Ark.
This one takes place
in a make-believe
kingdom called France.
"The French were
fighting the English
in the Hundred Years' War,
"which was then called
Operation Speedy Resolution. "
Son, how's it going
with the breakfast pâté?
I'm on it.
Bartrand,
where is your sister Joan?
Morning bells are ringing.
She's talking to her
invisible friend. God.
And please
bless Mama and Papa
and Bartrand and Coco Chanel.
Joan of Arc,
I am your God.
I have chosen you
to lead the French army
to victory
over the English invaders.
But I'm just a little girl.
I know.
I have three eyes.
Now get cracking.
God wants you to lead
the French army to what?
Victory.
Victory?
We're French!
We don't even
have a word for it!
God spoke to me.
I must obey.
Joan,
give me your dessert.
That's just you, Bart.
Joan,
give me your dessert!
Yes, sir.
That's going straight
to my five thighs.
All right, garçons.
Huh?
No, un.
You know, French for "one. "
Well, you keep
switching back between
French and English.
Just fire the damn thing.
My fault this time.
I didn't tuck in my legs.
Wait! I have been sent
to lead the French army
to victory!
Yeah, really?
And how are you
gonna do that?
With modern ideas,
like putting
bigger, harder people
in the catapult.
Or, how about rocks?
Rock.
I don't know how
to feel just now.
And now, attack!
Shouldn't we help her?
Yeah, right behind you, Lou.
Uh-oh.
There's my supervisor.
Hello, hello, hello.
What's all this then?
It's a little bird
with a knife, isn't it?
What a thing to happen!
Blimey!
We welcome our savior,
Joan of Arc.
It is customary to
kneel before the king.
I would gladly kneel,
were you the real king.
You are the true dauphin.
You had this impostor
try to fool me
to see if I was
truly sent by God.
Bravo, Joan of Arc.
You are as brainsome
as you are toothsome.
Quimbe, you may resume
your regular duties now.
It would be my pleasure.
Vibrate for me, footstool.
Loyal subjects,
let us drink to Joan of Arc,
who will conquer the English,
and has already
conquered my heart.
Uh, God says we should
just be friends.
I wouldn't say
King Milhouse is a loser,
but that's the 12th girl
he's struck out
with this week!
Boil him in oil!
So no 10:30 show?
Let us kill the English!
Their concept of
individual rights
could undermine the power
of our beloved tyrants!
They're attacking again.
I thought we had a truce.
Just because
you keep saying it
doesn't make it so.
Oh, my word!
You can't stop me!
I was sent by God!
I want my mommy!
I captured a wee girl!
I'm the greatest hero
in English history!
Joan of Arc,
you are accused of heresy,
witchcraft,
and that man told me
you pushed him.
I would like to call
my only witness.
Almighty God.
I told this maiden
to lead the French
to victory.
Wait a minute,
you two-timing spot of light.
You told me to lead
the English to victory!
Is that true, Lord?
Well, I never thought
the two of you
would be in
the same room, actually.
This is a little embarrassing.
Goodbye now.
That was weird.
Let's burn her!
Yeah! Burn her!
Burn her!
Don't burn her!
She's just an innocent child!
Burn this guy!
He lost a good bucket!
Joan, renounce your faith.
Save yourself.
Don't worry, beloved parents.
God won't let
anything happen to me.
Huh. Getting kind of
hot around here.
Wow.
What happened, Dad?
They didn't really
burn her, did they?
Of course
they didn't, honey.
"Just then,
Sir Lancelot rode up
"on a white horse
and saved Joan of Arc.
"They got married and
lived in a spaceship.
The end. "
Well, that's easier to chew
than that Bambi video.
Our next story is Hamlet,
by William Shakespeare.
Dad, these old stories
can't compare
with our modern
super writers.
Steven Bochco could
kick Shakespeare's ass!
Look, this story's
more interesting
than you think.
It starts with
Hamlet's father
getting murdered.
Cool. Does he get
to marry his mom?
I don't know,
but that would be hot.
"Once upon a time,
there was a young
Prince of Denmark. "
Hamlet! Avenge me!
Dad?
Yes. I have
returned from the dead.
Looks like you've
returned from the buffet.
Why, you little... D'oh!
My son,
I have some shocking news.
I was murdered.
Murdered, I tells you!
Really?
Behold! As I slept,
your Uncle Claudius
poured poison in my ear.
Poison most foul!
So he could marry your mother
and become the king!
Yeah,
that was quite a weekend.
Now you must avenge me.
Avenge me!
How?
I don't know.
Surprise me.
Surprise me!
Could that fat ghost
be telling the truth?
First, I've gotta
get Uncle Claudius
to confess.
Then I've gotta kill him.
It's cold outside.
You'll need a sweater.
A sweater!
And if your idea
of a first date
is burning down her village,
you just might be a Viking!
That's what I get for
sitting up front, eh?
I love these jesters.
They're exactly
what I need to forget
about my first husband.
Yeah,
I really miss the old guy.
It was all I could do
to put on his jewels
and score with his wife
every night.
How are you doing, kid?
Nice to see you.
Now we would
like to warn you,
our performances
tend to make audience members
blurt out hidden secrets.
Oh, boy.
Aha! Methinks
the play's the thing
wherein I'll catch
the conscience of the king.
Catch my conscience? What?
You're not
supposed to hear me.
That's a soliloquy.
Okay, well,
I'll do a soliloquy, too.
Note to self.
Kill that kid.
Okay, we're gonna open it up
with a little improv.
Somebody shout
out a location!
This castle!
Okay.
How about an occupation?
Usurper of the throne!
I think I heard
"usurper of the throne. "
Now finally,
I need an object.
Ear poison!
Hey, do you have diarrhea?
I have diarrhea.
Sit down!
Wait a minute!
I didn't use
that much poison!
I mean, I didn't use
that much poi, son,
at the royal luau.
Daddy, it's true!
Uncle Claudius murdered you!
Oh, great.
Now Hamlet's acting crazy.
Well nobody
out-crazies Ophelia.
Hey, nonny nonny,
with a hoo and a haw,
and a nonny nonny hey!
Hamlet, what'd I tell you
about running with swords?
Someone's behind the curtain.
It could be Claudius.
Only one way to find out.
Ow!
Polonius? What are you doing
behind the curtain?
I hide behind curtains
'cause I have a fear
of getting stabbed.
Daddy's stomach is crying.
Laertes, you gotta do
a special big-boy job
for Daddy.
I need you to
avenge my death.
I like revenging!
I'm gonna kill Hamlet.
Here's my mad face.
Cute kid.
But just in case
you don't kill Hamlet,
I put some
poison on the food,
on the drapes,
even on Rosencarl
and Guildenlenny here.
If Hamlet touches
either of us, he's dead.
Booyah!
Now, Hamlet,
you know the rules.
Laertes here gets
one practice stab.
Oh, boy!
Boy, did I bet
on the wrong horse.
Now there's
nothing to stop me
from getting my vengeance.
You sure you don't want
a nice piece of fish,
or to finger
the drapes a little?
This ends here!
Remember me as a peacemaker.
And now to celebrate life!
Whoa! Bloody floor!
No way
I'm cleaning up this mess.
And that's the greatest
thing ever written.
Are you crazy?
I can't believe
a play where every
character is murdered
could be so boring!
Son, it's not only
a great play,
but also became a great movie
called Ghostbusters.
English - US - PSDH