♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
Eye of the tiger, Bart!
Eye of the-- Ooh!
I stopped it.
And I hurt somebody.
Ha-ha!
Boys, it wasn't easy
choosing only one of you
for the free week at
Pele soccer and acting camp.
Let's all congratulate...
Nelson.
(scattered applause)
Thanks, Dad.
Told ya!
Come on, Bart.
We're going to go sneak
into an R-rated movie.
It's called "Barton Fink."
I can't. I told my dad
I'd wait for him.
TOGETHER: "Barton Fink!"
"Barton Fink!"
(wind blowing)
Homer, we're going
to my sister's.
Remember, pick up Bart.
I'm on my way.
(studio audience applause)
(chuckling)
What did you say, Marge?
(moans)
That could be Dad.
Station wagon,
luggage rack...
♪ I am woman,
hear me roar ♪
♪ In numbers
too big to ignore ♪
♪ And I know too much
to go back to pretend ♪
(thunder crashes)
(grunts)
Dad, where are you?
Tonight on "Wings"--
Ah, who cares?
(shivers)
This isn't funny!
Homer Simpson.
Pick up Bart.
Trab pu kcip.
What have we told you
about writing on the walls?
Go to your room!
ANNOUNCER:
After 16 glorious seasons,
the Green Bay faithful
bid farewell to
Bryan Bartlett starr.
Hmm. I keep thinking
I'm forgetting something.
CROWD (chanting):
Bart! Bart! Bart! Bart! Bart! Bart!
(barking)
Bart! Bart!
Bart! Bart! Bart! Bart!
Bart!
(belching) Bart!
I can't think
with all this noise.
What am I supposed
to do?
(voice)
Pick up Bart.
Pick a bar?
What the hell is
"Pick a bar"?
(snoring)
Bart!
(gasping)
Why?!
How?!
When?!
Which?!
Bart!
Dad, hide your shame!
NED: Hey, Homey,
I can see your doodle.
HOMER: Shut up, Flanders.
Hey, boy.
How was soccer practice?
Hey, Bart.
Son?
Here's my way of saying
I'm sorry.
Eew!
I know you're mad at me
right now,
and I'm kind of mad too.
I mean, we could sit here
and try to figure out
who forgot to pick up who
till the cows come home,
but let's just say
we're both wrong
and that'll be that.
Now, how about a hug?
KRUSTY:
Hello, New York.
(applause)
When Lorne asked me
to host this show,
I said, "Lorne, why me?"
(chuckling)
I mean, I did just star
in my first movie
with Marvin Hagler
and Tova Borgnine.
Yeah!
(quiet coughing)
Anyway, we got
a great show for you.
Well, actually,
the last half hour
is a real garbage dump.
We'll be right back.
(playing rock 'n' roll)
I miss Joe Piscopo.
MAN: Lost your dad?
Uh-huh.
He's not coming back, is he?
He might.
No, he's not,
but at Bigger Brothers,
we can help.
Hello, Bigger Brothers?
My name is Bart Simpson,
and I don't have a father.
And now it's time
for another episode
of "The Big Ear Family."
Honey, I'm home!
Oh, I got wax in my ears.
Better clean 'em.
Huh? Huh?
(coughing)
Oh, this goes on for
12 more minutes.
So the last time
you saw your father
was six years ago?
Yeah. He left me out
on the curb for the ashman.
What a revoltin' development.
You brave little soldier.
I've been saving
someone special
for a case like yours.
(all gasp)
Bart Simpson?
Yo.
I'm Tom. Let's ride.
Whoa.
Bart's dad has really
pulled himself together.
Bart's not mad at me.
He called you
a bad father.
Marge, when kids these days
say bad, they mean good,
and to shake your booty means
to wiggle one's butt.
Permit me to demonstrate.
No. I just think you should
talk to Bart about--
Good lord!
Homer, do you have
an explanation for this bill?
Oh, it's that record club.
The first nine were
only a penny.
Then they jacked up the price.
(sobbing)
It's not fair.
It's not fair, I tells you.
No, no. Someone made
$300 worth of phone calls
to something called
"The Corey Hotline."
Wasn't me.
(gasps)
Lisa!
Why didn't you ask
our permission, Lisa?
I did.
-Dad, can I--
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Aw, honey, I know
what you're going through.
When I was a girl, I had
a crush on Bobby Sherman.
(laughing)
The point is,
I want you to stop
making these calls.
All right, Mom.
I promise you will never be
billed for another call.
(giggling)
Bobby Sherman?
(groans)
ALL: Charge!
Your dad ever take you
to baseball games?
Nah.
His game was blackjack.
He bet our life savings
on a single hand.
-Nineteen.
-Hit me.
-Twenty.
-Twenty-one.
-Hit me.
-Twenty-two.
-D'oh!
If I ever meet your dad...
ANNOUNCER: The start
of the game will be delayed
so we can introduce
the recruiter
for the Springfield
Communist Party.
(crowd booing)
Well, this is better
than dart day.
Now, you just
let those ear drops sit
for about 20 minutes.
If you get bored,
here's a MASH coloring book.
Here's a good one.
"Hawkeye's antics irritate
the other surgeons."
(chuckling)
Hi, you've reached
the Corey Hotline.
$4.95 a minute.
Here are some words
that rhyme with Corey:
Glory, story...
-(sighs)
-... allegory, Montessori...
(grunting)
Okay, Bart, tomorrow
we'll blast your quads.
This meatball soup
is delicious, Stimpy.
That's not meatball soup.
That's my collection of
furballs in stomach acid.
(siren screeching)
You idiot!
You're trying
to kill me, man!
Someday I want to be
an F-14 pilot,
like my hero, Tom.
He lent me this new weapon
called a neural disrupter.
(choking and sputtering)
(kids applauding)
He's not dead,
is he, Bart?
Nah, but I wouldn't give him
any homework for a while.
Very good, Bart.
-Thank you.
-Oh, don't thank me.
Thank an unprecedented
eight-year military buildup.
Mmm. Milhouse, you're next.
Uh, I have a horsey.
(feeble neighing imitation)
Wuss!
Lisa, I'm glad you came.
I know you young'uns think
we old-timers aren't any fun,
but we'll show them.
We'll show them all!
(laughing)
(snoring)
(gasps)
Hi, this is Corey.
I hope you and I can
get married someday.
Hey, boy,
where you going?
Father-son picnic.
Have a good time.
Hey, wait a minute.
Lisa, I know I can
trust you
to inventory this
glee club peanut brittle.
Yes, Principal Skinner.
Now, I've got to slash
40% out of the budget.
So long... doo-doo-doo-
doo-doo-doo...
Science.
Ah, music and art.
(phone dialing)
What in blazes?
(beeping and ringing)
Good lord.
That's a 900 number.
COREY: Let's see
what's in the newspaper today.
-(paper rustling)
-Hmm...
"Canada stalls
on trade pact."
(phone disconnects)
(gasps)
Hey, look at that
forest fire down there.
-Yeah, great.
-What's the matter?
Well, I've been thinking.
You've been really great to me,
but there's probably
some other kid
who needs you even more.
Bart, I could kiss you,
if the bigger brothers hadn't
made me sign a form
promising I wouldn't.
No one needs me more
than a child with your
tragic upbringing.
Now, let's set down
at that frogurt stand.
So, that's it.
Hello, son.
Where have you been?
Playing with Milhouse.
No, you haven't.
You've been out
gallivanting around
with that floozy of a
bigger brother of yours,
haven't you?
Haven't you?
Look at me.
Dad, it just kind
of happened.
You're taking this
too hard.
How would you like me
to take it?
"Go ahead, Bart.
Have your fun.
I'll be waiting for you."
I'm sorry, I can't do it.
Well, what are you
going to do?
Oh, you'll see.
And what are your reasons
for wanting a little brother?
(thinking)
Don't say revenge, don't say revenge.
Uh... revenge?
(thinking) That's it.
I'm getting out of here.
(running footsteps
and door slamming)
Welcome aboard,
Mr. Simpson.
Any of these boys
would be thrilled
to have a bigger brother
like you.
Ugly, wiener,
crater-face.
Sooey!
Eh, maybe this
was a mistake.
Do you have a bigger
brother for me yet?
Okay, I'll be back
in an hour.
(crying)
I'll take him.
Do you have him in blond?
Lisa, the only way you'll lick
this is one day at a time.
If you can make it to midnight
without calling the Corey line,
you'll know
you've beaten it forever.
LISA: Midnight?
Listen to your mother, Lisa.
I owe everything I have
to my mother's watchful eye
and swift hand.
Oh, there's mother now...
-(crow cawing)
-...watching me.
What's that, mother?
They have a right
to be here.
It's school business.
I--
Mother, that sailor suit
doesn't fit anymore.
I think we should go.
Uh-huh.
-(siren wailing)
-(distant gunshots)
(snoring)
Heh heh heh.
Just like Oscar the Grouch.
-Pepe!
-Papa Homer!
Son, your life is going
to get better starting now.
(clunk)
Oh!
Your son Bart sounds
very bad.
Oh, he is.
Son, I just want you to know
I love you very much.
Shut up!
Mmm, grapefruit.
I just press this button
and the door opens like magic.
Why does it stop there?
Because it's a stupid
piece of junk!
Bart! Bart! Aah!
Well, I'd better
get you home.
What's the matter?
I've spent every night
of my life in the city.
I have never seen
the stars.
PEPE: Tell me more.
I want to know
all the constellations.
Well, there's...
Jerry the Cowboy.
And that big
dipper-looking thing
is Alan... the Cowboy.
Oh, Papa Homer,
you are so learn-ed.
(chuckles)
Learned, son.
It's pronounced "Learned."
I love you, Papa Homer.
I love you too, Pepsi.
-Pepe.
(thinking) Got to
make it till midnight.
Got to make it
till midnight.
(ringing)
(ticking)
(knitting needles clicking)
(ticking, clicking
and ringing grow louder)
Must you be forever
dialing that phone?!
Excuse me.
Oh, come on.
Hurry.
Lisa?
Oh, Lisa.
You tried your best.
At the tone, the time
will be 12:00 midnight.
(tone)
I made it.
♪ ...and Scratchy show ♪
(screams)
Hey, Homer, have you
seen my skateboard?
I gave it to Pepe.
Who the hell is Pepe?
He's my little brother.
That's right.
You're not the only one
who can abuse
a nonprofit organization.
Who needs you?
Tom's a better father than you ever were.
Come on, Bart,
we had our fun.
Remember when I used
to push you on the swing?
I was faking it.
(gasps) Liar!
Oh, yeah?
Remember this?
Higher, Dad, higher.
-Whee!
-Hey!
-Stop that!
-Push harder Dad, c'mon.
-Higher, higher, faster!
-Stop it!
Stop it!
You know, the whale
is not really a fish.
They're mammals,
like you and me.
Is that true?
Pfft. No.
(dolphin squealing)
Whoo!
Heh heh heh!
Come and get it.
Whoo!
Heh heh heh!
Come and get it.
Whoo!
Heh heh heh!
Stupid dolphin.
Hey! Hey!
(dolphin squealing)
HOMER:
He got my hot dog!
(Homer grunting)
Uh-oh, better not
let him see me.
What the--
Oh, it's you.
So...
you're looking well.
Come on, Bart,
you know better than to
talk to strangers.
For your information,
I'm his father.
His father?
The drunken gambler?
That's right,
and who might you be?
Hi-yah!
(karate yells)
There you go, fellas.
D'oh!
Look, there's another
disadvantaged boy.
Where?
Grr.
There's a couple of guys
fighting at the aquarium, chief.
Do they still sell
those frozen bananas?
-I think so.
-Let's roll.
This just in.
A fistfight is in progress
in downtown Springfield.
Early reports indicate, and
these are very preliminary,
that one of the fighters
is a giant lizard.
Do we have a source on this?
Uh-huh. A bunch of
drunken frat boys.
All right, I could
use some names.
I.P. Freely.
L-- Oh!
(punch landing)
(grunting wildly)
(glass shattering)
(Homer grunting,
glass shattering)
Uh, Homer?
Oh, right.
(echoed screaming)
(screaming grows louder)
(crack)
This is even more painful
than it looks.
This is all my fault, Dad.
I didn't want you
to get hurt.
Now I need to find
another little brother.
And I need to find
another big brother.
My car's going to feel
so empty on the ride home.
And me, I have
no ride at all.
I already bought
a giant ham for dinner.
It's gonna go to waste.
Don't talk about food.
I'm so hungry.
-Well, good-bye.
Wait, I've got an idea.
-An idea?
-Huh?
BART: Another beer, Dad?
Thanks, son.
Dad, remember when Tom
had you in that headlock,
and you screamed,
"I'm a hemophiliac"?
And when he let you go,
you kicked him in the back?
(chuckles)
Yeah.
Will you teach me
how to do that.
Sure, boy.
First, you've got
to shriek like a woman
and keep sobbing till
he turns away in disgust.
That's when it's time
to kick some back.
HOMER: And then when
he's lying out on the ground...
-BART: Yeah?
-...kick him in the ribs...
-...and step on his neck.
-BART: Yeah?
-HOMER: And run like hell.
(both laughing)
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.