♪ The Simpsons ♪
-(chalk screeches)
-(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(tires screeching)
(horn honks)
(tires screech)
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
Hey, what-- What? What the--
Who the-- (groans)
Dad, the next time
we see you
we'll do something
more fun.
Oh, what could be more fun
than today's trip
to the liquor store?
Thanks for the beef jerky.
Say good-bye to Grampa,
everyone.
-BOTH: Bye.
-Good-b--
(groans)
You know, Grampa kinda smells like
that trunk in the garage
where the bottom's all wet.
Nu-uh, he smells
more like a photo lab.
Stop it! Both of you.
Grampa smells like
a regular old man
which is more like
a hallway in a hospital.
Homer, that's terrible.
We should be teaching the children
to treasure the elderly.
You know, we'll be old someday.
(gasps) My God!
You're right, Marge!
You kids won't put me in a home
like I did to my Dad, would you?
-Well...
-(screams)
Marge, what do we do?
Well, I think we better
set an example.
Absolutely. Our third
Sunday of every month
should be a pleasure,
not a chore.
Where's someplace fun
we can take Grampa next time?
-To the pony ride.
-No.
-Yeah!
-Boring.
-He can't sit on ponies.
-Well, I always enjoy the glass blower
-at old Springfield town.
-Aw, he saw that.
Big yawner.
The Museum of
Barnyard Oddities.
-No, Bart, no.
-Bart, gross.
-BART: Gosh.
-I got it.
The Springfield Mystery Spot.
LISA: Dad, it's just
a dumb mud puddle.
(Homer gasps)
ALL:
Discount Lion Safari!
(muttering)
Hey! These aren't my pills.
Now, now, Mr. Simmons,
don't make me call Nurse Bronski.
(groans)
That's Simpson, damn it,
and these aren't my pills!
Excuse me, nurse.
My name is Simmons,
and I think I have
the wrong pills.
I get two red ones
for my back spasms,
a yellow one
for my arrhythmia,
and two of the bluest eyes
I've ever seen in my life.
Then these must be...
And I have your...
-They must have...
(both laughing)
(both coughing)
Look at us.
We're staring at each other
like a couple of stupid,
punk teenagers.
Oh, I wasn't staring.
It's, uh, my lazy eye.
I'm Beatrice Simmons,
but my friends call me Bea.
Well, I'm
Abraham J. Simpson.
Care to tip the wrist with me?
(clicks tongue)
(chuckles)
Oh, I would be delighted.
So, um--
(clears throat)
...tell me about yourself.
Eh, widower, one son,
one working kidney. And you?
Widowed, bad hip,
and liver disorder.
You left something out.
Ravishing.
(both laugh)
Mmm!
Ohh!
Mmm, num-num-num-num
num-num-num-num.
Num-num-num-num.
Mmm!
(moans)
(both slurping)
(cups clatter)
And what are you
doing tonight?
Sitting alone in my room.
Oh, well,  if you've
got plans already--
No. What were you
going to say?
-Oh, nothing.
-Oh, Abe.
You were going to say
something.
Well, I was wondering
if you and I,
you know, might go to the
same place at the same time, and--
Jeez, you think this
would get easier with time!
I'd love to.
(singing gibberish)
♪ Taxi, honey ♪
(gibberish)
♪ Half past three ♪
Okay.
Now where's that pomade?
Ah! "You'll never
fly solo again." Ooh!
(humming)
Ah, damn, out of pomade.
Oh, well.
(hocks)
Ooh, hello, young lady.
-Is your grandmother home?
-(chuckles)
Oh, Abe, I can tell I better
keep my good eye on you.
Damn straight.
♪♪
♪ Embrace me ♪
♪ My sweet embraceable you ♪
♪ You irreplaceable you ♪
BEA:
♪ Don't be a naughty baby ♪
ABE:
♪ Come to papa ♪
♪ Come to papa-do ♪
BOTH:
♪ My sweet ♪
♪ Embraceable ♪
♪ You ♪
Herman, a very special lady
is having her birthday tomorrow.
Ah, The battleship
"New Jersey."
No, you idiot!
My girlfriend Bea.
And since this is
the only store I know--
Oh, Grampa, nothing says
"I love you" better
than a military antique.
Let's take a look
at the bayonet case, huh?
Hey, what's that?
(chuckles) That, my friend,
was Napoleon's hat.
It doesn't look like
Napoleon's hat.
Well, it's not the famous hat.
It's the one he wore
for a week in April, 1796
just before he defeated
the Sardinians.
Ooh, how much?
-$400.
-I'll give you five bucks.
That's not the kind of offer
you should make to a man
with a Gatling gun
under the counter.
HERMAN: Why don't you try
Grandma's World?
Yo, active wear. I need
a price check on a wool shawl.
Dad, it's the third
Sunday of the month.
You know what that means.
-Go away!
-Oh, come on, Dad.
I promise we'll have more
fun this time. We're gonna see lions!
I can't go.
It's my girlfriend Bea's birthday.
Oh, you have a girlfriend.
(chuckles)
Well, happy birthday, Bea.
She can come with us.
Hey, there's room for all
your friends in the car.
No! She's not invisible,
you idiot!
See? It's her
birthday tonight.
Yeah, right.
Hey! You kids,
stop kicking the seat.
I'm kicking the seat.
Dad, don't you want to know
where we're going?
-No.
-ALL: Discount Lion Safari!
Damn these child-proof doors.
-Hello.
-That will be 18.50, partner.
LISA:
"Do not feed animals."
"Do not allow animals
in the car."
"Do not make eye contact
with animals."
(sarcastically)
Are we in Africa yet?
Did anybody notice
this place sucks?
It seems that most
of the animals are sleeping.
Well, let them sleep
on their own time.
(horn honking)
Homer, are you sure
this is the right way?
The road seems to have
gotten awfully bumpy.
-(screams)
-(roars)
ABE: What a wingding.
This is much better
than my girlfriend's
birthday party.
-Homer
-Bart, get out and push.
Yeah, Bart.
Get out and push.
No way, Jose.
ABE:
Okay, we've seen the lions.
Can we go now?
(screaming)
Oh, Bea!
(trumpeting)
(gunshot)
Mr. Simpson, I presume.
Out of my way.
I got a date with an angel.
You don't know
how right you are, Abe.
-What?
-I'm sorry to be the one to tell you this,
but... Bea passed
away last night.
Oh, no.
It was her ticker.
The doc said
her left ventricle burst.
Oh, no, Jasper.
They may say she died
of a burst ventricle,
but I know she died
of a broken heart.
ABE: I can tell she
really cared for me.
She didn't make me
a pallbearer.
(grunting and groaning)
I can't tell you
how sorry I am, Dad.
Is someone talking to me?
I didn't hear anything.
Oh, no,
Dad's lost his hearing!
No, you idiot,
I'm ignoring you!
You made me miss
the last precious moments
of Bea's life.
I'll never speak
to you again!
I have no son!
Oh, Bea.
Oh...
Hmm.
It was a beautiful service,
wasn't it, Mr. Simpson?
Ahh! Who the hell are you?
Lionel Hutts,
Attorney at Law.
I'm the executor
of Beatrice Simmons' estate.
Mr. Simpson,
Bea was a wealthy woman,
and, surprise, surprise,
she left everything to you.
-Really?
-There is one catch.
You must spend one night
in a haunted house.
-(gasps)
-Just kidding, just kidding.
Here's a check for $106,000
"To enjoy as you see fit."
Oh, I'm touched.
$106,000?
Ta-ta, Mr. Simpson.
By the way, old-timer,
I do wills.
Why don't I just give you
this pen with my phone number on it.
It looks just like a cigar.
Isn't that something?
-(telephone rings)
-Hello.
-Hello, Homer?
-Whoo-hoo! It's Dad!
Dad's on the phone,
he's calling me!
Oh, Dad, oh,
I knew you'd forgive me.
I haven't forgiven you.
I just inherited $106,000,
and I just had to tell you
that you're not getting
one thin dime!
-Ha-ha!
-D'oh!
-Mr. Simpson?
-Ahh! What is it?
I couldn't help overhearing
about your new-found fortune,
and let me assure you that here
at the Springfield Retirement Castle,
money does make a difference.
-Huh?
-(chuckles)
I mean, there are rubdowns,
and then there
are rubdowns.
Listen, you bloodsucker,
has it ever occurred to you
that old folks deserve
to be treated like human beings
whether they have money or not?
Yes, but it passes.
Ohh! You lousy son of a--
I'll take it.
Hey, big spender,
why the change of heart?
Bea told me to enjoy
my moolah,
and I'm going to, dagnabit!
Huh.
-(bell jingles)
-Yeah.
Yeah.
So, where to, pappy?
Eh, take me someplace fun.
You're the boss.
Next stop...
Funsville.
(crowd clamoring)
Ayah.
I miss Bea.
I miss you too.
(screaming)
Oh, Abraham, calm down.
I'm not here to scare you.
They've got me haunting
a family in Texas.
Oh, I'm glad
you're keeping busy.
Now listen Abe. I want to know
why my money isn't bringing you happiness?
Oh, Bea, I'm not cut out
for the high life.
Abraham, if you're not
happy with the money,
why don't you spread it around?
Make other people as happy
as you made me.
Oh, thanks, Bea, I will.
And go see your son.
He misses you.
Oh, I miss him, too,
the big, fat Dickens.
Hey, Bea, I've got to ask you.
What was death like?
Not as scary as this!
(all screaming)
(crying)
I miss my Daddy.
Homer, this thing
with your Dad
has had you moping around
the house for days.
I think it's time for you
to talk to someone who understands.
Hiya. You've reached
Doctor Marvin Monroe's anxiety line.
-(doorbell chimes)
-If you have a sullen teenager,
press one now.
If you're estranged from
your spouse, press two, now.
If you have trouble
maintaining an...
-Grampa!
-Huh?
-Dad!
-Sonny boy!
Is there room at your table
for a foolish old man?
Well, sure.
Eh, we'll have to move a chair
in from the den, but it's no problem.
-Bart!
-Choose your corn cob.
En garde.
Challenge accepted.
-All my precious stacks of gold...
-(belching)
...couldn't buy me the pleasures
of a simple family meal.
Pass the bug juice, Dad.
Wait your turn, you pig.
I have an announcement
to make.
I've decided to give
Bea's money away.
There are people who
really need it.
I'm gonna let them
come to me
and plead their case,
and then I'll decide
who needs it most.
Grampa, that's the noblest
thought that's
ever been expressed
at this table.
-Give it to us, Grampa.
-Bart! Forgive him, Dad.
He's just a stupid little kid,
who says the first thing
that pops into his head,
but you know, there's wisdom
in his innocence.
-You don't want it.
-Yes, I do.
Too bad,
you ain't gettin' it.
Not since this
reporter's marriage
to Stephanie
the Weather lady,
has this town been so consumed
with rumor and innuendo...
all because of this man.
Today, one
Abraham "Grampa" Simpson
announced that he will
give away over $100,000
to the person or persons
he finds most deserving.
Is Grampa Simpson a modern day
saint, a rich nut, or both?
Only time will tell.
This is Kent Brockman,
on line for
an old man's money.
Ah, you see, Gramp,
I want to customize the bus.
You know, chop the top
jack it up,
put mag wheels on it,
psychedelic paint job
from hell, man.
Jam the kids to school
at 150 miles an hour.
Here's an artist's rendering.
Note the cobra wrapped
around the naked chick.
-Next.
-Duh...
Grampa... I can call you
"Grampa," can't I?
Yeah, yeah, go ahead.
Alright. I need that money.
Please. Please!
Wait a minute. Wait.
You're that guy who owns
the nuclear power plant.
Well, the ownership is divided.
What the hell do you
think you are doing?
Mr. Simpson, I dread the day
when $100,000
isn't worth groveling for.
Get out of here!
You just made yourself
a very powerful enemy, old man.
Here's the deal, Grampa.
A guy I think was an explorer
left this in the bar one night.
It may be a map
to ancient treasure,
or directions
to some guy's house,
but to find out,
we'll need money,
we'll need provisions,
and a two-man diving bell.
It's pretty stupid,
-but so far, you're the front-runner.
-Hmm.
It's a special
isolation chamber.
The subject pulls levers
to receive food and warmth.
The floor can become
electrified,
and showers of icy water
randomly fall on the subject.
I call it the "Monroe Box."
-Uh-huh. Well, it sounds interesting.
-Uh-huh.
How much will it
cost to build?
Oh, that's the beauty part.
It's already built.
I need the money to buy
a baby to raise in the box
-until the age of 30.
-What are you trying to prove?
My theory is that the subject
will be socially maladjusted
and will harbor
a deep resentment towards me.
Hmm, interesting.
Let's see.
I want a tear gas pen,
-a blow gun with paralyzer darts...
-Oh, no.
-Nunchakus.
-Nunchakus?
-Yeah.
-What the hell are those?
A copy of
"Radioactive Man, #27."
That's the first time
he fights Dr. Crab.
And I wanna buy
that baseball card
where the guy's
flipping the bird.
Oh, yeah,
I've seen that one.
Oh, and a monkey.
What the hell is that?
Why, it's a death ray,
my good man.
Behold.
Hey, feels warm.
Kind of nice.
Well, it is just the prototype.
With proper funding,
I'm confident this little baby
could destroy an area
the size of New York City.
But I want to help people,
not kill them.
Oh. Well, to be honest,
the ray only has evil applications.
You know, my wife
will be happy.
She's hated this whole
death ray thing from day one.
Oh, Lisa, what makes you think
you deserve all that money?
I don't deserve it, Grampa.
No one here does.
The people who deserve it
are on the streets
and they're in the slums.
They're little children
who need more library books
and families
who can't make ends meet.
Of course,
if you really wanted to,
-you could buy me a pony.
-You're right.
I'll name her Princess
and I'll ride her every day.
No, you're right about
all the poor souls
who need a helping hand.
I need to take a walk
to clear my head.
-(siren wails in distance)
-Oh, dear.
(baby crying in distance)
Ah, I'm exhausted.
Oh, poor baby.
Been lifting your wallet?
No! I'll have you know
I've decided to give my money
away to truly needy causes.
-Hmm.
-But $100,000 just isn't enough.
I need more.
Well, why don't you go on
the seniors' gambling junket?
I bet you could
double your money or even triple it.
Well, it's tempting.
Plus, they got a 99¢
shrimp cocktail.
You sold me.
-(Otto humming)
-Slow down.
Are you trying
to get us killed?
It's too hot, ya' maniac!
Turn on the air already!
Hey, mellow out,
old dudes,
or I'll jam this baby
into a river, all right?
(humming to Edgar Winter's
"Frankenstein")
Miss, I'm looking
for Abe Simpson.
It's important
I get a hold of him.
I have to tell him
I don't care about his money
and I love him.
We get that a lot.
He left with
the senior casino junket.
Casino?
(screams)
(humming Jethro Tull's
"Aqualung")
Come on, everybody!
(humming together)
Hello, I am Plato.
Please partake of keno, craps,
and the loosest slots in town.
My philosophy is "enjoy."
Change, please.
(gasps)
(tires screeching)
A double cheeseburger, onion rings,
large strawberry shake,
-and, for God sakes, hurry.
-(distorted voice on speaker)
$5,000 on...
-What century is this?
-The 20th.
Great! Put it on #20.
Excuse me.
Excuse me, have you seen an old man
with a lot of money?
He looks like me,
but he's wrinkled.
Hello. Have you seen a-- Dad!
No!
-DEALER: 20 black.
-(Abe laughing)
-Holy moly. You're winning.
-All mine, all mine.
Beat it, boy.
You're cramping my style.
Dad, please, you gotta
quit while you're ahead.
You got to take your money
and leave, now.
Sorry, boy. I have to get
enough to help everybody.
But you could lose everything.
Come on!
Homer, I think Rudyard Kipling
said it best.
"If you can make one heap
of all your winnings
"and risk it on one turn
of pitch and toss, and lose,
"and start again
at your beginnings
"and never breathe a word
about your loss,
"yours is the Earth
and everything that's in it.
And, which is more,
you'll be a man, my son."
You'll be a bonehead.
Come on.
Put it all on 41.
I've got a feeling about that number.
The wheel only
goes to 36, sir.
Okay, put it all on 36.
I've got a feeling
about that number.
Dad! No!
Give me that money.
Come on. Stop it. Ow!
Ow! You're hurting me!
-Thirty-six!
-No more bets.
Oh!
Son, if this
lands on 36, I'll...
Double zero.
Son, you saved me
from losing all my money.
For the first time in my life,
I'm glad I had children.
So, uh, have you figured out
who gets the money?
Yes, Homer, I have.
(laughing)
(crowd gasping)
Come on in.
Dignity's on me, friends.
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.