♪ The Simpsons ♪
(chalk screeches)
(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(horn honks)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
Hello. I'm Leonard Nimoy.
The following tale
of alien encounters is true
and by true, I mean false.
It's all lies,
but they're entertaining lies,
and in the end,
isn't that the real truth?
The answer is "no."
Our story begins
on a friday morning
in a little town
called Springfield.
T.G.I.F., guys.
I'm off to Moe's.
But, Homer, it's 10:00
in the morning.
Don't worry, I have a plan.
I saw this in a movie
about a bus that had
to "speed" around a city
keeping its "speed" over 50
and if its "speed" dropped,
it would explode.
I think it was called...
"The Bus That Couldn't
Slow Down."
First, I hook this common VCR
into the security camera system
like so...
then I insert this old
videotape of us working
on a continuous loop.
(no audible dialogue)
So, another
Friday is upon us.
What'll you be
doing, Smithers?
Something gay, no doubt.
Wha...? What?!
You know,
lighthearted, fancy-free.
Mothers, lock up
your daughters.
Smithers is
on the town.
(laughing)
Exactly, sir.
(nervous chuckling)
Thank God it's Wednesday.
It's Friday.
Uh-oh. Wrong pills.
Uh... little help?
Sorry, Donkey Kong.
You're just not
a draw anymore.
Hey, he's still got it.
MILHOUSE:
...38, 39, 40 quarters.
This better be good.
Game over.
Please deposit 40 quarters.
What a rip!
Thank God it's Friday.
(hums)
-(X-ray machine buzzing)
-Hello?
Hello?
(dog growling)
Bad dog!
(cat screeching)
Bad cat!
Bad fawn!
Hmm.
-Shoo-shoo!
-All right!
It's time for ABC's
"T.G.I.F. lineup."
Lis, when you get
a little older
you'll learn that Friday's
just another day
between NBC's
"Must-See Thursday"
and CBS's "Saturday
Night Craparama."
Another Duff, Homer?
Nah. It's Friday
night, Moe.
I want to
try something special.
Uh, sure, sure.
Eh, here you go.
"Doof-uh."
From Sweden.
Skoal!
Wait a minute.
This is Duff.
(laughing)
You got me, didn't you?
All right, here you go--
Red tick beer.
Hmm.
Bold, refreshing.
And something I can't
quite put my finger on.
(barking)
Hmm... needs more dog.
(snoring)
Well, it's 1:00 A.M.
Better go home
and spend some quality time
with the kids.
Just a second, Homer.
You got to take
a breathalyzer test
before I let you drive home.
(Russian folk song plays)
(slurring) Ah... I guess
I'll walk home.
(moans)
(spooky music plays)
(dog howling)
(psycho theme playing)
Ooh!
(gasping)
(screams)
-(wind blows)
-(screams)
Oh, son, I'm
glad to see you.
I went for the morning paper
and I got lost.
-No time for you, old man.
-GRAMPA: Oh...
(hoots)
("The X-Files" theme playing)
(whimpering)
Please, don't hurt me.
Don't be afraid.
(screaming)
Unh!
(footsteps running)
-(panting)
-Homer, it's 2:00 A.M.
-What happened?
-It was an alien, Marge.
It appeared in front of me
and said, "Don't be afraid."
Have you been
drinking?
No... Well, ten beers.
(groans)
HOMER: I'm telling you
I saw a creature
from another planet.
Maybe you just dreamed it.
Oh, yeah?
Well, when I came to
I was covered with
a sticky translucent goo.
Explain that.
-More sausage?
-(drooling)
Dad, according to
"Junior Skeptic Magazine,"
the chances are
175 million to one
of another form of life actually
coming in contact with ours.
-So?
-It's just that
the people who claim
they've seen aliens
are always pathetic lowlifes
with boring jobs.
Oh, and you, Dad.
(chuckles weakly)
I am the thing from Uranus.
(shrieks)
Oh, it's Bart.
I can't believe it.
I'm being mocked
by my own children.
On my birthday.
-It's your birthday?
-Yes.
Remember, it's the same day
as the dog's.
Santa's Little Helper,
it's your birthday?
Ooh, we've got to
get you a present.
Yes, we do.
We love you, boy.
Good doggy. Good doggy.
Lousy lovable dog.
Oh, it was awful.
They set me
on a cold metal table,
and prodded me
with humiliating probes, and--
Oh, wait.
That was my physical.
(men scoff)
Great story, Homer,
really.
The alien has
a sweet heavenly voice...
Like Urkel.
And he appears
every Friday night...
Like Urkel.
Well, your story
is very compelling,
Mr. Jackass.
I mean, uh, Simpson.
So I'll just type it up
on my invisible typewriter.
(humming)
(sighs) You don't have
to humiliate me.
I just torched
a building downtown
and I'm afraid
I'll do it again.
Oh, yeah, right.
I'll just type it up on
my invisible typewriter.
(humming)
Fruitcake.
Look at this, Scully.
There's been another
unsubstantiated U.F.O. sighting
in the heartland
of America.
We've got to get there
right away.
Well, gee, Mulder,
there's also this report
of a shipment of drugs
and illegal weapons coming
into New Jersey tonight.
(scoffs) I hardly think
the F.B.I.'s concerned
with matters like that.
Hello. Can I help you?
Agents Mulder
and Scully-- F.B.I.
(gasps)
Is this about that pen
that I took
from the post office?
I-I swear, I didn't know
I put it in my purse.
Then I was going to bring it back
but the dog chewed it up,
and that just made things worse.
(hyperventilating)
Actually, we're here to see your husband
about his U.F.O. encounter.
Oh... come...
come in.
SCULLY: Mr. Simpson,
look at this lineup
and tell us if any of these are
the aliens you saw.
Yo.
No, I'm sorry.
(all grumbling)
Oh, this makes me
very angry.
Now we're going
to run a few tests.
This is
a simple lie detector.
I'll ask you a few
"yes" or "no" questions,
and you just
answer truthfully.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Ow.
(panting)
Wait a minute, Scully.
What's the point of this test?
No point.
I just thought
he could stand to lose
a little weight.
His jiggling
is almost hypnotic.
Yes, it's like
a lava lamp.
MULDER:
All right, Homer,
we want you re-create
your every move
the night you
saw this alien.
Well, the evening began
at the gentleman's club,
where we were
discussing Wittgenstein
over a game
of backgammon.
Mr. Simpson,
it's a felony
to lie
to the F.B.I.
We were sitting in Barney's car
eating packets of mustard.
You happy?
You are one
fine-looking woman, lady.
If I wasn't married,
I'd go out with you
like that.
I am so sorry.
Whatever you do,
don't tell Marge.
God, I love her.
I... Hey, a penny.
So, who are you guys anyhow?
Agents Mulder and Scully--
F.B.I.
F.B.I., huh?
Uh, excuse me.
All right, they're onto us.
Get him back to Sea World.
(vocalizing)
So I says,
"Blue M&M, red M&M.
They all wind up
the same color in the end."
Homer, why don't you
show us where you went
when you left the bar.
I was standing
right here
when the horrible creature
emerged from the woods.
For the love of God, help me!
I've been here for four days,
and a turtle's
got a hold of my teeth.
There he is.
Come back here, you.
Slow down.
I'll get you.
This is the worst
assignment we've ever had.
Worse than the time
we were attacked by
the flesh-eating virus?
Ow! He bit me
with my own teeth!
No, this is much
more irritating.
I've seen enough, Mulder.
Let's go.
Yeah, okay.
But somewhere out there,
something is watching us.
There are alien forces
acting in ways
we can't perceive.
Are we alone
in the universe?
Impossible, when you
consider the wonders
that exist around us.
...voodoo priests of Haiti,
the Tibetan numerologists
of Appalachia,
the unsolved mysteries
of "Unsolved Mysteries."
The truth is out there.
(Moe grunting)
Who would have thought
a whale could be so heavy?
(gasps)
Cheese it. The Feds.
(whale vocalizes)
Oh, Marge,
I've never felt so alone.
No one believes me.
Uh, this is the part where
you're supposed to say
"I believe you, Homer."
I don't believe
you, Homer.
You do? Oh, Marge,
you've made me so happy.
Mmm, you're not listening.
You're only hearing
what you want to hear.
Thanks. I'd love
an omelet right about now.
Homer, please,
I try to be supportive,
but this has gone too far.
Please just let it be.
No, I can't.
This is my cause.
I'm like the man who
singlehandedly built the rocket
and went to the moon.
What was his name,
Apollo Creed?
Please, let's
just go to sleep.
No, I refuse to share a bed
with someone who thinks I'm crazy.
Unless you're feeling amorous.
-(purrs)
-No, I'm not.
Well, then, good night.
Hey, Dad, what's the word
from planet crackpot?
Oh, I suppose
you're going to mock me too.
Well, actually, Dad,
I believe you.
-You do?
-Yes, I do.
You seem so damn sure.
Thank you, son.
And do you think you could
stop the casual swearing?
-Hell, yes.
-That's my boy.
Well, if you
believe in me
then I'm not
going to give up.
I'll prove I'm right.
This Friday we're
going back to the woods
and we're going
to find that alien.
What if we don't?
We'll fake it and sell
it to the Fox network.
(chuckles)
They'll buy anything.
Now, son, they do a lot
of quality programming too.
(laughing)
I kill me.
-Bud...
-weis...
er.
-Bud...
-weis...
er.
Coors.
Yo, Dad, can I have a sip
of your beer?
Now, son, you don't
want to drink beer.
That's for daddies
and kids with fake I.D.s.
Besides, it's such
a beautiful night.
How about a ghost story?
...and that is how much
college will cost for Maggie.
No. No! No!
You know, Dad,
it doesn't matter that
we didn't see the alien.
I really had
a great time out here.
Yeah, me too.
-("The X-Files Theme" playing)
-(gasps) It's him!
I bring you peace.
As a representative
of planet Earth,
let me be the first to say--
(screaming)
(gasps)
D'oh! It's gone.
And we still
don't have any proof.
Oh, yes, we do.
I got it all on tape.
Good work, son!
We did it!
And so, from this
simple man came the proof
that we are not alone
in the universe.
I'm Leonard Nimoy.
Good night.
MAN: Uh, Mr. Nimoy, we
have ten minutes left.
Oh... fine.
Well, let me just get,
uh, something out of my car.
(footsteps running)
(tires screeching)
I don't think
he's coming back.
Tonight, on
"Eyewitness News, "
a man who's been in a coma
for 23 years wakes up.
Do Sonny and Cher still
have that stupid show?
No. She won an Oscar,
and he's a congressman.
Good night!
(monitor beeping steadily)
But first,
E.T. phone Homer...
Simpson, that is.
Marge! Kids! They're about
to show my videotape.
Local man Homer Simpson,
shown here with his tongue
stuck to a lamppost,
has given us this videotape.
It's a close encounter
of the blurred kind.
(chuckling)
I bring you peace.
The alien has appeared in
the same Springfield pasture
the past two Friday nights.
Will it appear again
this Friday?
The entire Channel 6
news team will be there,
except for Phil,
the boom mike operator
who's getting fired
tomorrow.
Very unprofessional, Phil.
Well, Lis, what do you
think about the alien now?
I think there must be a
more logical explanation
and I think the people of this town
aren't going to be won over
by three seconds
of videotape.
(doorbell rings)
Uh... I'm happy to
answer any questions
you have about the alien.
Any questions at all.
Dr. Hibbert?
Yes, is the alien carbon-based
or silicon-based?
Uh... the second one.
Zilliphone.
Next question.
Is the alien Santa Claus?
Uh... yes.
Uh, were you on my roof
last night
stealing my weather vane?
This interview is over.
I remember another gentle
visitor from the heavens.
He came in peace,
and then died,
only to
come back to life.
And his name was...
E.T., the extraterrestrial.
(sniffling)
I loved that little guy.
(playing five-note tune
from "Close Encounters")
(tuba hits sour note)
Leonard Nimoy,
what are you doing here?
Wherever there is mystery
and the unexplained,
-cosmic forces shall draw me near.
-Uh-huh.
Hey, Spock, what do you
want on your hot dog?
Surprise me.
Take a look at this, Lisa.
You don't see any
"Homer is a dope"
t-shirts, do you?
We sold those out
in five minutes.
D'oh!
Marge, how could you?
These shirts are a
hundred percent cotton
and look at the fine
stitching on "dope."
I'll take two.
(all gasping)
Look!
There it is.
("The X-Files Theme" playing)
Oh, Homie...
Homie, I'm so sorry
I doubted you.
I bring you love.
Is that the love
between a man and a woman,
or the love of a man
for a fine cuban cigar?
Uh... I bring you love.
It's bringing love!
Don't let it get away!
Break its legs!
(crowd shouting)
Wait!
You want an alien?
This is your alien.
Hello, children.
I bring you love.
Eh! It's a monster!
Kill it! Kill it!
It's not a monster.
It's Mr. Burns.
Aw, it's Mr. Burns.
Kill it! Kill it!
No. No, let me explain.
Every Friday evening
after work,
Mr. Burns undergoes
a series of medical treatments
designed to cheat death
for another week.
First, Mr. Burns'
chiropractors
perform a slight
spinal adjustment...
(Burns groaning)
Then a team of doctors
administers eye drops...
painkillers...
Ooh.
...and a vocal
chord scraping.
Don't worry.
You won't feel a thing...
till I jam this
down your throat!
SMITHERS: The whole ordeal leaves
Mr. Burns twisted and disoriented.
♪ La la la la la ♪
The most rewarding part
was when he gave me my money.
But... what's with
the glowing?
Um, I'll field
that question.
A lifetime of working
in a nuclear power plant
has given me
a healthy green glow...
and left me as impotent as
a Nevada boxing commissioner.
And now that
I'm back to normal,
I don't bring you
peace and love.
I bring you fear,
famine, pestilence, and...
Time for a booster!
♪ Good morning, star shine ♪
♪ The Earth says hello ♪
♪ You twinkle above us ♪
♪ We twinkle below ♪
All:
♪ Good morning, star shine ♪
♪ You lead us along... ♪
Well, you said you'd
bring them peace and love,
and it looks like
you did it.
I'm proud of you, Homie.
Mwah!
Thanks, Marge.
♪ Tooby-ooby-walla ♪
-(Chewbacca gargling)
-♪ Nooby-abba-nabba ♪
♪ Early morning
singing song ♪
And so concludes our tale.
I'm Leonard Nimoy.
Good night,
and keep watching the skis...
Uh, skies.
("The X-Files Theme" playing)
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.