-CHOIR: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
-(Willie grunts)
(theme music playing)
(exclaims)
(school bell ringing)
(Barney belches)
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
-(tires screech)
-(grunts)
♪♪
(yells)
Mm!
(whistling)
(moaning eerily)
Hey! Huh?
-♪ The Itchy and Scratchy Show ♪
-(Bart slurps loudly)
(scary music plays)
It's alive!
(screams)
Friend?
(laughing)
Bart, you want to see
something cool?
Oh, did you pick that
big scab off your knee?
-No.
-Don't touch the scab!
My science fair project proves
that an asteroid
will strike the Earth on July 15th, 9789.
Who cares?
I'll be President of Hell by then.
Fine.
Good luck with your project,
which I'm sure
you haven't started yet.
I'll tell you my project.
A fisteroid hitting the planet Nerd!
That's pathetic.
Aw, geez,
I put a lot of time in this.
Back to the drawing board.
Hmm...
Hey, Bart!
Is your cootie shot ready?
No. The science fair's
not till next week.
I really need that shot.
My dog and I accidentally
touched tongues.
How is it "accidentally"
when this is the fifth time?
-(door shuts)
-Bart, isn't that awfully similar
to the cootie patch
you did last year?
That was preventative.
This is morning-after.
Oh, you're right.
Oh, what am I going to do?
Good ideas don't grow on trees.
Hmm.
Or do they?
(humming wistfully)
(grunts) Good shot!
Not really. I was trying to
bounce it off your left testie.
"Testis," my friend.
(sighs) Look, I need help
with my science fair project.
To sweeten the deal,
I'll pick you first for basketball.
Ah! To be a mathlete!
Without the "M."
(dance music playing)
Fly, orb, and find thy hoop!
I'm in!
(panting)
(bird caws)
"In the event of
a primary core breach,
you have 15 seconds
to avoid a complete..."
(yawns)
(snoring)
-Howdy!
-(sputters)
A woman of stature!
-Roz Davis, your new assistant.
-Assistant?
Well, I have been
pretty overworked lately.
But I guess I should find out
a little bit about you.
I'm just a gal from Ohio
who never wants to call her daddy again
and say, "I need to borrow money."
So your dad has money to lend?
(bird caws)
This is where we get our coffee.
Just leave a little at the bottom,
so someone else has to
make the next pot.
The burning smell
will let them know.
Genius.
Uh-oh. It's old man Burns.
Hello, young man Burns!
Oh, Simpson, you do know
how to whip my buggy.
(chuckles)
That sucker soaks up flattery
like a Twinkie soaks up gravy.
Well, when it's a handsome guy
like you talking...
(laughing) Well...
Your giggle's like strawberry wine.
Oh!
(giggles, snorts)
And your snort's like
a summer breeze.
(laughing)
(choking, coughing)
That's not very attractive, though.
-You okay?
-(grunts) I'm fine.
Bart, I fail to see
the scientific function
of this "Homer Humiliator"
you've devised.
Well, we gotta
come up with something.
Hey, what if we make
some kind of robopet?
What made you think of that?
-(panting)
-(shrieks)
Thy will be done, Lord Vader.
Just don't hurt me. Oh, please!
A robopet! Not a bad idea.
-Bully, Bart! Bully!
-Where? Is it Nelson?
No, Bart, it's just an expression.
Who hath summoned me?
(shuddering)
-♪ Everybody ♪
-♪ It's a future shock ♪
♪ Future shock ♪
♪ Future shock... ♪
-Baby seal, huh?
-Research shows it's impossible
to gaze at a baby seal
and say anything but...
-Aw...
-Precisely.
And at science fairs,
the "aw"s get the "A"s.
-(growling)
-Ah!
Heavens to Asimov! Hmm.
Must make sure
these wires aren't crossed.
Aw...
-(growling)
-(shrieks) Marge!
Get my seal club!
The big one!
They're all pretty big.
(grunts)
I'm an experiment.
(beeping faster and faster)
-Fine.
-(beeping)
(sighs)
BART: Check it out!
ALL: Aw...
So the soft fur, big eyes,
and gentle motion
are designed to make
it one hell of a pet,
with none of the poop.
This is the most adorable thing
I've ever seen in my entire life.
(clears throat)
What a wonderful science fair.
Unfortunately,
due to budget cuts,
we could not afford
our third place ribbon.
Now, in second place,
Lisa Simpson's grim description
of our shortsighted dependence
on fossil fuels.
It's about an asteroid.
They're all the same, Gloomhilda.
First place goes to Bart Simpson
and Martin Prince...
-Yeah!
-(kisses)
...for creating a furry robotic friend
who provides comfort
when humans fail to.
Which they will, trust me.
I carried you in my belly
for four and a half months.
When you fell out on the bus,
that's when my job ended.
(Ping-Pong ball bouncing)
Congratulations on
getting a ribbon, Lisa!
You must've baked
a mighty fine pie.
It wasn't a pie.
It was science!
And it's not fair.
My project was way better than Bart's,
and I didn't have help from a nerd!
-I'm my own nerd!
-Oh, sweetie.
Being second ain't the worst thing
that can happen.
Look at poor old Jasper over there.
(raspy sigh)
(sighs) He lost his wife,
his kids don't call.
Soon he'll just be bones and beard.
(muttering)
(electronic barking)
(barks)
(laughs)
(waltz music playing)
Wow.
While I was sitting here
feeling sorry for myself,
Bart's invention actually
changed someone's life.
And best of all, I got funding
for my Homer Humiliator.
Hmm!
Ooh! D'oh!
Why would a Homer Humiliator
do this to me?
(ringing)
Yello. Hey, Barney.
A free movie screening?
Of course I can go!
I just need somebody
to hold down the fort.
Hmm...
Hm! Oh, uh, Roz?
I have to step out
for one hour and 43 minutes.
-Could you cover for me?
-Go ahead.
(whoops) Oh, uh,
if an emergency alarm goes off,
there's earplugs
in the top drawer.
(horn honks)
(grunts)
Mm-mm.
(groans)
(laughing loudly)
Life imitates Flart.
-It says that on the poster.
-I thought of it first.
Marge, I just saw
the greatest movie!
Guess what happens when a mop
is replaced with an octopus.
I'll give you a clue.
It's funny!
Take off the 3-D glasses.
-(screams)
-Simpson-- a gangly little bird
told me you've been
lollygagging at the Biograph.
(stammering)
Someone snitched?
W-W-What are you
going to do to me?
-You're demoted.
-Up, or down?
-Down!
-(shrieks)
Don't tell my wife.
(children laughing)
So, partner,
what's next on the agenda?
Oh, um...
Back off, man!
Can't you see
you're embarrassing Bart?
When did you take that picture?
(chuckles)
Last time you slept over at my house.
I love when you're sleeping
and at peace.
(groans)
Hey, Skippy, we need some more
of them lovable critters
for our friends at the home.
(chuckles)
Unless you got any heroin.
You got any heroin?
Hmm?
Well, then, critters it is.
I'm telling you guys,
Roz told old man Burns
I ditched work early,
and now I'm her assistant.
I don't know, Homer.
You're saying she's nice on the outside,
but mean on the inside?
-No one could pull that off.
-Enjoy.
And as for you, Homer, don't worry.
You're at Moe's tavern--
lady-free since '83.
What the...
This is a gentleman's club!
Yeah! (belches)
So, what you boys drinkin'?
I'm buyin'.
Can we just have
the cash value of the drink?
-Be my guest.
-I'd rather use my money
to buy a Moe souvenir T-shirt.
That comes in kid sizes, too.
HOMER:
Oh, no, this is terrible.
What am I gonna do? Oh...
-Aren't you gonna come to bed, Homie?
-Can't, Marge.
I'm fighting for
my professional life here.
Do you know what I just learned?
My job is the reason
I get those checks every week.
And now that I'm demoted,
the checks have gotten smaller.
Not in physical size, but...
I know. I know.
♪♪
I represent the Eternal Valley
funeral home,
and I'm here to talk about
an extremely unpleasant subject--
people continuing to live.
If we don't have a frickin'
funeral soon, people,
you can say good-bye
to Howard's Flowers!
Calm down, Howard, Jr.
Now, here is the zip,
the zap, and the zing.
We're gonna rewire
Charlie Loveable here
into the greatest threat
to seniors' lives
since nursing homes themselves.
Switcheroo.
(growling)
Impressive.
Hard to believe two
ten-year-old kids built this.
And I heard one of them
did all the work.
-Wow.
-It's true.
(panting) Am I early?
You're late.
Since I got demoted,
I have to show my I.D.,
but the picture
was taken so long ago,
I put on a lot of weight,
so I have to stretch out
my face and say,
"I used to look like this."
Late.
You're mean.
Now, I want a list of 100 ways
to make your job worse
by close of business today.
-Can one of the 100 be making the list?
-No.
Can some of them be callbacks
to earlier ones?
-Also, no.
-(groans)
We're live at
the Springfield Retirement Castle,
where longtime resident,
Alice Glick, died last night,
at the paws of this
cuddly little killer.
Our Channel Six
substitute medical expert
Dr. Nick Riviera had this to say.
The champion was cleared to fight.
Ahem, Doctor, this press conference
is about a nursing home death.
The Springfield police are in the process
-of taking all the robots...
-(screaming)
...into custody,
safely returning the seniors
-to their hopeless, dismal lives.
-(gunfire)
Shut that thing off.
-(machine stops)
-I meant the TV!
-Sorry.
-(machine whirs)
(doorbell rings)
Hi. We need someone to reprogram
our robots to break out of jail.
(stutters excitedly)
A chance to reprogram robots?
Well, I had a date
with a beauty queen tonight,
but forget it.
(touch-tones beeping)
Uh, hello, yes, hello,
Miss Wyoming?
I'll have to climb
your Grand Tetons another night.
(laughs)
The breast joke!
I-I served it up.
Why won't he love me?!
(sobbing)
"Do this, do that."
Lousy Roz thinks she's so big.
Well, looks like it's time for another
"End of the Walk Talk
With Homer and Ned."
Tonight's topic--
the niceness of the evening.
-Hey.
-Homer, all nonsense aside,
are you oka-lidoka-laroony?
(sighs) I'm having problems
with my new boss Roz.
She's the most evil person
to come out of Ohio since LeBron.
But at least he thought
long and hard
before screwing everybody over,
in public, for no reason.
You know, I knew a backstabbing
Buckeye named Roz at Bible camp.
-Twice as tall as she should've been.
-(gasps) Is this her?
Come on!
The apple must be
wreaking havoc with the Twinkie!
(gasps) It is.
But if you've got the stones,
I can tell you
how to slay that "Gal-ioth."
Are you aware that "stones"
means man junk?
What the--
I've been using that around the boys.
(groans weakly)
Whew! Thank you.
Now, it was one of
our biggest celebrations,
the 19th Sunday after Easter.
We'd just had a rousing no-fun run,
and in the heat of the moment,
I wanted to offer
my respectful best wishes.
Peace be with you.
Well, sir, she went crazy.
Crazier than
sleeping in on a Sunday.
I can't stand to be touched!
Never tell anyone!
And I haven't. Not until now.
That's it! That's it!
My nightmare is over!
Oh, Flanders,
you are my personal savior.
Oh, that's nice,
but I don't approve of...
Hail Flanders!
Mightier than Jesus!
(groans)
Yes, I, uh,
I hereby call to order
this meeting of the North American
Man-Bot Love Association.
I'll say this one more time--
we really should change that name.
Yes, all right,
I'll change it to whatever you like,
as long as "Man-Bot Love"
is in there somewhere.
Now, let's look at
these blueprints, shall we?
(excited murmuring)
MARTIN: Wish I'd thought of that.
Uh, first, we remotely adjust them
so they will never be
malicious again.
There, there, and there.
Now, arise, little ones!
(snores, mutters)
Hey-Hey, what's going on here?
I better call 9-1-1.
(busy signal beeping)
Oh, it's always busy when I call.
(sighs)
What a bunch of idiots.
Hey-- Aw, I can't stay mad at you.
Go on, get out of here.
-Oh, oh, Chief?
-Yeah?
Yeah, you, too.
(chuckles)
Although this millennium
is still young,
I feel it is time to award
this giant trophy,
paid for with your health care cuts...
-(crowd groans)
-...to our beloved Roz.
(one person clapping slowly)
What the deuce?
Sarcastic clapping?
Congratulations, Roz.
What are you doing here, Simpson?
If there isn't dry cleaning
in the back of my car,
there's gonna be blood
on my knuckles.
Uh, I just came to say
that you're perfect.
So perfect, I think Mr. Burns
should give you a hug.
(gasps) Who told you?
I won't say,
but his initials are S.F.
Stupid Flanders!
(chanting)
Hug, hug, hug!
EMPLOYEES: Hug, hug, hug,
hug, hug, hug, hug.
(roaring)
(bones cracking)
You're fired.
I underestimated you.
I don't know what that
middle word means.
Well, it means my perception of you
is that you were kind of a goof,
but now I see you're rather clever.
-What is perception?
-It's how I view you.
-You understand that?
-No.
I used to think you were an idiot.
Now it turns out,
you're not such an idiot,
in fact, you might even be smart.
Little help?
(both grunting)
(muffled grunting)
Rub the butter around you.
(gulps)
Need more butter!
And not the unsalted.
Do you want to
get out of there or not?
Mr. J., if I don't get my green card,
they're gonna turn me
back into a washing machine.
No dawdling. Just move it along.
(sighs)
Oy, oy! My mechanical mensch!
How I missed you.
(grunts)
Bless you, boys.
Now that we got 'em back,
we'll never let 'em go again.
'Cause there's no stronger force
than a senior citizen
holding onto a freebie.
("Golden Years" by David Bowie playing)
♪ Golden years ♪
♪ Gold... ♪
(growling)
♪ Golden years... ♪
♪ Gold... ♪
♪ Golden years ♪
♪ Don't let me hear you say life's ♪
♪ Taking you nowhere, angel ♪
♪ Come, get up, my baby ♪
♪ Look at that sky, life's begun ♪
♪ Nights are warm
and the days are young ♪
♪ Come, get up, my baby ♪
♪ There's my baby lost, that's all ♪
♪ Once I'm begging you,
save her little soul ♪
♪ Golden years ♪
♪ Gold... ♪
♪ Come, get up, my baby ♪
♪ Last night, they loved you ♪
♪ Opening doors
and pulling some strings, angel ♪
♪ Come, get up, my baby ♪
♪ In walked luck
and you looked in time ♪
♪ Never look back,
walk tall, act fine... ♪
-(crowd murmuring)
-Shh!
Subtitled by A. Vandelay