CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
D'oh!
(tires screeching)
(grunts)
♪ ♪
HOMER:
D'oh!
♪ ♪
♪ Tonight, tonight ♪
♪ I'll win at cards tonight ♪
♪ My flushes will be ♪
♪ Straight tonight ♪
♪ Lenny's gonna dominate tonight ♪
♪ Carl's gonna be a little late tonight ♪
♪ Tonight, tonight ♪
♪ I'll cheat them all tonight ♪
♪ When they're drunk ♪
♪ They don't play cards quite right ♪
-♪ Tonight, tonight ♪
-(bottle shatters)
♪ I won't get drunk tonight ♪
♪ Without a beer, my head will clear ♪
♪ Tonight ♪
♪ It's fun to trick a rummy ♪
♪ To put liquor in his tummy ♪
♪ Your friendship's a delight ♪
♪ And you may lose your sight ♪
ALL:
♪ Tonight ♪
(burps)
♪ Tonight, tonight ♪
♪ Band camp calls tonight ♪
♪ My demo goes online ♪
♪ Tonight ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Tonight, tonight ♪
♪ My dreams come true tonight ♪
-LISA: ♪ Deposit's due tonight ♪
-HOMER: ♪ I'll take the pot tonight ♪
ALL:
♪ Tonight! ♪
Moe, what the hell is that?!
Sorry. I missed rehearsal.
MOE:
Damn it.
Marge, I'm heading out!
Poker night!
I don't want you losing
all our scrimpings!
Don't worry, Marge.
The real excitement for me
is staying within a budget.
(snickers)
This is just a friendly game, right?
Oh, super friendly.
Suckers.
Dad, Dad, Dad.
I need two things:
a good-night hug and a favor.
-Mm.
-To save time,
I'll start describing the favor.
I've just been accepted
to the best band camp
this side of the Mississippi!
Which side are we again?
Doesn't matter!
It's a great camp.
Notable graduates include Pete Barbutti.
Pete Barbutti?!
Yes! Anyway, it's a little pricey.
So, if you win big tonight,
maybe you could help make
a little girl really happy.
Don't worry, sweetie,
I'm gonna win.
And you know why?
I'm wearing my lucky T-shirt.
(sighs)
It was such a shame
he lost to President Garfield.
Oh, I'll fix this.
There.
(hums a tune)
The maestro is here.
-(screams)
-(crashes)
-Hey, who's the lady?
-What, are you kidding?
This is Laney Fontaine,
Broadway legend.
She starred opposite Al Pacino
in Does a Tiger Wear A Necktie?
Ooh!
Now I date Moe.
He's got everything I look for in a man:
a current liquor license.
(chuckles)
Well, it and you
are the two most precious
wrinkled yellow things I know.
♪ ♪
WOMAN (over headphones):
Three of a kind beats two pair.
Straight beats three of a kind.
Three beats two.
Four beats three.
(dog howling)
HOMER:
Oh, my God.
Full house.
We're gonna win!
That means Lisa goes to band camp.
As long as Homer doesn't let them know
how good his hand is.
Then he'll blow
the whole damn thing to hell!
That would be terrible.
Worst jammed-in movie parody ever.
Come on, Homer. Poker face.
Aah! Stupid git!
I raise, no calls, pot goes to me.
Hold on, Fat Folds Five.
(stammers)
I see your raise, and I raise this.
Is that real?
Won it for cinematography.
Invented a new kind of Steadicam
that's mounted on a dog.
That's five grand to you.
So, are you in, or are you...
(groans)
While I'm out, no one
look at my cards or my boobs.
(groans)
Aw.
Don't she black out like an angel?
Queens beat jacks.
No one heard that.
I'm in.
(hums a tune)
Okay, Homer.
Moment of truth.
Oh, four of a kind!
Hey, honey, you won!
Huh?
I lost.
I lost everything.
We're gonna celebrate, Moe.
-What's Springfield's version of Sardi's?
-Uh, Hardee's.
I know a nice booth
under a picture of a hamburger. Heh.
Aw, come on, Homer.
I'll drive you home.
(imitates engine revving)
Hey, off we go!
Vroom, vroom, vroom.
(imitates engine chugging)
(door closes)
WOMAN: You've completed
Poker: A Beginner's Guide.
Now go out there and win.
I bid two bucks.
(floor creaking softly)
-(belt cracks)
-(gasps) What was that?
Those aren't the tiptoes
of a successful gambler.
How much did you lose?
$5,000.
(high-pitched chirping)
Whoa, I never heard that noise.
(sobbing)
(Marge continues sobbing)
I'm just sayin', doesn't look like
band camp is in the cards.
(playing jazz)
Hey, this is my thing now.
So easy.
Guys, I need help with a plan.
Hey, what about a reverse mortgage?
I saw a commercial for one
where an old lady gave a thumbs-up
and it turned into money,
which filled up the screen.
The entire screen?
Swear to God.
Hey, Homer, here's a thought:
invite Laney over for dinner.
Show her your crummy home,
your unhappy kids.
Anyone with a heart would take pity.
Finally, my sucky life pays off.
Do you guys think she'll buy it?
Oh, yeah. Your whole house, uh,
it smells like a basement.
I've always hated your rugs.
Yeah... Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Why you have to go there, man?
He has such beautiful floors.
Why must he hide them? Why?
LANEY:
There I am,
on the main stage at Caesar's,
about to sing "Do You Love Me,"
when who do I see sitting in the wings?
Your boyfriend King Tut?
No. Jack Jones.
High on his success
from "Wives and Lovers"
with eyes for yours truly.
But you'd just accepted
a proposal from Mike Connors.
Which I broke off.
Let's just say
Mannix was the one man
I had to nix.
(laughs)
Oh!
Oh, that's rich!
Oh, my God.
That's going in your book.
Please tell me you're writing a book.
(choking)
(grunts)
Sit down, boy.
We're trying to show this dame
that we're deserving of her pity.
Where's that crutch I gave you?
There's nothing wrong with my leg.
There will be.
D'oh!
Ow! Ow, my leg!
(sobbing)
Oh! Oh, my leg.
Oh!
Who would take $5,000
from such a miserable creature?
(sobbing)
Laney, I know it's your night off,
but would you like
to sing a song for us?
You don't have to ask me twice.
♪ I'm just a Broadway lady ♪
♪ Dancing on my aching feet ♪
♪ Avoiding any foods with wheat ♪
♪ And no drinking pre-show ♪
It's okay if the producer don't...
♪ Know ♪
(playing jazz)
Wow.
You know your way around a horn, kid.
Oh, listen, I don't want to gush,
but I have all your albums--
Laney Sings The Blues,
Electric Laney Land,
Laney Butchers The Beatles.
Ooh, and my favorite,
Rehab Yourself
A Merry Little Christmas.
I'll tell you what, Marge.
I'll wipe the slate clean
on one condition.
I want you to give Lisa to me.
(grumbles)
Uh, for a month or so.
I see.
Get out.
I never want to see you again.
Let me explain.
Listen, lady,
you can't take a daughter
from a mother unless you're a bigger star
and this is a third-world country.
Marge, I know this sounds nuts,
but I never had the joy you have.
A child to hug me at the end of the day
or-or a chance
to pass along what I know.
I'm going out on tour,
and she's got all the makings of a star:
talent, smarts, and a star-shaped head.
Perhaps you didn't hear me.
Here's your coat.
Mom, Mom.
Mom, please. You were gonna
let me go to band camp for a month,
where people break curfew
and exchange reeds.
But this? This is the opportunity
to live my dream.
Come on, how many chances
in life do you get for that?
None!
I've been here. I've just been quiet.
♪ ♪
(sighs)
I guess I can't deny you this.
-All right.
-(gasps)
Oh, thanks, Mom!
And, Mom, if you have any doubts
how a showbiz kid will turn out,
just look at all of them!
(groans)
(tires screech)
Mom, I appreciate this so much.
You'll be the first person
I thank at the Tonys
after the great Angela Lansbury.
Bye.
(smoke hisses)
(tires screech)
Good night, kid.
Would you read to me
before I go to bed?
Anne of Green Gables?
I did the audiobook on this.
If chapter ten
sounds like it was Peter Falk,
it's because it was.
So I guess you don't want
to read it again.
How 'bout I give you
some showbiz advice?
Every piece of advice
someone gives you
will turn out to be wrong.
Particularly wrong are people like me,
who seem knowledgeable.
Aw, she's already out.
(phone rings)
MOE:
You watching Channel Six right now?
Hurry up! Hurry up! Aw!
Nah, too late.
The cops cleaned it up.
(piano playing)
Chazz Busby.
My director.
The man who's ruined more
productions than flu season.
Laney! My star, my muse,
my God,
what have you done to your face?
(laughing)
Who's the lampshade?
This is Lisa Simpson,
the sax prodigy who's gonna
blow life into my act.
Show him, kid.
(plays three notes)
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
I wanted an audition,
not a recital.
You're in, kid.
I made it in Hartford.
-Are you sure you set it up right?
-Yes!
Then why aren't we Skyping?
I don't know.
Maybe Lisa's drugged-out.
My daughter is not drugged-out.
Maybe she's just sleeping late
after partying at discotheques.
How do you know
about all-night discotheques?
We have Disco Stu in this town, Mom.
He's a resource. Use him.
(Skype ringtone plays)
How are you, sweetie?
(gravelly)
I'm good, I'm good.
What happened to your voice?
I don't know.
Late rehearsals, cheap root beer.
(coughing)
(normal voice) But I'm great!
We're heading to New York!
(blows)
Who's watching you?
Sonny and Stix.
(playing mellow jazz)
Do I hear syncopation?
Lisa, Lisa, I was thinking
maybe you could
come home a little early and...
I'm sorry. I got to go.
Our take five is over,
and jazz is all about
following the rules, you know.
Come on, guys.
Don't I get a puff?
(gasps)
I really have the munchies.
(crunching)
Bye!
We've got to get her back.
Pack your things.
We're heading for New York.
We should get a place there.
We go so often.
♪ ♪
I can't believe
I'm gonna be performing here.
(dramatic music playing)
I already got my ticket!
LISA: (nervously)
Ah, so many seats.
-(car sputtering)
-Damn it!
Lousy electric car.
Dad, just 'cause
it got hit by lightning that time
doesn't make it electric.
Shut up, boy.
How may I help thee, friends?
Our car... broketh down.
(gasps)
Springfield Englisher accent?
You must know
my ultra-liberal cousin Ned Flanders.
Oh, he's brought such shame to our family
with his lip hair and two marriages.
And do you know he's left-handed?
(speaks foreign language)
(wheels creaking)
Um, can I please use the, uh,
little bearded boys' room?
(horse neighs)
♪ ♪
(humming)
How deep did thou diggest?
30 hands.
With God's grace, it will be enough.
♪ Don't know why ♪
♪ There's no sun up ♪
♪ In the... ♪
♪ In the... in the... ♪
How about "in the sky"?!
The sky!
You ought to know, sweetheart.
You were there when God created it.
Eh, go shave a coconut.
(gasping)
I turned down Transformers on Broadway
for this?
I was a Megatron-sized fool!
Kristen Chenoweth was set to play
Sam Witwicky's mother.
This is how mad I am!
Fade to black!
You can't be serious!
I said fade!
Everyone, meet me back here
in however long it takes
to wake up from five Valium.
On the dot!
(horns honking)
Hey, man, how'd you get that seat?
They thought I was pregnant.
(indistinct chatter)
It's showtime, Laney.
Time to see if there's still a spark left
in that smoldering Duraflame log
you call a career.
Hey, Laney.
Moe, I need you.
To make me feel confident,
strong and beautiful.
Boy, I'm not real good
at boosting self-esteem there.
But, uh, if you make a mistake,
I can fire my gun.
And that's what the critics
will be yappin' about tomorrow.
(chuckles)
That's not encouragement!
Those are your lyrics!
-(applause, piano playing)
-♪ I had a dream ♪
♪ A dream about you, baby ♪
♪ It's gonna come true, baby ♪
♪ They think that we're through ♪
♪ But, baby... ♪
♪ You'll be swell ♪
♪ You'll be great ♪
♪ Gonna have the whole world on a... ♪
♪ On a... ♪
Plate!
(crowd cheering)
Cheering for someone
getting a word right.
That is a low bar.
(panting)
Four tickets, please.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
The show is sold out
for reasons that elude me.
My daughter's in there.
Eh, we all got our problems.
I'm a ticket seller
for a dying art form.
Hey, uh, you're a union man, right?
Brother?
Why didn't you say so?
I have no choice now but to be corrupt.
In you go.
LANEY:
♪ Everything's gonna be ♪
♪ Bright lights and lollipops ♪
(playing jazz solo)
(crowd cheering)
Come on, let's sneak her out.
Under the guise of soliciting
for Broadway Cares.
(coins jingling)
Wait. Wait, Homer.
Look at our little girl.
She's got chops.
Honest-to-goodness chops.
Yeah.
Letting our daughter go on the road
with an 80-year-old diva
and some sketchy jazz guys
was the best decision
we ever made.
♪ Everything's coming up roses ♪
♪ For me and for you! ♪
(crowd cheering)
(whoops)
Mom,
that was the greatest night of my life!
MILHOUSE:
Hey!
When does the show start?
It did, and it was wonderful.
Eh, she's been bitten
by the showbiz bug.
And when that happens,
only working with Bruce Willis
can extinguish it.
(giggles)
(sighs)
Okay. Just finish out the tour.
We'll see you in Pittsfield.
No way!
Pittsfield ain't happening
for this little scene stealer.
I love you, Lisa,
but you got a bigger ovation than me.
So we can never
share the same stage again.
What? How can you say that?
Showbiz lesson
number seven:
just when things are going great,
they pull the rug
out from under you.
Bad news, Laney.
We're shutting down.
Never cleared the rights
to "Everything's Coming Up Roses."
See what I mean?
Also, we're gonna need that rug.
-(grunts)
-(shouts)
(sniffles)
Mom,
suddenly I really want to go home.
Oh. Mm.
If you go,
let me give you one huge piece of advice:
take the Eighth Avenue side,
then catch a cab and circle back.
And away... I... go!
(scatting)
Pow!
Well, Laney, youse, uh...
you still got me.
♪ ♪
See how gaudy his house is?
A brass doorknocker?
Who lives here, Caligula?
'Tis troubling.
Cousin Jacob! All the way
from Pennsyl-diddly-vania!
I see thou art still using
the Devil's "diddly."
Well, I must confess, I-I do over-diddly.
And I see your house
is lit by Edison's witch lights.
(chuckles)
Who's holier than thou now, Ned?
Homer, you've shown me
that I'm guilty of the sin of pride,
and that just makes me love you more.
Oh, God, I'm stuck in a Flandwich.
With side orders of love and forgiveness!
D'oh!
-(murmuring)
-Shh!
Subtitled by Jimmy Boots