CHORUS: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(theme music playing)
(bell ringing)
(whistle blows)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
(jazzy solo)
(chimes)
(tires screeching)
(honking horn)
D'oh!
(screaming)
(tires screeching)
ANNOUNCER: You're watching PBS.
You're watching PBS?
Hey, I'm as surprised as you,
but I've stumbled upon
the most delicious British sitcom.
Do shut up?
It's about a hard-drinking
yet loving family of soccer hooligans.
If they're not having a go with a bird,
they're having a row with a wanker.
Cheeky.
(punk rock playing)
♪ A no feelings ♪
♪ A no feelings... ♪
Jolly sodding Xmas, Major.
Choke on it!
(both laughing)
Ohh, crikey!
You gave me a smash
on the noggin last year.
Not in my parlor, you don't!
-Me eye!
-I'm scalded, I am!
(both laughing)
The mother's the voice of reason.
Here come the cricket bats.
You don't have the cobbles.
(chuckling)
Classic.
Not hard to see why it's
England's longest-running series.
And, today, we're showing
all seven episodes.
Hey, what the hell's going on?
If you like great PBS programs
like Do Shut Up and Shut Your Gob,
you'll want to support our pledge drive.
BART: Pledge drive? Ugh!
That's right, Betty White.
Absolutely.
If you watch even one second
of PBS and don't contribute,
you are a thief.
A common thief.
OK, take it easy, Betty.
Sorry, but these thieves
make me so damn mad.
You know who you are.
Thieves!
You're mad? Where's my show?
And now it's time to go back
to Do Shut Up.
-HOMER: Finally.
-But first...
-Oh!
-With your donation,
you'll receive this classic PBS tote bag.
Or this umbrella featuring a picture
of our classic tote bag.
And the next 20 callers will
get this album of museum noises.
Now your music room
can sound just like
The Metropolitan Museum in New York.
(footsteps)
(museum guard clearing throat)
Outstanding.
Why are you torturing me?
I'm just a man!
You know, I've worked with so many
legendary actors over the years
who could be counted
on to "phone it in."
Well, now, it's your turn
to phone it in-- your pledge, that is.
Please. Please!
We're only $10,000 away
from returning to our show.
Well, why didn't you say so?
(phone ringing)
Yes, I'd like to pledge $10,000
to get them to shut up.
From anonymous.
Done and done.
Dad, you don't have $10,000.
Aw, how they going to find me?
Folks, we just reached
our goal of $10,700,
and it's all thanks
to one generous caller
who didn't leave his name.
(laughing)
But thanks to Insta-Trace,
we learned it's Homer Simpson,
of 742 Evergreen Terrace.
(screams) Oh, why did I
register with Insta-Trace?
Our pledge-enforcement van
will be at his house in moments.
Uh-oh. You got to help me, Bart.
That's it, boy. Go get help.
D-oh!
OK, Homer, don't panic.
Let me do the talking.
Here he is, folks--
The man who saved PBS--
Homer Simpson!
(crowd cheering)
Mom, Dad's on PBS.
Hmm? They don't show
police chases, do they?
Um... It's an honor to give $10,000.
Especially now, when the rich
mosaic of cable programming
has made public television
so very, very unnecessary.
(clapping)
From now on, one of us always stays home.
Agreed.
Well said, Homer.
And now for the moment of generosity.
Will cash be OK?
Absolutely.
Well, then we got a problem.
The banks are closed by now.
It's 12:15.
Maybe your movie star banks
are open crazy hours,
but we in Springfield are simple folk.
We like our cars fast
and our banks closed.
OK, fine, we'll go down there,
but they're not going to be open.
Yeah... It's a real ghost town
in there.
Get in there.
I'd like to withdraw $10,000, please.
"You are on television.
Please play along."
Are you robbing me?
I'll pay you later.
Um, is there a problem, Mr. Simpson?
Uh. Why, no.
Everything is just...
(sputtering)
Oh! I can't do it!
I can't kill a man.
(sputtering)
You don't have the money,
do you, Homer?
Mm-mmm.
And you thought you could
stab your problems away?
Mm-hmm.
Silly goose. Why didn't you say so?
Get him, boys.
Ah! The hooligans!
Bash his eyes out!
(screams)
(groans)
(clamoring)
It's a beautiful day
to kick your ass!
You die now!
(groans)
(squawking)
Bingo!
Sanctuary!
Oh, why did I teach him that word?
Quick, you got
to hide me from PBS.
Their bloodthirsty pursuit
is made possible
by a grant from the Chubb Group.
Give us the money!
Elmo knows where you live.
Please help me. I'll do anything.
I'll light a candle.
I'll help with your next charity scam.
The word is "drive."
Sure, sure. Bob's your uncle.
Let's just get out of here.
Open the door!
(crowd yelling)
(clears throat)
Nothing to see here, people.
Just headed down to the dump
with these children's letters to god.
(squeals)
We'll send you someplace safe
till the heat dies down.
Great, but why am I on a plane?
Homer, how would you like
to be a missionary
in the South Pacific?
South Pacific? I didn't agree to...
(groans)
Wa-Wait! I'm no missionary.
I don't even believe in Jebus.
Let me out!
Sorry. No can do.
Oh, save me, Jebus!
Mmm.
(chuckling)
Ah!
Mmm...
(smacking)
Well... little piece there.
(smacking) Mmm.
(clears throat)
So, you said on the phone
you had something to tell me?
Hmm? Oh, yes.
-Your husband's in Microatia.
-(gasps)
Microatia?
That's 12,000 miles away.
Uh-huh. He needed
to get away for a while.
I suggested missionary work,
and he jumped at the idea.
Missionary work?
He's dead, isn't he?
No, no. You can even keep
in touch with him
on this ham radio.
HOMER: Jebus, where are you?
Homer to Jebus.
(groaning) Oh...
(groans) Oh.
This doesn't look so bad.
Aw... Hi, there, little fella.
(mumbles)
(gasping in horror)
Welcome aboard, brother.
You must be Homer.
I'm Craig. That's Amy.
Well, see ya.
You're leaving?
Wait! What do I do here?
First of all, forget everything
you learned in missionary school.
Done.
We taught them some English
and ridiculed away most of their beliefs.
So, you can take it from there. Bye.
Don't let the bed bugs bite.
Seriously.
Me Homer.
Me hiding from PBS.
I am Qtoktok, and this is Ak.
Welcome, Reverend Homer.
We look forward to learning
about the Bible from you.
Here you go. Knock yourself out.
We cannot read.
Oh! Does the word "jet lag"
mean anything to you people?
HOMER: Jet... lag.
(Homer slurping)
Are you enjoying your ox testicle?
Oh, yes. Very much so.
Really?
You sure you wouldn't
rather have a coconut?
(chuckling) They're delicious.
No. I'm good.
Um...
Hey, what happened
to all the shirtless girls
you see in all
the geographical magazines?
Craig and Amy gave us the gift of shame.
All the naked women are on that island.
(women giggling)
Yeah, anything
goes over there. (chuckles)
Bouncy, bouncy.
-Ah!
-(rumbling)
What was that?
Oh, we call that...
(gagging)
Sorry, fishbone in my throat.
We call that "earthquake."
Great. Now my
testicle's got ants on it.
Thanks, sweetheart.
Have a Bible.
My name's Homer.
What's yours?
I am Oovilu-Eeoo-Kitana-Wanjay.
I'm going to call you Lisa Junior.
So, what do you do
for fun around here?
Craig and Amy were digging a well.
Craig and Amy were
also building a chapel.
"Craig and Amy, Craig and Amy."
Why don't you just
marry Craig and Amy?
I told you we should have asked them.
Oh, how's the TV reception here?
Excellent or...?
T... V?
You don't have TV?
But what will I watch
while I'm sitting on the couch?
Cou-ouch?
No couches either?
Oh, man, I need a beer.
(gasps)
Oh, god! Oh, god!
NATIVES: Oh, god, oh, god.
Oh, god, oh, god.
(grunting)
(smacking)
Nothing.
Here we go.
Ee... Yeah.
(Marge's voice) Homer?
Homer!
Huh? What the...?
Hello! Hello! Hello!
Is there anybody in there?
Marge!
Homer, are you all right?
I guess so, but that first month
was pretty rough.
You've only been gone two days.
Really? Without TV, it's hard to know
when one day begins and the other ends.
I miss you, Dad.
Mom won't let me read
Hagar the Horrible.
I just don't think it's funny.
Mmm, I can see the house
is falling apart without me
so here's the new order:
-Bart, you're the man of the house.
-Mmm.
-HOMER: Lisa, I'm promoting you to boy.
-(growls)
HOMER: Maggie's now the brainy girl.
The toaster can fill in for Maggie.
And, Marge, you're a consultant.
(groans) Oh...
-Dad?
-Yes, boy?
I just want to tell you
how proud I am that you're showing
an interest in your fellow man.
Really?
You're proud of me?
Oh, yes.
The whole town thinks
you're a real humanitarian.
Ned Flanders is green with envy.
Oh, really?
Well, if you'll excuse me,
I've got some civilization
to spread like butter
on the English muffin
that is these people, with all
their little nooks and crannies.
Dad, are you licking toads?
I'm not not licking toads.
Well, it's time to get to work.
Humanitarian Homer Simpson,
over and out.
(static)
(croaking)
Ah... Um...
-(croaks)
-(chuckles)
Gather 'round, everyone.
I'm going to teach you about religion.
NATIVES: Oh, god,
oh, god, oh, god.
Please, please, that's not necessary.
I'm just God's messenger.
And lo,
what a wondrous message it is.
Like this,
from the book of... P-salms.
God will shatter the heads
of his enemies.
The hairy crown of those
who walk in their guilty ways.
That you may bathe
your feet in blood.
As true today as it was
when it was written.
Now, let's open it up
to some "Q" and "A."
Yes, Lisa Junior?
Amy said there are lots of religions.
Which is the right one?
Well, not the Unitarians.
If that's the one true faith,
I'll eat my hat.
Um, if the Lord is all powerful
why does he care whether
we worship him or not?
Ak just saying.
Well, Ak, it's because
God is powerful but also insecure
like Barbra Streisand before James Brolin.
Oh, he's been a rock.
Oh, who am I kidding?
The truth is, I'm no missionary.
I work in a nuclear power plant.
Ooh, tell us all you know
about nuclear power.
Look, the point is, I want to help
but you don't need a well or a chapel
or an immunization center.
What you need is a little razzle-dazzle.
(snaps fingers)
Qtoktok, are you thinking
what I'm thinking?
I am Ak.
Hey, that's great.
Now let's get to work.
Now, if the Flintstones
has taught us anything
it's that pelicans
can be used to mix cement.
Come on, little friend,
make a wisecrack.
You know, "it's a living,"
that sort of thing.
Oopsie.
-Hiya, Homer.
-That's not Homer.
It's got to be.
He's parking in Homer's space.
Well, time to get to work.
(sighs)
-Simpson.
-D-ah!
I've just reviewed your ten-year
performance record,
and it's appalling.
But I'm not Homer Simpson.
I think I know
who Homer Simpson is.
In ten short years,
you've caused 17 meltdowns.
-One is too many.
-Yeah, but...
You sold weapons-grade plutonium
-to the Iraqis with no markup.
-But...
And worst of all, you took
the Hamburglar's birthday off
last Monday and Wednesday.
Which is it?
(sighs) Now my voice is giving out
so I'm just going to poke you
for the next hour or so.
-(grunts)
-(groans)
(groaning)
Friends, when I came here
one month ago
this seemed like a strange
and frightening place.
But now I've learned to love
this island
-as my second--
-(chopper blades whirring)
A plane!
Stop! Get me off this stinking rock!
(sighs)
Anyhow, I'm about to share
with you a modern-day miracle--
Something that has revitalized cities
from east St. Louis
to Biloxi, Mississippi--
The magic medicine of...
casino gambling!
"The Lucky Savage?"
It could be you.
Check it out.
There's Island Blackjack,
Island Craps,
Island Texas hold them...
But if like me--
you're mesmerized by pretty colors
and spinning things--
you'll prefer roulette.
Four sand dollars
on number six, please.
So, how you doing?
Staying out of trouble?
Yes, sir.
-Number six.
-Whoo-hoo!
HOMER: D-oh!
Now, over here, I've brewed up
my favorite beverage, beer.
It's mostly Dristan and holy water,
but it does the job.
Mmm, ooga booga.
(clamoring)
So, have fun, everybody.
And who knows?
Maybe you'll hit the jackpot,
get off this island
and spend the rest of your days
in a tropical paradise.
(murmuring assent)
Homer, I'm so impressed.
Everything you're doing
sounds so rewarding.
Oh, you should have seen
their faces, honey.
Now I know how Bob Stupak feels.
(whistling happily)
Is everybody happy?
(natives shouting)
(sighs)
Oh, my god.
(slurring) How can
Ace be one and 11?
Huh?
What kind of god
would allow that?
(grunting weakly)
(groans)
(gasps)
Oh, what happened?
I gave you a glittering Vegas
and you turned it
into a skanky Atlantic city.
Your alcohol and inexpensive buffets
have corrupted us.
I don't even like macaroni salad
but look at me!
(gobbling)
Please help us.
Our island has not been this damaged
since the A-bomb tests.
(sighs)
Guess who I saw
at the supermarket today.
Can it wait?
I just got off work.
I'm sorry, honey, I just thought...
Don't you do enough yakking
at the beauty parlor?
That's it, Bart.
You're taking this
man-of-the-house thing too far.
You're right. I'm sorry.
Tell you what--
Saturday night we'll go out for steaks,
just you and me.
Hmm.
A night out is a night out.
(grunting)
(speaking native language)
Why are you building chapel?
Because you're all terrible sinners.
Since when?
Since I got here.
Now, either grab a stone or go to hell.
(all gasping)
(groaning)
HOMER: Well, I may not know
much about God,
but I have to say, we built
a pretty nice cage for him.
(chattering)
These are from the children.
Thanks to you, they finally
have a place to pray.
Aw...
And I'm in a gambling program
for real, this time.
How many times must we
go to church to avoid hell?
Every Sunday for the rest of our lives.
(laughing)
-No, really?
-(bell ringing)
Not bad, Lisa Junior.
But god's palace is
way up on the moon
so if we want him to hear us
we've got to crank up the volume.
You hear me, Lord?
Homer's doing your work.
I'm the greatest missionary
(echoing) of all time!
(screaming)
(yells)
Oh, no. This looks like the end.
(screaming)
(chuckling) Oh, that Homer--
Always getting into trouble
and if you're one of the millions
who enjoys his adventures--
Or should I say, misadventures--
It's time to show your support.
Sure, Fox makes
a fortune from advertising,
but it's still not enough.
Not nearly enough.
So if you don't want to see
crude, lowbrow programming
disappear from the airwaves...
Please, call now.
(phone ringing)
Hello. Murdoch here.
Ten thousand dollars?
You've saved my network.
Wouldn't be the first time.
(theme music playing)
Shh.
HOMER: Save me, Jebus!
Captioned by Visual Data Media Services