-(all exclaiming)
-CHOIR: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
D'oh!
(tires screeching)
♪ I don't believe it ♪
♪ When you tell me ♪
♪ That it's all gone bad ♪
♪ It's true ♪
♪ To... you... ♪
-BART: Whoa!
-(tires screech)
-(alarm sounding)
-(birds squawking)
(alarm continues)
(soft groaning, snoring)
Huh?
Where's the snooze button?
Ah, that's better.
(explosion)
Hey, what?
I gotta get out of here!
-(alarm blaring)
-It's... (yawns)
After just five more minutes.
(yawns)
(alarm blaring)
(laughing)
Oh... Marge...
On a Tuesday?
DR. HIBBERT:
Yet again, Homer will be fine.
Mm. He's been sleeping
an awful lot.
Look at these vacation photos.
DR. HIBBERT: Oh, my!
(chuckling)
Man, you people sure
take a lot of vacations.
MARGE: That's just to remind me
where I parked.
Hmm. I think I have an idea
of what might be going on.
(gasps)
Huh? What?
First, you're gonna need
a spinal tap.
Please be the band.
Oh!
Aren't you supposed
to give him anesthetic?
Oh, I knew I forgot something.
(screaming) Ow!
(printer whirring)
Oof. Very low levels of hypocretin.
I'm afraid Homer has... narcolepsy.
Doctor, is it time to pull the plug
on my father?
No, wait.
I'll spare you that painful decision.
HOMER: No, Bart! That's the TV!
Ha-ha! That's the other guy.
Stop that!
(laughs)
Narcolepsy's merely
sleeping sickness,
and many narcoleptics
do lead normal lives
by avoiding stressful triggers
like, uh, oh, let's say...
-Helping with the laundry?
-Exactly.
Having to pay my doctor's bill?
(gruff voice)
Don't play with me, man.
I will mess you up.
Here's a signed certification
of your condition.
This is a bona fide
medical excuse
from doing anything
you find taxing.
But you'll only use that
when absolutely necessary,
right, Homie?
Marge, please!
I'll probably never use it.
Dad, can you drive me
to Milhouse's?
Narcolepsy.
There's a spider in my room!
Dr. Hibbert called in a prescription
for you to pick up.
Narcolepsy.
Yes, for narcolepsy,
which you should get now.
You can't spend
half your life napping.
Maggie does,
and you think she's adorable.
Yes, because babies
are always cute.
(grunting)
(coughing)
(sniffs) Oh, that baby needs
a diaper change.
Nar-co-lep-sy.
(groans)
Homie, you have no idea
what it's like
being married to you.
Me being married to me, eh?
("Bridal Chorus" playing)
(gasps)
Stop the wedding!
What about our child?
(baby whimpers)
(dog barks)
Don't forget me.
Now I've seen everything.
A window that talks?!
Okay, can you explain again
how I take this medication?
One a day with food.
Yeah, but what kind
of food, girly?
Stuffed cabbage?
A nice bowl soup?
(sighs)
Any idea when you'll get to me?
Well, there's four old people
ahead of you,
so how's Thursday at 1:00?
Oh, you know it's funny
that you should say "one,"
'cause that's how many
grandchildren that I have.
I'm gonna have grandchildren
by the time
I get through this line.
Oh, that's so nice.
-Oh, well, congratulations.
-(giggles)
Narcolepsy, take me away!
Oh! (grunts)
-(sighs)
-(toy squeaks)
(sniffing)
I smell beer.
Did you go to Moe's?
Every time I have beer
on my breath,
you assume I've been drinking.
(groans loudly)
Oh, that's a long one.
Did you at least
get the medicine?
I tried.
And I failed, miserably.
But I'm willing to work this out
in counseling.
(groans) We've been
to every counselor
from Avery to Zabinsky.
But not Zilowitz.
HOMER: And that's why
there'll never be
another golfer as good
as Chi-Chi Rodríguez.
The name and the game--
he had it all.
Okay, I think we got
a little off-track here.
I know this marriage
isn't perfect,
or even great,
but now I treasure the moments
where it's just so-so.
-(snoring)
-I'd kill for "okay."
Please, please,
just tell me what to do.
I've never said this--
and I don't even know
if I'm supposed to say this--
but this marriage is rotting
with the stench of death.
Oh, that seems a little strong.
How about reeking like
a trash can in a dog park?
Does my marriage have to be
something you can smell?
(snoring)
You see, Marge? You see?
The only way you and Homer
will ever be happy
is to spend a little time apart,
followed by more time apart,
followed by a divorce.
What?!
What is...
What, what's going on?
Wait, no, no, no,
I remember.
Happy anniversary.
Homer, Homer, listen to me.
There's just so much
I can take.
No, we can save this.
We'll go to a therapist.
We're at a therapist.
How you doin'?
What's going on here?
(sobbing)
Nothing.
Everything's fine.
-See?
-(sobbing continues)
I'll love you forever.
Kids, a professional felt
the best way
for your father and me
to work on our relationship
was to give up on it.
But after a while,
Dad's coming back?
-Oh, yeah, of course.
-Maybe not.
Oh, Marge, after all my divorce-worthy
statements and actions--
many of which
you don't know about--
how can you kick me out
now that I'm sick?
Narcolepsy is a serious thing.
Maybe because you didn't take it
seriously enough.
I pity you!
(Homer sobbing)
Why is Daddy going away?
Is it my fault?
Just kidding.
I have been waiting for this.
All my problems
are my parents' fault!
Mr. Flanders,
can I cry on your shoulder?
Boys, get my tear dickey.
BOTH: Yay!
(Homer snoring)
-(snoring)
-(alarm beeping)
Five more minutes.
(snoring resumes)
Poor guy, living at the plant.
And yet he's still late.
♪ ♪
(crow cawing)
Smithers, come up
through my rear and grab me.
Yes, sir.
(humming)
(blow dryer whirrs, stops)
(humming happily)
I don't get it, Homer.
You and your wife
may be calling it quits.
How can you be happy?
Oh, you guys missed
a very sad montage,
but then I remembered that
after every fight we ever had,
Marge takes me back.
I wouldn't be so cocky, Homer.
Marge has changed
her relationship status
to "It's complicated."
(whistles)
Not good.
Complicated?
What's complicated?
We're not together,
but we're not legally apart,
and I have to fight for
the right to see the children
I spent my life avoiding.
What's complicated about that?
Simpson,
where are your shoes?
-Narcolepsy.
-Oh, sorry, sorry.
Now,
to prove everything is fine,
I'm just going
to give Marge a call.
MARGE: Hello, you've reached
the voicemail for Marge Bouvier.
(beeps)
Oh, my God.
She switched
to her maiden name.
She must be serious.
She's gonna have
to order new checks.
♪ ...fight,
The Itchy & Scratchy Show! ♪
(Chopin's "Funeral March" playing)
(doorbell rings)
Eh? Mm!
(cackling)
Use a coaster.
Oh, the pigeon sisters!
(pigeons cooing)
Wish my head
was filled with guacamole.
Now, on the bright side, Homer,
guys get in much better shape
when they get divorced.
Not me.
I will not become a cliché.
Well, consider yourself lucky.
Most guys never even
get a chance
to lose an amazing woman
like Marge.
If Marge is in play,
I'm cleaning up.
♪ Got a date with an angel ♪
♪ Got to meet her at 7:00. ♪
(belches)
Hey, guys, knock it off, huh?
I'm sure Homer and Midge
just need to talk things out there.
(phone ringing)
And there she is now.
Hello, baby.
Y-- Oh, it's the pharmacy.
They want me to pick up
my prescription. (sighs)
Well, that man just won
the Saddest Man in the Bar
competition.
I was so damn close!
Whoa, nice fill.
You've got amphetamines,
anticataplectics and GHB,
also known as Georgia Homeboy
or Liquid Ecstasy.
Do not take these with alcohol.
What if I've already
been drinking,
and I don't plan to stop?
Are you asking me out?
I mean, you're not,
but it seems like
you'd be fun to hang with,
and I'm pretty fascinating myself--
I'm an author.
I thought you worked
in a drugstore.
Tennessee Williams
worked in a shoe factory.
Boy, you're pretty fast
with that fact.
You want to go out or not?
Well, I don't know
what you see in me.
I'm just a lonely guy
with a bag full of drugs.
Huh! Come with moi.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
You're moving way too fast for me.
I get that a lot.
(sighs)
No, what I'm saying is
you're walking faster
than I can walk.
How fast can you go?
Pretend you're walking
a very slow old dog.
(both growling, barking)
(rock music playing)
No autographs.
I just need you to sign your bill.
The monkey
made the reservation.
He pays.
I think it's cool
how you owned your own baldness
by shaving your head.
Well, I saw a picture
of Jeffrey Katzenberg once,
and said,
"Yes, that's for me."
Okay, listen,
I'm just floating this,
but have you ever thought
that it might be a good thing
Marge dumped you?
What are you saying?
You guys were so young
when you met.
She was your first girlfriend.
I've dated more girls than you.
But now you're free
to try something new.
Uh...
it's... getting late.
I should go.
The donut shop will be...
throwing out their...
unsold donuts, and...
you can buy them... cheap.
Don't you want
to finish your drink?
Eh, you're the pharmacist.
Whoa.
♪ Big city ♪
♪ Bright lights ♪
♪ Cool, cool people ♪
♪ Big city ♪
♪ ♪
-(Homer laughing)
-(heads laughing)
(Patty and Selma chuckle)
(gagging)
(grunting)
Mm!
(laughing groggily)
Hey.
What? Candles?
Clean sheets!
Did I pass out at Urban Outfitters?
Oh, God! Oh, God!
I've just committed
the one drunken mistake
I've never made.
Well, Bart.
Oh, my God,
oh, my God, oh, my God.
What am I gonna
tell Marge?
(gasps)
Don't move!
There's a snake
on your butt.
That's a tattoo.
Why would you do that
to your body?
I thought you had one, too.
Those are stretch marks,
young lady.
I've had three children.
I got to call my wife.
I thought you guys
were separated.
I'm the kind of man
who never gives up hope.
I own property in Detroit,
every Christmas I ask for
size 36 pants,
and I still buy Beanie Babies.
(phone beeps, line rings)
Hello, Homer.
Marge is getting ready
for a date.
Marge? On a date?
Yep, but I'll make you a deal.
I will try to save your marriage
if you can guess which one I am.
-Patty?
-Wrong!
(dial tone)
(sobbing)
(dog howls)
I'm gonna get one, two, three,
four, five scones.
You guys want anything?
-We're fine.
-No, thanks.
We're all right.
Candace, what is his deal?
-(gasps) Is he paying your rent?
-No.
-Is he giving a kidney to your mother?
Is he good at sitting on suitcases
that are too full?
Yes, but no.
Is he your guest
at a dinner for schmucks?
No.
(gasps)
Are you a Humpty Dumpty catcher?
Be honest.
All no.
Does her remind you
of a childhood snowman?
Yes, that's it!
And the great thing is
he will never melt.
Man, I would love to get back
into snowman shape.
I can't even fit
in my scarf anymore.
Whoa, this is serious.
Complimentary tattoos.
Yeah, I've always been looking
for the very special lady
who would match up with this.
(whinnying)
All right, very funny.
You two celebrating or what?
Two Scorpinos, Moe.
Scorpinos, you got it.
And those are served in a...?
Champagne flute.
Champagne flute, got it.
And that is a...?
Glass! A clean glass.
Ah, coming right up there,
Your Highness.
(quietly)
Nut case.
(car engine revs, tires squeal)
Wow, Homer,
you really stuck the landing
after your separation.
Yeah, it's great.
Except her friends
are always over.
I've been there for three weeks,
and I can't find the TV.
And no one has any problems,
except they talk about them
endlessly.
Kind of like you're doing now?
And the weirdest thing of all is
now she wants me
to meet her dad.
Wow, who pays for that dinner?
I plan to pretend
there's a bug in my food
and get the meal for free.
Smooth.
H-Hello, sir.
Thank you for inviting me
to dinner, sir.
Homer, relax.
I have no problem
with the age difference
between you and my daughter.
In fact, I've been dating
a much younger woman myself.
Oh, here she comes now.
(humming happily)
-(gasp)
Okay, okay,
we can be adults about this.
Waiter, champagne?
(sputtering)
So I can't date an older man,
but your girlfriend can?
She's not my girlfriend.
Candace and I don't use labels.
Mm, doesn't look like she uses
that much shampoo either.
Lay off my girlfriend!
Roger is great with the kids.
He even taught Bart
how to bunt.
Oh, so now you're super dad?
When I was a kid,
you were never around.
You missed my high school play.
You told me not to come.
You're supposed
to fight me on that!
Well, Marge,
your Roger's not so perfect now.
He's got a screwed-up daughter
with a pathetic boyfriend.
Candace, dear, I apologize.
I'm trying so hard
to set my life right.
Oh, speaking of which.
Marge, I am going to do
something I should've done
three weeks ago when I met you.
Will you marry me, Marge?
Yes.
As soon as my divorce is final.
Then you can put a ring
on my finger, Homer.
I'm already pregnant.
You're pregnant?!
But I kept my shirt on!
(echoing)
No!
(snoring)
Huh? What am I doing here?
Sleeping through
our therapy session.
Dreaming only about you.
So none of it happened?
We're still together?
-Somehow.
-Whoo-hoo!
And you thought our only option
was to break up.
I never said that.
If I told people
that didn't belong together
they shouldn't be together,
I'd be out of a job.
Huh,
I must have dreamed that, too.
Okay, why don't you tell us more
about this dream?
All you need to know
about my dream
is that Marge and I have been
completely turned around by it,
and like Scrooge,
I will demonstrate
I have learned my lesson
by making a boy run to the store
and buy me a goose.
I think you're going to have
to do a little more, Homer.
Oh, I'll do a lot more
than a little more!
I'll do some!
If you could just be good
for a month,
that would really
show me something.
Absolutely.
Can the month be February?
Okay, March.
(groans)
You did it, Homie!
And what a March it was.
A beautiful Easter,
a sober St. Patrick's Day,
and impeccable behavior
watching the NCAA
basketball tournament.
Mm-hmm!
And with your love, Dad,
I'm eating meat and Maggie's talking.
♪ I've seen trees of green ♪
♪ Red roses, too... ♪
What the...?
(man sings rock version)
♪ I see them bloom ♪
♪ For me and you ♪
♪ And I think to my... ♪
(grunts)
Huh? Huh? Huh?
I got you one of those beers
you enjoy unironically.
This won a blue ribbon in 1890?
What does that mean?
Wait, so this is reality?
That other dream
was just a dream?
No...!
But you forgot to pay!
(distant)
Oh!
(whimpering)
(gasps)
(sobbing)
I've lost everything.
My wife, my family...
(sobbing)
You didn't lose me, Dad.
(chuckles) Lisa?
You can never lose me.
We share the same blood,
the same mixed feelings
towards Bart,
and you know I'll need support
in my teenage war with Mom.
(sobbing)
Oh, Lisa.
(both laughing)
Oh, Dad.
Dad!
-Aw, sweetie...
-Nothing could ever come between us.
...we'll be together forever.
ROGER:
Lisa, where are you, dear?
I thought we'd get in
a game of chess
before we go pony shopping.
Gotta go.
Lisa!
I'll Skype you at Christmas!
(echoing)
No...!
(Homer snoring)
Huh, so it was all my dream.
I better find out
what this all means.
It means,
like all married women,
sometimes you're sick
of your husband,
but sometimes you're afraid
of losing him.
And like all married men,
I didn't hear that first thing,
and I'm overconfident
of the second.
So what do we do?
I need some kind of guidance
to take away from all of this.
Put your finger on it
so I can tie it in a bow.
Please?
Well, one thing
we therapists can give
is concise, simple solutions,
and yours is...
Hannah, what does that one mean?
It means don't get drunk in Brooklyn.
♪ I see babies cry ♪
♪ I watch them grow ♪
♪ They'll learn much more ♪
♪ Than I'll ever know ♪
♪ And I think to myself ♪
♪ What a wonderful world ♪
♪ Yes, I think to myself ♪
♪ A wonderful, wonderful ♪
♪ A wonderful, wonderful world ♪
♪ Wonderful world! ♪
Shh!
Subtitled by B. Everdene