Oh, no.
(exclaiming)
(school bell ringing)
(Barney belches)
(whistle blows)
(yells)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
(grunts)
(yells)
(screams)
(screaming)
(chuckles)
D'oh! Ooh!
(groans)
(mouth groans)
Ooh!
(gasps)
(belches)
(heart beating)
♪ ♪
(squishing, blurping)
Why, you little...!
(Homer and Bart grunt)
♪ The Simpsons 25x19 ♪
What to Expect When Bart's Expecting
Original Air Date
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
Huh...?!
Eh, welcome fellow barkeeps,
gin-slingers, and beer jerks.
We are all here because
drinkin' in our bars is down.
Mom-and-pop bartenders can't
compete with big box stores
like Booze Barn
and Hooch City.
(bell dinging)
(all clamoring)
Uh, folks, this is the owner
of the airport bar speaking.
Uh, we're experiencing
some financial turbulence.
Uh, please remain calm.
Now let's watch this informational
video that'll help save our business.
Thanks, Cap. Now what I'm proposing
is a superhero pub crawl.
Our clientele dress up in costume
and go drinking from bar to bar.
Their masks make 'em feel
uninhibited and invulnerable.
(all murmuring positively)
Yeah, and that's not all. Why
don't you tell 'em about it, Moe?
Yeah, you got it, Moe.
We can make up superhero drink
names and charge 'em double.
Like, uh, Nick Fury,
Agent of Schnapps;
Sex in the Batmobile;
And Wolveriskey.
Here, check out my,
uh, portfolium here.
(all clamoring, cheering)
Whoo! Yeah!
Flame on! (belches)
(gasps)
Oh-God-oh-God-oh-God!
I can't breathe!
No, no, no!
Why do they call
this a yard of ale?
Easy. After you drink one,
you're passed out in your yard.
Hmm.
(drunkenly):
Well, better get home.
The delightfulness
ended hours ago.
Homer, the best thing for you to do in
this situation is keep drinking. Heh.
(Homer moaning)
(groaning)
(Otto laughs)
Oh, why are you doing
this to me, booze?
I drank every kind of you!
- See ya, Homer!
- Bye, Dad!
Have a good day, you two!
Don't be me!
There's my dad!
Wait, I think I just
sucked up a dollar!
(grunting)
José, hit the switch!
We are not all Josés, man.
(other kids laugh)
Oh! Art.
Simpson! Smock up!
Every time I do art, some do-gooder
teacher sends it straight to a therapist.
Your stuff is
pretty disturbing.
I've never acted
on any of it.
You will take art,
you will enjoy art,
and you will make something
in a kiln your mother can use.
Oh...
(groans)
Maggie! Why'd you do that?
Oh, I just came in to
take out the trash!
And you shall
leave immortal!
Also, take out the trash.
Honest!
Inspiring!
Yes... necessary!
Oh, Milhouse-ian!
Oh, Bart, it's wonderful!
Really? Wonderful? I just
drowned a grasshopper in paint
and let him crawl on the
paper till he died.
You know what that's called?
Mixed-media conceptual art.
No, it's not,
because I hate art.
Oh, then it's protest art!
Stop encouraging me!
I will admire you
from afar...!
(exasperated grunt)
(gasps)
Shauna? What are
you doing here?
Training for the Olympics.
I gotta find a way to get
rid of my art teacher.
Easy. Voodoo.
Is there a voodoo queen
you can direct me to?
Oh, yeah. She lives in a
trailer down by Yogurtland.
Now kiss me. I wanna
make somebody mad.
(grunting)
BART: What are you doing?!
What's my no-good
daughter up to now?
Now u have everyt'ing
you need for the voodoo.
- Would you like a bag?
- Yes, ma'am.
Paper or plastic?
Uh, plastic.
Just like the chicken
foot say you would!
Okay, did you get
Trunch's DNA?
Yeah, got it out
of her purse.
(chuckles)
How'd you do that?
Art teachers don't
have a desk.
They just throw their
purse anywhere.
Voodoo spell, voodoo spell,
seagull beak and bone of Mel,
purple heart and tear of chum...
(grunts)
Just had to be
tear of chum.
Send her home
with aching tum!
Oh, right, we need one more
thing from her purse.
I've got these.
BART: Hmm, she's got tickets
to the play God of Carnage.
Orchestra?!
On an art teacher's salary?
That's black magic!
Where's Mrs. Trunch?
I need to know the correct density
of "points" in my pointillism.
Mm, sorry, but I don't think we'll
be seeing much of Trunch today.
Yep, I cast a voodoo
spell on her.
I won't bore you with
the dark details,
but let's just say she's in
no condition for teaching.
(gasps)
(disappointed):
Oh...
Class, I have an
announcement.
I'm afraid I can't teach today.
I have a tummy ache.
- Mm...
- A very special tummy ache.
I'm going to have a baby!
(gasps)
Aah! Bart Simpson got
a teacher pregnant!
(scoffing)
- Typical Ralph nonsense.
- (Milhouse panting)
Bart Simpson got
a teacher pregnant!
You happy with your
two-timing boyfriend now?
I admit, I did make a
voodoo doll of Mrs. Trunch.
But I just asked for a
stomachache, not a baby!
Classic wish-maker's
mistake: Vague language.
So I did make
her pregnant?
Of course not. Doesn't
work that way.
Just how do women
get babies?
I'm not allowed to discuss
that with fourth-graders.
Fifth grade, you get
every dirty detail.
Do you know how embarrassed I was
to get a call at my arraignment
for my behavior during the pub
crawl because of a voodoo curse
my son placed on
his art teacher?
I didn't mean to make her pregnant.
I just hate art so much.
Oh, everyone does, son.
That's why they lock it up in museums
where no one will ever visit.
So, uh, your boy's got magic
knock-up powers, huh?
Hey, I created three kids, and no
one's making a big deal of that.
Not true! Whenever I compliment
your virility, you act all weird.
And you are very virile.
- Uh, yeah. Just talk about sports!
- No problem.
Wish I had that Tom
Brady's libido.
(shudders)
Oh, it's amazing how many Cheerios
Maggie drops in the back seat.
Here you go. Put those in the trash, then
you can help me unload the dishwasher.
Oh! A minute of fun,
a lifetime of work.
I've never heard of a
pregnancy like this.
- There he is.
- Jenny, this is crazy.
Nothing's crazy
at this point.
Are you the boy
that makes babies?
I like to think I'm the
boy that makes families.
You see, Jenny?
He's just a jerk kid.
It's just... (sobs)
we've been trying so
hard to start a family.
With all the money
we've spent on IVF...
(sobs)
You have no idea!
Hmm, maybe I can help.
But it'll cost you.
- How much?
- Five dollars.
Plus one dollar
haw-haw insurance.
Trust me, the insurance
is worth it.
By the power of this place,
make a baby with a face.
That's great, really. Really glad we're
getting a baby with a face. Thank you.
(tires screech)
- Haw...!
- No haw-haw! It worked!
(groans)
I'm pregnant!
Look, Bart, I really, I can't
believe there's a connection here.
But, uh, we have some friends who are
in the same dark place that we were.
- Can we give them your name?
- Only if they have five dollars.
Yes, right. I'll make sure
that they have five dollars.
With them.
Look, I'm sorry our check bounced, man.
I can have the bank teller call you.
Just give me the cash and you'll
get your driver's license back.
Please keep the chatter down while the
Womb Wizard is casting his spells.
Ones are
appreciated, people.
Barbeque sauce and
teddy bear's eye.
They want a baby,
God knows why.
Homie, I can't
find my spatula.
Can you get another one?
Flanders, can we
borrow your spatula?
That was my spatula.
And you never bought
a replacement?
Ah, too much aggravation.
We just forego flipped food.
D'oh!
(grunts)
- Hmm.
- (humming a tune)
- Bart?
- Huh?
Why, you little...!
I'll teach you to answer
peoples' prayers!
(both grunting)
Yeah, you know, I just don't think we're
going to get in to see him today.
What is your problem, boy?
Maybe when I've got a dad
who shows up in the morning
with no shirt on and
rocks on his face,
it sets, I don't
know, a low bar?
Wow, I got to take that in.
While I do, have
some bar nuts.
Aren't those
full of germs?
Eat the nuts!
They're your dinner!
(guns click)
You guys are
coming with us.
Not so fast!
Nobody comes into my bar and
kidnaps two paying customers.
Aw, thanks, Moe, I...
Huh?
I must've left my
wallet at home.
All right, take them, take them!
Fill their pockets with corn
and toss them to the pigs.
Don't tell us
our business!
(sobs)
Huh? Fat Tony?
That's right...
- Fat Homer.
- Hey!
I need your boy
to make a baby.
Do you really need the
boy's help to make a baby?
Just do a little of the
bunga-bunga, and the hotsie-totsie,
and the bop-bada-
bop-bada-bop.
You sound like every
doctor I've ever been to.
But it's not for me.
It's for her.
Meet my filly, Cheesesteak.
The love of my life.
(baby-talking, kissing)
Who has apple breath?
You has apple breath.
(kissing, baby-talking)
And this horse, who I
have briefly "borrowed,"
is the winner of last
year's Springfield Stakes...
Rear Admiral.
So work your magic, and
breed me a champion.
Look, Fat Tony, I don't know
what you know about voodoo,
but it only works on people.
Horses? That's crazy talk!
You will breed me a champion by morning or
it will be the last sunrise you ever see.
Don't over-promise, boss.
It might be overcast.
How'd you like a
cast over your face?
Well, as long as there
re breath holes.
You know, I'm just saying.
Okay, boy, if there ever was
a good time for you to find out
where babies come from in
the grossest way possible,
with your life on the
line, this is it.
One more thing:
It better be a boy.
(scoffs)
Anything else?
It would be helpful if
he could go undercover
with police horses and
find out what they know.
(crickets trilling)
- Hey, this is all your fault.
- How is it my fault?
I wouldn't be here if you
were more of a role model.
Pub crawls, naked
Frisbee golf...
I just did that because it was
a series of funny words.
Well, it's your mediocre fathering
that put me on the path to hell!
Wha...?
Maybe you're right, boy. It's
time I was a better father.
And I'll start
by saving us.
I just need to facilitate
some horse intercourse.
Come on, buddy.
Just make a champion thoroughbred,
and we're out of here.
(neighs)
What's his problem?
♪ It's raining men ♪
♪ Hallelujah, it's raining men ♪
(neighing)
♪ Amen ♪
♪ I'm gonna go out ♪
♪ I'm gonna let myself get... ♪
(music stops)
Hey, you know?
I don't think this
guy likes girls.
(splutters)
Big deal. I don't
like girls, either.
Not like that.
It's like this.
(indistinct whispering)
Smithers...
Mr. Largo...
Danny Kaye.
What? Everyone knows.
(neighs)
Now, where's she going?
Hey, I know that horse!
It's Sudsley!
Sudsley Brew-Right!
(neighs)
That horse was instrumental
in me becoming a man.
♪ It feels like
the first time ♪
♪ It feels like the
very first time ♪
♪ It feels like the first time... ♪
(neighing)
(neighs)
Ew, that tastes horrible!
Beer transformed
that cute little boy
into the man you
see before you.
Hmm.
(neighs)
Whoa! They like
each other.
You know, pregnant
is pregnant.
- What a you talking about?
- We're not lost, boy.
Not by a long shot.
We just have to
set the mood.
(gentle orchestral intro begins)
♪ Let them play ♪
♪ We won't look ♪
♪ We'll turn away ♪
♪ Go make love ♪
♪ Then eat some hay ♪
♪ We'll be dead ♪
♪ Shot through the head ♪
♪ Be that as it may ♪
♪ Fat Tony's horse is gay ♪
♪ I do not hear no banging ♪
♪ No sound of
horseshoes clanging ♪
♪ Roll in hay ♪
♪ Or tomorrow we will pay ♪
♪ I don't care
about tomorrow ♪
♪ We need true
horse love today ♪
♪ Here's a blanket
they can borrow ♪
♪ Let them rock
the night away ♪
♪ I don't really
mind at all ♪
♪ But why must I go
muck the stall? ♪
♪ Roll in hay ♪
♪ Roll in hay... ♪
♪ Roll in hay! ♪
(bottle shatters)
(grunts)
(steady banging nearby)
Ah, young love.
So, where is the
pregnancy test?
Right here.
What does it say?
The Pimlico plus of joy?
Or the Maryland State
Fairgrounds minus?
It's a plus!
We're having a baby!
Hey, salute!
I've never seen Johnny
Tightlips so happy.
Simpsons, you're free to go!
Louie, drive 'em home.
- Cool, another limo ride!
- The limo's in the shop.
We have a loaner.
BART:
Ay, caramba!
You monster! My knees
will be in my throat!
There's another
way you can go.
Dad?
Cheesesteak, a little advice
from a mother of three.
They'll turn out the same
whether you gallop or trot.
Teach him not to pee
during parades.
He'll get more work.
(neighing)
Now that's what I
call a modern family.
♪ Hey, hey! ♪
♪ Hey! ♪
(clamoring)
The prosecution calls
Sudsley Brew-Right!
(gallery murmuring)
Sudsley, on the
night in question,
how many did you see
the defendant kill?
(knocks seven times)
Seven in one night?
What kind of a monster
could do that?
A party monster! Drinking the
new, convenient Duff Seven-Pack!
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
The Duff Seven-Pack...
one more for the road.
There's nothing
symmetrical about flavor!
So get your seven
pack today!
It looks wrong, but it is
oh, so right! Oh, yeah!
♪ Oh, yeah... ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
Shh!