Now that I, Chinnos,
finally wield the Doomsday App,
I can restart this planet
in flames,
as a utopia.
I don't know, Chinnos.
You say utopia,
but what I'm hearing is
kill everyone.
And I really don't want to find
a new dry cleaner.
Your funny-but-not-too-funny
banter
will not save you,
Magnesium Man.
Yeah, but it did distract you,
didn't it, Dad Bod?
Take him, Airshot!
Yes, Airshot, pump that air gun!
Five pumps?
Think of the pressure.
Aw, what's the matter?
Bad head day?
It's time I took the Vindicators
out of the equation.
I'll take that dance now.
Their first kiss was their last.
It was called Crystal War
because they were all
turned to crystals.
Hey, now is not the time
for your cold-hearted analysis.
The sequel isn't coming out
for a year.
What loving God would make us
wait that long?
A year?
That's, like, a million years.
I cannot wait.
Don't you leave me,
you be-cape-ed gob-smashers!
Children, I pulled you
out of your classes today
to warn you of a dangerous
new internet trend.
The paprika challenge?
The eight ball challenge?
No, the highly-imitatable stunt
I'm referring to
is the flag yourself
challenge.
Instead of a merely
verbal warning,
it's clear to me
a more effective deterrent
would be to show you
a video of the stunt
performed by YouTube star
Reaction Guy.
Reaction Guy?
Everybody who's anybody
gets reacted to by him.
Watch and learn...
to not do this.
What up, Reaction Faction?
It's your boy, Reaction Guy.
Today I'm gonna be reacting
to the Flag Yourself Challenge.
Shout-out to my crew, Hedgehog,
Thin Mint, and White Malik.
They're gonna raise me
like a flag.
Whoa, this is so clench!
Wow, cool!
Hey, guys, this is Bart Simpson
from my new channel,
Reaction Bart.
Big shout-out to my boy White
Seymour for putting me onto
the Flag Yourself Challenge.
So clench!
Okay, hit it. Check it out.
I'm waving at my haters
and they don't even know it.
Clench! Clench!
Buy my merch.
Merch to come. Merch!
His obliques
must be shredded.
I got to check them out
next time we go swimming.
Milhouse, no!
I need your passcode
to upload the video.
Yo, Milhouse, I got you
a balloon form the gift shop.
So what'd the doctors say?
I have a full-body sprain.
Most of my muscles are wrapped
around the wrong bones.
Okay, champ,
physical therapy time.
Who's ready for four hours
of stretch bands?
No, not the purple.
Glucose?
Don't mind if I do-cose.
Okay, mate, you can do this.
It's hard, but those little
buggers are counting on you.
Do it for the buggers.
Top of the bing-bong, ladies.
- You're Glen Tangier.
- You're Airshot.
Good on you, Nightingales.
Now, who can point me
towards...
Milhouse Van Houten?
Ooh, right down the hall
and to the left, Glen.
Flirt much, Debby?
Sorry, we can't all
be married to
Ogdenville's car detailing king
Duke Druthers.
What's up, little bro?
How's my favorite
real-life superhero?
Holy crap, you're Glen Tangier.
Never heard of him.
The name's Airshot.
You're my favorite Vindicator.
You don't even have any powers,
you're just super good at air.
Easy now. Don't get
too excited, Milhouse.
Oh, I'm not...
I am Milhouse.
That's right.
Calm down, hero.
Don't make whatever
you have worse.
Is it something that gets worse?
Please don't say it gets worse.
Oh, don't worry, Airshot,
I'm okay.
Well, aren't you just Pimm
to the brim with Adelaide spunk?
Oh, thank boomerang Jesus
you're not one of those
brave little buggers
that I have to show this to.
Wait, what do you got in there?
Oh, it's a laptop
with the sequel
to the Vindicators,
Crystal garbage.
All that matters is
you're gonna be okay, mate.
Never wanted
to be an actor anyway,
just a simple koala butcher
like me old man.
Yo, Airshot. Glen.
Hello.
Sweet boomerang Jeebus.
What an ending.
People are gonna freak out
when they see it...
in a month from now.
Till then, I'm the only one
that knows what happens.
Only I know.
I'm the most powerful kid
in the world.
Toss that Kanga shank
into the billy-boil.
It'll be tender by moon jump.
Yo, Fat Thor, I've seen
Vindicators, Crystal War 2.
- You blaspheme!
- My buddy Airshot showed it to me.
Ha. I repeat, ha.
As if Glen Tangier,
the Tasmanian Adonis,
would deign to interact with
someone of your insignificance.
You are defeated, Vindicator.
Not as long as
I'm still breathing.
Sweet batarang Jesus.
Tell me more.
The first taste was free,
the next is gonna cost you.
I've had my eye on that
Dr. 3 A.M. graphic novel.
Okay, strap yourself in.
The way it goes down is...
But pause.
The knowledge you offer
would spoil the movie event
of the year. Nay, century.
Nay, epoch. Nay, summer.
Tell me nothing.
Ah, but my curiosity consumes me.
All right, here's the deal,
the movie starts on the logo...
Silence! Speak!
Speak not. Expound!
I pass the test.
I will diminish
and remain Comic Book Guy.
Ooh, shrimp.
Hey. What would you give me
not to find out what happens?
Be gone, Spoiler Boy.
Spoiler Boy.
I like that.
That's the kid who saw
Vindicators, Crystal War 2,
Resurgence.
Do what he says
or he'll spoil the ending.
I must protect my virgin ears.
I think you can do better
than that.
Four chicken lumpettes
per person.
Even if that person knows
which Vindicator
loses a third of their powers
fighting Karate Scorpion?
Zip it. My boyfriend's taking me
to see that movie
when it gets to
the two-dollar theater.
Simpson, you're getting
one day of detention
for every extra
lumpette you eat.
Detention, is it?
I guess we'll have
plenty of time to discuss
the fate of your favorite
Vindicator, Black Voodoo.
The champion
of the French Quarter.
You wouldn't dare spoil
the only thing
that brings me joy
in this world.
Give me your toupee.
Toupee?
I don't wear a toupee.
We fade in on Bourbon Street...
Principal Skinner. To what
do we owe the honor, sir, at...
Oh, it's just you.
Hey, how'd you get
all this stuff?
'Cause people do whatever I say
or I spoil the Vindicators movie
for them.
Like so...
Tell Mom it's okay for me
to have soda on my cereal.
I don't know.
Mom's not gonna go for that.
Okay. Get ready to hear
the surprise ending.
Let me guess.
The good guys win.
Who told you?
You can't spoil
that movie for me,
because I don't care
what happens.
You see, as a grown-up,
I know that muscle jerks
in tights with magic powers
punching and hugging each other
is boring BS for babies.
So go ahead,
tell me what Captain Doodad does
to Zippity Whoever.
Because it means nothing.
My powers don't work on you.
But what if I could make them
work for you?
Your sinister tone
intrigues me.
All-you-can-drink beers on me!
Yeah!
But paid for by Moe.
All right, I'm not even gonna
dignify that with a whaaa...
Do the thing, boy.
No, no, don't ruin it, kid!
I'm taking my girlfriend
to that movie
when it gets
to the two-dollar theater.
What time did you get home
last night?
It's not my fault.
Bart used his superpower
to get me drunker
than I've ever beer.
I'm worried that
all this blackmail
is turning Bart
into a bad person.
What's the story,
morning glories?
Young man, I don't like the way
you're using those spoilies
to boss people around.
What?
I was given an amazing power,
so I'm using it.
If you were in my suitcase,
you would do the same thing.
Fans have a deep connection to
the Marble Cinematic Universe.
I would never exploit that,
not for anything.
Oh, wouldn't you?
Lisa Simpson,
I think your superpower
must be stealing hearts.
How do you feel
about exploitation now?
It's okay.
How much
longer do I have to keep up
this kookaburra charade?
How badly do you not want
your bosses at Marble Studios
to know that I used your drunken
thumb to see that movie?
You think I'm your jolly
swagman, do you?
Well, my jumbuck's gonna be free
from your tucker bag
next Thursday,
when that movie goes wide
on every screen in creation.
And after that, you're nothing.
Let's get this party finished!
He's right.
I'm running out of time.
This is... endgame!
And so, today, we celebrate
the 200th birthday
of our beloved oak tree,
Old Susie.
Her stately branches
have shaded our town's weddings,
family reunions,
and quincen... quincien...
Mexican bar mitzvahs.
We're...
Cover you ears!
It's Spoiler Boy!
That's right. It's me.
And if you don't want
the movie spoiled,
you'll all pull together
and build me
the ultimate tree house
of my own design.
Right here in Old Susie.
Not in Old Susie!
Everyone in this town
loves that tree!
We have no choice.
He's got us all
by the short and curlies.
Unless the boy should meet
with an unfortunate accident.
And if anything suspicious
should happen to me,
I've hired the loudest man
in town to yell the ending
on every street corner.
I'm on it!
You have 24 hours
to build my tree house.
The clock is ticking.
Hey, buddy.
You're out of the hospital.
Don't you hey, buddy me.
You stole my visit
from Airshot.
You... You villain!
Me, a villain?
No way.
You just blackmailed
the whole town
to build you a lair.
Okay. I will grant you
the optics on the lair
are less than ideal.
You have actual powers
which you use for evil.
You're a supervillain!
You dare call me a supervillain?
Then get a load of this.
The biggest spoiler
in the whole movie!
Magnesium Man!
Don't say another word!
The fate of our universe
depends on it.
Where the hell am I?
Relax there, Spoiler Boy.
All we did was take you
from your dimension into ours.
You know, the Marble universe?
What you consider to be movies
make up our reality.
No way. Superheroes aren't real.
How dumb do you think I am?
Actual superpowers!
Everything you see
in your Vindicator movies
actually happens to us.
Even the post-credit sequences?
We brought you here
to see the result
of your selfish actions.
Airshot! Dead?
But in the movie he lives.
What happened?
You happened!
You son of a swamp witch!
You showed your Comic Book Guy
a spoiler
of Airshot using his breath
to save himself.
The powers of evil
in our dimension
saw this and, so warned,
taped Airshot's mouth shut.
And killed him.
I didn't know!
I never dreamed that spoilers
really hurt people.
But they do.
Spoilers kill!
I love you, Airshot!
The virtual reality's working.
The kid has no idea
that this has all been fake.
I can't believe he didn't notice
that the dimensional portal
in his backyard
was just a garbage bag
full of glow sticks.
Tell me we're doing
the right thing.
Tell me this is
Bart's best chance
to choose to be a good person.
Don't worry, Marge.
No one's ever been hurt
by a little gaslighting.
Remember how
you always say that?
Remember?
Oh, don't think of it
as gaslighting.
Think of it as
an ultra-enhanced,
immersive fan experience.
All this, just to keep
spoilers from leaking.
Vindicators, colon,
Crystal War, colon, Resurgence
bombing at the box office
would have devastating
consequences.
Failing theme parks,
unsold Halloween costumes
rotting on the docks,
mass suicides
by popcorn farmers,
anything worse than a 55% hold
on its second weekend,
the global economy
collapses like a house of cards.
Is that what you want,
little girl? Is it?
No. No.
Bart clearly feels bad.
Can't we let him out now?
No. We have to be
absolutely sure.
Increasing simulation intensity.
Bring me the boy.
Remember, kid, no spoilers!
Our universe depends on it!
And don't pirate movies.
That hurts everyone.
So, the boy who's seen
how all this ends.
Tell me what you know,
so I can use it
to destroy the Vindicators.
In return, I will grant
your deepest desire.
Actual superpowers.
Muscles...
claws...
bike!
Real powers.
That's even better
than spoiler powers.
Oh, no. Our son is going
to choose evil.
Oh, no! Our son is so stupid
he's going to fall for this!
It doesn't matter
that's it not real.
Bart's soul is at stake.
Great emotion.
Talk about upping the ante.
Tell me the spoilers, child.
And embrace your destiny
as a villain.
Airshot.
All right.
I'll tell you
what you have to do to win.
- No!
- Uh-uh, kid.
Eat my shorts.
No. No.
No...!
Our son's a good guy!
A good guy.
But he's still stupid.
So stupid...
The kid turned down
actual superpowers.
I think he'll
keep his mouth shut.
Okay. We'll let him live.
For now.
I'm back.
I just hope it's not too late.
What day is it?
Why, it's the Wednesday
before Memorial Day, it is.
Then there's still time.
The movie hasn't been spoiled.
Don't worry, son.
Your secret I forgot
is safe with me.
I saved their universe.
I'm not a villain.
I'm a superhero.
- When can we tell him?
- Never.
All right.
No one's gonna talk.
The movie's safe.
We'll let them live.
For now.
I'm not a bad guy.
I'm a good guy.
I'll never spoil anything again.
I'm a changed boy.
A changed boy.
I always knew you had
the stuff of heroes.
Just tell me, does Moby Man
take his place
as the rightful sovereign
of Fishtonia?
Does he? Bart!
Tell me!
Stop your labors, good folk.
Magnesium Man bless us,
every one.
And Bart was as good
as his word.
He kept his mouth shut.
So when everyone finally
saw the movie on opening day,
they were filled with joy.
Then immediately
got on their phones
and spoiled it
for everyone else.