D'oh!
(tires screeching)
(grunts)
What the...?!
Well, this is
a no-brainer.
Woo-hoo!
D'oh!
D'oh! D'oh!
(groans)
Now what?
(screams)
♪ The Simpsons 25x21 ♪
Pay Pal
Original Air Date on May 11, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
(Marge humming)
♪ ♪
(laughing)
(whirring)
Mom, it's not funny if I can't hear
the cats drown in their own barf.
(screaming)
(whirring louder)
(retching continues louder)
Why can't kids still watch
Captain Kangaroo?!
Culture's in decline.
Deal with it.
(groans):
Oh!
(whirring louder)
(laughs)
Yay! A mess!
- Ooh! Can I lick the ceiling?
- (groans): Oh.
I was making that cake for
the block party today.
Now there's no
choice but to go...
store-bought.
(humming)
(over P.A.): I need a price check on
Gramma Shortcut's Store-bought Bundt Cake.
(crowd gasps)
Keep it! Let's go!
- We've got some put-backs.
- Roger dodger, boss.
Hey, don't turn
old man on me.
You know, I used to be the buyer
for the whole chain... 71 stores.
You heard of the A&P? Well,
we used to be the J&G.
♪ You like what you
see at the J&G ♪
♪ They're used to be three,
but we lost the "Z" and... ♪
If I make out with you,
will you shut up?
- Ah, give it a shot.
- (moans)
You know, we used to
give out gray stamps.
Remember green stamps?
Ours was gray.
Attention block
party losers!
We are Ear Poison!
(electric guitar riff plays)
♪ There were bells
on a hill ♪
♪ But I never heard
them ringing ♪
♪ No, I never... ♪
(gasps)
(British accent):
We must have the same recipe.
Drive to store, buy cheap
cake, serves them right.
Booth Wilkes-John.
My wife and I just moved
here from London.
Marge Simpson.
Congratulations on
Little King George.
Well, Marge, my wife and I
are hosting a get-to-know-you
game night on Saturday next... or
as you call it, next Saturday.
Ooh! Game night?
You know? Adult games.
Well, not "adult games,"
fun games, like Charades...
or as you call
it, Pictionary.
It sounds like fun.
I'll just tell Homer and...
Homer, for the last time, do
not drink the Yahtzee dice.
Fine.
(grunts)
Ooh! Doubles.
Mm, I don't know. We have church
the next morning, starts at 11:00.
Oh, we're going
to the game night.
Moving church
to Monday afternoon.
(groans)
Well, if you change your
mind, please let us know.
We could become
"couples friends."
Now, let me try some of Ned
Flanders' No Alarm Chili.
You'll only taste
the spoon.
Brilliant.
Why don't we have
any couples friends?
(groans)
Because... couples
friends are a myth,
started by restaurants
with tables for four.
I want friends!
Any friends.
Okay, sweetie. I'll
call the Van Houtens.
- Not the Van Houtens.
- But...
They're always bragging
about their trip to Rome.
It was 12 years ago,
and it was a layover.
I want new friends.
LISA: Can I make
an observation?
I'm okay with no friends.
It's easier to focus,
and it'll give me great material
for whatever art form I choose.
Right now, I'm
thinking long novella.
Good night.
Okay with no friends?
That's the saddest thing I can
imagine my daughter saying to me.
BART:
I can think of worse.
The saddest thing would be if you
were driving and texting Lisa
and you hit her. And the last thing
she texted before she died was,
"I got your message."
Good night.
Well, they all
make good points.
ANNOUNCER: And now, the moment
of truth on Topiary Wars.
This Taj Mahal should be
floated down the Ganges.
I'm sorry, Cathy. Turn in
your shears and ladders.
Come and get 'em!
(laughs maniacally)
(grunting)
Oh! Thank you.
Why was that on the
Military History Channel?
We're going to that game party, and
we're going to be charming and witty.
You're not going to
eat too much,
and we're not going
to stay too late.
MARGE: You will not sing
unless there's a sing-along,
and never take the tray
out of the caterer's hand.
Don't be too loud,
and don't be too quiet.
When you're too quiet,
you get that psycho look.
(jittering)
And stay in the living room.
Don't go to their kids' room
and watch a basketball game.
- Can I check out what
toys they have? - No.
(groans)
Dinner party
at the neighbors'.
- At least I can drink.
- One drink.
Wha...?! Walking
distance, Marge!
I've been looking forward
to this all week.
DUFFMAN: Don't show
your wife this app!
Powering down!
You were charming
enough to win me,
and that day you didn't
have a drink in you.
Marge! Homer!
Mwah! Mwah!
(quietly):
Homer.
You know, I have
more cheeks.
(chuckles)
I'd like you to meet
my wife Wallis.
(deep voice):
How ya doin'?
Wallis has unearthed the most
delightful entertainment
to thrill us for
hours on end.
It's a murder mystery,
and we're all suspects.
(crowd gasps)
Great! I've always wanted
to try and solve a crime.
(crowd gasps)
Please, everyone,
read your bio.
(gasps)
I am a humble farmer
from Yorkshire.
Humble I can be!
That's the spirit!
Wallis and I have found
this game to provide
a full evening of
divertissement,
building in suspense
to a masterful climax.
We've rented costumes you'll find accurate
to period and conducive to character.
We will serve food and wine
appropriate to period and palette.
(excited murmuring)
We've programmed music to
cover every dramatic event.
Hired a Foley artist.
(steady galloping)
I believe the mare
has a slight limp.
(erratic galloping)
Yes. Yes!
So, for the next three hours, I
welcome you to the moors of...
Question. Uh, it says here the
murderer is Admiral Wainsworth.
Who's that?
(crowd groaning, murmuring)
You've... you-you've
given away the game!
Well, you know...
Why you...!
(both grunting)
Thank you so much!
Now Wallis will once again
withdraw into melancholia!
(monotonous):
Birth, school, work, death.
Worth, drool, shirk, breath.
Mirth, cruel, quirk, meth.
Just so you know, Homer,
you were going to be a dashing
Russian count with multiple lovers!
Well, as we say in Russia,
- "Good-bye in Russian!"
- Do svidaniya!
Uh, nice night for a walk.
(sighs)
I'd like to be alone
for a while.
- You want to be more alone?
- Yes.
- More?
- Mm-hmm.
What the...?! D'oh!
(groaning)
That's good.
Okay, I slept on the couch and I
flipped the sweaty cushions over.
- What else can I do?
- It's okay.
I mean, those people didn't even want
us at that party in the first place.
I think it's time we learn to
live with being ostracized.
Mmm...
Don't you dare say
"ostrich eyes"!
Because... uh...
Oh! Oh, okay, okay!
What should we do?
Nothing. I give up.
No more dinner parties.
Our whole social life will be us
watching TV and you going to Moe's.
I see.
(quietly):
Woo-hoo!
(rattles)
Well, if that's how you
think it has to be.
Yes, for us.
But not for Lisa.
Never for Lisa.
We're going to help
her make friends.
It might be easier
with Maggie.
She's always getting letters
from the day care center.
- Those are past-due bills.
- They'll get their blood money.
And Lisa will
get a friend.
After this, we'll
do makeovers.
(groans)
So where are
all the friends?
I don't know.
I invited everyone
that Lisa's ever met.
- Who are you?
- Gus Huebner.
I was on Lisa's coed
soccer team two years ago.
Well, Lisa's gonna be
here in five minutes,
and the only kid who showed up
is Gus freakin' Huebner.
- Watch your mouth.
- (groans)
Oh, no, you're
right, Homer. Abort!
- Abort!
Oh, no.
I was the only chump who
showed up at this train wreck.
Well, I'm not leaving
till I get a party.
Fine, fine. Homer,
give him a party.
(The Streets of San Francisco
theme playing)
(Homer shouts)
Gus Huebner?
Is that you?
(chuckles):
I wish.
That kid can play
youth soccer.
Are you guys okay?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, sure.
I'm fine.
Yeah. That's...
Nothing's going on.
Right, right. Nothing.
- What's for dinner?
- Pizza. Mmm.
Lots of pizza.
So, as her teacher, I was
wondering if you could tell me
why Lisa has such
trouble making friends.
Marge, this is when I
normally eat lunch.
So I'll just tell you
Lisa is... unique.
And we're done.
All right. For some reason, square
dancing is a part of the gym curriculum.
Now, I'm gonna open the
divider to the girls' gym,
and if you don't find a dance
partner within ten seconds,
there is something
very wrong with you!
♪ ♪
Hmm.
(groans)
Aw.
That's tough luck, Lisa.
Looks like you're dancing
with Groundskeeper Willie.
Careful of your toes.
I got me cleats on!
I'll dance with Lisa.
Tumi? But you're from
the other second grade.
We only come together
for tornado drills.
(groans)
God, I hate
square dancing.
It ain't gym class
if a fat kid's not crying.
Let's do this thing.
(plucking notes)
(playing lively music)
♪ Swing your partner,
swing her hard ♪
♪ Do-si-do while I bombard ♪
Hey! Ha! Ho! Ha!
♪ Do-si-do while
I bombard ♪
♪ Oh, thank God, the
clock says 3:00 ♪
♪ 'Cause I have to take a pee. ♪
(school bell ringing)
- Finally.
- That was fun.
Yeah, it kind of was.
But I won't push it,
I promise. See ya.
Oh, wait, wait, wait. Um, I was going
to All Sales Vinyl after school.
The vintage record store?
Yeah. You want
to come with me?
At the risk of sounding like a
broken record, yes, yes, yes!
("Stolen Moments"
by Oliver Nelson playing)
(strained):
They will fit. They will fit.
(grunts)
Yes!
Hmm. Nobody likes
jazz that much.
Even the guy playing it
had to take drugs.
It's so much fun to finally have
a friend who likes the NPR show
Wait Wait... Don't Tell Me!
As much as I do.
PETER SAGAL: So, Carl Kasell, how did the
House Minority Whip do on our news quiz?
CARL KASELL: Well, Peter,
he got two out of three right,
so he wins me recording
his outgoing message.
MAN: Oh, that's okay. Really.
No, no, no. Please don't.
KASELL:
It's not optional.
(both giggling)
See, Marge?
Problems will work themselves out
if you just leave them alone.
Mm-hmm.
Want some more smoothie?
As long as you load up
on the kale and chia.
Oh, no one likes veggie
smoothies that much.
Or at all. Hmm. Something's
fishy about that girl,
and I'm gonna follow her
till I find out what.
And I'm gonna help you.
I think I'll need you back at
headquarters manning the phones.
Great. What do I say?
- Just let 'em ring.
- Got it!
♪ They smile in your face ♪
♪ All the time they want
to take your place ♪
♪ The backstabbers ♪
♪ Backstabbers ♪
♪ They smile in your face ♪
♪ All the time they want
to take your place ♪
♪ The backstabbers ♪
♪ Backstabbers ♪
♪ All you fellas
who have someone ♪
♪ And you really care ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Then it's all of you fellas... ♪
♪ Low-down, dirty. ♪
What do you want?
I've got two
things for you.
This envelope will change your life for
the low, low price of five dollars,
and I'll throw in a
piece of great advice.
Tempted?
What's the advice?
Don't open the envelope.
(snickers)
Oh, God, I'm
gonna be sick.
(gasps)
Mom paid her to
be my friend?
(crying)
That's mine. It's for
my library card.
(groans)
You don't want to be here.
(whimpers)
Neither do you!
Mom, how could you pay
someone to be my friend?
Answer me!
Oh, I wouldn't say I paid
someone to be your friend.
I just gave her money for
records and ice cream.
HOMER:
You gave away ice cream?!
I would've found
a friend eventually.
You couldn't wait a damn decade
until I got into college?
(crying)
Oh, Lisa. Lisa, wait!
Oh, God, oh, God.
I'm the smart parent.
I'm sorry she rejected
your "I'm Sorry" cake,
but, in a way, I'm not. I guess what
I'm trying to say is I like cake.
Marge, don't feel bad.
You did what any
parent would do.
No, I think I
went too far.
Let me tell you a little story about
a chubby unpopular boy named Homer.
Is that the boy you
named me after?
It is you, you idiot!
- Whoa. - Little Homer had a
devil of a time making friends.
No one wanted to
come visit him.
So I decided to take
matters into my own hands.
I paid a couple of boys,
Lenny and Carl, to make
my Homer feel loved.
A relationship I
continued to this day.
You pay Lenny and Carl
to be my friends?!
Yes, but Barney's
yours for nothing.
- Aw.
- Hmm.
Well, that makes
me feel better.
(lock clicks)
Lisa's door is unlocked!
Dad, is that story
really true?
(laughs)
I wouldn't pay ten cents to a
lion to stop him from eating you!
(groans)
Lisa, just say
something to me.
I'm gonna tell every psychiatrist
I ever go to what you did.
(voice breaking):
A mother's greatest fear.
(crying)
LISA:
Wow, I made Mom cry.
What unimaginable power.
I can use this to get
anything I want.
But right now, all I want
is for Mom to stop crying.
Mom, stop! Stop!
Stop. I'm sorry.
- Oh...
- Please stop!
(cries, snorts)
(sighs)
You're not mad anymore?
I'm fine. Fine.
It's funny, but...
hurting your feelings
made me feel better.
Mm, try to forget that.
But when I grow up,
I'll find other weird kids,
and we will have the most
intense relationships ever.
And I'll always love you.
Aw.
Happy Mother's Day.
- Mother's Day?!
- Mother's Day?! Crap!
Okay, initially I was just gonna be your
friend till I could afford a nice belt.
But I like you, Lisa, and I want
to keep being friends with you.
Great. But from now on, we have to
be totally honest with each other.
You're absolutely right.
I'm not really a vegetarian.
Have you ever
tried horse meat?
They eat it raw
in Japan, and...
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
Shh!