Come on. One more long one
and we can get this thing done.
Congratulations! It's a boy.
What?
Another boy? Plus Bart?
That's like introducing
Frankenstein to Dracula.
Or Cheney to Bush.
Or Ben Affleck to anybody.
Well, this is unorthodox,
but...
what would you think about
taking a cute baby girl instead?
Her mother died in childbirth.
The father is listed
as 10,000 lunatics,
but none of them
has shown up yet.
- Sold.
- I should warn you, however.
We ran the standard
newborn screen on her,
and she tested positive
for evil.
Still better than a boy.
Maggie darling,
these stuffed animals
are your fuzzy new friends.
And here's
baby's first music box.
The cow says...
your mother
dates jocks in hell.
Nemo's just like you.
His mommy died
at the beginning too.
Yes, she did.
Omen!
Palindrome!
Callback!
I'm beginning to wonder
if trading for this baby
of unknown origin
was the right thing to do.
Marge, I fed the baby!
The baby is making us
kill ourselves.
I thought this suicide
was just gonna be the two of us.
We'll figure it out in hell!
Oh, I must stop
this spawn of Satan.
But can I really find it
in my heart to kill a child?
I like Morrissey.
Reality bites.
Looks like I'll be digging
three graves.
Ned, stop!
It must be killed.
It bears the mark of the beast.
Sorry, not that one.
What do we do? What do we do?
Still better than a boy.
They'll never improve
on this game.
My mom won't let me
see the movie
'cause she thinks
the scientists will scare me.
We'd better go.
Parachute pants, activate.
Smell ya later.
Riding all alone
I shall get back safely...
Dang. I never get to finish
my "Safely" song.
Luann! I need extra cards
for my Rolodex!
As a yuppie,
I'm making lots more friends.
Milhouse still isn't home.
And it's 2:00 in the morning.
My Swatch watch says 7:30.
See? Squiggle hand
is just past the kissy lips.
Wait, no,
that's the zigzag hand.
The zig... The zigzag hand?!
Milhouse, where are you?
Oh, come on.
Maybe he's in this wall.
Kirk, you're going crazy.
Crazy?! Am I?!
Does this look crazy
to you, Luann?
Does this?
Your friend's bike crashed here.
We found his inhaler here.
And over here
is his final pee stain.
He did drink a lot
of New Cokes last night.
Look, what the hell year
is this anyway?
I'm really getting confused.
If Milhouse is
in another dimension,
he can communicate with us
by blinking these lights.
Come on, Milhouse.
You can do it.
Admit it. Our son is gone.
So, I can tell you.
I've been having an affair.
Is it Milhouse's
break dancing tutor?
Did you tell him yet?
Hold your horses.
Not now, Milhouse!
Mommy and Daddy
are loud talking!
Why don't you go
to your room, sweetie?
Easy on
the electric bill there, son.
Hello? Hello?
Is Lisa there?
Milhouse?
That depends.
Do you like Milhouse?
I like Milhouse,
but I don't like like Milhouse.
Wrong number!
Milhouse is alive.
I just talked to him!
I think he's in
another dimension.
This is my best game ever.
I'm not leaving till it's done.
Come on, Bart!
Fine.
You can reach
the parallel dimension
via this
sensory deprivation tank.
It requires somebody with
an extraordinary power of mind.
Glavin.
Why did you shave your head?
Was it to increase conductivity?
No, I was trying
to give myself bangs
and it got away from me.
Now let's do this thing.
I made it.
I'm in the Over Under.
Yo.
Milhouse!
You could've escaped anytime!
It felt nice to be embraced.
Okay, here's the secret.
Just hold still
and they can't see you.
See?
We are perfectly, perfectly...
I forgot we're not
supposed to talk either.
Tough luck, dude.
Oh, my God!
It's a twisted version
of reality.
It seems like someone hasn't
seen very much of season three.
How ya doin'?
Say hi to your mom.
I'd better use
my psychic powers.
I didn't know
you had psychic powers.
Girls are afraid to use them,
because then
we're called unfeminine.
We needlessly lost a lot
of good witches at Salem.
Now I have the power
to skip gym!
Boo-yeah!
- Dad?
- Quiet, sweetie.
Daddy's at work.
Mr. Burns opened a portal
to another dimension
that released a lot of monsters.
What was he looking for?
It's all part of
a secret government program
to find monsters.
A monster ate Carl,
but because Carl's inside him,
the monster's my friend.
He remembers when we were kids
and we used to go down to...
Well, they won't
bother us anymore.
You kids are safe.
But we are trapped
in this dimension forever.
Who wants a piggyback ride?
Trapped forever?
It's not so bad here.
Boy, these vines sure are good
at finding all the holes.
In the Over Under,
housing is affordable,
schools are excellent,
and you can walk to shops
and restaurants.
Does Amazon deliver here?
They have a fleet
of flying monsters.
Well, there is one thing
that's better.
At least there's no stupid...
Howdily-doodily, neighborino!
Well, sir, it's
fourth down and goal to go.
Quarterback Case Diggs
takes the ball.
Hickory dickory dock,
three ticks left on the clock.
He looks. He throws.
Intercepted!
The quarterback choked.
Choke, choke, choke!
Hot dog!
Choke!
Choke, choke, choke...
Choke, choke...!
Choke, choke, choke!
Homer Simpson,
welcome to Heaven.
Are you Saint Peter?
No, I'm Saint Greeter,
if you'll forgive the pun.
I don't forgive it.
Damn you...!
Heaven doesn't look
like I expected.
Yeah. God sold out to Google.
I really wonder
if I did the right thing.
Maybe global warming is real.
Oh, my. This is not good.
Not good!
Okay, according to this,
you're not supposed
to be here yet.
We have to send you back.
I get to see Marge again?
And eat that tub of lasagna
I have in the refrigerator?
It better still be there.
Send me back now!
Look, I would love to, okay?
But the paramedics
couldn't lift your corpse,
so they rolled it into a lake.
Pretty bloated.
Wait.
That's the before picture.
Here's the after picture.
And here's the way
after picture.
It's pretty disgusting.
You've got to get me
back to Marge.
Yeah, okay, got it, got it.
We'll disrupt the paradigm.
Homer, we're gonna put you
in the body of someone
who's supposed to die today,
and you can live as them.
Can I live
in the body of a pig?
I like the freedom
of not wearing pants.
Oh, there's a six-month
waiting list to be a pig.
I'm so sorry.
That's all?
Look, just choose
one of these, okay?
No.
Tempting, but no.
Forget it.
That's the one!
Hey, man, I've been
waiting here a long time.
Hello?
Hello, Marge.
How do you know my name?
Now, don't freak out,
but it's me, your husband Homer.
I died, and I'm inside the body
of this football player.
How could I possibly
believe that?
Because I know something about
you that no one else knows.
- What's that?
- I forget.
It's you!
Fat, fit.
Portly, sportly.
Jell-O? Hello!
Whatever body you're in,
I love the guy inside.
Oh, my God, I touched an ab.
I didn't think abs were real.
It's really weird snuggling
with the body of a man
who's married to someone else.
Not just someone,
Miss Nude Texas.
All right, Marge.
I'll find someone else's body.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, yeah.
Homie? Homie?
You ruined that body
in one night?
The funeral leftovers
were so good.
This is too creepy.
I want something else.
It's a real tragedy
more young people don't die.
Dad! You could be
Superintendent Chalmers,
my principal's boss.
Marge, what do you say?
I would like
to see Chalmers with somebody.
He's so lonely.
Boom. He's dead.
You wanted to see me, sir?
Skinner!
Because of new school rules,
from now on, Bart gets all A's.
Give yourself a purple nurple.
Purpler. Purpler.
This is pure indigo.
He said, purpler.
Yes, sir.
A toast to my new life
as public school administrator.
And now to open my paycheck
and see what I make.
Next.
This has gotten out of hand.
You're changing bodies so much,
I don't even know
who I'm married to anymore.
Oh, so that's why
I'm rooting for the apes
in Planet of the Apes.
Oh, please, just pick one man
I can be with
for the rest of my life.
He doesn't have to be perfect.
He just has to love me
like you do.
I know just the guy.
Well, I had my doubts,
but this works.
This is great.
My brain in Moe's body.
Yeah, and I'm in here.
And, Midge, I'm...
I'm very thirsty.
So, I'm the first person
to ever be fired
by the DMV for a bad attitude.
Isn't that something?
Huh? Isn't it?
I need to sneak a smoke.
I am Kang the Conqueror.
I am Selma the available.
This is so romantic.
Let me get a look at you.
Oh, you don't like what you see.
Quite the contrary.
Aah is our word
for beautiful.
Freak.
Can you turn yourself?
We're gonna make out.
Just kill me now.
What's wrong, my darling?
My sister says you just want
to eat me, or for a green card.
Or a human zoo.
Two of those are ridiculous.
Quick! Hide!
Hello. Just want you to know
we'll be dissecting you
tomorrow.
But I could teach you the secret
of clean, natural energy.
Then I'll dissect you tonight.
We have to save you!
What do you want?
How'd you like me to go to a
distant galaxy and never return?
You rang?
We've come
to get you out, my love.
Oh, we're using
the L word, huh?
Should've been a conversation,
but okay.
This thing is full of rats.
Very thoughtful.
Hold it right there, Simpson.
What are you up to?
I am, you know,
cover story,
stalling for time,
cover story, hemming, hawing,
excuse, alibi.
Promotion?
Don't shoot at the van.
Shoot at the driver.
Not my driver.
My partner Kodos will meet us
at the top of Mount Springfield.
- Partner?
- Writing partner.
They told us, if you want
to make it in showbiz,
you have to be on Earth.
Sorry I'm late.
By mistake,
I went to that other Earth
where the South
won the Civil War.
Far fewer Confederate monuments.
Kang.
I've been hit.
One moment, my love.
Nah! Nah! Missed me!
Fear not, my sultry smokestack.
I can heal you.
Maybe you should cut down
a little, dear.
For the baby.
- You mean...?
- That's right.
I'm pregnant.
Selma, no!
You two are too different.
You're a Leo,
and he's a Sagittarius.
I'm from Sagittarius.
Oh, don't go, Selma.
Please.
I can't live without you.
I have to warn you.
I'm gay.
That's all right.
I have 32 sexual identities.
I'm Klingon curious,
always up
for some Wookiee nookie
or an R2 threesome,
not to mention
some Deep Space Nine,
or possibly Jabba the Butt.
Are you enjoying
the honeymoon planet?
Why didn't we come here
in the cool season?
This is the cool season.
Shall I get a sweater
for you, dear?
It's 4,000 degrees.
Nag, nag, nag.