♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
D'oh!
-Ahh!
-(tires screech)
-GRANDPA: Are we there yet?
-HOMER: No.
-Are we there yet?
-No.
Where are we going?
We're going to Storytown
Village, Grandpa.
It's an amusement park
for babies.
Oh, just leave me in the car
with the window open a crack.
That's the plan.
I think it's nice
we're doing something
Maggie will enjoy for once.
Besides, I'm sure
Storytown Village
is also fun for everyone--
From eight to...
God only knows.
(all groaning)
(knocking)
Come out, come out,
or I'll blow your house in.
ALL: Not by the hairs
of our chinny chin chin.
What a load
of crappy crap crap.
Quiet, boy.
I have a feeling
some bad stuff
is about to go down.
This is where the wolf
blows down the pigs' house.
He blows all right.
He blows big time.
That's it, honey.
Get into the spirit.
(inhaling)
(soft puff)
Aw, it was good,
but not great.
Somebody's been
sleeping in my bed.
(distorted) Somebody's
been sleeping in my bed.
Somebody's been
sleeping in my bed.
Well, I'm sorry.
But it was 150 degrees
in the car.
♪ La, la, la, la, la
La la la ♪
So long, suck-- Aah!
(cheering)
Come on.
Eat the can.
You're supposed
to feed them pellets
from the machine
over there.
Oh, my.
ALL: Aw...
HOMER: Out of the way, you.
Aw...
Oh, you are so cute.
Yes, you are, you are.
I just love you.
(chuckling)
See? It was a good idea
to come here after all.
WOMAN (on PA):
Attention, families.
This is Mother Goose.
The following cars
have been broken into...
♪♪ (fiddle)
Hm?
FLANDERS: Allemande left and
do-si-diddley-diddley-do
swing your partner
to-and-froodilly-fro.
MAN:
All rightly, dittly!
Hey, Flanders.
ALL: Hidilly how,
neighbor-eeno!
-Shut up.
-ALL: Okaly dokaly.
So, Ned, you're having
a family reunion
and you didn't invite me?
Oh, gosh, Homer, this is
strictly a Flanders affair.
I got family here
from around the globe.
Here's Jose Flanders.
Buenos ding-dong-diddly-dias,
señor.
And this is Lord
Thistlewick Flanders.
Charmed.
Uh... A-googily-doogily.
(chuckles)
I can't believe
you didn't invite me
after I painted
those cool stripes
all over your car.
I know! I'll throw
my own barbecue.
The greatest barbecue
this town has ever seen
and I'll only
invite who I want.
That'll show you.
-Can I come?
-Sure... D'oh!
This barbecue will be
hard, thankless work
but I'm sure
you're up to it, Marge.
Well, it could be a good chance
to get to know our neighbors
outside of
a courtroom setting.
You know
what you should serve, Marge?
More of these lamb chops.
These are the best ever.
Why, thank you, Homie.
You might say
the extra ingredient is salt.
(loud chomping)
(sucking)
(bleating)
Ple-e-ease, Lisa,
I thought you lo-o-oved me,
lo-o-oved me.
What's wrong, Lisa?
Didn't you get
enough lamb chops?
I can't eat this.
I can't eat
a poor little lamb.
Lisa, get a hold of yourself.
This is "lamb",
Not "a lamb".
What's the difference
between this lamb
and the one
that kissed me?
This one spent two hours
in the broiler.
Bart, sensible bites!
All right, Lisa, if you
don't want lamb chops,
there's lots of other
things I can make:
chicken breast,
rump roast,
hot dogs?
No, I can't!
I can't eat any of them!
Wait a minute, wait a minute,
wait a minute.
Lisa, honey, are you saying
you're never going to eat
any animal again?
-What about bacon?
-No.
-Ham?
Pork chops?
Dad, those all come
from the same animal.
Yeah, right, Lisa,
a wonderful, magical animal.
(chuckling)
I think Lisa's right, Dad.
Eating meat is bah-ah-ad.
Hey, that's my chop.
(both growling)
My family just
doesn't understand
my newfound
vegetarianism.
Compared to them
the public schools are
a haven of enlightenment.
Okay, class.
Time to dissect our worms.
ALL: Yay!
First, pin them down
so they don't fly up
and hit you in the eye.
(muffled)
Um, Miss Hoover?
Yes, Ralph,
what is it?
My worm went in my mouth
and then I ate it.
Can I have a new one?
No, Ralph.
There aren't any more.
Just try to sleep while
the other children are learning.
Oh, boy, sleep.
That's where I'm a viking.
LAMB'S VOICE: Lisa,
what did I ever
do to y-y-you?
Why does it talk
like a lamb?
(whimpering)
Uh, Miss Hoover, I don't think
I can dissect an animal.
I think it's wrong.
Okay, Lisa. I respect
your moral objection.
Um, excuse me.
Isn't there anything here
that doesn't have meat in it?
Possibly the meat loaf.
Well, I believe
you're required to provide
a vegetarian alternative.
Yum. It's rich
in bunnly goodness.
Do you remember when you lost
your passion for this work?
(buzzing)
Uh-oh. Two independent
thought alarms in one day.
The students are overstimulated.
Willie, remove all the colored chalk
from the classrooms.
I warned you!
Didn't I warn you?
That colored chalk
was forged by Lucifer himself.
♪ The Itchy
& Scratchy show ♪
Hee hee hee.
(laughing)
I never realized before,
but some
"Itchy & Scratchy" cartoons
send the message that violence
against animals is funny.
Say what?
Cartoons don't
have messages, Lisa.
They're just a bunch
of hilarious stuff
you know, like people getting
hurt and stuff--
Stuff like that.
Oh!
Look, kids.
I just got my party invitations
back from the printer's.
(reading)
-What's that extra "B" For?
-That's a typo.
Dad, can't you have
some other kind of party--
one where you
don't serve meat?
But all normal people
love meat.
If I went to a barbecue
and there was no meat
I would say, "Yo, goober,
where's the meat?"
I'm trying to impress
people here, Lisa.
You don't win friends
with salad.
(conga beat)
♪ You don't win friends with salad ♪
♪ You don't win friends
with salad ♪
♪ You don't win
friends with salad ♪
♪ You don't win friends
with salad ♪
♪ You don't win
friends with salad ♪
♪ You don't win friends
with salad ♪
♪ You don't win
friends with salad ♪
♪ You don't win friends
with salad ♪
♪ You don't win
friends with salad ♪
Mom!
I didn't mean to take sides.
I just got caught up
in the rhythm.
Good morning, class.
A certain agitator--
for privacy's sake,
let's call her Lisa S.
No, that's too obvious.
Let's say L. Simpson--
has raised questions
about certain school policies.
So in the interest of
creating an open dialogue,
sit silently
and watch this film.
Nothing beats a stroll
in cattle country.
Hi. I'm Troy McClure.
You may remember me from
such educational films as
"Two Minus Three
Equals Negative Fun!"
And "Firecrackers:
The Silent Killer."
BOY: Mr. McClure?
-Oh, Hello, Bobby.
-Jimmy.
I'm curious as to how meat
gets from the ranch
to my stomach.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
slow down, Jimmy.
You just asked
a mouthful.
It all starts here in
the high-density feed lot.
Then when the cattle
are just right...
Mmm...
It's time for them
to graduate
from Bovine University.
(buzzer)
Come on, Jimmy.
Let's take a peek
at the killing floor.
(gasps)
Don't let the name
throw you, Jimmy.
It's not really a floor.
It's more of a steel grating
that allows material
to sluice through so it can
be collected and exported.
(cows screaming)
Getting hungry, Jimmy?
Uh, Mr. McClure,
I have a crazy friend
who says
it's wrong to eat meat.
Is he crazy?
No, just ignorant.
You see,
your crazy friend
never heard
of the "food chain".
Just ask this scientician.
Um...
He'll tell you that in nature
one creature invariably
eats another to survive.
(roaring)
(eagle screeches,
sheep bleats)
(growls)
Don't kid yourself, Jimmy.
If a cow ever got
the chance
he'd eat you and
everyone you care about.
Wow, Mr. McClure,
I was a grade-A moron
to ever question eating meat.
Yes, you were, Jimmy.
Yes, you were.
Ow. You're hurting me.
(mooing)
They can't seriously expect us
to swallow that tripe.
Now, as a special treat courtesy
of our friends at the Meat Council,
please help yourselves
to this tripe.
(cheering)
Stop it!
Don't you realize
you've just been brainwashed
by corporate propaganda?
Apparently my crazy friend here
hasn't heard of the food chain.
Yeah, Lisa's
a grade-A moron.
When I grow up, I'm going
to Bovine University.
Hi, Homer.
Thanks for inviting me
to your barbecue.
Wow, Barney, you brought
a whole beer keg.
Yeah, where can
I fill it up?
Wait, Dad.
Good news, everyone.
You don't have to eat meat.
I made enough gazpacho for all.
(all murmuring)
What is that anyway?
It's tomato soup
served ice cold.
(laughing)
BARNEY: Go back to Russia.
Ah, diagnosis: Delicious.
I've got the prescription
for you, doctor.
Another hot beef
injection.
(laughing)
Hey, Homer, wing me another
one of them, uh...
burgers, would you?
Can't quite seem to... stand up
under my own power anymore.
One whopper for the copper.
Can I have a burger, Dad?
Here you go!
It's bad enough
they're all eating meat.
They don't have
to rub it in my face.
Ah!
Okay, everybody,
it's the moment
you've all been waiting for...
the pig de resistance.
ALL: Ooh!
Ah!
(laughing)
Look at his nose.
Congratulations, Homer.
Your Q's a huge success.
A toast to the host who
can boast the most roast.
(chuckles)
Thanks, Flanders.
I have to agree
that everything certainly--
Huh?
(gasping)
Bart, no!
What?
Sorry. Force of habit.
Lisa, no!
Ah! Oh!
(groaning)
It's just a little dirty.
It's still good.
(honking)
It's just a little slimy.
It's still good.
It's just
a little airborne.
It's still good.
-It's gone.
-I know.
You know, Smithers,
I think I'll donate
a million dollars
to the local orphanage...
when pigs fly.
(both laughing)
That's a good one.
Will you be donating that
million dollars now, sir?
No, I'd still prefer not.
Give it up, Dad--
Piggy ain't coming back.
Lisa, you ruined
my barbecue.
I demand you apologize
this second.
I'm never ever apologizing
because I was standing up
for a just cause
and you were wrong,
wrong, wrong!
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm going to my room.
That's it!
Go to your room!
Marge, since I'm not
talking to Lisa,
would you please ask her
to pass me the syrup?
Please pass your father
the syrup, Lisa.
Bart, tell Dad I'll
only pass the syrup
if it won't be used
on any meat product.
You dunking your sausages
in that syrup, homeboy?
Marge, tell Bart
I just want to drink
a nice glass of syrup
like I do every morning.
Tell him yourself.
You're ignoring Lisa,
not Bart.
Bart, thank your mother
for pointing that out.
Homer, you're not
not talking to me
and secondly, I heard
what you said.
Lisa, tell your mother
to get off my case.
Dad, Lisa's the one
you're not talking to.
Bart, go to your room.
Why don't you
just eat him, Dad?
I don't need any serving
suggestions from you
you barbecue-wrecking,
know-nothing know-it-all.
That's it!
I can't live in a house
with this
prehistoric carnivore!
I am out of here!
That's it!
Go to your room!
Look, it's Mrs. Potato head.
She has a head
made out of lettuce.
(both laughing)
I can't believe I used
to go out with you.
Are you gonna marry
a carrot, Lisa?
Yes, I'm gonna
marry a carrot.
She admitted it.
She admitted she's gonna
marry a carrot.
I can't believe it.
...your windows.
Mmm! The next--
The whole world wants me
to eat meat.
I can't fight it anymore.
(gasping)
(gulps)
There!
Is everybody happy now?!
I take it from you're yelling
that you like my tofu dogs.
-Tofu?
-Oh, yes.
No meat whatsoever,
and only thrice the fat
of a normal hot dog.
I made the switch
and nobody noticed.
But why, Apu?
Because I'm a vegetarian.
Haven't you ever seen
my T-shirt?
That's cute.
Here, let me show you
something, Lisa.
Wow. A secret staircase.
But what do you do if somebody
wants a non-alcoholic beer?
You know,
it's never come up.
LISA:
Oh, Apu, it's beautiful.
Yes, this is where I come
when I need some refuge
from the modern world
or when I want to see
drive-in movies for free.
I know it is not easy to be
a vegetarian, Lisa.
That's why I ran away
from home.
What? She's leaving home?
Wow. Paul McCartney.
I read about you
in history class
but where's your wife,
Linda?
Right here, Lisa.
Whenever we're in Springfield,
we like to hang out in Apu's
garden in the shade.
We met him in India years ago,
during the Maharishi days.
Back then, I was
known as the fifth Beatle.
Sure you were, Apu.
You know what, Lisa?
Paul and Linda
are vegetarians too.
In fact, Linda has her own
line of vegetarian entrees.
Apu, I'm sure the last thing
they want to talk about is--
We weren't satisfied
with the other
vegetarian meals
on the market.
You'd be surprised how often
you'd find a big hunk
of pork in them.
Ew.
Linda and I both
feel strongly
about animal rights.
In fact, if you play
"Maybe I'm Amazed" backwards,
you'll hear a recipe
for a really ripping
lentil soup.
When will
all those fools learn
that you can be
perfectly healthy
simply eating vegetables,
fruits, grains, and cheese?
Ooh! Cheese.
You don't eat cheese, Apu?
No, I don't eat any food
that comes from an animal.
Oh, then you must
think I'm a monster.
Yes, indeed,
I do think that.
But I learned long ago, Lisa,
to tolerate others
rather than forcing
my beliefs on them.
You know, you can
influence people
without badgering them
always.
It's like Paul's song,
"Live and Let Live."
Actually, it was
"Live and Let Die."
Whatever, whatever,
it had a good rhythm.
I guess I have been pretty hard
on a lot of people,
especially my dad.
Thanks, you guys.
Lisa, before you go,
would you
like to hear a song?
Wow! That'd be great!
Okay. Take it, Apu.
♪ I'm Sergeant Pepper's
Lonely Hearts Club, man ♪
♪ I hope I will enjoy
my show... ♪
Lisa!
Lisa! Come back before
everyone finds out
what a horrible father I am.
Hi, Dad. Looking for me?
I don't know.
Are you looking for me?
Oh, Lisa...
I was looking for you.
I wanted to apologize.
I don't know exactly
what went wrong
but I know
it's always my fault.
Actually, Dad, this time,
I was wrong...
(gasps)
-Too.
-Oh.
While I was gone, I got
some really good advice
from Paul
and Linda McCartney.
Rock stars-- Is there
anything they don't know?
I still stand
by my beliefs
but I can't defend
what I did.
I'm sorry
I messed up your barbecue.
I understand, honey.
I used to believe in things
when I was a kid.
Come on, I'll give you
a piggyback ride--
Whoops, I mean
a veggie-back ride home.
Come on.
(both giggling)
♪ Baby, I'm amazed at the way
you love me all the time ♪
♪ And maybe I'm afraid
of the way I love you ♪
♪ Maybe I'm amazed at the way
you pulled me out of time ♪
♪ You hung me on the line ♪
♪ Maybe I'm amazed at the way
I really need you ♪
(McCartney
speaking backwards)
♪ Baby, I'm a man,
maybe, I'm a lonely man ♪
♪ Who's in the middle
of something ♪
(McCartney
speaking backwards)
♪ That he doesn't
really understand ♪
(McCartney
speaking backwards)
♪ Baby, I'm a man,
and maybe ♪
♪ You're the only woman
who could ever help me ♪
♪ Baby, won't you help me
to understand? ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh
ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
(McCartney
speaking backwards)
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.