Stick close by, kids,
and I'll explain everything
you need to know
about the briny deep.
I want to see a giant squid
attack a sperm whale
and battle to the death.
I want to swim free
with the fishes.
I brought
my lucky red swim trunks.
All right, can the chatter
and listen up.
Here we have
the hideous moray eel.
And over here, we have the tasty
but repulsive sea bass.
Yuck! What the hell is that?
- Bart!
- Come on in.
The water's fine.
Boy, you come out of that tank
right now!
Do some tricks, Bart.
Stop that.
It only encourages him.
Dad, you got to see this!
The Simpsons
The Simpso...
Oh, not again!
I nailed it.
I have tears in my eyes,
like when I saw David
Attenborough's Blue Planet.
Did you really watch them all?
Well, most of the first one.
- Lisa?
- Yes, Mr. Largo?
- I just want to say...
- And I just want to listen.
I'm a tuna!
You really should give up
the saxophone.
What?!
Oh, I know. I know.
You're fabulous.
Well, then I shouldn't
give it up.
I mean, what would you say
if I said
you had to give up
teaching music?
I'd say, Hallelujah!
I could go back to my first
love, not teaching music.
We can't do the couch gag.
When is Lisa gonna get here?
Worry about yourself.
Why would you ask me
to give up the saxophone?
Lisa, sweetie, I'm afraid
this world is filled
with Lisa Simpsons.
Bright, talented
and doomed to disappointment.
What you're saying is horrible.
It's horrible.
Mr. Largo,
what is going on here?
I'm trying
to encourage a student
to give up on her dreams!
You're crushing it
as always, Dewey.
I'll take it from here.
Now, Lisa,
this is for your own good.
For every Yo-Yo Ma,
there's a million Ma-Ma Yos.
And for every Shaun White,
there are a million
White Shauns.
And for every Albert Einstein,
there are a million
Herman Schmidbergs.
Okay, so maybe
I'll never be great,
but shouldn't I try?
No.
Sleeping people are my canvas.
That's some cutting satire,
Simpson.
Yeah. Check out Bill Maher
over here.
Ay, caramba!
Let's see. Little Bo Peep?
That'll traumatize him good.
Oh, I got it, the perfect one.
No, not that.
Anything but that!
Oh, thanks for your input.
I'll try to come up
with an alternative.
Put it on.
Get in there.
Sing like we rehearsed!
The sun'll come out
tomorrow...
More pep!
Bet your bottom dollar
that tomorrow
There'll be sun!
Sing until food fills
your mouth!
Tomorrow, tomorrow
I love ya tomorrow!
You're always a day away
Now get the Wite-Out.
Leapin' lizards!
He's right.
I know it's true. I always have.
Honey, ignore everyone,
and listen to someone objective,
your mother.
You're great!
It's too late.
I'm quitting music.
There's a microscope
in there too.
You can sell it.
Don't give up your dream.
When I was little, I dreamed
about marrying a dashing prince,
and it actually happened!
You were married before Dad?
No! I mean your father.
My father.
So that's Homer, or...
There's no or!
You can't let someone else's
opinion tear you down.
I want to hear your sweet music,
so suck it in
and get downstairs right now!
You're the best.
Herman Schmidberg!
For the love of jazz?
I can't play! I just can't!
It's in my head,
but my hands won't do it!
What's with her?
I'm suffering from beer-tigo!
You don't have to worry
about what's wrong with you.
Just find out whatever it is,
and you can fix it.
ADHD? No, that's Bart.
OCD? No, that's Mom.
This one's Dad. This one's Dad.
What is the name
when you can't perform something
that you've practiced four times
a week since you were three?!
The yips,
named for Dr. Augustus Yip.
A mysterious
psychological condition
where well-rehearsed skills
suddenly become impossible.
Like all mental disorders,
the yips are likely incurable.
Oh, for God's sake.
The yips. I have the yips!
Bart, what happened
to your pupils?
They're Annie'd, okay?
Lisa, you want
to play some more?
No!
Lisa, honey, are you okay?
You barely touched
your green disgustos.
Some nights, there's isn't
enough kale in the world
to brighten a girl's mood.
Oh, that's a good one!
- Don't you dare.
- Okay.
I have some news.
My great half step-aunt
Eunice Bouvier
is turning 100 years old,
and she wants us there.
Is this the aunt
who lives in Florida?
It's not just Florida.
It's Gainesville!
I only have two weeks vacation,
and I have to spend 'em
in Dullsville?
Gainesville.
If we have time,
we'll take a day trip
to Dullsville.
It's my turn
to pick the vacation!
Also, she loves music,
so I'm sure she'd like
Lisa to play for her.
Stop it!
Fine.
The Simpsons are going to...
Oh, I can't say it.
Gainesville.
I was born
in Gainesville, Florida
And my father
Was a tailor
And my mother
Ran a cafe
Near the university
Takeoff is
the most perilous phase
of air travel.
If you're gonna crash,
that's when it happens.
Wait. Am I on mic?
Yes, Frank.
Folks,
you were just listening
to a new play I wrote,
Death at 600 Feet.
Yeah.
I don't think
that's making it better.
Well, thank you for the note,
Scott Rudin.
I'm sorry to announce
that all our TVs are out.
But you're welcome to read
our in-flight magazine,
featuring an interview
with our CEO, Hanuki Atanawa.
Maybe we'll have
one of those passenger riots
that seem to occur every
other day on U.S. airlines.
- Could I get another seat?
- No, absolutely not!
You chose
an economy modest ticket.
Please! They're both farting!
All it would take
is a single spark
to set this powder keg off.
Hey, hey, TWA!
How many flights
did you cancel today?!
Hey, hey, TWA!
Folks,
I'm afraid due to turbulence
among the passengers, we are
gonna have to land immediately.
Looks like we will not
be going to Gainesville.
It is pretty great, isn't it?
Our new destination is,
let's see...
New Orleans!
It's a miracle! Everyone wins!
Happy birthday to me
Look, Lisa! Isn't that nice?
The sign's telling you
to celebrate!
What are you celebrating?
Humidity at a 98%.
Don't they sound great?
Yep. More musicians
better than me.
Oh, boy.
You're good at cheering her up.
I'll take Bart.
Whoop-de-do.
Well, I appreciate
you choosing me, Dad,
but I don't know
how much fun I'll be.
I think I can
cheer my princess up.
- I don't think you can.
- Oh, I think I can.
I'm a pretty tough nut.
Well, if you're a nut,
I will crack you up.
Not with puns, I'm afraid.
- Yes, I can.
- No, really.
- You like puns.
- No, I don't.
I said cheer up!
That kind of scares me.
- Scary eek or scary ha ha?
- Why would you say that?
There is no scary ha ha.
- Yes, there is.
- No, there isn't.
- What about scary clowns?
- Nobody likes scary clowns!
- Go to your room!
- I'm in New Orleans!
That's your answer
to everything!
Did you know that a man
can fall in love with a city?
It happens slowly at first.
Then when you develop a crush,
you find your love
just grows and grows.
If you like, you can take
that drink on the street.
Even Bourbon Street?
Oh, I'm out.
Enjoy.
And then you discover
a thousand little things
you love about the city.
Cajun crawfish.
Lamb tagine.
Grilled lamb sausage.
Zucchini bisque.
Crabmeat po'boy.
Duck po'boy.
Chicken sausage po'boy.
Crawfish sausage po'boy.
Cochon de lait po'boy.
Turkey giardiniera po'boy.
Roast beef po'boy.
Alligator po'boy.
Catfish amandine.
Crawfish amandine.
Crawfish étouffée.
Boiled crawfish.
Cajun crawfish.
Cajun shrimp and duck pasta.
Fried crab cake.
Pecan catfish.
Blackened redfish.
Seafood mirliton casserole.
Fried chicken.
Fried green tomatoes.
Stuffed shrimp. Muffuletta.
Barbecue brisket sandwich.
Barbecue chicken sandwich.
Smoky bacon greens.
Seafood au gratin.
Seafood gumbo. Frogs' legs.
There's also a lot
of historical sites.
Chicken gumbo.
Jambalaya.
Spinach artichoke.
Creole sweet potato pone.
Red beans and rice
with sausage.
Veggie red beans and rice.
Pralines in cookies.
Oyster pralines.
Oyster shots.
Oyster patties.
Bananas Foster.
King cake. Dixie cake.
Pecan pie.
Cajun boudin.
Boudin balls.
Crawfish rémoulade.
Shrimp and lump crabmeat
ravigote.
Au croissant crawfish po'boy.
And yaka mein.
Yeah.
Okay, sweetie, Daddy's in love.
So now we'll deal
with your sadness.
Okay. It's good
to see you happy, Dad.
Hold that thought.
My good boy,
is there a vomitorium?
This town is famous
for five vomitoria.
The elegant Creole Vomitorium,
the Blues Vomitorium,
the traditional
Heritage Vomitorium,
the Upchuck Mangione Museum,
and the bucket over
at Chartres Street.
Alert them all.
Would you like to look
at historic homes
in the Garden District?
Historic? Homes?
Garden? District?
Which of those words
do you think appeals to me?
Okay. We could talk
about your hat.
It has a lot of history too.
Did you know that it...
All right, wise guy.
Here's something you'll like.
Cool. I always read better
when the letters
are dripping like blood.
Bart, you go in there,
and I'll pray for you in here.
Please, Lord, please.
I need to finish this, okay?
All day, you had.
Please, Lord.
We're a family on a budget.
We just need a little relief
from our demons, please.
Where are we?
I smell Pringles.
You'll pay.
You'll all pay!
Mom, will you pay for this?
Now, sweetie,
let's find a restaurant for you.
I don't think
my problem can be solved
by crawfish and jambalaya.
I wonder, do they have jazz
in New Orleans?
Okay, Lisa,
look at your hero for an hour.
I'm gonna take a whiz
in the cemetery next door.
Okay, who to choose?
Who to choose?
Ooh, Etienne de Boré.
I wish you could talk.
Man, I have been waiting
for someone to make that wish.
What's on your mind?
My music teacher says
there'll always be
someone better than me.
Well, that's not the only way
to be part of jazz.
Well, I could be a jazz critic
or a music executive.
Jazz critic? Music executive?
They're nothing
but glorified grave robbers.
Look what I found
in one of the graves.
Put that back!
Lisa, darling,
you just keep searching.
You can find anything you want
in New Orleans.
Except, apparently,
statue polish and pigeon poison.
Thank you. And may I ask you,
how are things in heaven?
You know that thing
we used to call reefer
and you people
now call medicine?
I do.
Well, they have it up in heaven,
and it is mighty fine.
Mighty fine!
So, any last advice?
Your father knows best.
Let's go to a bar.
- But...
- Daddy's right.
Can I sing you out?
Anything but,
What a Wonderful World, please.
Can you sing,
What a Wonderful World?
What a horrible world.
Okay, I moved her
from crying to glum.
Now to shoot for happy.
I just pray they don't
see through her fake ID.
Well, it's better than his.
Milhouse, anything yet?
No effect.
But how's Lisa dealing
with her depression?
Oh, give up on Lisa.
Wait for Maggie.
Oh, I don't...
Wait! Maggie likes me?
Still not working.
What's not working?
Bart's got voodoo dolls
of all you guys.
There's no voodoo
in Gainesville.
Their flight got diverted
to New Orleans.
You hackeyed the wrong sack!
It's working!
So, has Maggie said
anything about me?
We have a lot in common.
Same bedtime.
We both like clapping.
Come on, we've got to go
meet your father.
Let's go.
Well, there's no miracle
for me here.
Why?
Don't worry, sweetie.
No one can see you.
You're alone in the dark,
anonymous.
- Spotlight?!
- What?!
Lisa, would you do us the honor
of joining us onstage?
How do you know me?
That man is my uncle.
Bleeding Gums Murphy?
- We called him Oscar.
- Oscar!
Oscar Gums Murphy.
You still play bari sax?
I wish I could play for you,
Bleeding Gums' nephew,
but I have the yips.
Oh, that's too bad.
Well, could you hold this
while I play clarinet?
Now, could you give
the mouthpiece a little kiss?
I think I see through
your simple plan.
My uncle said you were the most
promising young musician
- he'd ever met.
- He did?
It was kind of
an insult to me,
but he was
pretty passive-aggressive.
So, are you gonna play?
Yes! I want to jam!
I want to scat! I want to riff!
I want to get down!
She's playing.
You did it, Homie!
Marge, I just realized,
we've helped everyone else,
but we haven't done
anything for you.
A mother's happy as long as
all her children are happy.
Another one, sir?
No, that's not my... Yeah.
This one straight up.
Lisa, knock off that racket!
Oh, how I've missed this.
Mr. Armstrong!
- Why does a ghost sweat?
- I don't know.
But I would give anything
for a new shirt.
I'd also really like
to be alive again.
The beignet eliminates
the only flaw of the donut.
There is no hole.
Well, we did it, kids.
And the best thing is,
the next episode
will beat Gunsmoke.
What about all the episodes
they made on radio?
Have a beignet.