(SlNGlNG) The Simpsons
(TlRES SCREECHlNG)
D'oh !
(SCREAMlNG)
(BRAKES SCREECHlNG)
Homie, what are
you doing?
l'm changing
the batteries
in all the remotes.
We're all out
of triple A's so l'm gonna
whittle down
a couple of these D's.
(ELECTRlClTY CRACKLlNG)
You're getting
acid in the bed.
l'm gonna sleep
on the couch.
(DOOR BANGS SHUT)
She sure loves
that couch.
BART: lt's the World
Series of kickball,
Bart Simpson on the mound.
The catcher gives
him the signal.
Mmm-hmm.
And here's the pitch.
(GRUNTS)
(WHlSTLlNG)
Oh, my God !
l've shredded a child !
Again !
(YELLlNG)
Venezuela, here l come!
SEYMOUR: And whiIe
the schooI's onIy baII
is being repaired,
the foIIowing
aIternative sports
will be offered.
Dodge-rock,
voIIey-brick and base-game.
l want to play
dodge-rock.
NELSON: You're out!
SEYMOUR: FinaIIy,
on a personaI note,
Mrs. KrabappeI and I
are to be joined in hoIy
wedlock this Saturday.
We'II be honeymooning
at Lake Shelbyville Lodge,
cabin 32, room three.
And we do not
wish to be disturbed.
Way to go, Mrs. K.
You finally hooked
the Skin-fish.
lt looks good.
But l'm not gonna celebrate
till he's gaffed,
gutted, and hanging
in my trophy room. Hah !
We have
the same dream, ma'am.
(lN A MECHANlCAL VOlCE)
My Bonnie
lies over the ocean
lies over the sea
(CHUCKLlNG)
All right, we got
Sex With an Alligator,
Screaming Orgasms,
and Virgin Screaming
Orgasms.
Oh, sexy drinks,
adult board games.
l'm glad l sent
the kids to Grampa's
to protect their
innocent minds.
And here's some
more Germans we killed.
That flamethrower
really toasted
their waffles.
BOTH: Ugh !
Grampa, how do
you sleep at night?
They drug us.
lt's another pair
of edible panties.
(ALL GlGGLlNG)
Now, that's sexual.
(SLURPlNG NOlSlLY)
Homer, this bachelor party
seems to have peaked.
Could you please
return my pants
and/or underpants
so l can go home?
Come on, it's your
last night of freedom.
You gotta have some fun.
Who are all
of you people?
We're your buddies.
Now come on,
Homer's kid's principal,
have a beer.
l can't. l might be
called upon to give
directions later.
Skinner!
You were asked to
chug-a-lug. And a-lug
you shall chug.
(PANTlNG)
Here's something l've
wanted to say to you
for a long time!
Am l a good principal?
You're the best
we could get with
the funds at our disposal.
Yeah !
(ALL CHEERlNG)
Delivering these
ice cold Lady Duffs
has made me hot!
Really hot!
(UPBEAT MUSlC PLAYlNG)
Come on, Duffman !
Thirty bucks an hour!
Oh, yeah !
DUFFMAN: Oh, yeah.
(DOORBELL RlNGS)
Sorry to bother you
but we got
an anonymous tip
about loud music and
"a strip-da-diddily-dipper."
Oh. . . Look, girls.
A policeman is here.
We've been
awfully naughty.
You better lay
down the law.
(UPBEAT MUSlC RESUMES)
(ALL CHEERlNG)
Ladies, ladies,
l really am a cop.
Oh, is that a five?
Well, this uniform
is a little snug.
(WOMEN CATCALLlNG)
Oh, yeah !
Eddie, Lou, how about
a little backup here?
Like what you see,
ladies? All right!
CLANCY: Oh, yeah !
(GROANS)
Okay! Can we. . .
l think l threw
my back out.
(GULPlNG)
l wish l had an exciting
life like that class
picture photographer.
Whoa! How many
women has he had
in that van?
Two that
l know of.
Let's kick this up
a notch and get you some
wiggle in your lap.
Oh, yeah.
No. Absolutely no
friction dancing.
(GROANlNG) Come on !
Why, you killjoy?
Wussy!
Grinch !
Hey, take it
easy on Skinner.
He's just down
'cause after tomorrow,
everything he does
is wrong.
Oh, marriage is
gonna be great.
Now you'll have someone
who'll rub your back
without being asked.
Ugh ! Not this again.
Yes, this again.
You know, Homer,
Edna was bugging me and
bugging me to set a date.
And l picked one
that seemed far away.
And it zoomed
up like a Junebug
flying in my windshield.
What are you trying
to tell me, Skinner?
(SLURRlNG) Homer, Lenny,
my man,
l could never lie
to you guys.
l'm. . . l'm starting
to get cold feet.
Please don't
tell anyone.
Don't worry.
Your secret's
safe with me.
Marge, guess what?
Skinner wants to
bail on his wedding !
Homer, you're still
talking to me.
Oh, man, is this awkward.
l'm out of here.
(GROANS)
Principal Skinner is
having second thoughts?
Poor Edna.
Yeah, Marge.
lt looks like you got
the last perfect man.
Oh, by the way,
can l borrow your
car tomorrow?
Mine's acting up.
(MARGE GASPlNG)
(GRUMBLES)
Every day you find
a new way
to aggravate me!
Hey! You're the one
always bugging me
to screw up our marriage!
Spice up!
Whatever. The important
thing is to get Skinner
to that altar.
Because once
a union has been
sanctified by God,
it takes at least
six months to
tear it apart.
Right, naked Duffman?
Hmm? Oh. . .
Oh, yeah !
(MELLOW MUSlC PLAYlNG)
(PLAYlNG SCOTTlSH TUNE)
l think Skinner
might make
a run for it.
He's eyeing
the exits and doing
calf stretches.
Don't worry.
l got a man
on the perimeter.
BART: Cowabunga One
to Fat Load.
This is Fat Load.
l'd like to request
a new code name.
BART: Denied.
Okay, Fat Load here.
Here comes the bride.
Repeat. Here comes the bride.
Mrs. K, you look awesome.
Thank you, Otto.
That cloud looks awesome.
That rock looks awesome.
My hands look awesome.
(PLAYlNG WEDDlNG MARCH
DlSCORDANTLY)
Hey, champ,
ready to take
the plunge?
You know l'm not.
We had a long
discussion about that
where l clearly indicated
the coldness of my feet.
Happy 50th anniversary,
Seymour.
l was thinking it might
be time to combine
our CD collections.
l don't know, Edna.
l'm not quite ready
to take that plunge.
Seymour, my larval
sac fell in the toilet!
Go fish it out!
Quick, Edna.
l'll use your
purse as a scoop.
Well, this is it, Edna.
As l once said at
the Battle of Khe Sanh,
"l surrender."
We are gathered
together today
to join
Seymour and Edna
in holy matrimony.
Does anyone present
know any reason
why these two
should not be wed?
l do.
(ALL GASPlNG)
No. You say
that part later.
l'm sorry, Seymour.
l can't marry
someone who doesn't
want to be with me.
(SOBBlNG)
We got a runner!
Snipers, take your shot!
l can't do it!
That dress is
a Vera Wang !
Edna!
Mmm.
(SNlFFlNG)
ls this corn oil?
Canola.
He drove her
to it, you know?
She was only doing
it for the appliances.
He's a she!
She's a he!
They're both both !
(LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
l'm afraid Edna has
gone from tardy to absent.
(CHUCKLlNG NERVOUSLY)
So let's move on
to the reception
and forget this awkwardness
with some delicious
shrimp mocktail.
Principal Skinner,
l feel so bad for you.
Well, in retrospect,
l could've been
a little more
"into" the whole thing.
(SlNGlNG) Just the two of us
BuiIding castIes in the sky
(SlGHlNG)
Just the Two of Us.
l spent $1 5 on
those dance lessons.
Might as well use them.
Forward, side, together.
Back, side, together.
This is so sad.
Yeah, he's crazy
all right.
EDNA: All right, students.
What is the center
of the circulatory system?
lt's the heart.
The heart?
You mean like
Principal Skinner's,
which you broke?
What do you care?
You hate Principal Skinner.
Meh. Bro's before ho's.
Nelson !
l'll see you
after class.
l'll be there.
Will you?
(BELL RlNGlNG)
Mom, what are you doing here?
Did our house burn down?
That'd be cool.
No. l'm here to
have a little girl
talk with Mrs. Krabappel.
So how are
you holding up?
Actually, l feel fine.
Why should l settle
for someone who's not
passionate about me?
Oh, passion's for
teens and immigrants.
l'm just glad to have
someone to look at when
l wake up in the morning.
Really?
Well. . .
Un-kink the hose.
(GRUMBLES)
Sure there are
downsides.
But a relationship can't
be all hand-holding
and restaurant desserts.
Why not?
lf l can't have
romance and excitement,
then what's the point
of being married?
Well, it's. . .
ln my case. . .
Hmm.
Oh, God, l've lost
the love of my life.
(SlGHlNG)
Bart's right,
l am a wiener.
(SOBBlNG)
Geez, Homer,
this guy's bringing
the whole bar down.
l finally got
Barney back
on the sauce.
lf he doesn't have fun,
he could easily slip
right back into sobriety.
(SLURRlNG)
Don't worry.
lf l feel the urge
to sober up,
l'll just talk
to my sponsor.
Drink or l'll die!
Wait a minute.
l thought you didn't
want to get married.
That was before
l missed her smell,
her warmth,
her beautiful,
beautiful penmanship.
Don't worry,
Principal Skinner.
Seymour.
Really? Boy,
it sucks to be you.
Mmm.
Anyhoo, if there's one thing
l know, it's how to win
back a furious woman.
We'll go to her house
and l'll whisper to
you exactly what to say.
Really? You'll be
my Cyrano?
Hey, if we get
your girlfriend back,
l won't have to.
Okay, just repeat
after me,
"Edna, l made a huge
mistake and l want
you back."
Edna, l made a huge
mistake and l want
you back!
How's that, Homer?
Mmm-hmm.
Oh, God, it's Seymour!
What do l say?
You just say. . .
lt's too late.
l'm free and loving it,
Principal Skinner.
Now tell her. . .
(WHlSPERlNG)
Every second without you
is like a million
kicks in the crotch !
Oh, that's so lovely.
But it's too late
to win us back
with sweet talk!
What the. . .
Marge, are you
helping her?
l won't let Edna
throw her life away for
some passionless marriage
where two people
lie in bed together
with no contact,
whittling away
the batteries
until they die!
Which are you
saying is dead?
Our marriage
or our batteries?
Let's just say
in an emergency,
l wouldn't count
on either one!
Homer, Marge,
if l could just speak
to Edna for a moment. . .
Shut up! l didn't
tell you to say that.
Just why am l
taking your advice?
Because l'm
successfully married.
There's no ring
on that finger.
Uh-oh !
Oh, why did l
take it off?
Oh, right.
To see if l could skip it
across Lake Michigan.
l'm here to return
the gift you brought
to our wedding.
Ah ! Yes. An lncredible
Hulk melonballer.
(ROARlNG)
Well, l'm glad
you'll be able
to enjoy it.
l think you did
the right thing.
You didn't want your life
to turn out like this.
(CHUCKLlNG)
Oh, you're cute.
ls there
a Mrs. Comic Book Guy?
Well, l was married
once in an online
fantasy game.
We were thinking
of having children,
but that would have
severely drained
my power crystals.
(GlGGLlNG)
Stop it,
you big kidder.
(CHUCKLlNG)
Yes, "Kidder."
Would you like to
get some coffee?
And a family
bucket of chicken.
We've made it to my car
and you haven't left.
A new record.
Oh, l love your
black tinted windows.
Actually, they are
trash bags.
Now could you give
me a pushing start?
(VlOLlNS PLAYlNG)
String quartet,
are you tuned up?
As tuned as
we're gonna get
in this humidity.
And the castrati?
The what now?
And a one,
and a two,
and a. . .
(SlNGlNG) Oh, Edna-K,
oh, Edna-K,
oh, Edna-K
Oh, Edna-K,
oh, Edna-K,
oh, Edna-K
Oh, Edna-K,
Miss KrabappeI,
a sad principaI
is desperate and needy
If you come home,
l won't die alone
and that's what I'd prefer
Oh, please
Settle for Seymour
So please
Come back to the dork
Well, if it isn't
the square in our
love triangle.
What are you doing
at Edna's place?
Where is she?
My beloved is
napping blissfully
in the many folds
of my Spider-Man T-shirt.
As for myself,
l am popping
kettle corn.
This can't
be happening !
Oh, but it can.
l adore Edna.
She is near mint
and comes from
a very limited edition.
Females who will
talk to me.
Give her back
to Skinner!
A fat, bald guy
like you, you could
have anyone!
Forget you !
Edna and l
are in love.
We're doing
everything together.
Breakfast, bath,
and then the Bi-Monthly
Science Fiction Convention.
Enjoy me.
The Bi-Mon Sci-Fi Con?
You've heard of it?
ls it romantic?
Hey, women have
put out just to get
out of there.
(SNARLS)
Edna's with
Comic Book Guy?
Oh, God.
She's on the rebound.
And you meet
the worst guys
on the rebound.
lt's how Jackie
got her "O."
Okay, we'll go to
the convention,
sell my Lois Lane comics,
buy some Jimmy OIsens,
and stop Edna from
making a terrible mistake.
l wish you'd devote
this much time and attention
to our relationship.
Don't worry, Marge.
We'll get something to eat.
(GRUMBLES)
l don't see
Skinner anywhere.
He's probably in costume.
He could be any
of these people.
They're all too
old to be dressed up
like super-people.
Homer, let's just hurry up
and go home so l
can yell at you.
Oh, my goodness.
lt's Matt Groening !
(DR. HlBBERT CHUCKLlNG)
Wow! The creator
of Futurama!
Mr. Groening,
will you autograph
my Bender doll?
Sure. l'm happy to give
anyone my autograph
anytime or anywhere.
On the street, in a store
or on my private property.
But why be happy
with just an autograph?
What about
an original sketch
or snippet of my hair?
And don't forget
to pull my beard.
They say it's good luck.
Look, there they are!
They're going into
Multi-Purpose Room B.
That room has
a dry erase board !
They could be doing
anything in there!
Anything !
Edna, the Klingons
have a romantic saying. . .
(SPEAKlNG KLlNGON)
ALL: Aw!
Roughly translated
it means,
"l would kill the children
of a thousand planets
just to see you smile."
Aw!
That is the most romantic
thing l've ever heard.
Which is kind of sad
if you think about it.
(GRUNTlNG)
Edna, l want you
to marry me
right here and now!
lf you marry me,
we will honeymoon
in Nebulon Five,
also known as San Diego.
SEYMOUR: No!
Hands off my fiancee,
wide ride!
Why are you dressed
like Catwoman?
You. . .
They told me
it was Catman !
Now prepare for
some roughhousing !
(BATTLE DRUMS BEATlNG)
(GRUNTlNG)
(GASPlNG)
(SPEAKlNG KLlNGON)
(BOTH GRUNTlNG)
Stop it! Stop it,
both of you !
Seymour,
it's too late for
you to win me back.
This man worships me.
He actually wants
to be my husband.
The female has
made her decision.
Prepare the feast
of Goldfish crackers.
l'm not marrying
you either.
There are a million
valid reasons,
but which one did you pick?
We've had
a great time together,
but we're too different.
l don't understand.
lt's like l'm DC Comics
and you're Marvel.
l understand completely.
l don't think
l want to be tied
down to anybody.
Take me to some
real men.
Okay.
You can watch my
dad and my brothers
beat me up.
Come back home
with Mama, Son.
l'll make you
some hot cocoa
while you sit in
your shame closet
and think about what you did.
Well, at least l
went down like a man.
You look like
a Malaysian transsexual.
Good for you,
Mrs. K.
Yeah, you don't
need a husband
to be happy!
Okay, Marge,
l hear ya.
Now that Krabappel's
made her decision,
it's time to whitewash
over our problems.
l'm afraid this time
a coat of whitewash
won't cover it!
(GASPlNG)
Our marriage is
just an illusion.
He doesn't care
how l feel at all.
He doesn't know how to love.
Marge, the greatest
day of my life
was the day you
and l became one.
Would you
marry me again?
Oh, it's very sweet,
but l don't need a. . .
(WEDDlNG MARCH PLAYlNG)
Where's that
coming from?
A band in a closet,
every girl's dream.
And now, Padre,
if you would do
the honors.
(SPEAKlNG KLlNGON)
MARGE: l do.
HOMER: Marge, you just
agreed to raise
the kids Klingon !
MARGE: D'oh !
English - US - PSDH