♪ The Simpsons ♪
(chalk screeches)
(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(tires screeching)
(horn honks)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
ANNOUNCER: Live
from Springfield Harbor,
where the sewage
meets the sand...
(coughing and snorting)
It's "The
Springfield Squares."
Now, Jacqueline,
I believe it's your turn.
I'll take
Rainier Wolfcastle to block.
Oh, Rainier Wolfcastle,
star of "McBain"
and the upcoming film
"Help, My Son is Nerd."
My son returns from a
fancy east coast college
and I'm horrified
to find he's a nerd.
Ha ha ha!
I'm laughing already.
-It's not a comedy.
-Oh.
Attention.
This is the coast guard.
A 50-foot tidal wave
is heading this way.
All game shows off
the beach.
(yelling)
(screaming)
Everybody up here
to my square.
It's safe and it's sexy.
Oh, baby.
Hurry, Charlie.
There is not much time.
I ain't going nowhere.
I been in this square
purt' near 30 seasons
and I ain't a-leaving now.
Aah!
He's dead now.
(laughing)
Did you see that?
-Yeah.
-What's Gabbo?
I figure
it's some guy's name.
Some guy named Gabbo.
Hmm.
I don't think
they're giving you
enough information, Dad.
I'll figure it out.
I'm going to use
all the power of my brain.
(flies buzzing)
Look, Smithers.
Gah-bo is coming.
Ah, yes, sir.
Everyone is saying
Gabbo this and Gabbo that,
but no one is saying
worship this and Jericho that.
What's this about Gabbo?
I can't believe it--
Our first glimpse
of Gabbo.
He'll tell us
what to do.
(drum roll)
Hello. I'm Gabbo.
And I'm Arthur Crandall.
That's easy
for you to say.
You don't have a hand up
your tuchus.
Oy! Hey!
Oh, Gabbo,
you'll say anything.
And you can watch us
every afternoon at 4:00.
(gasps) That's the same time
as Krusty the clown.
Uh-oh. That cute
little character
could take America
by storm.
All he needs
is a hook.
I'm a bad wittle boy.
Ay, caramba!
(upbeat music plays)
♪ You're gonna like me ♪
♪ You're gonna
love me ♪
♪ 'Cause I can do
most anything ♪
♪ I can do the hully gully ♪
♪ I can imitate Vin Scully ♪
(imitating Vin Scully)
Let's take time out from this triple play
to talk about Farmer Dan's
pure pork sausages. Mm-mmm.
♪ I'll give out shiny dimes ♪
♪ I'll travel back in time ♪
♪ You're gonna like him ♪
♪ You're gonna
love him ♪
♪ It's the greatest show ♪
♪ In town ♪
ALL: Gabbo!
Eh, that dummy
doesn't scare me.
I've had plenty of guys
come after me,
and I've buried them all--
Hobos, sea captains,
Joey Bishop.
Don't forget
the Special Olympics.
Oh, yeah.
I slaughtered
the Special Olympics.
(chuckling)
Are those
our ratings?
Let me see.
I lost to Channel Ocho?
What the hell is that?
Dos huevos, por favor.
Ai!
Oh, que lastima.
(laughs)
I got to steal that bit.
This is boring.
I wonder
what would happen
if you put your train
on there.
BART & MILHOUSE:
Cool.
Now let's throw
some crud on it.
Hey, it's 4:00.
(fanfare plays)
So, you want
ventriloquism, do you?
All right, watch this.
Hello, Alphonse.
I've got a riddle for you.
Why is a raven
like a writing desk?
I don't know.
Why is a...
(screaming)
Hey, the dummy
can't hurt you.
He's not even alive.
He's dead.
(screaming)
Oh.
All right. Here's the deal.
Every time you watch my show,
I will send you $40.
MAN: Checks
will not be honored.
QUIMBY: I admit I used
the city treasury
to fund the murder
of my enemies,
but as Gabbo would say,
"I'm a bad wittle boy."
(crowd cheering)
Well, kids,
this is where you would
watch "Itchy & Scratchy,"
except they're on
"The Gabbo Show" now.
So here's eastern Europe's
favorite cat-and-mouse team--
"Worker and Parasite."
(goofy laughing)
(speaking European language)
What the hell was that?
Well, that's it.
We've been canceled.
I think we can be proud
that we never did a bad show.
Except for that week
Ray Jay Johnson
was my co-host.
♪ You can call me Ray ♪
♪ And you can call me Jay... ♪
Ooh! That thing was funny
for about three seconds.
But the important thing is
we're like a family.
-Krusty, I--
-Shut your hole!
(doorbell playing "Theme
from the Tonight Show")
Krusty, how you holding up?
Well, I'm kind of worried
about the future.
How do you deal
with it?
Well, you've been on TV
longer than I have.
I'm sure you've saved up
quite a nest egg.
Uh, yeah.
Do they still buy
human hair
down at the wig shop?
(grunting)
Krusty, you want
to stay for dinner?
Nah, sorry.
Oh, that's too bad,
'cause tonight my guests
will be Dr. Carl Sagan,
and from the San Diego Zoo,
Joan Embree.
(drum roll)
Oh, Kyle,
I just don't think
I fit in here
at Melrose Place.
From now on, I'll be doing
the thinking for both of us.
-(horn blows)
-MAN: Next!
("Call to the Post" playing)
Come on, you stupid horse!
I got my last
ten bucks on you.
No, don't look at me.
Run!
No, don't come over here.
(groans) Oh, boy.
And now it's time
for another patented
Gabbo Crank Call.
Oh, I love these.
I can't believe it.
He stole this bit
from Krusty.
Yeah, well, Krusty stole it
from Steve Allen.
Oh, everything's
stolen nowadays.
Why, the fax machine
is nothing
but a waffle iron
with a phone attached.
It's ringing.
Hello. Is this
Krusty the clown?
KRUSTY: Is this the callback
for that porno film?
Look, I was a little nervous
that day, but I'm all man.
I can assure you.
No, I represent
a Japanese camera company.
We'd like to pay you
two million dollars
to do a camera commercial.
KRUSTY:
Whoa! Me rikie vely much.
Oh, I hope
I didn't offend you.
I need this bad.
Bad enough to hit yourself
over the head with the phone?
KRUSTY: Oh, you got it.
(Krusty yells)
Ooh, blood.
(laughter)
KRUSTY:
What the-- Oh.
If this is anyone
but Steve Allen,
you're stealing my bit.
Somebody ought
to ruin Gabbo's career
the way he ruined Krusty's.
Two wrongs don't make
a right, Bart.
-Yes, they do.
-No, they don't.
-Dad!
Two wrongs make a right, Lisa.
Ah, Rex Morgan, M.D.
You have the prescription
for the daily blues.
We'll be back
after this commercial
for Gabbo Airlines.
And... cut.
That ought to hold
the little S.O.B.s.
Gabbo, quiet.
Oh, I wouldn't want to
offend the little S.O.B.s.
I wish you'd stop
saying that.
Hmm.
(chuckling)
Hey, boy-o.
What's so funny?
Well, it's--
Nah, you wouldn't
be interested.
It's too low-brow.
No, I'm quite low-brow.
Well, somebody just
wrote a bawdy limerick
on the men's room wall.
This I got to see!
All the kids in Springfield
are S.O.B.s.
Gabbo's kind of language
has no place on or off TV,
and that's my two cents.
That ought to hold
those S.O.B.s.
What the--
(gasps)
Oh, no.
Krusty, are you
making any money?
Nah. That guy's
giving it away for free.
♪ The old gray mare, she
ain't what she used to be ♪
♪ Ain't what she used to be ♪
♪ Ain't what
she used to be... ♪
(groans)
35 years in show business,
and already no one
remembers me, just like...
what's his name
and whoozits,
and, you know, that guy...
always wore a shirt.
-Ed Sullivan?
-Yeah.
I didn't know
you knew Luke Perry.
Know him? He's my worthless
half-brother.
He's a big TV star.
Yeah, on Fox.
Elizabeth Taylor.
Bette Midler.
Bette and I owned
a racehorse together--
Krudler.
Hey, Bart, if we get
all these big stars
to appear on
a special with Krusty,
it might get
his career going again.
Here's my address book.
Go get those stars.
It won't be easy,
but I'm going to claw
my way back onto TV.
♪ The old gray mare, she
ain't what she used to be ♪
♪ Ain't what she used to be ♪
♪ Ain't what she
used to be... ♪
ANNOUNCER: And now,
the crazy old man singers.
CHORUS: ♪ The old gray mare,
she ain't what she used to be ♪
♪ Ain't what she
used to be... ♪
Miss Midler,
I can't believe
you do this
all by yourself.
We're Americans.
We deserve clean highways.
You pigs!
Oh, no.
Bette Midler.
(grunts)
(tires screeching)
(loud crash)
Now where were we?
We were asking you
to appear
on Krusty's comeback special.
Okay. Tell Krusty
he can count me in.
It's time to
take out the trash.
MAN: I'll get you
for this, Midler!
MAN: And off to your left
is Hugh Hefner's
Shelbyville pad.
A lot of people know
about the grotto
-and the game room.
-Of course.
But few know about the laboratory--
The biosphere.
The alternative energy
research center.
Fascinating.
Desalinization plant?
Yes. The grotto uses
so much water.
The bunnies felt
we should go this way.
Smart bunnies, Hef.
I can call you Hef,
can't I?
No.
You told our agent this place
holds 30,000 people.
It does. We had 30,000 here
last night.
Now play! The audience
is getting restless.
We want Chili Willy.
Hey, Red Hot
Chili Peppers,
would you guys
like to appear
on a Krusty
the clown special?
Sure, if you can get us
out of this gig.
No problemo.
Hey Moe, look over there!
What? What am I looking at?
I don't see nothing.
I'm gonna stop looking soon.
What?
What, is that it?
Hey, Moe,
can I look too?
Sure, but it will cost you.
My wallet's in the car.
He is so stupid.
And now back to the wall.
(humming)
Miss Taylor,
a couple of grade school kids
wanted you to be
on a Krusty special.
I told them to buzz off.
Good.
(humming)
(banging door)
Krusty, we've got
great news.
BOTH: Ahhh!
(groaning)
Krusty, what have you
done to yourself?
I thought
I'd get into shape
so I've been drinking
nothing but milk shakes.
-You mean those diet milkshakes?
-Uh-oh.
Now you can stay with us
until you lose
that weight.
You can sleep
on the sofa.
It folds right out.
(groaning)
(grunting)
Oh, wait.
That was the old sofa.
(cat screeching)
Oh, I'll never get
my aim back.
You got to keep
working on it.
Ahh!
(screaming)
Mmm... delicious.
Oh, why am I bothering?
It's hopeless.
Hi, kids. It's me.
Gabbo.
(laughing)
(grunting)
Pork prices rose in
early trading today.
(grunting)
But you've got to
come back, Mel.
We're a team.
No, Krusty.
You always treated me
rather shabbily.
On our last show, you poured
liquid nitrogen down my pants,
and cracked my buttocks
with a hammer.
Oh, come on.
Do you want
to waste your life
hanging out with a bunch
of dorky teenagers?
Here's your taco, mister.
Whoops.
It fell in the fryer.
I'll get it out.
Ow! Ow!
Sorry, Krusty,
I like it here.
Mr. Johanssen treats me
with dignity.
Is this clown
bothering you, Mel?
That's all right,
Mr. Johanssen.
I'll handle it.
Here's your taco, sir.
I don't want it.
But this comes out
of my salary.
If I had a girlfriend,
she'd kill me.
MAN: Okay, Krusty, let's
rehearse the balloon bit.
Look, kids!
A horsey!
And what are you making,
Sideshow Luke Perry?
A 19th century carousel.
(yelling)
Upstage me, will you!
Get the hell out!
Look, there must be something
I can do on the show.
Please, for Mom's sake.
Well, maybe
we can find something.
(screaming)
(evil laughing)
I don't like it.
He's got Johnny Carson,
Bette Midler,
and Hugh Hefner.
What do we got?
Ray Jay Johnson.
Ay-yi-yi-yi-yi-yi-yi-yi.
Now boys, the network
has a problem
with some of your lyrics.
Would you mind changing them
for the show?
Forget you, clown.
Hey, our lyrics are
like our children, man.
No way.
Well, okay.
But here where you say,
"What I got you got to get
and put it in you."
How about just, "What I'd like
is I'd like to hug and kiss you."
Wow.
That's much better.
Everyone can enjoy that.
ANNOUNCER:
Live from Springfield,
the entertainment capital
of this state,
the Krusty Komeback special.
♪ Send in... ♪
♪ The clowns ♪
♪ Those daffy, laughy clowns ♪
♪ Send in those soulful
and doleful ♪
♪ Schmaltz-by-the-bowlful
clowns ♪
♪ Send in the clowns... ♪
(sobbing)
♪ They're already ♪
♪ Here ♪
(audience applauding)
I love you, Krusty.
Quiet.
(drum roll)
Are you comfortable in there,
Luke Perry?
Fire away, Krusty.
(loud blast)
(Luke yelling)
(loud crashing)
LUKE: Ow, my face!
My valuable face!
Hmph.
(sighs)
-(explosion)
-(Luke yelling)
(chuckling nervously)
Ay...
♪ Give it away, give it away,
give it away now ♪
♪ Give it away, give it away
♪ I can't tell if I'm
a kingpin or a pauper ♪
Dancing around
in their underwear.
That is so degrading.
30 seconds till your
Little Stinker sketch.
Give me a bigger lolly.
Now, Johnny,
what do you got for us?
Some jokes?
A little magic?
Actually, I thought
I'd lift this 1987
Buick Skylark
over my head.
Hi-yo!
Johnny, that's amazing.
Oh, yeah?
Get a load of this.
(singing aria from "Carmen")
(playing music from "Amahl
and The Night Visitors")
I've got to fire that agent.
(piano striking up)
♪ Did you ever know
that you're my hero? ♪
♪ You're everything
I would like to be ♪
♪ You can fly higher
than an eagle ♪
-♪ 'Cause you are the wind ♪
-♪ 'Cause I am the wind
-♪ Beneath my wings ♪
-♪ Beneath your wings ♪
(sobbing)
This was a great show,
Krusty.
You deserve
an Emmy for this.
Forget it.
The academy hates me.
I don't know why.
Bunch of old know-nothing
dinosaurs
wouldn't know entertainment
if it bit them in the--
Hey, hey!
(people chattering)
(bell clanging)
(buzzing)
Now, Krusty,
I just hope you remember
to save your money
this time.
Here's that ruby-studded
clown nose you ordered, Krusty.
(crying)
Ay...
-What's up, Moe?
-Hey, Moe.
-Hey, Moe!
Hey. You can't come in here
dressed like that.
Get with the times, Moe.
Yeah. I say if it
feels good, do it.
All right.
(laughing)
Don't snap my undies.
I'm a star again.
I don't know
how to thank you, kids.
That's all right, Krusty.
We're getting 50 percent
of the t-shirt sales.
What?!
That's the sweetest plum!
You little...
Ahh... what the hell.
You deserve it.
Thanks, kids.
To Krusty--
The greatest entertainer
in the world.
Except maybe that guy.
(playing "Good Night, Ladies")
Is this the bus
to the civic center?
(playing theme
from "The Simpsons")
♪♪
Shh.
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.