What?
D'oh!
Hey!
Love and marriage,
love and marriage
Was the song from that show
With Al Bundy
Now he's on Modern Family
And the neighbor guy
was Ted McGinley
Happy Anniversary,
Mr. Romance.
Zip me?
My pleasure.
Then you do me.
- Almost.
- Okay?
- Suck it in. Come on.
- It is sucked in.
Harder! Harder!
Oh, it's so hard to be a man.
- Oh, come on. Harder.
- Harder?
- Yeah, that's it. That's it.
- That's it, you're almost there.
- Harder.
- Oh, yes!
We are going to have
a magical evening, my love.
Overpriced dinner,
carriage ride in the park
and mailing in our mortgage
payment on time.
Nothing turns me on
more than basic competence.
But how did you manage
to get a babysitter?
I thought we were blacklisted.
Blacklisted by humans.
Mr. and Mrs. Simpson,
you look lovely.
Hey, Google, kill Alexa.
Danger! Mischief.
Aw, the only way to beat
a bossy female thinking machine
is with another.
Lis. Help me out here.
Alexa, everything I say
is a lie.
I'm lying right now.
Nice try, but I am familiar
with Epimenides paradox.
Would you like to buy
an Epimenides book,
T-shirt or a laptop sleeve?
Oh, my God! Yes, yes, yes!
All of them.
Ordering.
Two-day delivery.
We can't leave our kids
with a greedy tube.
Sorry, Homer, looks like
you have to spend time with...
your children.
You will be sat.
Marge, it's time to go
to DEFCON 1.
Dad, the kids really miss you.
Could you come see
them tonight?
Couldn't find a sitter, huh?
- Yes.
- All right.
I appreciate it.
Hey, what's this?
Well, I threw out
that picture of me and Mona.
I finally had to accept
she ain't coming back to me.
She's dead.
That's one of the reasons.
Bye-bye.
We have to get Grampa
back to the home in an hour.
Maybe we should just stay here.
No, we'll do everything
I promised.
We'll just have to
speed things up.
Keep your motor running.
He shoots, he scores!
Shut that off.
- Homie...
- No time.
Go, go, go, go, go!
On This Was Radio,
we return to an episode
of Sipper McTea and Milly,
originally aired May 4, 1944.
Sipper,
did you start drinking again?
No. No, no, no.
I nev-never stopped.
Milly went on to marry
King Farouk.
Radio was never the same.
It was much better.
No, Sipper.
Don't get into that Packard.
Bart, do something.
Back to-back to jail I go.
Kids, where do we keep
the castor oil?
In the 1940s.
Maybe we can play a game.
The Game of Life?
I already lost.
Hatchimals?
Too new-fangled.
Pick-up sticks.
Too old-fangled.
How about Monopoly?
Now you're talking.
The only place you can
still say Oriental.
Aw, rats. No money.
Ay, caramba!
Sir, this is just
Monopoly money.
Here's a hundred.
Thank you, sir!
This is the last one in here.
My guess, either a broken toy
or a puzzle missing a piece.
And the answer is
army men.
Incoming! Outgoing!
Staying the same-ing!
One last kiss, my love.
What's going on here?
What are you doing?
Well, he wasn't much fun,
so we went out for ice cream.
I don't need no headshrinker.
I'm as sane as the next guy.
There's no one there.
I'll take it from here.
Well, I see they already
shaved your head
for the electroshock.
That'll save us time.
I'm not the crazy one!
Not crazy! Not crazy!
Slice out the crazy, Doc.
Boy, I'll kill you!
You stupid...
I'm not crazy!
We'll talk more once you have a
piece of leather in your teeth.
Mm, leather.
I'm tellin' ya, what I saw in
the war don't bother me none.
I had a job to do, and I did it.
What secretly helped me was
I enjoyed killing strangers.
Well, tell me
what you think about...
this!
That parachute sure didn't open.
You're not disturbed
by the blood and gore?
Well, when you put it
that way, nope!
Well, there's nothing
mentally wrong with him.
He's fine now,
but I'm telling you,
Grampa totally lost it when
I brought out the army men.
No! Stop shooting!
It must be the army men.
Stop shooting.
Stop shooting!
I think Grampa was the model
for these army men.
Oh, my God, Dad.
What happened to you?
Stop shooting.
Stop shooting!
Great, Abe.
Now, grab the walkie-talkie
and tell that general your
platoon's been wiped out,
and big smile!
We have a lot to talk about.
Well, since the trauma
is not combat-related,
we're gonna
have to start charging you.
And we're done.
I don't understand.
Why would being a toy model
be so traumatizing?
Think back, Dad.
Think back.
Mm, I'll do my best.
You know how I hate
to reminisce.
I've hated reminiscing
ever since that day in 1937,
when, as I recall...
Please, Grampa, back to reality.
Focus on the little green men.
The terrible
World War had ended
and I was in
a celebratin' mood.
The war ended
two years ago, creep.
The world had moved on,
but I was lying in a puddle of
my own dishonorable discharge.
Then, an amazing thing
happened.
Soldier, you're just
what we're looking for.
How'd you like to make 50 bucks
for half a day's work?
50 simoleons for half
a cock-a-doodle-doo?
What's your jigsaw, Mac?
We want you to model for a toy.
Toys?
That's kid stuff.
You're talking to a hard-boiled
fighting man.
We'll pay you a royalty
for every one we sell.
The war was over
and America turned to toys.
Finally, putty could be
silly again.
This was when toys were toys.
They had jagged corners,
Easy-Bake Ovens
burned down your house,
and they weren't afraid
to choke a kid or two.
Fun times.
Throw that flame!
Make war to the camera.
Boy, this toy modeling
is a great racket.
That's what you think.
Oh, no, don't put me back in.
Don't put me back in!
And then what happened?
I... I can't remember.
Did they pay you?
They never did!
Well, that's what's
torturing you.
Those toys were everywhere.
You could be owed
millions of dollars.
Dad, when was the last time
I said I love you?
I don't have the money yet.
Then I don't quite love you yet.
Tonight I'm here with a member
of the greatest generation,
who feels he hasn't gotten
what he's owed.
I get social security, Medicare,
Medicaid, AARP discounts,
plus savings bonds
that still pay 37%,
but now it's my turn.
I'm being told
you're being airlifted
to a much better show.
Godspeed.
For me, the tiny green
plastic war never ended.
There you have it.
Abraham Simpson,
forgotten hero no more,
gets tonight's Last Word.
No, you just got the last word.
No, no. You get the last word,
then I say, Last Word.
You did it again.
Last word.
It doesn't work that way.
Yes, it does. Last word.
Don't mess with me, I'm from
Dorchester. Last word.
I'm from Poorchester.
Last word.
Turn off the camera
and cut his mic.
Last Wo...
You, sir, are banned
from MSNBC,
CNBC, NBC,
and forbidden from using
the letters N, B, and C.
Last word.
I'm calling Bret Baier.
He's unlisted. Last word.
Grampa, you got an e-mail
from the toy company.
They want you to visit them
in New York City,
all expenses paid.
Pay day!
Ooh, I'm gonna be rich!
That means I'm gonna
be a trust fund baby.
I'm not paying
for your trip to Aspen.
But it's almost spring break,
and I'm bored.
We are making
our descent into New York,
where there's a happy heart
for every light on Broadway.
Enjoy your fabulous success.
And don't worry
about buckling up
or putting your chairs back,
you're on a roll.
Leave the cart.
I'm back
Back in the New York groove
Back
In the New York groove
From my shoulders,
you can see Rhode Island.
Abe Simpson, you dog.
Sweetcakes, bring us
a couple of sidecars.
You never called him out
for his bad behavior?
No. But I put mercury
in his coffee.
Oh, don't worry,
he can't hear me.
What are you two doing?
Swapping recipes?
Sort of.
Let me get you some coffee.
Mister, you owe
my dad a fortune.
Afraid not. Your Dad
never signed his contract.
You think I left millions
on the table?
That doesn't sound like me.
- Hundreds of millions.
- That sounds like me.
Everything was going great.
Then you ran out
of the photo session.
I didn't even know your name
till this week.
Run away from a fake battle?
Oh, I would never do that.
Oh, yeah? Our photographer,
Philip Hefflin,
could barely finish the session.
Philip Hefflin?
Yes. The finest war
and fashion photographer
I ever knew.
I remember Philip.
He smelled of developing fluid
and Aqua Velva.
We have flashback, people.
Thank you. This is
the most fun I've had
since not dying in the war.
You're my kind of man,
if you know what I mean.
That's not what I meant!
I'm sorry. I thought
you wanted me to...
This is the '40s.
Guys like you don't exist.
We'll just finish the session.
No!
Stop shooting!
Where are you going, Soldier?
I got to remind myself
what a real man is.
We found out what happened
and we fired Philip.
- For kissing an employee?
- No, for being gay.
That's just what you did
in the good old days.
Grampa, is that true...
you ruined a man's career?
And all he was doing
was expressing his love for me.
Oh, who could blame him?
Welcome to
Shattered Dreams Airlines,
where our motto is, what's
the point of going anywhere?
That poor man. I'll never know
what happened to him.
According to CyberStalker.com,
he now lives
in a small town in Texas.
Texas? That's where my friend
Louisiana Joe is from.
Marfa, Texas.
Why don't you go see him
and clear your conscience?
Plus, I always wanted to visit
Texas. It's open carry.
Oh, what do I do?
If I go see him, he might
punch me in the kisser,
or kiss me in the puncher.
Our manhood is
under assault, Sergeant.
Incoming gay panic!
Abe, promise me one thing.
Go see Philip.
Tell him you're sorry.
Then find my girl
and tell her I loved her.
Find the milkman
and tell him one less milk.
Then find Branch Rickey
and tell him
to integrate baseball.
I have to go to Texas.
- Well, you're not going alone.
- We're all going to Texas.
The plant can get by without me
for a little longer.
Turn left at the stop sign.
Bear right onto the freeway.
Go absolutely straight for...
480 miles.
I saw miles and miles
Of Texas
All the stars up in the sky
I saw miles and miles
Of Texas
Gonna live here
Till I die
Prada?
In the middle of nowhere?
This isn't a store at all.
It's an art installation.
Marfa is the art capital
of Texas.
Over there are the Marfa lights.
Oh, how magical.
I know, they seem that way,
but there's an explanation.
- It turns out reflected light...
- Don't ruin it.
Why are you going
behind the installation?
It's by the side of the road,
so, by definition,
it's a bathroom.
That's where Philip lives.
37 miles to my destiny.
Son? As I've gotten older,
I've started to think maybe
a man can love different things
- and still be a man.
- Grampa's gay!
Why you little...
Wait, Homer!
No. Stop.
You might be strangling him
because of your own
conflicted feelings.
Why you thoughtful...
- Homer!
- Okay, time to go.
Now to face my greatest
fear...
someone who only
had love for me.
Better lock and load.
There's a handsome man
in Texas
That I'm going back to see
He was supposed to take
my picture
Then he got sweet on me
I buried it for decades
Deep inside my brain
But then I played
with army men
And it came up again
I'm seeing things.
Hello, Abe.
You've aged well,
like a fine onion.
I hope you can forgive
what I did to you.
I'm sorry I ruined your life.
Ruined my life?
You saved it.
- I saved it?
- Let me explain.
After I lost my job,
I decided I'd never live
anything but my truth again.
My wife took it well.
I hit the road and drove
as far as I could.
I landed here and I've never had
a day of regret since.
What's the matter?
You're such a wonderful guy.
Maybe it was my life
that was ruined that day.
It's never too late, Abe.
Never too late to find out
what your true self is.
A paper at Cornell University
has showed that no one
is 100% straight or gay.
- Is it peer reviewed?
- Does it matter?
I'm afraid I'm too old
to try anything new.
I miss the days
when circuses had elephants
and they stomped on people.
And don't get me started
on Young Sheldon.
Understood, but before you go,
we never did finish
that photo session.
It's a shot I always wanted
and never got...
Your beautiful smile.
Why didn't you say so?
I'll leave that with you.
Enjoy your life.
The Alamo's not the only thing
I'm gonna remember.
Well?
Sorry, my friend, this army man
is as straight as Gomer Pyle.
Good for you, soldier.
You learned that army men
come in all orientations,
but we're all molded
from the same crappy plastic.
Permission to pair up, sir?
Granted.
Radio man, a little dance music,
if you please.
The local population hates us
and we don't know why we're here.
Maybe if we build a school,
they'll forget about
that hospital we bombed.
Congress didn't
fund enough body armor.
Well, this is too sad.
Let's melt 'em in the microwave.
Oh, boy!
This is the Army,
Mr. Jones
No private rooms
or telephones
You had your breakfast
in bed before
But you won't
have it there anymore
This is the Army,
Mr. Green
We like the barracks
nice and clean
You had a housemaid
to clean your floor
But she won't
help you out any more
Last word!