(crow squawks)
(The Simpsons' theme
playing in 8-bit audio)
(crackling)
Yeah, how ya doin'?
(explosion thunders)
♪ The Simpsons 25x17 ♪
Luca$
Original Air Date on April 6, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
(snoring loudly)
(tires screech, horn honks)
H-Hey, what?
Oh! Oh, cleats!
(sighs)
Homie, what happened?
Uh... maybe some
easy-listening music
will make you feel
better about the story.
Turn on 89.9.
(Marge grumbles)
(easy listening music playing)
Like most of my problems,
it all started at Moe's...
CARL: All right, so the rules are every
time the news guy says "senator,"
we got to take a drink.
Huh. It'll be nice to let someone else
decide when I drink... too much pressure.
(new theme playing)
(quietly): Uh, yeah,
Channel Six tip line?
I just caught two senators
doin' it in the alley.
And me?
I'm just a reliable source.
Not "sauce," "source."
Source! S-A-U-R-C-E!
We have heard from a
very reliable sauce
news involving
multiple senators.
I'm going to read a
list of senators,
with possibly more
senators to be named later
by other senators:
Senator Abercrombie,
Senator Billingsley,
Senator Beaumont...
(snickers)
Hmm? Oh, damn, the
plaster's flaking again.
HOMER: Once intoxicated,
we had a great idea.
Hey! Swings!
(laughing):
I'm a kid again!
(laughing)
Oh... gah...
I'll save you!
(grunts)
(grunting)
Oh, the only
way out is in!
Hey, look at me!
I'm going up a slide!
BOTH (chanting): Homer! Homer!
Best recess ever!
(shouts)
(clang)
- Whoa.
- (gasps)
Help me, guys! Guys?
(grunting)
Don't worry, Homer,
I'll call the cops!
I'll write my senator.
- Senator!
Oh, am I gonna die on a playground,
like some uncoordinated child?
But I did learn something
from all this:
The sprinklers in this
park come on at 3:00 a.m.
Hey, thanks for throwing
the ball back. Really.
(sighs)
I'll come back with
the fire truck.
I just have to get the
kids to school first.
Oh, are the kids with you?
- LISA: Hi, Dad.
- BART: Homer.
Hey, guys! Why are you
ducked-down like that?
BART: Don't want to be seen with
you when you're hitting bottom.
LISA: At least we
hope it's bottom.
Don't worry, it's
bottom, all right.
(grunts)
(Marge groans)
BART: And that's why
I was tardy today.
And with that tardiness,
you have at last crossed
the boundary where I can legally
apply physical discipline.
Willie, cut me a switch!
What about the one
your ma used on you?
It, uh, broke
on my buttocks.
Serves you right for eating
jam straight out of the jar.
Damn it! That's not
even a swivel chair.
Skate, skate as
fast as you can.
But I'll catch you...
I'm the Principal Man!
That's the kind of
education you're missing.
(car backfiring)
Oh, no. Uphill. The one
place my car can't go.
(gears grinding)
(steam hissing)
Uh, would you
like a quote?
Uh, yes.
"Some cause happiness
wherever they go;
Others whenever they go."
Oscar Wilde.
Uh, P.S. Your
car is totaled.
Whew! Safe.
JAILBIRD:
Oh, not totally.
Whoa! What-what are
you doing in here?
Hiding from the cops.
Well, I can't have cops
sniffing around here.
- Some of them might be girls.
- Can't I just stay a little?
I only committed this
robbery to help my kid.
See, this is Jeremy.
I need to get him braces.
I always thought that if I'd had
braces, I'd have smiled more.
Hey, I bet you have
a great smile.
- Huh?
- Ay, caramba!
Bart, Bart, we're in
whatchamacallit... a pursuit!
So why'd you come here?
I run a respectable tree house.
Just wondering if
you've seen anything.
Uh, word is you'll, uh...
you'll snitch for candy.
You can't buy me with a
candy bar that has coconut.
Then maybe this is more your...
neighborhood.
Nice real estate.
You got a deal.
So, what do you know?
I saw a guy with a gun
and a snake tattoo...
say he was gonna hide out
on top of Mount Springfield.
Mount Springfield, eh?
Strap on your
crampons, boys!
Eddie! Prepare my litter!
Lou, you are responsible for my
oxygen, food, water and cleaning!
- You have to clean me.
- I clean you. Yeah.
Dude, thank you.
Why did you save me?
We outlaws have
to stick together.
Outlaw? You?
Stolen bowling shoes, 3-D glasses, Krusty
standee and this "cage" for my pet.
Oh. What do you feed him?
My A.D.D. meds.
(trilling)
(chuckles)
Um, listen, would you like two
tickets to the school musical?
My son plays the butcher.
In Fiddler on the Roof.
I'm busy that night.
Yeah, lucky you.
(indistinct chatter)
(grunting)
Huh?
(gagging)
(gasps)
Are you okay?
Don't put more in there!
(choking):
Going for the record.
(choking)
What record?
Stupidest death?
Aah!
(grunting)
Blagh!
Merci beaucoup!
- Oh, well, you're very wel...
- That's French for "hello."
- Actually, I think it...
- Lucas Bortner, competitive eater.
A fat kid with a dream?
I can't compete with that.
What does a competitive
eater eat?
All the glamour foods: Pizza,
boiled eggs, chicken wings
and the big enchilada, which
is not enchiladas but hot dogs.
69 hot dogs is the current record.
As the great Kobayashi says,
"Detekurutoki itaiyo."
What does that mean?
"That's gonna
hurt coming out."
Is Kobayashi the
number one, um, uh...
The correct term
is "gurgitator."
I won't be using the
correct term then.
Virtually everyone uses
his technique: Japanesing.
Shall I demonstrate?
Um, why don't I just go sit
alone... Oh, you're doing it.
Ready, set...
Japanese!
(choking)
(grunting, groaning)
That's not going down.
(gagging)
- This happens from time to time.
- Maybe this isn't the sport for you.
It's not a sport.
It's my life.
Aw, he's sweet.
(chuckles)
What am I doing?
He's just Ralph with a dream.
The dream of not ralphing.
But I'm sure I could totally
change and fix him.
- Can I join you for lunch?
- Um, sure.
- How many whole pizzas would you like?
- Um, can I just have a slice?
Interesting technique.
(chuckles)
BART:
Whoa.
You didn't tell me you
had a PlayStadium 4!
It's the first
I've seen it.
Something's fishy, Bart.
Where's the gift receipt?
Where's the packet of desiccant
that says "Do not eat"?
And, believe me,
you shouldn't.
I have a feeling this
PlayStadium was liberated
from its previous owner and
given to me in gratitude.
Liberated? You
mean "stolen"?
You can't spell "crime"
without "me."
C-R-I... (gasps)
There it is, at the end!
(doorbell rings)
Oh, hi. Is-is Lisa home?
Yes, she is. And
who are you?
Lucas.
It's pronounced "Luca-dollar."
That's my competition name.
I'm a competitive eater.
HOMER: Competitive eater?
Did I hear right?
- I could be a competitive eater?
- No! You didn't hear anything!
Yes, I did! I heard
"competitive eater"!
It's for people who haven't
had heart problems.
Then that makes me the Jackie
Robinson of the sport,
and you are the racist
Philadelphia manager.
Quit comparing me
to Ben Chapman.
I will when you open
your mind to change!
Oh...!
So, what should we practice:
Um, Vienna sausage;
Blueberry pie, short form;
Oatmeal, long course;
Freestyle baked beans;
Catfish... ooh!
- Cow brains.
- Beans, beans!
We'll do beans.
Hmm. Never saw the pork
eat the beans before.
(both laugh)
Actually, I'm a little
surprised Lisa likes him.
Really! Justin Blobber over there
doesn't remind you of anyone?
$800 to cut me out
of that slide?!
It's all about the money
with those firemen.
Women marry their
fathers, Marge.
So you just might be meeting
your future "ton-in-law."
(both laughing)
Ton-in-law.
God bless us.
(gasps)
You can do better.
(Homer snoring)
MARGE: My sisters are nuts. I'm
happy being married to Homer.
Most of the time.
(groans)
(barking)
Ooh! What the...?
(sighs)
(Rossini's "The Thieving
Magpie" playing)
♪ ♪
(slurps)
(yelling)
Meep, meep!
(descending whistle)
(gunshot)
Hmm...
Maybe you're not cut out
for competitive eating.
Are you calling
me not fat?
No, I'm just... I...
Maybe you just haven't
found the right food, huh?
- How 'bout ice cream?
- Yes!
I will lay some
hurt on that cream.
Oh, my God! Brain freeze!
Oh, my God.
Kick me in the head
till I pass out.
Harder! I'm still conscious!
You must kick me harder.
Okay, honey, I made you pork
chops just like you like 'em.
- Twenty.
- Thanks, babe.
Sorry you had to drop out of
college to feed me full-time.
Now give us a kiss.
(Lisa screaming)
(gasps deeply)
What the...?
Oh, yawn.
Another freebie.
Better be a 64 gig.
Huh? It's full of lame apps:
Bully Avoider, Nosebook,
Insta-Grandma.
This was stolen from Milhouse!
From my backpack.
Where Puppy
Goo-Goo sleeps.
Maybe it's time to tell me
exactly what's going on.
Relax. Listen to the music
of this bubble game.
(gentle music plays)
So peaceful.
No! I won't let this go!
It's time you told me how you've
been getting all this stuff.
(sighs)
I helped Snake out of a jam so
he paid me back in stolen stuff.
It was an honorable arrangement. But
I never thought he'd steal from you.
Snake, eh? I never would've
suspected the one criminal in town.
(chuckles)
You seem stressed. You want
to suck some Squishee?
Sure.
(whooshing)
- Mmm!
- Careful. It's uncut syrup.
They give it to horses
before they race.
(sucking, slurping)
BROCKMAN:
Jailbird, A Snake.
That's his real name. Albert
Knickerbocker Aloysius Snake...
has been arrested for a series
of thefts and may be
put to death under a
controversial new statute.
(gasps)
Yeah, we had a law stating
"Three strikes and you're out."
But I thought it was "You're
out." So I let people go.
So now it's "Four
balls and you walk.
Right to the electric chair."
It's, uh, much clearer, Kent.
Bart, I'm so sorry.
I just wanted to ruin
his life, not end it.
You ratted him out?
(groans)
- He's got a kid.
- A kid?!
I was crushed when
I lost my dad
and all he did was move
to the Holiday Inn.
I can still see him
smoking on the balcony.
He looked like he
missed something.
Maybe me.
So you see, we can't
let Jailbird fry.
Time for the
Sleepover Detectives.
I didn't say there'd
be a sleepover.
Too bad, 'cause I'm wearing
my pajamas under my clothes.
And my swimsuit under those.
One day it'll all pay off.
(Homer humming jauntily)
Oh! There's my magazine.
Why, look at this. "What every
father should do for his daughter."
Oh, Marge, if you want me to
do something, just tell me.
Don't hide behind a magazine.
Right. Right, right, right.
According to Judy Kleinsmith,
a professional
freelance writer,
fathers should take their
daughters out on little
dinner dates and treat them
like a gentleman would.
Then she'll expect the same
from the men in her future.
Wait, let me get this straight: Sit
and eat? That's my punishment?
It's not a punishment. But
you can't just eat dinner.
You have to be gentlemanly
and attentive.
Oh, I can fake attentive.
I've been watching a football
game this whole discussion.
Not fake attentive.
Real attentive.
Okay, okay. I'll make it fun.
I'll take her to that crab place.
- All the crabs you could smash.
- You know Lisa's a vegetarian.
She can smash a salad.
No. Homer, you can't just do
the things you want to do.
You have to act like someone
you'd want Lisa to marry.
If you just act like yourself,
she might just... um...
Oh, you know... um...
She might marry
someone like me?
You think that
would be bad.
Homie, I love you.
But you can be a challenge,
like doing the Daily Jumble.
Marge, you are comparing me to the most
infuriating thing in the newspaper!
Well, I was
just trying to...
Oh... I'm sleeping on
Flanders' couch tonight.
Ours is crap.
(door shuts)
So Marge says I gotta
ask Lisa on a date.
Sure you remember how
to ask out a girl, Homer?
Yeah, you've been out of
the game a long time there.
Guys, lay off Homer.
Now you quit stalling and call
your daughter like a man.
Oh... it feels weird.
Just ask your daughter to have dinner
with you. What is the big deal?
Ah, he's doing it!
He's calling a girl.
Oh, my God, oh, my God,
oh, my God... (line ringing)
Oh, it's ringing.
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
LISA:
Hello?
Uh, hello. Lisa? I know
your brother and...
Oh! Stupid,
stupid, stupid!
Calm down, calm down.
She doesn't know it's you.
(phone ringing)
Ah! Hide! Hide!
(Moe sighs)
Uh, hello? Oh, sure, Lisa,
uh, your dad's right here.
Dad?
Did you just call?
Uh, yeah. Hey, listen, your mom
thinks that maybe you and I
should have dinner
together sometime.
Just the two of us?
Ah, yeah, I knew
you'd think it's dumb.
I'd love that.
See you tonight.
(whoops)
- I got a date with my daughter!
- Yeah, we all been there.
No need to act like you just
invented air conditioning.
So, you see, Chief, Snake wasn't
stealing that stuff out of greed.
He was stealing
it to thank me.
Plea denied. Warm up the
electric chair, Lou.
You're not done yet?
The instructions are
in Swedish, Chief.
We got this from IKILLYA.
- Yo, I totally speak Swedish.
- Fluently?
Um, ja.
Uh, do what he says, Lou.
- But Chief...
- But-but-but.
Quit arguing and give
him the little wrench.
Ow. Ow. Ow. Ow. Let him
out, Lou. Let him out.
But Chief, we got guns;
He's got a little wrench.
It's cold!
Y... oh...
(sighs, groans)
All right.
(Wiggum whimpers, groans)
Thanks for coming
down, Bart.
You won't need to
save me a third time.
- You're going straight?
- If I get caught, it's suicide by cop.
Oh, I don't like
the sound of that.
It means I get you
to shoot me, dude.
Yeah, still sounds like
a lot of paperwork.
Hair volumizer?!
Cologne?!
Hello, Marjorie.
Homie. You look
like an NBA coach.
Yes, well, it's a special evening and I
thought it best not to look like a monkey.
Mm!
Don't worry. I won't
embarrass you.
I will put my napkin in my lap, I will
use the utensils provided for me,
and if I our food is slow in coming,
I will "blow my stack" in a manner
befitting the Earl
of Yarborough.
All right, you've
made your point.
Hey, I can't screw this up or Lisa
will get stuck with someone like me.
Homie, I don't have
a problem with you.
Except your buttons
are off one.
Actually, this is a collar
button, see? It goes like this...
Tuh! Is there no end
to your fault-finding?
Maggie, help me
with this shirt.
(groans)
(Homer and Lisa laughing)
So Mr. Burns never realized it
was Maggie who saved the plant?
Nope. Now, how's
that drink?
Can I Temple up
that Shirley?
Oh, I'm fine.
(giggles)
Well, have we decided?
Uh, yeah, help me out here.
What is the normal amount
of entrees per person?
Eh, one, sir.
- I mean for adults.
- One.
No, I mean for
adult males.
Yes. I repeat, eh, one.
All right, I'll
have the lasagna.
All right. Meat
or vegetarian?
Oh, uh... Oh...
Vegetarian.
(quietly): Can the red
sauce be cow blood?
We'll see what we can do.
Is that Mom?
Homer, can you come
with me for a minute?
Marge, please, control your jealousy.
This is your daughter.
We need to have a conversation
in loud whispers.
Uh, excuse me, Lisa.
A friend from high school.
Homie, I felt terrible when you
said I felt stuck with you.
But then I realized:
I am stuck with you.
I couldn't stop loving
you if I tried.
I'm sorry, that's
all very nice.
But I can't forget
what you said.
I know, Homie. I know
you well enough to know
you're not ready
to forgive me yet.
But I also know you well enough
to know that this will work.
Where'd you get
that dress?
Remember that sewing machine
you say I never use?
Well, I sold it and
bought this dress.
Wow... Wow, that
looks just like
the dress you wore
on Project Runway.
- Shush-shush-shush.
- Oh, right.
I mean, this looks like a dress
from a local Springfield store.
All is forgiven.
Let's have dinner.
(clears throat)
Dad, I believe we
were on a date?
Oh, of course.
You're right, honey.
I'll just, um... I'll
park it at the bar.
Well, hello.
And your lasagna
with cow blood, sir.
- Thanks, Frenchy.
- I'm not French,
I'm just pissy.
Lucas. You're not
competitive eating anymore?
No. I realized that
was unrealistic.
Well, that's a relief.
My new goal is to become
whatever Adele is.
Just call me Pound-Uca-Dollar.
(chuckles)
What if I just taught
you how to whistle?
You know how to whistle?
Like with your mouth?
(whistles)
(blows air)
Hey, I'm doing it!
(blowing air)
I sound just like a bird!
(whistling theme song)
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
Shh!