The Simpsons
D'oh!
What are you reading,
Homie?
The Bridge column.
Oh, that South.
You never know
what he'll do next.
Oh, look at that,
"Dad and Drabble. "
He's like
an unfunny version of me.
Where's Bart?
His Mountain Dew's
getting flat.
That's odd.
He's outside digging.
Probably digging for drugs.
There's no drugs
out there.
No, of course not.
It's not a school project.
I'd have heard of it.
I'd better go
check it out.
What are you doing?
Digging.
Why?
To make a hole.
A hole for what?
More digging.
Okay, then.
Don't worry, Marge.
I'll find out
what he's up to.
Kids shouldn't
have secrets.
Oh, hello, young man.
Beautiful day for
digging, isn't it?
Yep.
Yeah.
Uh...
Digging for
anything in particular?
Nuh-uh.
So, I guess you
wouldn't mind if I was
to dig a hole of my own?
Go for it.
Maybe I will.
What's stopping you?
Very little.
I'm having chest pains.
Where's the defibrillator?
Clear!
This thing pays for itself.
Bart? This is Dr. Kaufmann.
He's a special kind
of "talking" doctor.
Call me Bob.
Well, that's quite
a hole you're digging.
Thanks, Bob.
You know, a hole is
a great place to hide
when people are fighting.
Are there angry people
in your house?
My dad's always yelling
that whitey's
keeping him down.
I see.
You keep digging like this,
you're gonna go straight
through to China.
If it happens, it happens.
Those inscrutable Americans.
What are they up to now?
I will stop them.
I am strong.
I am the Great Humungus!
We all know you're
the Great Humungus!
Well, I'm just saying...
Oh, you're always
"just saying. "
Homer,
is this story going anywhere?
Yes. Eventually,
I become king
of the Morlocks.
But Morlocks are
from the future.
You calling me a liar?
Wait a minute, Homer.
If it's true,
what about all the stuff
you weren't around for?
Yeah. How'd you know
the Chinese were
spying on you?
Well,
I just naturally assumed.
That is the stupidest
story I ever heard.
And I've read the entire
Sweet Valley High series.
I am sick of you drunks
and your shaggy dog stories.
Sorry, Shaggy.
Now I got to
go home to that!
Thanks a lot!
Oh, quit your bellyaching,
Coffee Boy.
You're lucky
I let you in here.
Geez, Moe. You've been
a real crank lately.
You take that back!
Now you see?
That's what I'm
talking about.
You're always pointing
that shotgun at us.
And calling us "dumbasses. "
Which we're so not.
Well, can you blame me?
Every day it's
the same old routine.
I serve you drinks,
You yak on and on and on,
and I never get
one stinking tip.
Maybe we'd tip you
if you'd smile
once in awhile.
What do you call this?
Don't do that.
Who am I kidding?
I ain't smiled for real
since I nailed that
rat with the ice pick.
Remember that?
That was an amazing throw.
How did I lose my
passion for the job?
When I was in
bartending school,
I thought I had
the world by the jigger.
Hey, where'd that
painting come from?
I put this up recently,
and it's a good thing I did
because it really
illustrates my point.
Yeah, good old Swigmore U.
Gee, when you talk
about that school,
your voice fills with...
What do you call it?
Human feeling.
Yeah. Maybe you should...
What's the expression?
Go back there.
What's the word
I'm searching for?
Uh...
Yeah.
A trip to the alma mater
might really rekindle my love
of getting people loaded.
But who'll run the bar
while you're gone?
Ooh! Ooh! Pick me!
Pick me, Lenny!
Oh, pick me!
I'm an urban Lenny!
Look, I don't want to start
a tinkling contest here.
Or do I?
Woo-hoo!
Oh, don't look so proud.
That was wind-assisted.
And if anybody
wants potato chips
or anything fancy,
tell them to go to hell!
Can do.
Now don't you
worry about a thing.
Hey, what are you doing?
I got to pay for that!
No, Moe.
You've got it all wrong.
People buy beer from you.
Look, I got to go.
I thought you said
you had to go?
Ah, the old college gates.
Ah, geez.
The old college clock.
Man, when's the last time
Moe cleaned this?
Hey, Homer, another Duff.
Hey, Homer, do you mind
if I bring in some
outside food?
Well, I don't know.
What would Moe
say about that?
But on the other hand,
Moe's not here.
Homer, you're the greatest.
Hey!
Lenny!
Sorry. Sorry.
For what?
A little splattered food
never hurt anybody.
Now everybody
shut up and dance!
Matty told Hatty
About a thing she saw
Had two big horns
As time goes on
I realize
I realize...
Hey, what happened
to the music?
Don't worry.
You got to hit it
just right, like Fonzie.
Eh!
Oh! Whoa!
Hemorrhage-amundo!
Are you gonna be okay?
Eh!
Now can anyone tell me
how much grenadine is in
a Cosmopolitan?
None.
A Cosmopolitan is made
with cranberry juice.
Moe Szyslak,
you old glasswipe.
Yello?
Yeah. I'd like to speak
to a Mr. Tabooger.
First name Ollie.
Ooh! Bart!
My first prank call.
What do I do?
Just ask if anyone
knows Ollie Tabooger.
I don't get it.
Yell out,
"I'll eat a booger. "
What's the gag?
Oh, forget it!
Professor, I'm...
I'm burned out
on bartending.
When I first saw
the movie Ironweed,
I thought, you know,
this is for me.
But now, well,
I'm not so sure.
Nonsense.
You were born
to sling suds.
The problem
must lie elsewhere.
Describe your tavern
in one word.
Uh...
Is "crap-hole" one word?
Yes, if it's hyphenated.
Then I'll stick
with crap-hole.
Well,
no wonder you're depressed
working in that environment.
If you want my advice,
beautify your hole,
and you'll
beautify your soul.
Nice hole, nice soul.
Hmm.
Look at that pond.
Why does the water
sparkle so?
I'm dying, Moe.
Is there anything
I can do?
No. Unless you have
a cure for cancer.
Do you have
a cure for cancer?
Because that would be great!
I'm sorry, Professor.
Goodbye, Moe.
Bye, Professor.
Hey, don't you want to
take your shoes off
before you go swimming?
Professor?
Oh.
Um...
Hmm.
I'm a-walking down the street
Gonna open Moe's bar
I'm a-singing
what I'm thinking
Hey, look at that dog...
Huh?
Teen vandals
smashing the bar!
Moe's gonna kill me!
Hey, Homer.
You dirty teen!
Hey, Homer, stop!
Stop! It's me!
Sheesh!
Moe wrecking Moe's bar?
I almost fainted,
but then I didn't.
What are you doing?
My professor said
if I prettied up this dump,
it would renew my zeal.
And it would
look pretty, too.
And now I want
you to meet the guy
who's gonna help bring Moe's
into the 20th century.
I am Formico,
the dean of design.
Hi, Formico.
Uh-uh-uh.
My name must never
be spoken.
Sorry. He seems nice.
Not fair.
Just when I was
getting to be the world's
greatest bartender,
it's all snatched away.
Freshen your drink, pal?
Just leave the bottle.
There you go, doll.
Ew!
Look, buddy.
I don't care where you go,
but you can't sleep here.
Wow.
Check out the new Moe's.
It looks like an
alien headquarters.
Couldn't you just see aliens
running out of there?
Couldn't you?
Hey, wait up!
Looks like a long wait
to get in.
Not for friends of Moe's.
Oi! Oi!
Is your name on the list?
Don't you know who I am?
It's okay, Cecil.
They're VIPs.
Cecil is a girl's name.
Oh!
Welcome to m!
So, what do you
think of the new joint?
This place
looks like it's from
the not-too-distant future.
Yeah. You like it, Homer?
Um...
The rabbits are cute.
That one ain't moving.
Change number seven.
I don't get all
this eyeball stuff.
What are they supposed
to represent? Eyeballs?
It's Po-Mo.
Postmodern.
Yeah, all right.
Weird for the sake of weird.
Oh!
Where are the barstools?
Up there.
Ain't it trippy?
Whatever.
Just give me a Duff.
We don't serve Duff
no more.
We got a Malaysian beer
that's better than Duff.
It's made out of soy sauce.
Whatever.
Just give me a Duff.
Hey, Formico.
Say hello to my
beloved regulars.
Oh, hello.
Moe, would you like to meet
some attractive young models?
Models? Oh, boy.
Okay,
look cool.
Wait a minute.
You're all from Russia?
And you really think
I'm attractive, huh?
I don't know.
What's so great
about this oxygen bar?
Yeah, I think I'm
getting the bends.
Lenny, stand on my chest.
I'm trapped.
This is creative
design run amok.
That's it!
I'm gonna tell Moe exactly
what I think of his...
After Chernobyl,
my penis is falling off.
And "penis" is
Russian for...
Moe, we want our bar back!
Yeah, this place
is crazy!
All these beautiful people
make us feel like losers!
You'd be having a great time
if you'd stayed
in your dark spot.
Oh,
so you're ashamed of us.
Well, you've turned
into a big phony!
Hey! Nobody calls
Moe St. Cool a phony!
All this yelling
is taking away my horny.
Is it? Oh, that's it...
That... Dagmar, Julian.
Throw this bum out.
I'll throw myself out,
thank you.
I believe I had a hat!
Suckers!
What are you doing, Dad?
I think it's pretty obvious.
I'm turning our garage
into a tavern!
The kind Moe's used to be.
This is pretty far to go
just to spite Moe.
It's not about spite.
It's about petty revenge
and getting back at
that traitor, Moe!
Now help me nail up
this urinal.
Beautiful.
Running a bar
is a full-time job,
and you don't even do
your full-time job.
But when I'm
passionate about something,
I see it through to the end!
Father, give me legs.
Father!
That is so interesting.
So what you talking about?
Something interesting?
No, I was just comparing
Kurosawa's films to Herzog's.
Uh-huh.
Carry on.
My diet lets me eat anything
I want for one minute a day.
My youth consultant
gives me Botox injections
in my head,
neck, and navel.
Hiya, pal.
So how about
them current events?
Oh, you got one of them
cell phones, huh?
Yeah.
No cord at all on those.
Hey, game's on!
Hey, we were watching that!
Come on!
Sports!
Unless you're being ironic,
turn that off now.
I'm glad you ain't around
to see what a mess I made.
Oh, but I am.
You've discarded
your loyal regulars
for a mob of soulless snobs.
Well, at least
the tips are good.
Are they, Moe?
Take a look.
Oh!
Hey, why you mocking me?
We're friends.
Oh, right. Sorry.
I won't drink at Moe's!
Homer's old garage
is all I need
I won't drink at Moe's!
Because Moe's a big jerk
and a she-male, too!
That calls for
another beer.
Barkeep!
I thought this was
gonna be your bar.
It's a family bar.
Right, kids?
Can we go to bed now?
As soon as you finish
cutting up those lemons.
But you're not
even using them.
She's so "sweepy. "
She doesn't know
what she's saying.
Aw!
Who am I kidding?
I ain't Moe St. Cool.
How could I toss my friends
out into the cold
with no place to
get liquored up.
Hey, what's going on?
We're rocking great!
Mount St. Edelite
Leonard Bernstein
Leonard what's-his-name
Herman Munster motorcade
Birthday party, Cheetos
Pogo sticks and lemonade
You symbiotic, stupid jerk
That's right, Flanders
I'm talking about you
How did you
get R. E.M. to play
in your garage?
I told them it was a benefit.
They think they're
saving the rain forest!
Suckers!
Yeah, baby!
Michael, are you sure
these guys are millionaires?
Come on.
Would a poor person
have a bar in his garage?
Hey, guys.
Stand around me.
I can't go with
Lenny watching.
So, got to pee, huh?
Forget it.
What the...
You can't open your own bar!
Seems to me I already did.
But it's illegal!
You can't run a bar
in a private residence!
Bar? I see no bar.
This is a hunting club.
Which is permitted
by state law
to serve beverages
of a refreshing nature.
Hunting club?
You lied to us!
Michael, no!
That's not
the R. E.M. way.
You're right.
Let's recycle those shards
and get out of here.
Here we go.
It also says,
"A licensed hunting club
must actively
"engage in
the sport of hunting. "
Which I'll be doing
tomorrow morning,
smart guy!
Hunting? Dad, no!
Lemons.
It's not fair, Dad.
Why should an animal die
just because you and Moe
are fighting?
It's the law.
My hands are tied.
Okay. Cranberry sauce,
stuffing, potatoes.
Come on, turkey!
Join your friends!
Do you really
think the turkey's
just gonna climb
onto the plate?
I would.
Psst. Lisa.
Moe?
Listen. I don't like you
and you don't like me,
but we both want to
stop Homer from
shooting a turkey.
You don't like me?
I like you.
You do?
Then I like you, too.
Here. Have a towelette.
Here,
turkey-turkey-turkey!
Turkey-turkey-turkey-
turkey-turkey!
Nobody's gonna kill you.
All right.
From now on, no talking.
If you want to signal me,
use this bird call.
Ow! Ow!
Not the face!
Ooh! Ooh!
Okay, the face!
Oh, that actually feels good
after the crotch.
All right,
turkey, where are you?
Turkeys, the only animal
smarter than man.
What the hell is that?
A turkey!
Dad's gonna slaughter
that poor turkey!
Not if I scare it away
with this cougar call.
You did it, Moe!
A cougar! Die, cougar!
My leg! Oh, geez!
Got that cat
right in the leg.
Dad, you shot Moe!
Oh, no! This time
I really am gonna faint!
Son of a...
How'd they get
your bar back to normal
so quickly, Moe?
It's a snap when
you use certified contractors.
Like the ones found in
your local yellow pages?
Exactly.
I'm sorry I shot you, Moe.
Aw, that's okay.
It's like my dad
always said,
"Eventually
everybody gets shot. "
Oh, I'm glad you two
are friends again
so we can all have
Thanksgiving dinner
together in this bar.
Hey,
who invited the hippies?
I did. You owe R. E.M.
an apology for eco-fraud.
All right, I'm sorry.
But I will not
save the rain forest!
Good enough.
Let's eat.
And we should all
be thankful to Michael,
Peter, and Mike
for supplying
this beautiful turkey
made entirely of tofu.
Tofu and gluten.
I'm thankful
I ate before I came.
Oh, come on, Bart.
Smell those curds.
Mmm!
Curds.
And I'm thankful
I get to spend Thanksgiving
with my family,
these alternative rockers,
and my favorite bartender.
Here you go, pal.
And here you go!
ENGLISH - US - PSDH