The Simpsons
D'oh!
The Itchy
and Scratchy Show!
Tee one up
for me, catty.
Sure thing, mousy.
Nice follow-through!
Now that's what I call
a moon shot.
Dad, that line was
in the cartoon.
I'm pretty sure it wasn't.
Our phone bill is $400!
They charged us
for a call to Brazil.
Boy, did you make
a prank call to Brazil?
No, sir. I didn't.
Choke on your lies!
Homer, they must've
made a mistake.
We'll just go down
to the phone company
and straighten it out.
Which phone company?
There are hundreds of them.
And they all keep
changing their names.
I think
we're with Comquaaq.
No,
I think its Niagular.
No, last week they
became Vertiqual.
Wow.
Everything is so high-tech.
Dialing Murray Hill,
5-6-3-0-9.
So, I says to Myrna,
I says, "That guy's a bum!"
Ooh! That's the
Movie Phone guy.
The movie we've selected
plays at 8:00 p. m.
at Springfield Cinema Six.
Thank you for dating
Mr. Movie Phone.
Our evening
will be rated R,
for brief nudity.
Ma'am, would you
be interested in
changing your
long-distance service if...
What the...
She hung up on me!
What did I do?
Hello. I'm your
customer service rep,
Lindsay Naegle.
We've met you many times,
Miss Naegle.
Why do you keep
changing jobs?
I'm a sexual predator.
Oh.
Now, how may I best
dispense with you today?
We've been charged
for calls to Brazil
that we didn't make.
We are not
paying this bill.
Fine.
I'll cut off your service.
Fine!
I'll cut off your ponytail!
Homer!
Marge,
it's called negotiating.
Ooh. Fascinating.
I need to call Janie,
but I can't get a dial tone.
We're not paying our bill,
so the phone company
shut off our service.
Why must you fight
with every utility?
I told you,
I have too much
time on my hands.
Homer.
We were cleaning out
a cooling duct at the plant
and found a box
of old taco shells.
Oh, why didn't you call me?
We tried,
but a recording said
you were
a bunch of deadbeats. Mmm.
That's it!
They have awoken
a sleeping giant.
Homer,
what are you going to do?
Crazy scheme,
crazy scheme,
crazy scheme.
Get me tools and beer!
Yes!
Free service,
here we come.
All right.
Let's try the red one.
Okay. I'll try the green.
Let's try the red one again.
Oh, not again!
Let's try them together.
Maybe the red one.
How did I get here?
We found you
smoldering in the bushes.
That's it!
We're just going to have to
pay for that call to Brazil!
What call to Brazil?
The one I didn't make
and Marge didn't make
and Bart didn't make
and hence, no one
in the house made.
Uh-oh.
You made that call?
But you're the good one.
Yeah. The one we both like.
Why did you do it?
Please don't be mad.
I've been sponsoring
an orphan boy in Brazil.
Oh, aren't you sweet?
Sharing your allowance
with a poor Brazilian boy.
Don't you know
the boys from Brazil
are little Hitlers?
I saw it in a movie,
whose name I can't remember!
Ronaldo used to
send me a letter
every month,
but then they stopped.
That's why
I called the orphanage.
But they said he disappeared.
How come you talked
for $400?
Well, then they
started pressuring me
for more donations,
and you can't
hang up on a nun.
That's right.
They have powers.
When I sent my
first donation,
the charity mailed me
this video.
Hi, Lisa.
Thank you for your donation.
Because of your generosity,
I bought sturdy shoes
that will last for
a thousand sambas!
Aw!
He's so adorable.
Can we have another baby?
No way! I still haven't
lost the weight I put on
from the last one.
And with the money left over,
the orphanage was able
to buy a door.
Now the monkeys
cannot bite me.
Uh-oh.
I am like sugar to them.
Oh.
That poor little boy.
We've got to find him.
How many people
live in Brazil?
A hundred and
fifty-six million.
D'oh!
Well, we've got to find him!
What? I'm really concerned.
Fine.
I want to meet monkeys.
I don't know.
It's awfully expensive
to fly to Brazil.
Not if we buy our
tickets on the Internet.
It's really cheap
if we change planes
in Phoenix,
Honolulu, Sun City
and East Saint Louis,
spend a night
in a haunted house
and leave right now.
Then it's settled.
The Simpsons are
going to Brazil!
And I'll have been
on every continent.
Except Antarctica.
The Simpsons are
going to Antarctica
next year. This year, Brazil.
Okay,
here are some travel tips.
"Only drink bottled water.
"Don't get into
an unlicensed taxi.
"And remember,
they have winter
during our summer. "
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
So, in August, it's cold?
That's right.
And in February, it's hot?
Mmm-hmm.
So, it's opposite land!
Crooks chase cops,
cats have puppies.
No, Dad.
It's just the weather.
So, hot snow falls up?
Yes.
Woo-hoo!
Get ready, Brazil.
I now speak fluent Spanish.
Well done, Bart.
But in Brazil,
they speak Portuguese.
Forget every word, boy.
It's useless.
But, Homer...
I said forget it!
All gone.
This is your
captain speaking.
The local temperature
in Rio de Janeiro
is hot, hot, hot,
with 100% chance of passion!
Fernando, you make
that joke every time.
It was that joke
that made you
fall in love with me.
Hey, Maggie,
how are you
doing back there?
Oh, so helpless.
Look,
it's the giant statue
of Christ on Corcovado.
Wow. It's like
he's on the dashboard
of the entire country.
It says here we can
get anywhere we want
by taking a conga line.
Way ahead of you, Marge.
Take me to the hotel
My hands are on a guy's ass
Boy, this dude must work out
Hey! Hey!
Boy, they sure love
soccer here.
Kick it!
Goal!
Look, Marge.
I'm Brazilian!
"How to Loot Brazil"?
I got it!
Bart,
what are you watching?
Kids' show.
Bert and Ernie
left it to your imagination.
Look, the room
came with a fruit hat.
Hey, and a mini bar hat!
I'm Chiquita Banana
and I'm here to say
I will eat this Toblerone
and I will not pay
Guys! While you're
singing and dancing,
somewhere out there
Ronaldo is waiting
to be found.
There he is! Oh, wait.
You said brown hair, right?
What a charming neighborhood.
Mom, these are slums.
The government just
painted them bright colors
so the tourists
wouldn't be offended.
Works for me.
Yeah. Check out the rats.
Ooh! They look like Skittles!
Here we are!
"123 Papaya Street. "
This is Ronaldo's orphanage.
Excuse me.
We're looking for
this little boy.
Ah, yes. Ronaldo.
He went out months ago.
And we haven't
heard from him since.
Every day we light
a candle for him.
Have you tried
looking for him?
That's plan B.
We're never
going to find him.
Now, Lisa,
it's not as bleak as that.
Can you fly me over
town to look for him?
We nuns cannot fly.
Oh, too much
junk in the trunk, eh?
Yes.
Have some meat
on a sword, Lisa.
It'll cheer you up.
You know I'm a vegetarian.
But you're on vacation,
honey.
I'm not wearing
my wedding ring.
Homer!
Okay. On this map I marked
all the places that
Ronaldo liked to go.
If we split up,
we should be able
to search them all.
We'll do our best.
Now, let's get going!
Check, please.
Si!
Does that include tip?
Hey, look.
There's Copacabana beach!
The heart and soul of Rio!
Excuse me, Americans!
How did you know?
There is a dress code
on this beach.
But we can help you.
I feel so European.
Huh. Mine keeps disappearing.
Oh, well.
Oh, I hope they're
going somewhere good.
Okay, boy.
Let's strut our stuff.
I'm in Rio
and I'm walking on the beach
I'm in my Speedo
No! No, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Excuse me.
We think this boy
might be here.
Okay, this is a samba school.
This is not a lost and found.
This is where we invented
the lambada and the macarena.
We are now developing
our most powerful dance,
the penetrada.
It makes sex
look like a church!
I don't think my daughter
should hear this.
You can't
protect her forever!
You stupid lady!
Give me a drink with all your
sweetest Brazilian fruits
mixed together.
Here you go.
Sweet. Sweet. Sweet!
There's got to be
a million kids here.
We'll never find Ronaldo.
Ronaldo?
You know him?
No, no.
I was just distracting you
while my children robbed you.
Oh, look at all
the stuffed coatimundi.
I bet Maggie would like one.
I'll just get
her this bracelet.
Everything here
is something.
Hey, Bart.
How many more places
do we have to search?
Just one,
and it's across town.
Taxi!
My American friend,
I'm afraid that this
is a kidnapping.
So that means
I don't have to pay the fare?
I suppose...
Woo-hoo!
I'm afraid you
don't appreciate
the seriousness
of the situation.
Fine. Take me,
but let the boy go!
I'm afraid he has
already gone.
Where are you taking me?
Shut up. And take that
stupid bag off your head.
No. It smells like cinnamon.
Behold, the Amazon.
But quick because
we're burning it down.
Listen,
I really need a rest stop.
Again?
I have a bladder
the size of a Brazil nut.
We just call them nuts here.
Suckers.
Suckers!
I guess
planning a vacation
around a missing kid
is not the way
to have fun.
Hey.
Time for
Brazil's favorite
kids' show, Teleboobies.
Clockwise!
Counter-clockwise.
Where's your father?
Kidnapped.
Oh, my God!
What are we supposed to do?
I don't know.
Wait for the call.
On top of. Beneath.
So, you want me to
find your husband?
Yes.
And you also want me
to find a little boy?
That's right.
I don't think there
is a boy or a husband!
I think you have
a thing for me.
I've been shot!
I am flattered,
but I do not swing that way.
I have another itch.
Yeah, well,
scratch it yourself.
I'm not going there again.
I have sent the ransom note.
If your family wants
to see you alive again,
they would be wise to pay.
I don't know.
They've been seeing me alive
for free for a long time.
So, have you got
the $50,000?
Well, with all our savings
and the money
Grampa wired us,
we have $1,200.
That's very nice, honey.
That'll buy you
one of my legs
or something they
call a mystery bag.
I'll get back to you.
They have $1,200.
$1,200?
You've already
eaten that much.
Come on. I didn't...
Well, maybe.
Enough of your blarney!
Get the money!
Ahoy-hoy.
Mr. Burns,
it's Homer Simpson.
I've been kidnapped
and I need $50,000.
Hmm. Well,
I'm high on sheep embryos,
so I am feeling charitable.
How about
I advance you the money
and you work it off?
No deal!
Moe's Tavern.
Home of the stinkiest
rag in America!
Hey, Moe.
Homer, listen.
I need 50 grand.
Don't ask me why.
No, no.
I need 50 grand!
I asked you first!
Fine.
I'll send you 50 grand.
Thanks.
Hello, Flanders.
I need 100 grand.
Well, I don't
really have that much.
But if you need it that bad,
you'll be in my prayers.
Go suck a Bible!
This is all my fault.
I came to find someone,
but now I've just
lost Dad and...
What is that noise?
That irritating,
intoxicating music
with a beat
that sends your
inhibitions packing?
It's Carnival!
Oh, your father
would've loved this.
The drunkenness,
the ambiguous sexuality...
I've got to
get out of here!
You cannot run from Carnival!
Because even running
is a kind of dance!
I am on fire, and I dance!
I'll just dance and
worry at the same time.
Hey, look!
It's the stripper
from the kids' show.
She makes paying
attention cool.
Lisa! Lisa!
It's me, Ronaldo!
Ronaldo!
Yes.
I am Flamenco Flamingo.
And it all started
with the dancing shoes
you bought me.
Why didn't you tell me?
I tried to write.
But I didn't know
what state you lived in.
It's a bit of a mystery, yes.
But if you look at the clues,
you can figure it out.
Oh, no!
The parade, she starts.
Meet me at the estudio.
Where is it?
That way!
Here is the ransom
for your father.
Are you sure
you can afford it?
I make as much as
Malcolm in the Middle.
And because I
have no parents,
my earnings remain unstolen.
We're supposed to
bring the ransom money
to the top of
Sugar Loaf Mountain.
The tension is killing me!
How about this?
That's not tense enough.
It's making light
of the situation.
Yup, that's it.
Just right.
That's the one.
Look, there's Dad!
Listen,
I made a little scrapbook
to remember the kidnapping.
I'm still working on it.
But as you can see...
Look.
This is that cigarette butt
you burned me with.
You slept like a baby
that night.
I remember that, yeah.
Homer,
why are you laughing?
He has
the Stockholm syndrome.
He has come
to identify with
his captors.
They let me
stay up all night!
Well, you won't be
doing that at home.
Now, hand over the money
and you get your Homer back.
Look at all that
pink and purple.
Our money sure is gay.
You are free to go.
Woo-hoo!
Piece of cake!
We should make
these transfers
in a safer place.
It was Homer's idea.
You say no to that face.
Homie, are you okay?
Yes, honey.
I'm better than okay.
Because I've learned
that no matter
how bad I screw up,
you'll always bail me out.
Aw...
Mom? Dad?
We better do
something about this.
Don't be sad.
It's Carnival!
Whoopee!
English - US - PSDH