CHORUS [SINGS]:
The Simpsons
Old Yeller-Belly
[BELL RINGING]
[WHISTLE BLOWING]
[BEEPING]
[LISA PLAYS SOLO]
D'oh! Ah!
[BART & MARTIN & NELSON
& DATABASE & MILHOUSE SINGING]
Glory, glory, hallelujah
Teacher hit me with a ruler
I cracked her in the bean
With a frozen Jimmy Dean
And she ain't my teacher no more
Because she's dead
Mr. Secretary, can you read
the minutes of our last meeting?
"Girls are yucky.
Seconded and carried.
A fart was detected. Martin denied it...
- ...and so was ruled to have supplied it."
- Good.
Security officer,
anything on the scope?
MAN:
Mm-hm, Mm-hm, hmm.
These Batpants have been shredded
by the Riddler.
No, just your ass.
That's what I call my ass.
MARTIN:
Oh! Lisa is having a tea party.
If I understand the female mind,
and I do, they're plotting against us.
We've gotta get audio.
Uh, I'm on it.
[GRUNTING]
LISA:
Janey, more tea?
Operation Ladybug is a go, eh! Over.
Today, Balthazar will tell us
about global warming...
...in the land beyond the rainbow.
Each year we lose seven species
of gumdrops.
[IMITATING MARGE]
Lisa, this is your mother.
The doctor says your butt's too big.
That's not Mom.
[GASPS]
Oh, someone is spying on us.
[GRUNTING]
[ALL GRUNTING]
No one told me there'd be pulling.
[ALL SCREAMING]
Skinned elbows?
All right! Time to score some pity.
[WHIMPERING]
Mommy!
Don't worry, son.
I'll build you a new tree house.
One so grand...
- ...it'll be an affront to God himself.
- Can it have a rope ladder...
- ...you can pull up after you?
- Only if it's an affront to God.
- Hey, you passed the lumberyard.
- Only losers buy wood.
We're going to nature's lumberyard.
[HOMER LAUGHS]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Isn't this dangerous?
It's okay, Bart.
This track has been abandoned
since 19... Uh-oh.
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
Nothing beats flying across the country
on a train.
I'm impressed
that you drew up blueprints...
...but these are for a go-cart track.
Hmm. Did Frank Lloyd Wright
have to deal with people like you?
Actually, Frank Lloyd Wright endured
a lot of harsh criticism.
I have no idea
who Frank Lloyd Wright is.
You said his name two seconds ago.
I was just putting words together.
[HOMER COUGHS THEN SNEEZES]
- Ha, ha, gotcha.
- Well, two can play at that game.
Ow! Ha, ha.
Oh, that's it. You are going down.
Ha, ha. Don't! Stop it!
[LAUGHS THEN GRUNTS]
[BOTH LAUGHING]
That tree house is never gonna get built
at this rate.
Time to call in the pros.
[RINGING]
Didst thou hear that, Isaac?
Aye. Someone needs the Amish.
To the Buggymobile!
[WHISTLES]
[ALL GRUNTING]
Oh, the Amish are so industrious.
Not like those shiftless Mennonites.
MENNONITE 1:
Roll them bones. Three craps.
Son, that tree house is gonna be bigger
and better than ever.
It really restores your faith
in helpful weirdoes.
[CHATTERING]
Bumblebee Man, mi tree
house is su bee house.
Reverend, love the cassock.
Moleman, looking good.
Very nice.
Did you do the wiring yourself?
Heck, no. The Amish did it.
Who knows more about electricity
than the Amish?
[ALL SCREAMING]
Watch your step! Don't panic!
By going down the ladder,
you're agreeing not to sue.
[SCREAMING]
[GRUNTS]
Head burning.
Legs freezing.
Middle very pleasant.
Oh, thank God. The dog's here.
Pull me free, boy.
Don't be scared. You can do it.
[WHIMPERS]
Hey, where you going?
I'm your pal.
I took you for a walk once.
[SNARLS]
[COUGHS]
[SIGHS]
[SNARLS]
Family head count.
Pointy, pointy, spiky, stylish...
Aah! Where's baldy?
[HOMER SHOUTING]
[GRUNTS]
[MEOWS]
What's the...? Wha...?
[CATERWAULS]
[SCREAMS]
Flames? Searing pain? A black cat?
I must be in heaven.
MARGE:
Homie, get out of that tree house!
Move the net under the window!
MARGE:
There's no net!
[HOMER SHOUTS]
I always thought cats were just
for losers who live in apartments...
...until my life was saved
by this sweet little kitty.
[MEOWS]
But as for you,
Santa's Little Helper...
...you are a selfish coward
and a bad dog!
[WHIMPERS]
Get out!
And stay out!
[WHIMPERS]
[SCRATCHING ON DOOR]
Our little hero sure likes
Kahlua and cream.
[WHIMPERS]
Quit following me, you coward!
You heard him, fleabag.
Get out of my bar. You're unsanitary.
Oh, how precious.
The cat's sitting in my dinner.
No, no. Don't get up, sweetheart.
I'll just pick around you.
Here we go.
Mm. Ha, ha.
Long live the hero cat of Springfield!
[CROWD CHEERING]
I make you lasagna.
You eat it up like the cat
in the funny papers...
...who's not so funny.
Today I can truly say
Ich bin ein feline.
And I hereby
rename Springfield Dog Park...
...the Snowball II Municipal Cat Park
sponsored by Buzz Cola with Lemon.
Damn, that's a lemony cola.
[WHIMPERING]
[ALL GROWLING]
Mr. Simpson,
how long have you been a cat person?
All my life, Kent.
I prefer catsup to ketchup.
And to me, Yusuf Islam will always be
Cat Stevens.
[LAUGHS]
Terrific stuff. You must really love
the Broadway musical Cats.
- God, no. It sucks.
- Seems like you're quite the animal lover.
Do you have any other pets?
A dog, perhaps?
Kent, let me make this perfectly clear.
I have no dog.
[WHIMPERS]
Strong words.
Strong words from a strange man.
Don't worry.
We'll get you out of the doghouse.
And then you and Dad will be
chasing butterflies together again.
Here's a role model for you, boy.
Rin Tin Tin.
He was brave on and off the screen.
He was the first openly gay dog
in Hollywood.
[BARKS]
[SNARLING]
[SPEAKING IN GERMAN]
He bit me right in the Axis!
See? Now that's the kind of dog
you should be.
Mailman.
[GROWLS]
[MAILMAN GRUNTS]
"Grow a mustache," says the wife.
"You'll look handsome,"
says the wife.
[SANTA'S LITTLE HELPER
GROWLING]
Hmm, needs beer.
Why, you little...!
[GRUNTING]
Stop it, Homer. That's inhumane.
- Use the choke chain.
- Fine.
I want you to sit there, look through
the window, and watch me eat a ham.
Marge, prepare the emergency ham.
[GROANS]
[SNIFFS]
Oh. This is the kind of shot
you only get once in a lifetime.
Once in a lifetime.
Hmm. This photo gives me an idea.
We might've found
our new Duff spokesperson.
He's young, he's slim,
and he can stand on his hind legs.
Unlike our current spokesman.
Oh!
Duffman could use an eye-opener.
Take a hike, Duffman.
You're a disgrace to the unitard.
You're firing me?
But what about my children?
Duffgirl and Dufflad?
Oh, those were one-shot characters
in a Super Bowl ad.
Oh, yeah.
According to this contract...
...we have to change his name
to Suds McDuff.
I don't care if his name is Bony McDork.
Just make the checks out to me.
It also says
"we will receive royalties in perpetuity...
...a bottomless keg of beer...
...and unlimited use
of the Duff corporate jet."
Corporate jet?
Oh, pilot, let's swing by,
oh, Heidelberg.
And drop in on Oktoberfest.
[SCREAMING]
Sweet.
Welcome back to the family, boy.
Dad, five minutes ago you hated him.
Who are you? My biographer?
[KRUSTY THEME MUSIC
PLAYING ON TV]
Krusty, our animal today
is the toxic pricker snake.
Very good.
Now, let me stand on my mark...
...between the snake and its baby...
[SCREAMS]
Cut to commercial!
Hey, boy. This is your commercial.
Houston, we have a problem.
This place is dullsville.
How can you get a buzz
chewing freeze-dried beer?
BOTH:
Wha...?
It's Suds McDuff.
Where the shuttlecraft
is genuine draft.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
- Whoo!
- Ooh, party.
ANNOUNCER:
Duff, the official beer of NASA.
National Association
of the Sellers of Alcohol.
[CHEERING]
Why does a dog have
human girlfriends?
People do crazy things in ads.
Like eat at Arby's.
Eight, nine, 10 wads of cash.
Your dog has sent Duff Beer sales
through the roof.
Boy,
you're now second best in the family.
Right ahead of Marge.
[BARKS]
[DOOR OPENS]
There you are, old pal.
Ha, I finally found you.
Who the hell are you?
I'm this dog's owner.
I raced him at the greyhound track
under the name Santa's Little Helper.
Good times.
Well, he's not yours anymore.
You threw him out on Christmas Eve.
Yeah, don't listen to him, Mr. Duff VII.
We took this dog in and loved him.
And that makes him ours.
Oh, really?
Well, this tape says different.
Kent, let me make this
perfectly clear.
I have no dog.
Dad, you can't let him take our dog.
My wads!
I never even broke the wrapper.
[CRYING]
Who's gonna eat my homework now?
Okay, boy, fetch!
What do you do for fun?
[COUGHS]
Suds, you're looking great.
Did you have a bath or something?
Look, I'm talking to a dog.
So, what do you think?
If I keep talking here, Kelly can't jump in.
Come on, Suds. Toss me a bone.
Poor Santa's Little Helper.
He's overworked.
Suds, I hear you're doing
game shows now.
Gelman, roll the clip.
[BARKING]
Uh, things you buy in a dime store.
Uh, famous first ladies.
Uh, things your
toothbrush might say.
[YELLING]
[GROWLS]
Later that day,
you had a book signing.
[CHATTERING]
That guy exploits his pets
worse than Bob Guccione.
Well, I'm afraid the law is clear.
And Dad did renounce all claim
to ownership.
But I miss him.
He was my best friend.
[SOBBING]
Aw, there, there, boy.
I'll help you get him back.
He may have been a dirty
stinking coward.
- But show me a Simpson that isn't.
- I'm not a coward.
[YELLING]
You're not a coward.
And that's beside the point because...
[YELLS]
Look, to get our dog back,
we need a plan.
A plan, eh?
[YELLS]
Okay, we'll use a plan.
MARGE:
This is where Duffman lives now.
- But I'm not sure we should go in there.
- Mom, we need him for our plan.
I'm sorry,
we have a six-month residency limit.
Well, old Gil is gonna surprise you.
I'll make something of myself,
you'll see. I... Uh...
Hey.
What do you use for anesthetic?
A big mallet?
Gee, I'm starting to have second th...
[GIL GRUNTS]
[POPS]
Look, there's Duffman.
Okay, if you have 6 liters of blood
and your blood is 80 percent alcohol...
...how much alcohol do you have?
Anyone?
Hey, Duffman.
Please, I'm not Duffman anymore.
Just plain old Barry Duffman.
Oh, yeah, ha, ha.
But we need you to be Duffman again
so we can get our dog back.
But I like it here
helping the less fortunate.
It will be a cold day in hell
before I shill beer again.
An icy-cold, full-bodied,
beech wood-aged, amber-hued day in...
Oh, who am I kidding?
Where is my trademark headgear?
[CHEERS]
You really are Duffman.
Then I must be Jesus.
Up, up and away!
[GRUNTS]
[MAN GROANS]
Stay cool, hopeless drunks!
Oh, yeah!
BART: Here's how
we'll get our dog back.
Dad will pretend to drown
and call Suds to save him.
But he won't
because he's too cowardly.
Oh, yeah!
Once again, Duffman's mug...
...will be the only one you chugalug.
Give it a rest, Barry.
Sorry, sorry.
[CHEERS]
Now, to honor America...
...Navy paratroopers
will jump from their planes...
...and crown Suds McDuff
king of Six-Packistan!
All hail his royal Duffness!
This stunt cost $50 million.
Help! Help!
I'm drowning!
Uh-oh.
Who will save that poor fat man?
I know who'll save him.
The bravest dog in the world:
Suds McDuff.
[WHIMPERS]
[CROWD BOOING]
That dog is a coward.
And I know cowards.
Mother, I served in Nam.
And you've been bitching about it
for 30 years.
[LAUGHS]
Everything is going according to plan.
I'll just keep thrashing around
like an injured seal.
[GRUNTS]
Now is your chance, Duffman.
You can save my dad
and look like a hero.
Don't send a Duff Dog
to do a Duffman's job.
Hold on, sir!
Soon you'll be filling your lungs
with Duff, Duff Light or new Duff Blue.
Tap in to the peppermint pleasure.
[GRUNTS]
[GASPS]
[DUFFMAN GRUNTS]
Are you there, God?
It's me, Duffman!
Let me think. How did that beautiful
young naked lady in Jaws...
...make it out alive?
[ALL GASPING]
[GRUNTS]
[GROWLS]
[GROANS]
Check it out. That shark's wasted.
He's gone from predator to partier.
[GROANS]
[CROWD LAUGHING]
The crowd is going crazy
for that shark.
Guys wanna be him,
girls think they can change him.
Everyone,
say hello to our new mascot:
Duff McShark.
ALL [CHANTING]:
Duff McShark! Duff McShark!
Duff McShark!
Well, Suds, it looks like
you're no good to me anymore.
You might as well be
with a loving family.
[WHIMPERS]
I missed you so much, boy.
Good to have you back
with the Simpsons.
I'm sorry I was ever mean to you.
Marge, prepare the celebration ham.
All we have left are the earthquake ham
and the condolence ham.
Marge, they're just hams, okay?
Well, boy, now that we've got you back,
I'm never gonna let you go again.
Uh-oh, Dad, I think he peed on the rug.
[LAUGHS]
To me, that says "I love you."
I think he left a "big hug"
in your lunchbox.
- Eh, it's probably that stupid cat.
- That cat saved your life.
What has he done lately?
He woke you up
when you stopped breathing last night.
Yeah, but he ate the last can of tuna.
Dad, you ate the last can of tuna.
Everyone's against me.
WOMAN:
Shh.
[English - US -SDH]