The Simpsons
D'oh!
Oh! My brain!
A library
selling books?
If I don't want them
for free,
why would I want
to pay for them?
Why do you always
wait till we arrive
to complain?
I don't know.
Ah. The full
Leonard Nimoy cycle,
I Am Not Spock,
then I Am Spock,
and finally,
I Am Also Scotty.
Mmm. That's what
we look like inside?
It's disgusting!
Oh. That lady
swallowed a baby!
Good heavens!
Lisa, you're not
buying more than
your weight in books.
But I have to save them.
The books no one buys
get chopped up
and fed to pigs.
Helen Fielding's
giving them pigs
Bridget Jones' diarrhea.
Well, what about this?
The Duff Book of
World Records.
It's got pictures
of deformities.
Okay.
Oh.
Oh, my God!
Wow. Now that's a goiter.
Why would Duff beer
put out a book?
It was originally
published to settle
arguments in taverns.
She said tavern!
I'm going to Moe's!
I never agreed
to that rule!
Well, I say
the most clothespins
a man could attach
to his face is 87!
You counting the neck?
You know I am.
All right. Outside.
Peace, my people.
All shall be looked up.
Let's see.
Most clothespins
swallowed, inserted...
Here we go.
Clipped to face
and neck. 116.
Jeez, I was wrong.
But I ain't angry.
And I'm magnanimous
in victory.
Wow, that's the best book
I've ever seen.
No. The best book
you've ever seen is
Tom Clancy's Op-Center.
That thing knows me
better than I know myself.
Oh. Here's a good one.
The world's most
overrated saint...
Francis of Assisi.
Oh, I've used up
all these records.
Why don't you try
to set a record, Dad?
That's a great idea!
Do you think
I could run a mile in
three-and-a-half minutes?
Only on Mars.
The Simpsons
are going to Mars!
So pack your...
Or maybe I'll think
of something else.
You're a cinch
to be the world's
fattest man.
No, I'm here for
the greatest living actor.
I'm here to break
a world record.
What's the longest
anyone's ever done this?
Three years.
Fine. I'll just
play the banjo
with this cobra.
Wait, wait, wait!
Technically the cobra
would get the record.
He's the one playing.
But it's my banjo!
Mr. Simpson,
there are thousands
of people like you
with no
discernable talent.
Yeah.
They're called Congress!
Shut up.
Okay.
All the individual records
were set by crackpots
who half killed themselves.
The only way someone new
can get in the book
is with some kind of
group stunt.
Group stunt?
Like that town that
made the world's
largest omelet.
Denver?
No, Spanish.
Fellow Springfielders!
I have called you all here
so we can enter
The Duff Book
of World Records!
We're going to build
the world's tallest
human pyramid!
Finally this town
will have a real
claim to fame.
Aye. We can
stop all the lies.
I haven't seen
this much flesh
since Elke Sommer's
hot tub party.
Seriously, Elke's great.
Always there
for sick kids.
Doing great things.
Okay. Let me
check the specs.
Ah!
My vision is
coming to life!
Hey!
Thanks, great.
All right, I'll make
base camp here
and try for
the summit tomorrow.
Yeah, Dad.
You can be the world's
laziest stunt organizer.
Why, you little...
You're about a foot
short of the record.
Wait a minute.
We did it!
Springfield rules!
Not yet.
You have to hold it
for three Mississippi's.
One Mississippi...
Two Mississippi...
Dude, you're
touching my hand!
Ewe!
Oh, my hairstyle!
Not again!
Goodbye, cruel world.
Hello, ironic twist!
I am so far from my car.
Dude, you're lying
on top of me! Dude?
Wait a minute.
Look at the scale!
Divide by
the number of people,
subtract belts and shoes...
Everyone, welcome to
The Duff Book
of World Records!
Springfield is
the world's fattest town!
Woo-hoo!
In your face, Milwaukee!
Congratulations,
fellow Springfielders.
This town will
no longer be known
as "America's Sorrow. "
Today I declare Springfield
"Fat City, USA!"
I can't believe it.
Everyone's celebrating
their obesity!
Yee-ha!
Now that everyone's
so open about being fat,
I can finally stop
sucking in my gut.
I don't know how
this town got so fat.
Mom, we're out
of Frosting Gobs.
Here, have one
of my fudge-stuffed
toaster pies.
Mmm.
You kids do eat
a lot of sugar,
but at least Homer can have
a nice healthy grapefruit.
Yeah. You can't
improve on nature.
Look at all
the empty calories.
Ooh!
Sugar-free donuts!
No, that is sugar
with free donuts.
Huh.
Apu, everything in this store
is overloaded with sugar.
Marge has a point.
Sugar is
not only fattening,
it's also terribly,
terribly addictive.
Is my carton
of Pixy Stix in?
No, it hasn't come in yet.
Damn it!
When they come in,
you call me
at this number.
I am sorry,
but everything
in this store,
from the honey-glazed
cauliflower
to the Choco-Blasted
Baby Aspirin,
comes from
the Motherloving
Sugar Corporation.
Well, I'm going to
have a talk with them.
Where are their worldwide
headquarters located?
Why, right down
the street.
That's lucky.
Excuse me. I'm looking
for the head of
Motherloving Sugar.
Yes.
I'm Garth Motherloving.
I'm Marge Simpson.
Long-time customer,
first-time complainer.
Hey, Marge.
I'm not up on
the current slang,
but do the kids
still say,
"Get the hell
out of my office"?
I want you to stop putting
so much sugar in everything.
Or at least warn people
that it's so unhealthy.
Mmm. That'll boost sales!
While we're at it,
why don't I just change
my name back to Hitler?
Don't you have any sense
of corporate responsibility?
Hey!
Look, lady,
if you have a problem,
bring it up with
your sewing circle, okay?
But we're on hiatus.
Everyone's everywhere.
Note to Marge.
Get out!
I'll play it later.
If you looked up
meanie-beanie-fo-feanie
in the dictionary,
you'd see his picture.
Wait! You went
to a sugar factory?
Were there
Oompa Loompas?
There was one in a cage,
but he wasn't moving.
Oh.
That company's ruining
the whole town's health,
and I don't know
how to stop them.
Why don't you file
a class-action suit?
Oh, yeah!
Like Erin Brockovich.
The prostitute
with the heart of gold.
I'm not sure
I can afford
a fancy lawyer.
That's okay, Mom. Today's
law schools are churning
out 2.1 lawyers
for every person
in America. Look.
Pick me!
Me so litigious!
Pick me! I just
passed the bar, see?
Oh. Hop in.
We want to sue
the sugar industry
for selling
a harmful product.
We have to sign up plaintiffs
and take depositions
from the townspeople.
Ah, jeez.
You don't want old Gil
going door-to-door.
Oh, I've made
too many enemies
selling suckless
vacuum cleaners
and Rick James Bibles.
Don't worry.
I'll do the legwork.
I'm filing
a class-action lawsuit
against big sugar.
Would you like
to give a deposition?
Sure.
I'll join your lawsuit.
Sugar's made my Ralphie
hyperactive.
I'm happy and angry!
Oh, shoot. I'll sign.
Figure them sugar folk
owe me
for what they done
to my cousin,
Dia-Betty.
I'm trying to slim down
so I can fit into
Momma's coffin.
That's my reward.
Now let's see
if I can remember
how to make my mark.
I'll get down
with your lawsuit.
Disco Stu got hooked
on the white stuff
back in the 70s.
More, more, more
How do you like it?
Oh, hello, Homer.
Well, well.
If it isn't the woman
who's too busy
saving the world
to save her own marriage.
What are you talking about?
Is that dinner?
It was dinner!
Why didn't you just
turn off the oven?
I was hoping we could
do that together!
Hello?
Marge Simpson?
Who is this?
I'm an anonymous
whistleblower.
I worked on
a top-secret project
called Operation
Hoyvin-Mayvin!
Professor Frink?
Oh, what gave me away?
Out of curiosity,
was it the hoyvin
or the mayvin
or was it the whole
gahoyving thing that I do?
So, Professor,
tell us about
Operation Hoyvin-Mayvin.
Well, we knew
perfectly well
it was addictive.
Candy was just
a sugar delivery system.
We thought we were God.
Hoyvin-mayvin.
Frink, you little weasel!
I'll kill you!
May I remind you
we're in open court?
I'll kill you, too!
I'll kill you all!
Mr. Motherloving,
that could be interpreted
as a threat.
I'll kill you
while you sleep.
Objection!
I'll allow it.
Now, Count Fudgula,
how long were
you spokes-vampire
for Motherloving's
breakfast cereals?
Twenty of
your mortal years,
but I had to quit when
my fangs succumbed
to gingivitis.
Now all my victims
have to be mashed up.
Aw.
Your Honor, I admit
it looks bad for me,
but I think you might be
turned around
by some surprising
taste-imony.
Sir, this is
a house of justice,
not a sugar shack.
It's Hershey
highwaymen like you
who made me fat.
Well, Your Honor,
the court carries it well.
Silence! I rule in favor
of Marge Simpson!
Yay!
Oh, I am so proud
of you.
And thanks to
Marge Simpson's
damning evidence,
I hereby ban
all sugar products
from Springfield forever.
Get in the car.
Good evening.
Our top story,
Springfield's cake-hole
has been shut forever.
Under what has been dubbed
"Marge's Law,"
all forms of sugar
are now illegal.
Thank you,
Erin Choco-snitch!
That was
a group effort.
I was just trying to make this
a healthier place to live.
Well, good work,
Blue-hair-in-Brocko-witch.
Okay, that was mine.
So, say a bittersweet
farewell
to such old friends
as mud pies,
Bite 'Ems, Eclairios,
Chew 'Ems,
Kellogg's All-Fudge,
Big Red Snack Foam,
Milk Chuds, Eat 'Ems.
And all sugar pills
will be changed back to
highly concentrated opiates.
That's it, boys!
Burn it all!
Even this
promotional Johnny Depp
from the movie Chocolat?
We melted for him.
Now he's gonna do likewise.
All right.
Time to throw in
the Butterfingers.
Hmm.
It's not even singed.
Even the fire
doesn't want them.
Sugar! Need sugar!
Aye. They're not riding
the white horse anymore.
My baby!
Where's my baby?
Nothing left!
Ooh. A sticky spot!
Mr. Simpson,
you're licking blood
and VapoRub.
Part of me knew that.
There is a small group
committed
to bringing sugar
back to this town
by any means necessary.
I'm with you all the way.
But first...
Cool.
Gentlemen, I have
found the final member
of our cabal.
Count Fudgula?
I thought you wanted
to get off the stuff?
I'm a monster!
Don't look at me!
Homer, we need you
to help us smuggle in sugar
from south of the border.
Oh, you mean Tennessee?
No, the island
of San Glucose.
Good times.
Is it really worth
risking your lives
just for some sugar?
Dessert's on!
I steamed some limes!
Godspeed.
There is the island.
It's go time.
Oh.
I'm only doing this
one more time!
How's he doing?
I think he's grossed out
by some seaweed.
Ew!
I touched it! Over.
Get a grip, Simpson.
You're doing fine.
Now, do you have your map?
Kind of.
Come on! Give it!
I know.
I'll try reverse psychology.
I don't want
that stupid map.
D'oh!
Okay, man, here's the sugar.
Now, you give us the money.
That wasn't
part of the deal.
He's right!
Who wrote this thing?
Well, we're almost home.
Has everyone keistered
their personal supply?
'Cause I sure haven't.
Hold it right there!
Surrender or
prepare to be sunk!
No way!
We'll defy you
to the death!
Stroke, stroke, stroke!
I'm rowing
as fast as I can, sir!
No! I'm having one.
Remember what I told you
about running away
from your troubles?
Yeah.
Let's do it!
My baby!
I like to think we've
made a difference today.
Good work, Simpson.
Before I bring
the sugar in,
I want to see
the Oompa Loompa.
He's right over there.
That guy is freaky.
Well, here's your sugar.
No, Homer!
You'll be condemning
this town
to a life of obesity
and diabetes!
Don't listen to her,
Homer!
Oh, they both make
such good arguments!
Please, Homie.
Dump the sugar. For me.
Sugar is pouring
into the water!
Aye, 'tis a sugary brine.
Mmm.
This sugar shark is delicious.
Ow! Hey, he bit me back!
Oh.
So that's how
it's gonna be, huh?
Gee, everyone looks
so happy.
Indeed, Marge.
And now that
I think of it,
I wildly exceeded
my authority,
and I declare
the sugar ban over!
Can we, Mom? Can we?
Please, please, please?
Oh.
All right,
but take Maggie with you.
Mmm.
I guess you just can't
use the law to nag.
Maybe I should
just stop trying
to change the world.
No, Marge.
I love when you do that.
You're a regular
Caring-a-lot-ovich.
That's the best one.
That's what I told Lisa.
Sugar
Ah, honey, honey
Hey, I found some pearls.
No, wait.
They're just my teeth.
Well, I can still
make a necklace
out of them.
Honey
Ah, sugar, sugar
You are my candy girl
And you got me wanting you
I just can't believe
the loveliness of loving you
I just can't believe it's true
I just can't believe
the wonder of
this feeling, too
I just can't believe it's true
Ah, sugar
Ah, honey, honey
You are my candy girl...
English - US - PSDH