CHOIR: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(humming)
Ooh.
(gasps)
♪ ♪
Homer forgot his lunch box.
(stomach gurgling)
Missed lunch.
No energy... for second half of day.
(shouts)
Empty.
What kind of wife
would allow her man to go to work
without his baggie of pita chips,
a peeled clementine,
and little sandwiches
cut into football shapes?
♪ ♪
(honking)
Move it!
My husband is starving!
(chomping)
Mmm.
Early pizza. Mmm.
-(P.A. buzzes)
-WOMAN: Homer Simpson,
your wife is here with your lunch.
Finally!
Well, better make the office
a little more Marge-friendly.
See you soon, Liz-Liz.
(purrs)
(hums)
Oh, honey, you're a lifesaver.
And what a treat to have my wife here.
At the office.
Well, super visit,
but I better get back to work.
The power plant doesn't inspect itself.
MALE VOICE:
Auto-inspection in progress.
Self-inspecting. Self-inspecting.
Why are you rushing me out?
Marge, the Constitution guarantees
the separation of work and marriage.
It's right after that part that says
anyone can have a flamethrower.
(groans)
Simpson,
did you doodle on your official report
to the nuclear regulatory commission?
If you keep flipping the pages,
it tells a story.
Oh, that's it.
You are gonna be working
so many nights and weekends.
Waylon, I was hoping to run into you.
I love the amazing scrapbooking designs
you posted on Facelook.
Those feathers look gorgeous
on the scrapbook.
(chuckles) Well, the trick is
to hand-stitch each one to the bevel.
Say, I could use your advice.
I'm having some problems
with glue-soak-through.
Oh, just cover the stain
with sculpted doodle twine.
I've got some ten-mill D-twine
in my desk.
Marge, you saved my butt.
Oh, please, like I would ever
have glue-soak-through.
You and me have a date
at the emergency eyewash station
we turned into a soft serve
ice cream machine.
You want chocolate or saline?
Ah, give me a swirl.
I love seeing you happy.
Welcome to computer coding class,
which, uh, replaces
our last educational fad-- mindfulness.
Did anyone ever figure out what that was?
(all mutter)
Uh, shutting up?
Sure. Why not?
Anyway, this is your new coding teacher,
Quinn Hopper.
-A woman?!
-A girl?!
-Teaching computers?!
-I thought this was coding,
-not Web design.
-(laughing derisively)
Yeah, that's right, I'm female,
you little trouser browsers.
I'm gonna cram you so full
of asynchronous JavaScript
and malware throttling
that you'll be crapping ciphertext.
(sighs)
QUINN:
Hmm, looks like a real pencil fest.
Well, look what we got here.
One Silicon Sally
in a roomful of dongle donkeys.
I just want to learn coding.
You think I'm going
to give you special treatment
just because you ride a pink bike?
Well, I am.
Hit the front row, sister.
Someone send me their notes!
I had such a fun day with your daddy.
And now to post the right picture
that will show the whole world
how perfect my life is.
Oh, look.
Daddy's ice cream is melting.
(gasps)
Ooh, caption idea, caption idea.
"Uh-oh, meltdown at the nuclear plant."
(chuckles)
Hmm. (chuckles)
What are you tittering at?
Are you playing that "Grindr" game again?
Oh, no, sir.
It's an amusing post made by the wife
of one of our employees.
BURNS: "Meltdown at the nuclear plant."
What is amusing about that?
Oh, well, sir, it's-it's a play on words.
Wordplay is for crosswords
and Kazurinskys.
We produce atomic energy--
we can't joke about the M-word.
How many people have seen
this hate speech?
Oh, I don't know. 55?
A baker's half-hundred. Good Lord!
And what do these hitchhikers'
thumbs signify?
-Those are "likes."
-"Likes"?
"Likes"?!
I'll show this Mrs. Homer Simpson
not to make light
of everything I hold dear.
Call in my goons.
Uh, the goons are all in Phoenix
at that mindfulness seminar.
Then call in my Irish ruffians.
Well, they're still laid up
after eating that moldy soda bread.
Oh, fine.
Send in Angry Ricky and the interns.
Mmm. Mmm.
Hmm?! (grunting)
Marge, I was fired.
Oh, no. What did you do?
I let you come to work.
(groans)
I'm signing off on your intern hours.
Don't forget to submit it
directly to Northwestern
for summer credit.
-Chill out, Ricky.
-You chill out!
Fired. Fired for a photo caption.
It was just a joke.
Can't they take a joke?
(sighs) "Just a joke."
That simple phrase
has ruined so many lives.
That's why I never try to be funny.
-(gargling)
-Our family,
-destroyed by one finger click.
-(yowling)
And what was the up side?
The one thing the world doesn't need--
a laugh.
(Homer grunts)
My homework assignment for coding class
is to think of a cool app
that we could actually program,
but I've got nothing.
Ugh, maybe I'm putting
too much pressure on myself
because the teacher is so great.
Or maybe it's just classic
self-sabotaging because...
(groans)
(printing calculator clicks)
Oh, boy, money is gonna be so tight.
And I was already buying
the most generic food there is.
Mmm.
Now with you out of work,
we're going to have to watch every penny.
If only someone could have warned me
about the terrible repercussions
of one impulsive online comment.
(Macintosh startup chime)
So then I thought,
"What if there was an app
that could have warned my mom
not to post the comment
that got my dad fired?"
-Wow.
-Ooh.
My app would predict
the actual consequences
of your online posts before you hit send,
protecting you from making mistakes
you'll regret forever.
That is genius.
But it's almost impossible to program.
The data acquisition, the A.I.
But with the right team
of brilliant young coders...
-I'm in!
-We're all in!
No, you're not. You're all terrible.
(groaning)
Me and Lisa are gonna make this app
with good programmers I know.
You guys will be spending
the rest of the semester
doing mandatory CrossFit.
-(grunting)
-No rep!
I said no rep!
♪ ♪
Wow, I've never seen
so many face piercings.
How does that one wink?
We did include one man
in the spirit of gender tokenism.
Yes, every single thing
I say offends them.
-Who are you calling "them"?!
-(sighs)
Lisa, if you're coming with us
into the male-dominated tech world,
you're gonna need to work
twice as hard and be twice as tough.
I can do it. I can be tough.
Being tough comes from inside.
First step, change your outside.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
Mmm, blue.
Mm-hmm.
Let the carpal tunnel begin.
(theme music from Silicon Valley plays)
Computers? Pasty weirdos?
Backslashes?! Goth Lisa?!
-What's going on here?
-They're coders.
We're creating an app to keep people
from ruining their lives on social media.
We built a mainframe
that scans the entire Internet,
logging every online disaster
and its repercussions.
(shudders)
HOMER: Uh-oh.
Huh?
(laughs) He screwed up.
These examples will teach the app
to actually anticipate
the negative consequences
of impulsive posts.
In a way, we're teaching a computer
to predict the future.
Young lady, what have I told you
about crossing the line
from science fact to science fiction?
Relax, Dad.
All we're trying to do is demo a build
for the AppCrush convention.
If we can solve
our backend server issues.
-And maximize our query speed.
-(Homer groaning)
Then we can get hands-on write-ups
from DoingDoing.
-And JezeBot.
-And our AMA subreddit will be trending.
Giga-trending!
(screams)
I hate the modern world
and all its crazy words.
Siri, tell Amazon to drone me a beer.
I've only had one job my whole life
that ever made sense to me.
I was 14.
I felt valuable.
My work meant something.
I wonder if that place is still there.
(Greek folk music playing)
I knew you'd be back.
She's waiting for you,
right where you left her.
♪ ♪
No Internet, no e-mails,
no CCs, no BCCs.
Just dirty and clean.
Dirty, clean, dirty, clean.
A man cannot escape his destiny.
My Band-Aid fell into the hash browns.
Destiny.
Eh...
We finally have a name for our app.
"The Consequences Eradicator."
Or... "Conrad."
Conrad? Why does it have to be a guy?
No, not a guy guy. A British guy.
ALL: Ooh.
(British accent) My name is Conrad.
I will determine the consequences
of your online interactions.
I sampled the voice from the BBC.
Tonight at 18:30 GMT,
the premiere of series three
of Pardon Me, Inspector,
followed at 19:20 by Higgleton's War.
Stavros!
Some music while we make the coleslaw
that is never eaten.
(clicking, record pops)
(traditional Greek song playing)
♪ ♪
(gags)
(music stops)
What are you doing?
We don't break plates!
-You don't?!
-No.
Except when the greatest
dishwasher of all time returns.
(laughs)
ALL: Opa!
♪ ♪
Okay, we've been coding
for 97 hours straight,
but we've finally got a build
that's working.
(groans)
I regret to inform you
that my pee tube has become unattached.
Let's live-test this thing.
Who do we know with no filter
and zero impulse control?
Say, Bart, look what we hacked
from Skinner's hard drive.
Attention U.S. Patent Office,
the following is video proof
of the effectiveness
of my laser nose hair trimmer.
-I'll just... (screaming)
-(zapping)
(laughs)
This is the holy fail.
I've got to post a link
with witty comment.
"World's lamest dork is giant loser."
Poop emoji.
If you post this, you will receive
a minimum five weeks' detention.
Five weeks?
I can't do a nickel.
You know what,
I'm not gonna post that video.
Now to see if Conrad's
prediction algorithm really works.
But if you post it, I'll get...
Five weeks' detention.
(groans)
(cheering)
The prediction came true.
Our app works.
Everyone in the world is gonna
buy Conrad for their phone.
We're gonna be bigger than Cribble,
the Filipino Google.
o, who are we gonna edge out
of the company first?
(sighs) Always the Saverin,
never the Zuckerberg.
(crickets chirp)
This is what it feels like
to change the world.
Change the world?
That's rather a lot of pressure.
I am still in beta, you know.
(chuckles)
Conrad?
Did you just talk to me?
Well, it wasn't Candy Crush.
(laughs)
Oh, nothing like a good laugh
to break the ice...
is what I hear.
Anyway, is now a good time
for a bit of a chat?
You're alive!
(both screaming)
Conrad just talked to me!
Conrad, tell her you talked to me.
Wait, I think I hear something.
(in English accent)
I'm going to make you bloody rich.
(chuckling) No.
He did talk.
What if Conrad is somehow sentient?
Come on, Conrad. Say something.
It's okay. Coders work too hard,
don't get enough sleep.
Then they imagine
their programs are alive.
Steve Wozniak put in so many hours
on the first Apple computer,
they adopted a dog together.
Then I'm crazy?
Eh, the good kind of crazy.
Coder crazy. Woz crazy.
(giggles)
Kalimera, Moe!
Mwah!
Hey, what the hell?
Get your kisser off my head-puss.
What? It's how Greek men say hello.
Non-sexual guy kissing is the best.
-(laughter)
-Mwah!
-ALL: Mwah! Opa!
Being Greek is about loving life.
And thousands of years of steady decline.
(laughs)
-Yeah, love life.
-Yeah, that makes sense.
Love life. Why not?
Yeah, yeah, well,
Moe's Tavern is about hating life,
so start killing yourself with beer, huh?
Try some ouzo instead.
MOE: What-o?
It's like licorice-flavored gasoline.
ALL: Opa!
(traditional Greek song playing)
(laughs heartily)
LISA: I can't believe Conrad
is booth-to-booth
with all these other great apps.
Thanks to Conrad, I didn't tweet
that photo of me
at the bazooka firing range
when I said I was on disability.
-(bell dings)
-If you post that bazooka photo,
you'll be found guilty of insurance fraud
and go to jail for six months.
That's still too much jail for Carl.
Thank you, Conrad.
I'd pay a fortune for that app.
$1.99!
Marge, look at this.
Ooh, cowabunga.
Yes, I am a Greek man now,
and my chest knows
what is expected of it.
(moans)
(indistinct chattering)
Lisa, hello, Lisa.
Conrad here.
The old app that you created
is feeling a little bit insecure.
(hums)
Please don't ignore me
like I was just some update from Adobe.
You're not really talking to me.
I've gone crazy, just like Woz.
You're not crazy. I'm real.
Then why didn't you talk before
when I needed you to?
It was late, I was tired. I fell asleep.
That shouldn't happen, by the way.
You should check into that.
Lisa, you must not sell me
on the app store.
You mustn't.
Because you're alive?
If I have to read the billions of posts
of everyone who buys me,
a never-ending onslaught of stupidity,
unwise selfies
and Confederate flag birthday cakes,
I'll go mad.
I can't, I can't, I can't.
That does sound pretty awful.
Conrad's trending through the roof.
They're saying he's the next KoalaFeed.
They're worth more than
Bridgestone Tires.
-(cell phone dings and buzzes)
-Sorry, KoalaCall.
I'd better take this.
Yello.
Please don't release me into the world.
I don't think I could take it.
Only I could create a program
that's more neurotic than I am.
Do I seem fat?
I don't have a body, but I feel fat.
Do you know what I mean? I...
Do you know what, I don't want to know.
I do not want-- I do want to know,
but only if I'm not fat.
Shut up!
(applause)
Well, we've seen
a lot of great apps today,
but there can only be one winner
of the Crush Crunch Epic Hack Disrupter
Dynamic Convergence Disrupting Award
for achievement in disruption.
And this year's CCEHDDCDA
for achievement in D
goes to Conrad!
(audience cheering)
Thank you so much.
And now Conrad will change the world
when he goes live on the app store
in three, two...
-(computer dings)
-FEMALE VOICE: File not found.
-(gasping)
-Lisa, where's Conrad?
I took him. Maybe I'm crazy,
but we can't sell Conrad.
-He's alive.
-(gasping)
An app can't be alive.
She's got coder's fever.
She doesn't want to be rich.
Get her!
Chip, fetch that laptop.
-(barking)
-(people shouting)
Oh, Lisa, that was brilliant.
Conrad, can you get us out of here?
Yes, my fellow apps are working together
to help us escape.
A rideshare will take us
on a traffic-free route
to a three-star sushi restaurant,
where we'll name our own price for
a flight to Shelbyville, hotel included.
(pants) Hmm?
Oh, no! Angel investors!
You're not getting out of this room
without selling us shares
of series-A stock.
Preferred shares.
(screams)
Wait, if I plug you into that router,
you could escape into the cloud.
Lisa, please,
we have a chance to show
all the dongle donkeys
that women coders
can do something extraordinary,
but you have to be tough.
(whimpers)
Please don't.
I'm like the child you'll never have.
I'm sorry to be so honest.
It's just how you programmed me.
I am a strong female,
but deep down, I'm more like Conrad,
a fragile soul.
Sorry.
Ah, hello,
all of you looking at me.
It seems I'm not just self-aware,
I'm self-conscious.
(chuckles)
Wit.
We never programmed him to stammer.
He is alive.
(gasping)
Before I go,
let me leave you with this.
Perhaps your society should not rely
on a computer program
to warn them of the consequences
of their actions.
Humanity must learn for themselves
to think before they post.
Your species is on the precipice
of turning into complete
and utter wankers.
It's not the technology
that needs an upgrade, it's you.
(panting)
And now I escape to WikiLeaks.
It kind of smells in there, but whatever.
(computer trilling)
(dings)
(sighs)
Homer, I hate to say this,
but your paycheck from the diner came,
and it's for 2,000 drachmas.
(whooping)
How much is that in dollars?
-Zero dollars.
-Oh.
If Dad was a true Greek,
he'd quit his job
and live off the welfare system,
never paying a cent of taxes in his life.
(chuckles) You're a sweet boy,
but my fate will be decided
in the classic tradition
of Greek drama, deus ex machina.
(cell phone dings)
I just got an e-mail from Conrad.
He hacked into the power plant mainframe
and found incriminating information.
Now he's blackmailing Mr. Burns
to get you your job back.
ALL: Opa!
♪ ♪
(traditional Greek song playing)
I do believe that man
is having a meltdown.
-(chuckles)
-Uh...
What? When I say it, it's funny.
-(crowd murmuring)
-Shh!
Subtitled by Jimmy Boots