D'oh!
They fought for years
With guns and garden shears
Years, years, years,
tears, tears, tears
It's the Itchy and
Scratchy Marathon!
Sponsored by
delicious Cream of Rye.
Which one's the cat?
Okay.
Hour 14 of our marathon.
Now let's watch
episode 10,433.
Cat Scratch Cleaver!
Enough with the cartoons.
You'll rot your brains.
Leave brain alone.
I've been watching so much TV,
I can't move my head.
- I'll fix him.
- Careful, Dad!
If I'd have been careful,
I wouldn't have had you.
Now I can't go to school.
Or church.
Hallelujah!
We're going to spend
family time together
without watching TV.
Mom is right.
Americans watch way too much TV.
How many hours?
Let me Google that.
Instead of TV, I typed TB.
Turn off the devices, pronto!
Pronto. Odd word.
Let me Google that.
Hey, I'm doing
something educational.
Educational, my foot.
I saw pixels.
It's TunnelCraft.
A simulated world where you
explore, mine resources,
and work with friends to build
replicas of real buildings.
Can you die in it?
- Yes.
- It's a video game.
I got a family activity for ya.
In the Depression, we'd sit
around the wood stove
and sing songs about poverty.
Old poor Joe,
the starving boy
Had worms burrow
in his feet
He heard there was
work in Portland
But sadly he heard wrong
Oh, the railroad bulls,
they rousted him
And stuck him in a sack
They tied him to the train
And pulled him down the track
They threw him off the bridge
And they kicked him
in the head and they...
Enough!
I know what we're going to do.
We're going to go out.
We're going to get some books
and we're going to read
those books.
This is the very last chance
for this family to get
reading in their lives.
So get on your feet, bubs.
We are taking a walk.
To the library.
Where you'll have to be quiet.
Wait, you're closing?
You wanna read?
Start with the sign.
Oh, can't we just go
in for five minutes?
Up to you.
But after 2:00, the
silverfish take over.
I just wanted to renew my card!
DVDs, plush toys, crullers...
I don't see many books.
Yeah, the only actual books
are coffee table books.
Barn Doors of Topeka,
Dogs Eating Ice Cream,
Jigsaw Puzzles
with One Piece Missing,
Man-Killing Snakes
of the Amazon...
Sir! Never say Amazon
in a bookstore.
Amazon! Of course!
Alexa!
Order books!
I already did.
Your mind is open to me.
They'll be home before I am.
Ma'am, if you really
want to read,
check out our
proprietary e-reader.
The Bookaccino Niche.
Excuse me.
That device is poorly
designed.
I would register
my disgust,
but it corrects
with auto praise.
Finally, a bookstore
that sells books.
- I love the smell of old books.
- Oh, oatmeal.
Wouldn't do that, miss.
The air in here has a lot
of particulate rat droppings.
Okay.
Let's book up and bug out.
Here you go, Bart.
The Sisterhood of
the Traveling Pants.
Maggie, In Cold Blood.
Lisa, With No Apologies,
The Memoirs of Barry Goldwater.
Lisa, look!
The Princess in the Garden,
by Heloise Hodgeson Burwell.
It's my very favorite book
from when I was a girl.
It's for ages ten and up,
but I think you're ready.
If you think so.
Wait a minute.
One bar... two bars...
five bars.
You're not reading a book.
- You're in a Wi-Fi hotspot!
- Dad, please.
I'm trying to reserve
tickets to TunnelCraft-Con.
What?
What the hell is that?
Duh, it's a convention
for kids who play TunnelCraft.
It's got skins, betas, mods...
exclusive access
to the top devs.
No convention.
And that's almost final.
But I'm dying to go, fatso.
Now it is final!
What do you have for a kid
who wishes
his father was dead?
Try this. The Art of War,
written 3,000 years ago
by General Sun Tzu.
Well, there's war in the
title and very few pages.
The only flaw is it's a book.
Young man, are you sure you
want war with your father?
I do not seek war,
but neither do I turn away.
If you use this book,
your father will lie shattered
before the gates of your palace.
Oh, mighty general!
I beg to be
your unworthy footstool.
When he sleeps, I will steal
the jewels from his topknot.
Hey, Mom,
I found something to read!
Wonderful!
What a great family day.
And there is only
one perfect way
to complete a great
family day.
So, how's the family?
I think they went to dinner.
Something nice.
Nelson's coming our way.
My nose is pre-bleeding.
I'm picking on Bart.
You like books, huh?
Well, here's a bookmark.
If your enemy is easily
enraged, irritate him.
I heard you're not
strong, you're just fat.
Fat? Me?
You try eating healthy
at a strip club buffet!
Willy!
Get me out of here!
It's on fire! Willy!
Maybe wisdom isn't
so stupid after all.
Milhouse, I'm gonna use this
book to go to TunnelCraft-Con.
Here's the book I'm reading.
When I finish this,
I'll have read every
Mary Kate and Ashley book.
Sometimes I feel like
the third sister.
He opposed the religious right.
Okay, this is my favorite book
ever, but no pressure.
You realize saying
no pressure
puts me under
tremendous pressure.
Then let's get started.
Not all English girls
grow up in England.
Clara grew up
in South America
where she was raised
by many native servants.
But they were too naturally
servile to oppose her will.
Naturally what?
Uncle Juan?
Would you clap as I dance?
Rhythm... rhythm...
Mind the rhythm
or you'll feel the lash!
Mom, why'd you stop reading?
It's just a little different
than I remembered.
Let's skip ahead.
A father murdered by
loco banana picker,
Clara baptizing savages
without their permission...
Oh, okay, okay, here we go.
Clara is now an orphan
and was sent to live with
her lonely uncle in the hills.
She meets a boy named Conor.
Like all Irish, he was
feeble-witted and drunk.
This is the part
you deem acceptable?
The Irish are nobody's
joke anymore.
Hoi-dee toi-dee
toi-dee toi!
I'm goin' on a hunger
strike in here!
So weak. So weak...
Another childhood
classic bites the dust.
Is that a coolie hat?
Nighty-night!
I bet my booklight is shining
on something offensive.
Darn it.
Heloise Hodgeson Burwell?
Why did you stop
reading my book?
Your daughter is just the kind
of girl I wrote it for...
Obedient, well-fed and white.
Oh, calm yourself, Marge.
Dreams are where it's okay
to be racist.
Rudyard Kipling!
Yes. You should read my first
draft of The Jungle Book.
At the end,
Mowgli uses his elephants
to stomp out some Hindus
seeking limited voting rights.
All in good fun.
Marge, I suppose
you could edit my book
to your daughter's
sensibilities.
An author that wants rewrites.
Well, that's what makes
this a dream.
Now the war begins.
Not yet!
I haven't finished my costume.
I'm doing period sewing
with bird bones as needles.
Wait.
Why do you want me
to text you
when your father's
getting in the car?
That's none of your business,
but let's just say
both of us will benefit.
A trombone mute?
But I don't have a trombone.
Open the other box.
Oh, my God!
All right, Simpson,
blow into this.
Now make it into a rabbit.
All right.
Ralphie's birthday is today,
and you're the entertainment.
What's going on? It's like
someone's out to get me.
I have to be focused and careful.
Nothing will break my concen...
Ooh! Wild milk ball.
Bart! You're behind this?
That's right. And it looks like
someone is stuck in the mud.
Help me, boy!
I will save you if you do
what I say from now on...
starting with going to
TunnelCraft-Con.
Sure. Just pull me out
by your sneaky little neck!
Just be aware that
if something happens to me,
Mom finds out about your
secret stash of Drake's Cakes.
What secret stash?
Pier 18, shipping container
number 4-7-9-5-2.
D'oh!
I was offered a deal and I took it.
Okay, I give.
Louder, dog!
Okay!
You really think
you can control me?
Malted milk ball.
Okay. Here's a new version
of The Princess in the Garden.
- Mom, you're exhausted.
- It takes a lot of work
to take the spirit and
character out of a book.
But now it's as inoffensive
as a Sunday in Cincinnati.
Once there was a cisgender
girl named Clara.
She lived in South America,
fighting for wild horse
rescue...
and net neutrality.
This new Clara
sounds like she starts
out pretty perfect.
You betcha!
But since she's already evolved,
she doesn't really have an
emotional journey to complete.
- Nope.
- Kind of means there's
no point to the book.
Well, what am I supposed
to do?
It's hard to say.
Something that started
decades ago
and was applauded
and inoffensive,
is now politically
incorrect.
What can you do?
Some things will be dealt
with at a later date.
If at all.
Hey, Simpsons.
We'll see you in church.
Not today you won't.
Well, we'll say
a prayer for you.
Don't mention my name, weirdo.
Dear Lord, forgive that boy.
He knows not what he says.
What does that weirdo want now?
My feet hurt.
There's too much cosplay,
whatever that is.
- Can we go home?
- Quiet, you.
It's the two greatest
TunnelCraft players of all time!
Those guys make
awesome videos
where they play
TunnelCraft together.
Has the world gone mad?
Their banter is legendary.
- Got that?
- Yeah.
- Go left.
- Right.
- Left. Go right.
- Dig.
Dig.
- Cool.
That's why they call me
Tunnel-Rat.
- I'm Tunnel-Rat.
- Oh, right.
Oh, awesome!
- What the...?
- Calm down.
It's me, Daniel Radcliffe.
This is how I see
conventions, incognito.
Otherwise the fans envelope me.
Oh, that's ridiculous!
Daniel Radcliffe!
He knows Rupert Grint!
Yes, I do. He's lovely.
Oh! Oh, God!
What are you...
I loved him.
Please, can we go now?
No! You wait in
the poster-signing line.
And don't sign them
yourself.
I'll know.
Milhouse, by God,
if you want a ride home,
you tell me what Bart's up to.
Okay. Bart's been using
an ancient Chinese book
against you.
I knew it. Except for the
ancient Chinese book part,
I knew it!
Why are you bringing
me here?
These professors have some
very interesting news for you
about Heloise
Hodgeson Burwell.
Meanwhile, I'll sit
on this chair
and imagine
I'm grading papers.
Marge Simpson,
the fan of Burwell.
We are all Burwelleans.
You don't mind that her
books are a little...
grandma on the veranda?
Marge, Burwell's whole life was
a protest against conformity.
- Yeah, she never married.
- Had no children.
She lived in Provincetown,
Mass...
a-chu-setts.
Heloise Burwell
is a lesbian icon!
Her offensive stereotypes
were actually a self-consciously
ironic protest
against her own oppression.
How much of that
do you actually believe?
Most.
So much to take in.
How do you deal with it all?
With the help of Sherry.
Yes. Sherry, bring in
the hard liquor, please.
Okay. Now you can ask me
about Lewis Carroll.
Remember,
all warfare is deception.
Shut up.
I'm trying to fool my kid.
Bart, son, if you don't mind,
I brought a friend over.
Flanders?!
Great to be here, pal-o-mino.
I brought some potent grass
that'll get this party started.
Bluegrass!
Chicken's in the henhouse,
pig is in the poke
The whole dang farm
feels okily-doke
Goin' up to Cripple Creek,
swimmin' fully dressed
Not being naked,
oh, that's the best
Mr. Flanders. Again?
No siree, Bart!
It's me, your Homereeno!
Morning, friend-till-the-end.
Ready to greet the day
with a big ho-hey?
Call me the Pillsbury Doughboy,
'cause I'm ready to roll!
Then let's hi-diddley-go!
If anyone can do it,
it's we two-it!
- Yes, indeedle, doddily...
- Okily-dokily, dokily, dokily.
Oh, my God.
He's even gone left-handed.
Now we're gonna take you
to a movie rated R
for really old and boring.
Oh, no, he daren't!
Dad, please, isn't there any
way to get the old Homer back?
Well, now, Bartly, why would
you want that balding boob...
Ooh, I said boob!
Time for me to do a turtle.
I'll come out when the
B-bombs stop flying.
Please, I want my dad,
not this horrible creature
from the depths of heaven
you've become.
If you truly surrender,
give me your Halloween candy.
But it's March.
Most of it's still good.
Fine.
Now, bow to your master,
because you are the fool,
and I, the greater fool!
Dad! You read the book too?
Up to page five.
Now, come here, son,
and grab some belly.
Excuse me. These films
are original nitrate prints.
Which means the theater has
just gone up in a terrible fire.
You have seconds to escape!
They never tell the organist.
So that film is
a hundred years old?
No. We shot it
at my place yesterday.
Well, now it's time to say good-bye
To Ned and Rod and Todd
And I'll remind all you folks
you should be praisin' God
If you don't, you'll rot
in hell for all eternity
It's all a part of God's great
love he has for you and me
Y'all come back, now.
Y'hear?