(grunts)
(caws)
(exclaiming)
(school bell ringing)
(Barney belches)
(whistle blows)
(yells)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
(gunfire)
(tires screeching)
(horn honking, Grampa shouts)
D'oh!
(tires screeching)
(grunts)
(bluesy jazz music playing)
(sirens wailing in distance)
(sign buzzing)
-(clicking)
-Hmm?
(clicking)
(scratching)
(footsteps approaching)
-You little!
-(gun cocks)
-(saxophone playing)
-(gasps)
(playing the blues)
(shotgun cocks)
(all growling)
(sighs)
-Mm?
-(ice clattering)
Hmm?
Mmm.
(all gasp)
(kids chattering)
Everybody out.
Everybody in.
-Bathroom break!
-I spilled my pills!
Music today has no melody!
-(tires screech)
-Everybody out!
Children, you can stop
writing letters of support
to our troops; that was just busywork.
Now, I want to explain
Miss Hoover's absence.
She is suffering from severe...
...depression.
(kids murmuring)
Not to worry,
she has been treated
with heavy doses of...
Lorazepam and other drugs from the...
Benzodiazepine family.
Now, until Miss Hoover returns,
this class will be getting
a permanent substitute.
(excited chattering)
Please let it be someone smart, motivated,
and who won't just teach us
corporate-sponsored lessons.
Lisa, without corporate sponsorship,
we wouldn't be able to teach you
the three R's:
reading, refreshment,
and Raspberry Buzz Lite.
Get your razz on!
(tires screech outside, kids murmuring)
Confident,
Vassar sticker on the windshield.
(gasps) Could it be?
Do I detect enthusiasm?
She's brought her own orrery!
And it's got no Pluto!
How cutting edge.
Please be her, please be her.
Is this Ms. Hoover's class?
(quietly) Score!
Meet your new teacher, Ms. Cantwell.
Do not call her by
the obvious dirty nickname.
Now I must meet with
the new art teacher, Mr. Testacleese.
(snickering)
Lisa Simpson. Hi.
As second grade student-faculty liaison,
-I'd like to welcome you...
-Get back in your seat.
If I have any apples that need polishing,
I'll let you know.
I understand there are
homework assignments.
Mm.
Well done, Ralpa.
If I can't remember the right letter,
I just put an "A."
Well, here's another one.
Well, while you're grading
so generously, here's mine.
"B."
-As in, "because I say so."
-(gasps)
(Lisa groaning)
Nothing brings them around
like old cafeteria meatballs.
Meat?!
(Lisa groaning)
I thought you might be cold, honey,
so I put this chinchilla coat on you.
-Fur?! (gasps)
-(chuckles)
It's not really chinchilla.
I just thought she needed more sleep.
(doorbell rings)
Hey, Flanders.
-Can I borrow some sugar?
-Sure.
-Uh, a little cream?
-Goes with the sugar.
Now if you could make with
some bacon and eggs,
I'll be on my way.
(sighs)
Why don't you come on in
and have breakfast with us?
Are your kids gonna be there?
Eh, for a little bit.
(sighs) Okay.
Homer, you know my parents,
Capri and Nedward.
Hey, hey, Homer J.
How many beers did you kill today?
(laughing)
Dad, don't encourage him!
Son, you are the Mayor of Dullsville.
Now, you know we don't
discuss politics at the table.
Hello, police?
I'd like to report
a buzz-kill in progress.
There's no emergency here.
And please charge us for the false report.
I'm going out for a power walk.
Whoa, this room just got
a whole lot cooler.
-(laughter)
-Oh, man.
(both sigh)
Okay, children, ten minutes of free play.
-(kids chattering)
-I'm a fun factory.
Lisa, free play.
But I am playing.
I'm hop-scotching
from paragraph to paragraph,
climbing the monkey bars
of plot and theme.
Ugh, bull-pie.
You're trying to get ahead
of the other children.
That's it, you're losing joeys.
Please keep them together.
If not for me, for the mother.
LISA:
(gasps)
Is it possible I've met
a teacher who doesn't like me?
The joeys go in feet first. (chuckles)
(gasps) Chauncey!
(panting)
Six miles, and I'm all smiles.
Whew.
Funyuns? Little Debbies?
-(sitar playing)
-That's cross-legged music.
(laughter)
Look at the size of that bird.
I'd go Henry VIII on those drumsticks.
Homer, I can't believe
you're partaking with my parents.
Yeah, it's medicinal.
We had a pain in our neck.
(laughter)
(laughter continues)
(grunts)
I didn't know you were left-handed.
(groans)
Homer, you'll need to wear this eye patch
for a couple weeks.
And, uh, you may never
see a film in 3-D again.
(laughs)
But the storytelling
is finally catching up to the technology.
Ned Flanders.
I can't believe you struck my husband.
Marge, I've been
racked with guilt and pain.
My mustache fell out; this is a clip-on.
Sorry, Homer. Now, do you mind
if I pray at your bedside?
No, I don't. If you pray to Superman.
(chuckles) Not praying to a character
in a comic book.
What about Christian Archie comics?
Neither canonical nor comical.
Here, I'll get you started.
Hail Superman, wearing tights,
Clark Kent be thy name,
one nation, under Zod...
-Not praying to Superman.
-Grouch.
Ned, Homie's a little cranky right now.
More than his eye,
I think you hurt his feelings.
Give him one of your
famous murmurs, Marge.
-My what?
-Your famous murmur.
You know. (murmurs)
I never made that noise in my life!
(murmurs)
Thanks, Flanders.
Punch my eye, destroy my marriage.
Now just pull the plug and let me die!
That's the plug for the light.
(imitating flatline)
(sighs)
(yawns)
Neddy, I know you feel guilty
about coldcocking Homer.
Please don't use that word in bed.
(groans) You need to get some sleep.
(sighs) Dare I take another sleep aid?
(sighs)
Better not take a full dose.
Mmm. See you in eight hours.
(snoring)
(groaning)
(gasping)
(screams)
(gate creaks)
Was this always waiting for me,
or was it recently thrown together?
That's what I want to know.
MALE VOICES: ♪ Hey-diddly hell-diddly ♪
♪ Welcome neighborino ♪
♪ Hey-diddly hell-diddly ♪
Down here, we worship
famous atheist Richard Dawkins,
author of The God Delusion!
(laughs maniacally)
I'm making Catholic saint stew.
(gasping)
(gasps)
No, not Surf 'n Murph.
(screams)
The answer to my woe must be in here.
♪ Whoo, let's get it on ♪
Nope, not that. Not to my taste.
Flag that for later. Finally.
I know what I must do.
(school bell ringing)
(sighs)
-Ms. Cantwell?
-Yes?
-Why are you so mean to me?
-You really want to know?
More than I want unicorns to be real.
Well, if you guess,
I'll give you extra credit.
-I remind you of you?
-Now you've got a demerit.
This class doesn't give demerits.
Now it does,
and you just got another one.
What if I homeschool?
You're bluffing; I've driven by your home.
(gasps)
Principal Skinner...
Not now.
I'm dealing with Mr. Testacleese.
Look, kids can be cruel, Dick.
NELSON: Ha-ha!
We don't know when we've gone too far!
(growls)
"Ann, Mark, Bill and Sally
are on the Ferris wheel.
Ann is behind Sally.
Mark is in front of Bill." (gasps)
Look who's on the Ferris wheel.
Your precious joeys!
(laughs maniacally)
(panting)
Better switch to social studies.
"Eleanor Roosevelt became
Franklin's eyes and ears and..."
(gasps)
Here's the new deal: you fail!
(cackling)
(groans)
(grunts) Oh!
I wish you wouldn't wear sweaters
that the senior ladies knit.
Well, putting my arms in sleeves
is about all I got to offer a woman.
-(groans)
-What's the matter, sweetie?
Is a book character having difficulties?
I have a bully at school.
Oh. Did you tell the teacher?
My bully is my teacher.
A teacher can't be a bully.
Oh, they sure can!
When I was a boy,
teachers would rap my knuckles
with a yardstick.
Now you've got the metric system.
We don't have the metric system.
What? This isn't Sweden?
And I'm not King Olaf?
Oh, I got some explaining to do
down at the bank.
CHALMERS: Skinner!
Why am I here?
Did this fat boy injure his eye
in shop class?
That place is a killing field.
We're here because our daughter
is being bullied by your teacher.
Mrs. Simpson, this school
does not hire bullies.
-That's right. We...
-Quiet, nerd!
Well, she's just a substitute.
Maybe you could transfer
Ms. Cantwell to another school.
Nix. She's already got two weeks tenure,
so she's impossible to dislodge.
I hate unions.
There's this guy at my plant,
caused three meltdowns,
and he still keeps his job.
Homer, that's you.
Oh, yeah.
I say, "Union," you say, "Power"!
-Union!
-Power.
(quietly) Marge, you're really
dogging it on the "power."
But don't worry.
Because of the union, you're safe.
So, just what are you
gonna do for our daughter?
We should talk about what
we're going to promise to do,
not what we'll actually do.
We really appreciate that.
(murmurs)
(bird squawks)
Look at those eyes.
There's an employee with
a healthy case of the go-get-'ems.
(snoring)
Hear that lion's roar of determination.
Homer, Homer, I found the answer!
Wha...? Huh?
Flanders. How did you get in here?
This place is a highly-sensitive area.
Who here wants to touch radiation?
"Life shall go for life,
eye for an eye, tooth for a tooth."
Hey, I don't go to where you work
and read the Bible to you.
I would embrace such a glad visit.
Just what do you want?
I want you to punch me in the eye.
If you do, then we're even,
according to Exodus,
Leviticus and Matthew.
You went and hired a law firm, eh?
That's pretty aggressive.
(sighs)
Jeepers creepers, pop my peeper!
Come on, man. What's the catch?
Homer, just call me a little bubble,
'cause I'm on the level. Punch me.
Hmm.
Come on, Homer.
I'm insisting on a fisting.
What's this about a fisting?
I'm not punching you, Flanders.
What? Why?
Because if I hit you back, we'll be even.
But if I don't hit you,
that makes me the better man.
And I'm liking the way that feels.
No, you can't.
If I'm not as good as you,
then I'm horrible!
It's not for me to judge, Ned, because...
I am the better man!
-Now, there's no need to...
-Better man, coming through!
Way better-better-better!
-Zing!
-Enough.
You may be the sweater man,
but Homer is the better man.
-Now you're rhyming?!
-Oh!
I didn't know you were left-handed.
Hello, Lisa.
I was shocked to hear
from Principal Skinner
that you and I aren't getting along.
You should never tell on a bully, Lisa.
Everyone knows that.
Lisa Simpson?!
In detention?
Every rap sheet has a first line.
What are you in for, murdering Chopin?
(laughter)
Chopin.
Can I ask you guys something?
Why does someone become a bully?
-Neglect.
-Abuse.
I'm a Cubs fan.
But why would my teacher be a bully?
-What? Huh?
-I don't know.
Your bully's a teacher?
That means all of us can be teachers.
Boo-yah!
I'm gonna buy me a Hyundai Elantra!
-Oh, cool!
-Whoa!
(sighs)
Do not cross.
It is that monster
that terrorizes the jolly fat man!
Come on, people.
You're safe as Sunday with me.
I wouldn't hurt a fly.
(coughing, gagging)
I saw the whole thing!
That innocent fly
flew from that fresh pile
of dog feces right into
that monster's mouth!
(spits)
Fear not, people.
I will lead you safely across.
(horn honking)
-MAN: Idiot!
-Help me, Flanders.
(sighs)
Never get into Heaven.
Took harp lessons for nothing.
ANNOUNCER (over TV):
And here comes the tarp.
The word "tarp," of course,
is short for "tarpaulin,"
which Wikipedia defines as a strong,
resilient, water-resistant material.
That definition is a hit with no errors!
What's wrong, sweetie?
My teacher's still bullying me.
Even after we came to school?
(sniffles)
That just made it worse.
Oh, every time I try to fix things,
it just makes things worse.
But I'm gonna fix this.
Uh-huh.
I think I have an idea.
Now there's a baby duck
paddling around on the tarp.
You think they move those legs
one at a time or both at once?
ANNOUNCER 2:
Oh, I'd go with one at a time, Vic.
ANNOUNCER: You know,
the great Mel Ott used to raise ducks
in Louisiana during the off-season.
And when a duck got sick,
he would take it to bed with him
till it got well.
Mm-hmm.
(doorbell rings)
Flanders, I've come to forgive you.
Oh, my prayers have been answered!
Well, actually, just this one.
Uh, there is one condition.
You want to hit me.
Well, sir, here's a roll of quarters
to put in your fist
for extra punching power.
Now, you can shatter my orbital bone.
That'll knock the wax off my candle.
Don't want to hit you.
I want your wife.
(gasps)
To elaborate,
I want your wife, the teacher,
to help get rid of Lisa's substitute.
Edna? You know how you said
you could help me
with any desire,
and nothing was forbidden?
Well, sir, I want you
to get rid of Lisa's bully teacher.
Ooh. Well, there's only one way:
the nuclear option.
How much plutonium do you want?
Got to warn you,
it might take me 20 minutes to get it.
-Ms. Cantwell?
-Yes?
I have a new student for your class.
(demonic voices singing)
-Yo.
-Yes.
This is a very rare mid-year
two-grade send-back.
Something's fishy.
Are you dating this boy?
Right. I can't be around him
'cause he's so delicious.
(laughs)
Well, I can't see
what harm one kid could do.
When I come out of this,
I'll be a butterfly.
(lawnmower whirring)
I just went to the bathroom
for two minutes.
I know. Posted a video online.
Stupid Lisa, stupid Lisa, stupid Lisa.
Okay, you've won.
You've driven me out of this
plum substitute teaching job.
Ms. Cantwell, I can make this stop.
All you have to do is like me.
I... I can't.
Wait, wait. There's no need to leave.
You showed up before
the students; that's all we asked.
You two are the worst-dressed
gay men I've ever met.
(tires screeching)
Ms. Cantwell, wait!
I've got to know before you leave.
Why don't you like me?
Lisa, sometimes you just
don't like a person.
There's no logical explanation.
It just is.
That is so unsatisfying.
(sighs)
Here we go.
If you don't get what you want,
you get all pouty.
All you pretty girls are the same.
You think I'm pretty?
Right, like you don't get told that
every day of your life,
with your perfect blonde hair,
that Kewpie doll voice
that drives the boys crazy.
And what eight-year-old wears pearls?
Bookworms like me
can't stand party girls like you.
She hates me because I'm pretty!
(whoops)
Not so pretty now, are you?
Can you sign my yearbook?
I'm glad the only beef between us
is this burger.
Mm, they sure are getting along.
(laughs) They don't know it,
but I slipped a little (whistles)
into the brownies I gave them.
How long has it been since
we prayed together, neighbor?
This is praying? Let me out of here!
(whimpering)
HOMER: Help me, God.
Shh!
Subtitled by A. Vandelay