♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
SKINNER: Children,
we've just been tipped off
that Superintendent Chalmers
is planning
a surprise inspection.
So let's clean up this pigsty.
Wha!
(cawing)
On another topic,
the following students
have won mountain bikes:
Bart Simpson,
Jimbo Jones,
Nelson Muntz.
I want you to keep filling
your shirt with crud
till I get back.
Yes, sir.
You may pick your bikes up
in utility basement B.
Fools.
(laughter)
Oops.
Still on.
Hey, what do you think
he meant
by that "fools" remark?
Eh, who cares?
Time to get me a mountain bike.
NELSON:
Hey, what gives?
Where are
the mountain bikes?
SKINNER: Sorry about
the ruse, gentlemen.
You're being swept
under the rug
for the superintendent's visit.
Enjoy.
(locks clicking)
How are we going
to get out of here?
And when are we going
to get our mountain bikes?
Would the world
judge me harshly
if I threw away
the key?
No, but the P.T.A
would tear you a new arse.
Wise counsel,
William,
but the potty talk
adds nothing.
Aye, sir.
You bath-taking,
underpants-wearing, lily-hugger.
Superintendent Chalmers,
welcome.
Hello, Seymour.
So, what's the word down
at 1 School Board Plaza?
We're dropping
the geography requirement.
The children
weren't testing well.
It was proving to be
an embarrassment.
Very good.
Back to the three "r's."
Two "r's" come October.
Hmm.
What do you think
of the banners?
Nothing but
transparent toadying.
They were the children's idea.
I tried to stop them.
It's always
the children's fault,
isn't it, Seymour?
Yes. Yes, it is, sir.
Imagine a school out there
with no bullies.
Science geeks
not getting beat up.
Kids using their
lunch money for food.
I can't take it!
Uhh! Huh!
Ooh! Ooh!
Hey, I think I can squeeze
through that vent.
All right.
All right, Bart.
Do it, man.
Now, remember,
little dude,
you're our only hope.
Uh!
Ow!
Got him!
-Way to go, man!
-Ha-ha!
May I interest you
in a Jell-O brick, sir?
There's a grape
in the center.
Well, I'm not made
of stone.
(laughs)
You're not made
of stone.
A brick, and you're
not made of... stone.
Ah, my beauty.
Wait till the
superintendent sees you.
Were it not a violation
of God's law,
I'd make you my wife.
Now there's a lonely man.
(gulp)
I'm new in town.
Be there a cool loch
where a lass could
wash her long red hair?
Nay, but there's a pool
at me apartment complex.
There was a rat
in the deep end
but we got him.
Ah. Lead on.
48... 49...
50.
Flag's up to date.
Very good, Seymour.
Now, are these children
as smart as they look?
Well, let's pick one
at random.
Uh... Hmm...
How about that one?
-You mean this boy here?
-No! No, Lisa Simpson.
When was the Battle
of New Orleans?
January 8, 1815,
two weeks after the war ended.
First-rate.
What's a battle?
(forced laughs)
Let's go.
Did that boy say
"What's a battle?"
No. He said
"What's that rattle?"
It's about
the heating ducts.
It sounded like "battle."
I've had a cold.
So you hear
"r's" as "b's"?
Yes.
I understand.
Come on, Bart.
Ride me.
I better not.
(clucking)
He's insulting
both of us.
Let's go.
(screaming)
(kids screaming)
Excellent.
Not a trace of urine.
Seymour,
you run a tight ship.
Well, you know
what they say, sir,
where there's no smoke,
there's no fire.
What an odd remark.
Why, that looks
like a 50¢ piece.
I'll just bend over
and get it.
(screams)
-It seems to be caught...
-(screams)
...between
these two flowers.
Aah!
No!
Ow, ow, ow.
Seymour, I was thinking
of promoting you
to assistant superintendent,
but instead, that plum
goes to Holloway.
Oh, but, sir,
he's a drunk.
-And a pill-popper.
-If I could just--
Silence!
And why is a cafeteria worker
posing as a nurse?
I get two paychecks
this way.
D'oh.
There's no detention
this time, Simpson.
This is the end.
You are expelled
from Springfield Elementary.
(tractor laughing)
(laughing hysterically)
Aw...
KENT: Tonight, on
Eye on Springfield:
The munchkins
from "The Wizard of Oz."
Where are they now?
And, we'll visit
a nudist camp...
for animals.
But first, a look
at the local holiday
that was called
distasteful and puerile
by a panel of hillbillies--
Whacking Day.
Oh, no! No!
In a tradition that dates
back to founding father
Jebediah Springfield,
every May 10th,
local residents gather
to drive snakes
into the center of town
and whack them
to snake heaven.
(grunting)
(crowd cheering)
After exposing Alger Hiss,
honorary grand marshal
Richard Nixon
goes after
another deadly hiss.
(grunting)
Is-is Whacking Day over?
(crowd booing)
Thank you.
Thanks for coming out.
(shuddering groan)
It's all so barbaric.
Hey, kids, how was school?
I learned how many drams
in a pennyweight.
I got expelled.
That's my boy.
Mmm... beer.
What?!
Look, Dad,
I don't need school.
I'll make my way
as a bootblack.
Shine your boots,
guv'nor?
No son of mine is gonna be
a 19th century
cockney bootblack.
We're gonna find
you another school.
Now, remember, Bart,
this is a religious school.
So be very careful about
what you say and do here.
No problemo.
Now, Bart,
since you're new here,
perhaps you'd favor us
with a Psalm.
How about... "Beans, Beans,
the Musical Fruit?"
Well, beans were a staple
of the Israelites.
Yes, proceed.
(clearing throat)
"Beans, beans,
the musical fruit
the more you eat,
the more you toot."
(humming)
Avert your eyes,
children!
He may take
on other forms!
I guess that's it.
I just can't be educated.
(sighs)
I can always get a job
testing dangerous
food additives.
We'd like you to try
this new diet cola.
We call it
Nature's Goodness.
-What's in it?
-2-4-desoxyprophenuramine.
(burps)
(grunting and growling)
Sweet.
Pleasing taste,
some monsterism.
Cool.
You're going to get
an education.
I'm going to teach you myself.
Marge, it's too late.
The boy is ten years old.
Let's focus our energy
on Lisa and the other one.
What's your problem?
-Whacking Day is coming.
-Whoo-hoo!
The greatest day
of the year.
But killing snakes is evil.
Maybe so, Lisa,
but it's part of our,
oh, so human nature.
Inside every man is a struggle
between good and evil
that cannot be resolved.
♪ I am evil Homer,
I am evil Homer ♪
♪ I am evil Homer
I am evil Homer... ♪
Have a nice day
at school, Lis.
I'll just try and make
the best of a bad situation.
(stretches)
Ah!
Bart, get dressed
for school.
I expect you to be in your
seat when the bell rings.
(giggling)
I bought a bell.
-(loud clanging)
-(both yelling)
I think I'll unplug that.
I'm your new teacher.
My name is Mrs. Simpson.
(chuckles)
(uneasy chuckle)
(groaning)
(tooting)
I didn't do it.
(groans)
(knocking)
Oh, that's right.
I invited a guest speaker
to talk to the class.
Hello, children.
I got separated from my platoon
after we parachuted
into Dusseldorf.
So I rode out the war
posing as a German
cabaret singer.
♪ Won't you come home,
Franz Brauder? ♪
♪ Won't you come home? ♪
MAN: Yoo-hoo!
Ach, du lieber!
Das ist not eine booby!
Is that story true, Grampa?
Well, most of it.
I did wear a dress
for a period in the '40s.
Oh, they had
designers then.
(garage door opening)
(yelling)
Look what I got, Marge.
A new whacking stick.
Whack!
Ooh!
Excuse me.
Whack, whack, whack!
Whoo, whoo, whoo!
Bart, I'd like you
to read this copy
of "Johnny Tremain."
It's a book I read
as a girl.
A book?
(blows a raspberry)
I think you might
like this.
It's about a boy
who goes to war.
His hand is deformed
in an accident.
Deformed?
Why didn't you say so?
They should call this book
"Johnny Deformed".
♪ Fight, fight, fight,
fight, fight, fight ♪
♪ The Itchy
and Scratchy show ♪
(gunshot)
-MAN: Oh, god!
-MAN 2: Get his gun!
♪ The Itchy
and Scratchy show ♪
"...hundreds would die
"but not the thing
they died for.
A man can stand up."
Wow.
Mm-hmm.
If you'd like to learn more
about colonial times, we could take
a field trip to Olde Springfield Towne.
(garage door opens)
(yelling)
D'oh!
(karate grunts)
(karate yell)
-LISA: Dad.
-Wha!
Dad!
Everyone likes Whacking Day,
but I hate it.
Is there something wrong
with me?
Yes, honey.
Then what should I do?
Just squeeze your rage
into a bitter little ball
and release it at
an appropriate time.
Like that day
I hit the referee
with a whiskey bottle.
-Remember that?
-Yeah.
When daddy hit
the referee?
-Yeah.
Any experience?
Yes. I played
Panicky Idiot #2
in "The Poseidon Adventure".
Sorry, we're looking
for more of a "duh, duh" idiot.
But... No, I see.
-(Barney groaning)
-Hello, Barney.
Are you playing
the town drunk?
Actually, I'm supposed
to be the governor.
(belching)
The enemy
surrounded the fort,
and said that if
the captain was sent out,
the rest would be spared.
-What did they do?
-They sent him out.
-Was he killed?
-And how!
That's why they call it
Fort Sensible.
MAN: This is Jebediah Springfield
at the Battle of Ticonderoga.
Next.
And here he is
killing a snake
on the very first
Whacking Day in 1775.
Hey, wait a minute.
That was the same day
he was at Ticonderoga.
How could he be in
two places at once?
Uh... um...
you see...
He'll blow the whole deal.
Get him out of here.
Roger.
(gasping)
If you want to learn
more about Whacking Day,
there are many fine books
in our gift shop.
Welcome to your official
Whacking Day headquarters.
I've hidden a snake
somewhere in the store.
The first one to whack it
gets a free Squishee.
(grunting)
I got it.
No. That's a licorice whip.
MAN:
Over here near the beer.
-Hey, hey!
-Aah!
Oh, I should have put
more thought into my promotion.
Aim for the body, men.
Right, chief.
(gunshot)
And the Lord said
"Whack ye all the serpents
which crawl on their bellies
"and thy town shall be
a beacon unto others."
So you see, Lisa,
even God himself
endorses Whacking Day.
Let me see that.
Mmm, no.
(to tune of "O Tannenbaum")
♪ O Whacking Day ♪
♪ Our hallowed
snake skull-cracking day ♪
♪ We'll break their backs,
gouge out their eyes ♪
♪ Their evil hearts,
we'll pulverize ♪
♪ O Whacking Day,
O Whacking Day ♪
♪ May God bestow
His grace on thee ♪
Here you go.
Official Whacking Day parking.
Ten dollars per axle.
(brakes screech)
Woo-hoo!
Hooray!
(Barney grunting)
Take that, snake.
And you too.
Snakes! Snakes everywhere!
Getting ready
for Whacking Day?
What's Whacking Day?
Did you bring
the pre-whacked snakes?
Beautiful.
Well, Marge,
should I whack slow or fast?
Slow, then fast.
(both giggling)
Uh-oh.
Dad, please,
for the last time,
I beg you,
don't lower yourself
to the level of the mob.
Lisa, maybe
if I'm part of that mob,
I can help steer it
in wise directions.
Now, where's my giant foam
cowboy hat and air horn?
(air horn blows)
And now to open
this year's festivities,
here's our Grand Marshall
the prophet of love,
Larry White.
Barry White.
No, it says here
Larry White.
I know my own name.
Yeah? Well, we'll see.
(crowd cheering)
Ladies and gentlemen,
my unlimited love to y'all.
It's truly an honor
to be here at this...
Hey, what is this
all about anyway?
(whispering)
Oh, God, no.
You people make me sick.
(cheering)
Were they even
listening to me?
I, uh, don't think so.
And now, let's hear it
for our own Miss Springfield.
Gentlemen,
start your whacking.
D'oh!
Eww! A bug!
(screams)
If the snakes
were in here,
we could protect them.
Well, according to this,
snakes hear by sensing
vibrations in the ground,
so if we put our
stereo speakers on the ground
and play something
with a lot of bass,
those snakes will be in here
like Oprah on a baked ham.
Oh, good idea. Let's see.
Bass, bass...
"Tiny Tim",
"The Chipmunks Greatest Hits",
"A Castrato Christmas."
(groans)
♪ Can't get enough
of your love, babe ♪
(gasps) Mr. White, can we
borrow you for a minute?
Anything...
for a lady.
("Can't Get Enough
of Your Love, Babe" playing)
♪ Don't bother the snakes ♪
♪ Leave all the snakes ♪
♪ Alone ♪
♪ Ah, yeah ♪
♪ Oh-whoa, babe ♪
♪ Come here ♪
♪ My darling, I... ♪
♪ Can't get enough
of your love, babe ♪
♪ Girl, I don't know,
I don't know why ♪
♪ Can't get enough
of your love, babe ♪
♪ Some things
I can't get used to ♪
♪ No matter how I try ♪
(rumbling)
♪ It's like the more you
give, the more I want ♪
♪ And, baby, that's no... ♪
♪ That's no lie ♪
♪ Tell me, what can I say? ♪
In here!
♪ What am I gonna do? ♪
♪ How should
I feel when-- ♪
-(record stops)
-(indistinct yelling)
Hey, where did
all the snakes go?
(hisses)
BART: People of Springfield,
Whacking Day is a sham!
It was started in 1924
as an excuse
to beat up the Irish.
(murmuring)
'Tis true.
I took many a lump,
but 'twas all in good fun.
Now wait a minute!
How can you people
turn on snakes
after all they've
done for you?
I'm an old man.
I hate everything
but Matlock.
Ooh, it's on now.
Mrs. Glick, who killed
all those rats in your basement?
Snake did.
You like snakes,
don't you, Barry White?
I love the sexy slither
of a lady snake.
Oh, baby.
ALL: Hooray for snakes!
Hooray for snakes!
Look at this, everyone,
12 dead snakes.
(booing)
I'm sick of you people.
You're nothing but a pack
of fickle mush-heads.
He's right.
Give us hell, Quimby!
(cheering)
♪ Born free ♪
♪ As free as the wind blows ♪
♪ As free
as the grass grows... ♪
Bart, I'm very impressed
at the independent learning
you've displayed here.
Thanks, Seymour.
Uh... yes.
Um, anyway, as a reward
for your studying,
I've decided to welcome you
back to our school.
You'll be reunited with
your chums, Nelson, Jimbo, D--
Oh, dear God!
I guess I've always
used violence
as a way of
getting attention.
Yes, yes,
me too.
-Oh...
Faster, Willie, faster.
Now we give them the bikes,
no one sues.
(chuckles)
(forced chuckle)
What if they're dead, sir?
Then we ride these bikes
to Mexico and freedom, Willie!
Freedom!
Freedom.
(laughs)
Yeah, I'll turn you in
at the first toll booth.
♪♪
Shh.
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.