♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
(whistle blowing)
(beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Ahh!
-(tires screech)
(snoring)
(growling)
(whining)
(mumbling)
(sniffs)
Ooh!
(snoring)
♪♪ (low note)
-(snoring)
-♪♪ (low note)
(snoring)
(honking)
(moaning)
(mumbling)
-Dad, we've been robbed!
-Wake up, Dad! Wake up!
There was a burglar,
and he took my saxophone!
Whoo-hoo!
-And our portable TV.
-D'oh!
-And my necklace.
-Ah, that's no big loss.
Homer, that necklace
was a priceless
Bouvier family heirloom.
You probably got
a whole drawer full of 'em.
Well, yes, I do,
but they're all heirlooms too.
The burglar even took
my stamp collection.
You had
a stamp collection?
(laughing)
(phone rings)
NELSON: Stamp collection?
Ha-ha!
Ohh. Bart's pain is funny,
but mine isn't.
That saxophone was
my one creative outlet.
It was the only way I could
truly express myself.
Shh! Quiet, Lisa.
Hey, the burglar left
his calling card.
(Marge reading)
Cute.
Hidilly-ho, neighboreenos.
Can't talk. Robbed.
Go hell.
You folks
got robbed too?
The burglar took my
Shroud of Turin beach towels.
Wow!
It's a crime wave.
Good Lord! My Stormin' Norman
commemorative plates stolen!
Again.
Hey, I thought I had
more stuff than this.
We are insured,
aren't we, Mom?
Homer, tell your child
what you bought
when I sent you to town
to get some insurance.
Curse you, magic beans!
Oh, stop blaming the beans.
Hello, police?
Are you sitting down? Good!
I wish to report
a robbery.
A robbery, right.
Thanks for the report.
That's another one, Lou.
723 Evergreen Terrace.
Well, there doesn't seem
to be any pattern yet,
but if I take this one
and move it here...
and I move these
over here--
Hello! It almost looks
like an arrow.
Hey, look,
Chief, it's pointing right
at this police station.
-Let's get out of here!
-(all screaming)
When cat burglaries start,
can mass murders be far behind?
This reporter isn't saying
that the burglar is
an inhuman monster
like the wolfman,
but he very well could be.
So, professor,
would you say it's time
for everyone to panic?
Yes, I would, Kent.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Ladies and gentlemen, please.
We have a major break
in the case.
We recovered
the burglar's handkerchief
from one of the crime scenes.
Now, one sniff
of this baby,
and our tracking dog
will be hot on his trail.
Gosh, look at me.
I'm sweatin' like a pig here.
Ah. Ah, man.
That's better.
All right.
Get the scent, boy.
Come on, get the scent.
-Now kill him! (yells)
-(growling)
-Hey!
-(gasping)
Ah, my jugular! Ah!
Oh! Any questions?
Well, as you can see,
when the burglar
trips the alarm,
the house raises
from its foundations,
and runs down the street and
around the corner to safety.
(nervous chuckle)
Well the--
the real humans won't, uh--
won't burn quite so fast
in there.
Aye!
(metal clanging)
Cool!
High-tech security system.
(lasers firing)
(shouting, laughing)
All right!
Free laserium.
All the colors
of the 'bow, man.
Ow! Oh.
My cataracts are gone.
I can see again.
All the beauty of na--
Oh!
I'm blind. Oh, well.
Easy come, easy go.
(snoring)
(screams)
It's the cat burglar!
Please don't kill me!
Abe, can I borrow
your ointment?
Oh, it's you, Malloy.
All right.
But this time clean off
the applicator!
-(gunshot)
-(gasps)
Thank you for coming.
I'll see you in hell.
All right. These are our new
family security rules.
Be home before dark,
and make sure
you're not followed.
Lock all doors
and windows.
And don't take candy
from strangers.
Marge, they're only human!
What's the point
of all these precautions?
I've already lost
the only thing
that matters to me.
Oh, Lisa, stop pining
for your saxophone.
I got you
another instrument.
-What, this jug?
-(rhythmic tones)
Hee-hee! (laughing)
Whee! Whoa-ho-ho!
Lisa, never, ever stop
in the middle of a hoedown.
(crying)
Oh, honey,
I didn't realize how much
that horn meant to you.
Don't worry.
Daddy's gonna get it back.
I don't know how but
I'll figure out something.
Thank you.
You know, Lisa,
music helps Daddy think.
-(groans)
-(rhythmic tones)
-(crowd chattering)
-FLANDERS: Welcome, neighbors.
Since the police can't seem
to get off their duffaroonies
to do something
about this burglareeno,
I think it's time we start
our own neighborhood watch...
aroonie!
-(cheering)
-Now, who should lead the group?
-You!
-ALL: Yea!
(chanting)
Flanders!
Flanders! Flanders!
I don't really have
very much experience, but--
-Someone else!
-ALL: Yea!
(chanting)
Someone else!
-I'm someone else.
-He's right!
We don't need a thinker.
We need a doer.
Someone who'll act without
considering the consequences.
ALL: (chanting)
Homer! Homer! Homer!
-I'm with you, Homer!
-I be with ya too, matey.
-I'm with you, Homer.
-You're the man, Homer.
-You should do it.
-You're the man, man.
I'll join! I'm filled with
piss and vinegar.
At first I was just
filled with vinegar.
Hmm, sorry, Dad.
You're too old.
(sputtering)
Too old?
Why, that just means
I have experience!
Who chased the Irish out
of Springfield Village
in aught-four?
Me! That's who.
And a fine job
you did too.
Aw, Dad, you've done
a lot of great things,
but you're
a very old man now,
and old people
are useless.
-Aren't they? Aren't they? Huh?
-(giggling)
Yes, they are!
(baby talk)
Stop it!
It's a form of abuse!
Hmm. Mm-hmm.
-Mm-hmm-hmm.
-Arr!
I don't think the guns
are a good idea.
Marge!
We're responsible adults.
-(gunshot)
-Whoops.
And if a group of
responsible adults
can't handle firearms
in a responsible way--
-(gunshot)
-Sorry.
-Uh-oh.
-(gunshot)
-Me again.
-Sorry.
Okay, we've got the secret
vigilante handshake.
Now we need code names.
I'll be Cue Ball,
Skinner can be Eight Ball,
Barney will be Twelve Ball,
and, Moe, you can be Cue Ball.
You're an idiot.
(grunts)
So, wedding, huh?
No, we're forming
a vigilante group.
Come with me.
See, it's a miniature
version of the A-bomb.
The government
built it in the '50s
to drop on beatniks.
"Radiant, cool,
crazy nightmares.
Zen New Jersey nowhere."
-(finger snapping)
-(jet engine roaring)
Put this in your pipe
and smoke it!
-(engine rattles)
-Hmm? (grunt)
"How now, brown bureaucrat?"
(grunting)
Whoo-hoo!
Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
Whaa-ha-ha-ho!
Take that,
Maynard G. Krebs!
-Hey, see the sign?
-Sorry.
Okay, men. It's time
to clean up this town!
Meaning what,
exactly?
You know, push people around,
make ourselves feel big.
Bart, give me
that megaphone of yours.
It's not just
"a megaphone," Dad.
It's a Rapmaster 2000.
Never mind the commercials.
Just give it to me.
I've gotta whip
this neighborhood into shape.
-Move along there.
-(gasps) It's Hammer!
♪♪ (dance)
Return to your homes
and places of businesses.
(chattering)
-(grunting) Hmm?
-♪♪ (saxophone)
(gasping)
Hey, you!
Where'd you get
that saxophone?
-Sears.
-Get him!
-(angry shouting)
-I got him! I got him!
HOMER: No burning leaves
without a permit!
-MAN: I got one.
-HOMER: Too late!
(footsteps approaching)
You better have a good reason
for doing that, boy.
It makes me feel
like a big man.
Let me check my reason list.
Yep, it's on here.
Hey, you're that
drunken posse.
Wow! Can I join ya?
I don't know.
Can you swing a sack
of doorknobs?
-Can I!
-You're in. Here's the sack.
But you gotta supply
your own knobs.
So I said to him,
"Look, buddy,
"your car was upside down
when we got here.
"And as for your grandma,
she shouldn't have
mouthed off like that!"
Dad, don't you see
you're abusing your power
like all vigilantes?
I mean, if you're the police,
who will police the police?
I dunno.
Coast Guard?
Homer, wasn't the whole point
to catch the cat burglar?
And I still don't have
my saxophone.
Lisa, the mob is working on
getting your saxophone back,
but we've also expanded
into other important areas.
Literacy programs,
preserving our beloved
covered bridges,
world domination.
-World domination?
-Oh, that might be a typo.
(thinking)
Mental note:
The girl knows too much.
Mr. Simpson, how do you respond
to the charge
that petty vandalism
such as graffiti is down 80%,
while heavy sack beatings
are up a shocking 900%?
Oh, people can
come up with statistics
to prove anything, Kent.
Forfty percent
of all people know that.
I see. Well, what do you
say to the accusation
that your group
has been causing more crimes
than it's been preventing?
Oh, Kent, I'd be lying
if I said my men
weren't committing crimes.
Hmm, touché.
(phone rings)
Well, it looks like
we have our first caller.
And I mean ever because
this is not a call-in show.
-Hello. You're on the air.
-MAN: Hello, Kent.
Hello, Homer,
my arch nemesis.
Y'ello.
Uh... you do realize
who this is.
Uh... Marge?
No, Homer,
I'm not your wife,
although I do enjoy
her pearls.
As a matter of fact,
I'm holding them right now.
-Listen.
-(pearls clattering)
Why, you monster!
And you have my daughter's
saxophone too!
-(man gasping)
-(roaring)
Homer!
That's our stage manager!
Oh. Sorry.
I'm a little nervous.
It may interest you to know
that for my next crime,
I'll be pinching
the pride and joy of
the Springfield Museum,
the world's largest
cubic zirconia.
Listen, Mr. Cat Burglar.
I vow to go without sleep
and guard the Springfield Museum
day and night
for as long as it takes
from now on,
unless you want to
taunt me more
by giving me
an approximate time.
-We'll be right back.
-I get to say that!
Son, we want to help you
catch that plug-ugly yegg.
Dad, the best way
for you to help
is to set a good example.
Just stand around
and don't steal anything.
-Hey!
-We're on our break!
-Any sign of the burglar yet?
-He'll show.
-How's that?
-It's his job.
-He's a burglar.
♪♪ (theme from "Dragnet")
Well, Mr. Cat Burglar.
You'd like to get in here,
wouldn't you?
There's just
one little problem--
thirty-six years ago,
some lady gave birth to
a man named Homer J. Simp--
Oh, my God!
Underage kids drinking beer
without a permit!
BOYS: (chanting)
Chug! Chug! Chug!
"Asleep at the switch"?
I wasn't asleep.
I was drunk!
I believe you, Dad.
Well, no matter
what the paper says,
I still have a job to do.
-(angry shouting)
-(grunting)
Go home, Simpson!
You let me down, man!
Now I don't believe
in nothing no more.
I'm going to law school.
No!!
Dad, maybe this
will cheer you up.
(rhythmic tones)
Oh, this doesn't work
anymore.
I didn't say stop.
Oh, my. I had no idea
how much this town loved
that zirconia.
Let me through!
Coming through! Oh!
Oh, Grandpa,
they pelted you too?
No, actually I fell down
at the Big Boy.
Son, I've come
to help you.
I know who
the cat burglar is.
-What?
-Who?
-Huh?
-What?
Well, well, well.
Before, I was too old
and no one wanted my help.
Suddenly, look who comes
to old grandpa with--
Wait! Where are you going?
Come back. I'll tell you.
He was right under my nose
the whole time.
He lives in my
retirement home.
His name is Malloy.
Wow! How'd you
track him down, Grandpa?
Good question.
On one of my frequent trips
to the ground--
(yelps)
I noticed Malloy
wore sneakers...
for sneaking!
My next clue came
just yesterday
at the museum.
We felt slighted
by your age bashing
and started home.
Malloy said,
"I'll catch up with you."
I couldn't quite
put my finger on it.
There was something strange
about the way he walked.
Much more vertical
than usual.
And finally, Malloy,
unlike most retired people,
has the world's largest
cubic zirconia
on his coffee table.
Aw, Dad,
I could kiss ya!
Well, kiss me right here.
It's the only part
that still has feeling.
-Mwah!
-Hmm.
-(angry shouting)
-No, wait!
I know where the burglar is!
-To the retirement home!
-ALL: Hooray!
-MAN: Let's go!
-(angry shouting)
And there she is,
the world's largest
cubic zirconia.
What an eyesore!
So, Mr. Malloy,
it seems that the cat
has been caught
by the very person
that was trying to catch him.
-How ironic.
-Homer, old chap, well done.
If anyone
was going to catch me,
I'm glad it was you.
Actually, it wasn't me.
It was my dad, Grandpa.
Thanks, son.
So you see, old people
aren't so useless after all.
Malloy's old, and he
outsmarted the lot of you.
And I'm even older,
and I outsmarted him!
(laughing)
-Shut up.
-I've had my moment.
And of course,
I'm happy to return
all of your
treasured possessions.
(happy murmuring)
-Selma, my dear,
-Ohh.
your lock of
MacGyver's hair.
Thank you.
I'll add it to the ball.
And little Lisa,
here's your saxophone.
Thank you,
and thank you, Dad.
You got it back,
just like you said
you would.
I sincerely regret
any inconvenience
I may have caused,
and although I have stolen
your material goods,
let me assure you
that your dear town
has stolen my heart.
ALL: Aww!
-Oh, he's so charming.
-Let's let him go.
-Yeah!
-Oh, sorry, folks.
Gee, I really hate to spoil
this little love-in,
but Mr. Malloy
broke the law.
And when you break the law,
you gotta go to jail.
Uh, that reminds me.
Uh, here's your monthly kickback.
You just-- You couldn't
have picked a worse time.
HOMER:
I caught the cat burglar!
That means you!
You are the cat burglar!
I suppose you're
wondering where I hid
all the millions of dollars
that I stole over the years.
-Shut up!
-Wait a minute.
Maybe we should hear him out.
Where'd you hide
the loot, Malloy?
It's buried right here
in Springfield,
under a big "T."
No kidding.
Big "T," huh?
Well, I guess I'll be going
to my home now
and sleep.
Yeah, me too.
I will also go home...
for sleep.
(all shouting)
Let me through!
I gotta find a big "T"!
There's millions of dollars
buried under a big "T"!
-What?
-(people screaming)
We need
more information.
Very well. It's buried
at 4723 Maple Valley Road.
(sighs)
You take highway 201
south for 15 minutes.
You take a left,
a left--
(shouting)
-(yells)
-(whimpers)
(siren wailing)
Whoa!
That was fun, ladies!
(horn honks)
What's the matter
with you, kid?
You told me
the stream was shallow!
Why, you-- I--
(chuckling)
Oh, you. Oh, kid.
I'll get even with you.
(gurgling)
Hordes of panicky people seem
to be evacuating the town
for some unknown reason.
Professor,
without knowing precisely
what the danger is,
would you say it's time
for our viewers to
crack each other's
heads open
and feast on
the goo inside?
Yes, I would, Kent.
(siren wailing)
♪♪ (choir vocalizing)
Whoa.
I found something.
(excited chattering)
WOMAN: Come on.
Pull it out.
-It's just a piece of paper.
-It's mine!
"Frightfully sorry,
"but there is no
hidden treasure.
"I have already used this time
to escape from your jail.
Fondest wishes--"
Oh, I can't make out
the signature!
Keep digging. We're bound
to find something.
QUIMBY: Mmm. I guess we're
not gonna find anything.
OTTO: Uh, how are we gonna
get out of here?
HOMER: We'll dig our way out!
(grunting)
WIGGUM: No, no.
Dig up, stupid.
(shovels digging)
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.