♪
Here's your ticket
to witness history.
Chuck Wildler breaking
the pitching record
- for most batters
knocked unconscious.
- Mm-hmm!
Upper deck. We're so far away.
I wanted to see teeth fly.
Relax, nobody comes
to Isotopes games.
We'll move into the empty seats
behind home plate.
You'll be so close
to the carnage,
you'll have flashbacks
for the rest of your life.
What the heck?
Why is it so crowded?
And why are they all girls?
And why are they all checking
each other's teeth
for lipstick?
- Do I have lipstick?
- Is it gone?
ANNOUNCER (over P.A.): First up,
a young slugger batting .320
with a hat size of 11...
Tork "Lollipop" Williams.
(laughs)
Wildler hates this guy's head.
FEMALE VOICE: Your jumbotron
is now under the control
of the Ashlee Starling
Murmur Nation.
(girls cheering)
Why are you all standing
at the same time?
That's not how the wave works.
You've got to undulate.
Ashlee's album Squeeze Play
drops now.
Featuring her
hit single "Glitter!"
- ♪
- (girls cheering)
What the hell
is an Ashlee Starling?
Ashlee Starling
is a whiny pop singer
for whiny girls
who love to whine.
♪ Yeah, yeah,
you broke my heart ♪
♪ Into a million pieces ♪
♪ And like glitter
those pieces shine ♪
♪ They reflect all the
bad things you said and did ♪
♪ And I can't get them
out of my mind ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ I'm not bitter,
now I'm glitter ♪
- (grumbles) Ah! (grumbles)
-♪ You threw me away
like litter... ♪
Stop this stupid
well-planned thing!
-♪ I'm not bitter,
now I'm glitter ♪
- (both groaning)
(gasping)
- HOMER: Oh, my God,
it's happening.
-♪ Bet your new girl will find ♪
- For the record! And... Oh.
-♪ Pieces of me everywhere ♪
-♪ Like glitter. ♪
- HOMER: D'oh!
- (grunts)
- We missed it.
- (girls exclaiming)
Childhood officially ruined.
Let's get a dozen hot dogs
and head home.
- (gasps)
- Oh...
- What?
- Do I have hot dog?
- Am I good?
- (indistinct chatter)
Oh, I should have hot dog
in my teeth.
Sir, how long have you been
a proud member
of the Murmur Nation?
Since never.
Ashlee Starling
is a whiny pop singer
for whiny girls
that love to whine. Right, boy?
I disagree.
Ashlee Starling's
well-crafted songs
speak to the inner lives
of teens and tweens alike.
- But you said...
- I've never met this man.
If I knew him,
I would teach him to love Ashlee
by sharing that one song
about how you're beautiful
no matter what
your face looks like.
Why are you talking like that?
(gasps)
Did one of them bite you?
Do you have any idea
what you just mobilized?
You insulted Ashlee Starling
on camera.
I am looking into the eyes
of a dead man.
Wha...?
(vocalizing)
MARTY (over radio):
Looking for the fifth caller
to win all you can eat bread
- at Yeasties Doughhouse and...
- (radio static)
- Huh?
-♪ I'm not bitter... ♪
What? Oh... You again.
Not on my radio.
(grunts)
-♪ I'm not bitter... ♪
-♪ Not bitter... ♪
- What's happening?
-♪ You threw me... ♪
-♪ Threw me... ♪
- (grunting)
-♪ Like glitter. ♪
- (screaming)
Glitter?
(whimpering)
Eh, who's there?
I-I see you.
(panting)
(gasps)
(girl's laughter echoing)
What the...
(whimpering)
(gasps)
A seed cake?
Well, you know my motto:
even the worst cake
is still cake.
(shrieking)
(screaming)
(shaky breathing)
- Aah!
- (screeches)
"Love" is in quotes.
What were you thinking?
You've made
the nuclear power plant
a very dangerous place to work.
You have become the target
of a highly organized,
newly-hormonal fan army.
Because of you,
I have to wear this T-shirt.
In case anyone's wondering,
I don't agree with Homer.
Whew. You don't know
these fan armies.
They're all ruthless psychos.
Except for the BTS ARMY,
- who are just and pure of heart.
- Mm-hmm.
(groans softly)
Dad, if you ever want to breathe
un-glittered air again,
you have to repent and devote
your life to Ashlee.
Oh, you're blowing this
out of proportion.
Everything's gonna be f-f...
(sneezes)
Unrelated.
I got glitter in every fold,
crack and wedge.
I really need
the comforting burn
of Flaming Hot Oreos.
(screeching)
(whimpering)
Oh, God.
No!
We did it.
We have broken him.
You sure you're cool with this?
Totally.
My dad has to pay
for what he said about Ashlee.
Great job, Murmur Nation.
We've got D'oh-boy on the ropes.
I feel bad for the ropes.
We couldn't have made it
this far without you, Lisa.
I'm doing it for Ashlee.
I'm a hardcore Starling fan.
She encourages girls everywhere
to speak truth to power
and never date John Mayer.
But selling out your own dad?
That is Stone Cold Creamery,
and I'll take two scoops.
I love my dad,
but you guys are my besties.
(gasps)
I've never used the plural
of bestie before.
Marge, did you get the paper?
(groans)
Once again, Marge is out living
it up at the grocery store.
(grunting)
Ooh, lawn burger.
Mm?
(grumbling)
(gasps)
The mothership.
Mm...
Oh!
(grunts)
I'm still waiting
on cheese fries.
(grumbles)
(scoffs)
Just as I thought,
Ashlee what's-her-face.
I'm not Ashlee.
Aah!
What's your face?
I'm pop sensation,
U.N. AmbassaDiva
and lip gloss spokesmouth,
- (echoing): Echo.
- Mm?
I had my name
legally changed to do that.
I hear the birdbrain fans
of Murmur Nation
have been giving you trouble.
I haven't had a single day's
sleep at work.
Miss Ashlee and I have
the standard megastar feud.
We released dueling diss tracks
then diss sketches on SNL.
We both diss-dated
Pete Davidson.
That guy's got big diss energy.
I've always believed
the frenemy of my frenemy
- is my ene-friend.
- Obviously.
Why don't we team up
and clip some Starling wings?
I have my own fan army.
(echoing):
The Echolaliacs.
Hmm...
An eye for an eye.
(gasps)
Everyone wins!
Let's do it.
Oh, careful...
- (gasps)
- 'Sup, Books.
Ooh, looks like
you're making a glitter bomb.
Don't be ridicu...
(coughs) ...lous.
Look, I know
you're part of the army
that's driving dad bananas.
- I want in.
- No way.
You don't believe
in the power of music
and weaponizing breakups.
Lisa, I have spent years
thinking of ways
to screw with dad,
and they're all right here.
Hmm.
Skunk vendors,
atomic whoopee cushions.
This is exactly what we need.
But why would you help us?
Because, for the first time,
you have something I want:
an army.
I can finally bring my wildest
prank dreams to life
on a grand scale.
Like this. I call it
the Alley Oops.
Okay, as soon as
the Fat Lebowski
sticks his fingers in the ball,
they'll be Krazy-Glued in
and he'll bowl himself
down the greased alley
right into the waiting pool
of garbage juice.
The pool's in place.
We drained
every dumpster in town.
- Yes!
- Got him.
Whoa.
What's happening?
Oh, God!
My fingers seem to be...
(grunts)
...great at bowling.
- (gasps) He must be on to us.
- Abort!
- Everyone back to HQ.
- Go.
- But quietly.
My mom's got an Herbalife thing.
Hm?
♪
(gasps)
Homer Simpson is now
under the protection
of my Echolaliacs.
(echoing):
Echolaliacs.
(coughs)
They're smoke bombing us
with her signature scent,
Reverb by Echo.
- (coughing)
- KID: My lungs!
Your dad has made an alliance
with the Echo fan army.
Maybe we should leave him alone.
No. We can't back down.
Ashlee isn't just
a singer we like.
She's the photo in our locker.
She's our one and only
Google Alert.
She's the tattoo
I've been designing
for when I turn 18.
We aren't just fans of Ashlee,
we are Ashlee!
ALL:
We are Ashlee!
Lis, are you really gonna
whip up these psychos
into a full-fledged fan war?
- Yeah.
- Cool.
You psychos heard my sister.
It's war.
(cheering)
♪
- (phone dings)
- (grumbles)
(growls)
(grunting)
D'oh!
(grunts, sighs)
The winner is Ashlee Starling.
(cheering, applause)
- (grunts) Yoink!
- BOTH: Oh!
Huh? (exclaiming)
Ew, carrot.
Glitter war is sparkly hell.
Mrs. Simpson, are you proud
of what your husband
- has done to this town?
- No.
The thing I hate most
about armies,
fan or otherwise, is the mess.
I love my husband,
but I disagree
with him about Ashlee.
I listened to one of her albums.
It was great.
She sure knows which of
her boyfriends were bad for her.
- All of them.
- (laughs)
You heard it here first.
Ashlee Starling is great,
but not as great
as BTS or their fans,
- who are sane and perfect.
- Mm-hmm.
I got the family size.
This'll make enough slime
to fill his toilet
and his secret toilet.
Maybe we could work in
Tabasco toilet paper.
- Whoa, that's messed-up.
- Thanks. (chuckles)
I'm learning from you.
(chuckles)
This has been really great.
Who would have thought
that you and I could connect
- on such a deep level?
- (phone dings)
- You're out of the group.
- What?!
Yeah. Mackenzie said you weren't
excited enough to meet her dog.
But-but who names
their dog Greg?
That's a man name.
And why didn't you
stand up for me?
Meh, sheroes before bros.
- I'll tell dad everything.
- If you do,
then I'll show him
your little notebook of pranks.
Dad would be so surprised
to learn that the handsome pills
he's been taking are actually
the dog's heartworm medication.
- Oh...
- (doorbell rings)
(gasps)
It's the Wingmen!
Ashlee Starling's
live-in aerialists.
Oh!
Aah!
What?
What happened?
Ashlee Starling wants
to have dinner with me.
Aah!
She sent a dress for me to wear.
Whee! (grunts)
"Hope this fits you, Marge"?
(gasps) It's for me?
She must have heard me tell
Kent Brockman
that I listened
to her song once.
What? I mean...
(laughs)
I have been a very dedicated fan
since I was four,
but you... you just made
one comment.
(laughs) Good for you.
I'm having dinner
with a famous person.
(giggles)
I'm team Sparrow.
It's Starling!
As a great man once said,
"Haw-haw."
I can't believe you're
having dinner with my nemesis,
after all the handsome pills
I take for you.
- (helicopter approaching)
- That's my ride.
(gasps)
Hello, Marge.
- I'm Ashlee Starling.
- I know.
We hired a look-alike of you
for Lisa's birthday.
You're taller.
She had bigger boobs.
Ooh, thank you.
- Ooh, wow!
- (chuckles)
It's my own line
of sparkling whiskey.
Mmm, yum.
Mmm, mmm. (smacks lips)
Look at your sweet family.
I'm sure your husband
- is perfect.
- (kids growling)
- Stop it!
(laughs)
Homer is far from perfect.
Really?
Tell me everything.
Mmm, ooh.
(grunting)
(laughs)
Ashlee said
the funniest thing at dinner.
No one wants to hear
about your thrilling night
with a vengeful pop diva.
Lisa, sweetie, delight us
with one of your little stories
about how the planet
is choking on plastic.
Don't "sweetie" her.
She's the one behind
those Murmur Nation
- attacks on you.
- (gasps)
(gasps)
Lisa. Wh...
But you're the one kid
I had on purpose.
Well, Bart was part of it, too,
and he doesn't even like Ashlee.
He did it just for the fun
of torturing you.
(gasps)
You?
The person I would most suspect?
I never could have
seen it coming.
Kids, how could you do that
to your father?
What? You're the worst
betrayer of all.
Dad, you should see
the video Ashlee just dropped
after her night of girl talk
with Mom.
♪
♪ When we first got together ♪
♪ I didn't see your flaws ♪
♪ But then I saw you
eating ChapStick ♪
♪ And it kind of gave me pause ♪
♪ Your man-boobs
you call cha-chis ♪
♪ Your fontanelle
that never fused ♪
♪ When I thought
that you were perfect ♪
♪ I must've been confused ♪
♪ And it's hard to ignore it ♪
♪ When you burp-talk
in your sleep ♪
♪ Somehow, you've got
athlete's foot ♪
♪ On both of your knees ♪
♪ Whoa, oh ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ We had dinner
with my sisters ♪
♪ And it turned into a fight ♪
♪ You kept insisting
that the Moon ♪
♪ Was just the Sun at night ♪
♪ Seeing you the way they do ♪
♪ Makes me realize ♪
♪ You're far from perfect ♪
♪ When we moved in together ♪
♪ I learned things
I never knew ♪
♪ That you sit for number one ♪
♪ But you stand for number two ♪
♪ Not even close,
it's kind of gross. ♪
That last one is not true.
I hover 'cause I'm afraid
of being flushed.
Oh, my God.
Ashlee took the things
I told her
in new-friend confidence
and made it into
a bad boyfriend song.
This has been quite the morning.
But I'm most disappointed
in you, Maggie.
Mm? Eh?
Evil triumphs
when good babies do nothing.
I'm leaving.
Homer? What happened? Aw.
I can't believe
they would do this to me.
Hey, could I use
your billion-dollar
entertainment complex
to produce a diss track
to take them all down?
You should be careful with that.
When my dermatologist
wouldn't fly to Japan
to remove a culturally
insensitive mole,
I hit him with my single
"Mole Check, Soul Check."
It destroyed him.
Do you want to do that
to your family?
No. I love them.
Homer, music isn't just
for dissing people.
Wha...?!
Why don't we make a video
that tells your family
how much they hurt you?
An "I've been dissed" track,
- if you will.
- I will.
It's been three days.
Dad's never
stayed mad this long.
Maybe we should
run the can opener.
He always comes
when he hears that.
I tried that already.
- (whimpers)
- (burps)
Tomorrow, we'll start
calling theme park jails.
- Homie!
- Dad!
- Where you been?
- LISA: Hmm?
- MARGE: Hmm.
♪ One opinionated man ♪
♪ Doesn't stand a chance ♪
-♪ Against an army of tweens ♪
- ECHO: ♪ Damn tweens ♪
♪ It's like trying to fight
an angry hill of ants ♪
♪ Flying on the backs ♪
-♪ Of killer bees ♪
- ECHO: ♪ Killer bees ♪
HOMER:
♪ I don't change ♪
♪ My shorts no more ♪
♪ Glitter bombs inside my ♪
-♪ Undie drawer ♪
- ECHO: ♪ Undie drawer ♪
♪ The word "family"
has a bitter ring ♪
ECHO:
♪ Bitter ring ♪
HOMER:
♪ It's my family who's been ♪
-♪ Glittering ♪
- ECHO: ♪ Glittering ♪
♪ It's my family ♪
Breakfast and betrayal.
Pancakes bitter in my mouth,
yet I ate seven.
You sent an army
against those who are me.
You three took.
Three-took,
the opposite of for-give.
Yet, I forgive.
-♪ Marge ♪
- ECHO: ♪ You brought
joy and dinner to my life ♪
♪ You're still
a Fudgie Whale of a wife ♪
-♪ Even when I do things wrong ♪
- HOMER: I wrong do things!
ECHO: ♪ Like pass out
on the lawn at crack of dawn ♪
- HOMER: ♪ Bart ♪
- ECHO: ♪ This verse
goes out to Bartholomew ♪
- HOMER: Why, you little...!
- ECHO:
♪ When I smell mothballs ♪
♪ Now I think beef stew ♪
♪ Why, you little... You ♪
♪ You're kind of cool,
stay in school ♪
- HOMER: ♪ Lisa ♪
- ECHO: ♪ You don't suffer fools
or eat baloney ♪
- HOMER: ♪ Mmm, baloney ♪
- ECHO: ♪ Just jamming on your
brass saxo-ma-phony ♪
♪ You're my little
lampshade girl ♪
♪ In white pearls,
you're my world ♪
♪ 'Cause we ♪
♪ Me, you three and Maggie ♪
♪ Can bring this war down ♪
HOMER:
ECHO:
♪ Can bring this war down,
we, me ♪
♪ You three and Maggie ♪
-♪ Will be okay now ♪
- HOMER: ♪ Will be okay now ♪
ECHO:
♪ We going to be okay now,
if we ♪
♪ Me, you three and Maggie ♪
-♪ Just stick together ♪
- HOMER: ♪ If we just ♪
♪ If we stick together ♪
ECHO:
♪ We, me ♪
♪ You three and Maggie
could stop ♪
♪ A meltdown ♪
To stop this war,
we don't need a grand gesture.
We don't need to make a stand.
We just need
to sit down together.
(crying)
I'm sorry I betrayed you.
We're all sorry
Lisa betrayed you.
ALL:
Mm.
LISA:
Sorry! Accident.
Forgot where I put them all.
There's probably more.
(all coughing)
LISA:
That's gonna happen for a while.
Captioning sponsored by
20th CENTURY FOX TELEVISION
and FOX BROADCASTING COMPANY
and TOYOTA.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org
- (doorbell rings)
- Mr. Simpson,
the Murmur Nation has decided
to stop attacking you.
My video made you think, huh?
No. It was super cringe,
like watching
two teachers make out.
I understand. Been a pleasure
doing war with you.
May psychotic super-fandom
always lend meaning
to your otherwise
anonymous existence.
BOY: Hmm.
(all grunting)
It's crazy that
I believed in someone
so much that I got
swallowed up in groupthink.
I know. So scary.
(gasps) Oh, my God,
we're late for church!
I'll get nice, crisp dollars
for the donation basket.
Shh.