-CHORUS SINGS:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
-(vintage car horn honks)
(tires screeching)
D'oh.
(grunts)
(gasps)
Okay kids, time to apply
the final "date night" touch.
Lisa, spray just a hint
of perfume on my neck.
Bart, you tell me this dress
doesn't make me look fat.
And now!
-(mist spritzing)
-You don't look fat.
Thank you!
(bird squawks)
-(spritzing)
-Homer, you don't look fat.
(chuckling):
Oh, Carl!
You're a liar,
but I love it.
Date night:
it's the embalming fluid
that keeps the mummy
of a marriage fresh
after the heart
and brain have been
pulled out through the nose.
Ugh, I never should've given
you that Egyptology book.
Gentlemen, I'm afraid
we've detected a small leak
somewhere in the heavy
water piping facility.
Don't leave until you
find that leak!
Uh, Mr. Burns, couldn't
we patch the leak tomorrow?
It's date night.
Oh, indeed it is.
Tonight I will be
continuing my courtship
of Princess Wilhelmina
of Prussia.
(whimpers)
Tonight's the night
I pop the question:
Where is the
Kaiser's gold?
Now get to work
on that leak!
(sighs disconsolately)
TV ANNOUNCER:
We now return to:
Angelo stood me up on date
night, so I showed him:
I had one of my
boobs reduced.
You're one smart
cookie, Rosemary.
That left boob was
too good for him.
(clink)
HOUSEWIFE:
We're appalling!
(TV turns off)
I'm sorry
I missed dinner, honey.
We still have time
to catch a movie.
-That can be romantic.
-Really?
How romantic?
It'll make a walk
on the beach
seem like a punch
in the face.
Whoa!
Did you call
the furnace man?
-You said you were gonna call him!
-He's your cousin!
-Well, maybe we can
just get through
-(chewing ice)
-the winter without heat.
-(cell phone rings)
Guess I'll have to
take care of this
-like I took care of
your speeding tickets!
-(crunching ice)
(sighs)
It's so noisy in here.
I can't hear the ad telling
everyone to be quiet!
Hey, we came here
to enjoy the movie,
and we're going to
enjoy the movie.
We're out of here.
This isn't fair;
I want romance.
How about bromance?
It's not the same.
Dude...
I'm not a dude, I'm a hottie.
This bromance
just got interesting.
(groans, gasps)
Ooh, ice skating.
A sport that encourages
hand-holding.
Would you like to wear
mittens or go commando?
Oh! (giggling)
Oh!
-Why not?
-Sorry, no skating tonight.
What, they come here
on Saturday night to
clean the ice?
Losers.
Actually, it's
called "curling."
Players slide the heavy stones
toward the circle, or "house,"
as teammates control the
direction and speed of
the stone
by sweeping in front of it
with a special broom.
Marge, this is perfect
for both of us!
It's got bowling for me
and sweeping for you.
Maybe you'd like
to give it a try?
Mm... hmm.
Let us curl, milady.
Let us throw
and sweep a'twain
until the Heavens themselves
drop their jaws
in wonder and envy!
And afterwards there'll
be beer and cocoa,
with marshmallows
floating in the foam.
And if, from now
till the end of time,
someone should ask
what we were doing
on the eve of the
17th of November,
we shall proclaim that
we... were... curling!
This is what you're like
when you don't drink!
(orchestral waltz playing)
Young woman.
Where'd you learn
to sweep like that?
I've been training
all my life.
I once swept red wine
off a white carpet.
I like your style, Blue.
Want to join our team?
If Homer can join with me.
Fine. You two are off the team.
I see.
Well, I guess we can return
these bodysuits to the store.
Hmm.
So, we'd just
thrown a biter,
and Homer said to kick
harder off the hack.
So I did and I almost
fouled the hog line!
(laughing)
Exciting, exciting.
I just have one question:
Is curling a real thing?
Yeah, or is it just a cover
story for a grown-up thing
we're not allowed
to know about?
Yeah, like the time you said
Dad was taking a weekend
leadership seminar,
when he was really stuck
in a barrel at the junkyard?
Curling is real.
The realest thing
I've ever done.
(doorbell rings)
Hmm.
(gulps)
Principal Skinner?!
This is bogus, man.
You know the rules:
two letters and a conference
before I get a home visit.
Bart, my cargo pants indicate
that I'm not here
on school business.
I'm here on "cool"
business, i.e. curling.
Hey, look who slid into
our house.
(chuckling)
Great curling reference.
What's up, Seymour?
Astonishing news out of
Eau Claire, Wisconsin.
The Olympic Committee has
announced that Mixed Curling
will be a Demonstration Event
at the Winter Olympics.
There's a Winter Olympics?
(Christmas music plays)
(laughing)
Homer, while you were imagining
what the Winter Olympics were,
Seymour said we were all
going to the Olympic trials!
Olympic trials, eh?
He usually stays out like
this for about 30 seconds.
Want some coffee?
Mmm, that'd be great.
Terrible, Seymour!
You're a disgrace
to frozen water!
You love your son.
How can you be
so hard on him?
Marge, love has nothing
to do with winning.
Believe me, I know.
I was in love with a soldier
boy, on leave from Korea.
It was a 50's style romance--
three minutes of sex
and a lifetime of regret.
He went back to his war,
and I went back to my dream:
pole vaulting in the
Helsinki Olympics.
But there was a bump
in the road...
A bump named Seymour!
The whole nine months,
Seymour had just
laid there like a lump.
Then this pre-natal nitwit
decides to do his
Rockettes impression.
(all sigh with disappointment)
Before he was even born,
he ruined my life.
Yes, that involuntary
pre-conscious reflex
I made in utero
was unforgivable.
The point is,
don't let your feelings
get in the way of winning.
They don't give out medals
for being a loving wife.
Well, they should.
Well, they don't!
(barking)
(fussing)
(snoring and snorting)
(grunting)
(guzzling)
(jabbering)
Oh, wise guys, eh?
(slapping)
HOMER:
Sweep, sweep.
Left, right, left,
right, back and forth.
(humming)
Hmm?
Excuse me?
I think this fell
off your hat.
Oh, thanks! That's Chilbert.
One of the four
Winter Games mascots.
Would you like it?
I've got doubles.
Thank you.
Just beware, collecting Olympic
pins can be kind of addictive.
(chuckles) Come on,
they're just pins.
(chuckling)
He does look lonely
all by himself.
(gasps) Oh!
Buy us!
Buy us with money!
One Labatty, please.
(chuckling) Looks like
we hooked another one.
(hoarse male voice):
Please let me go back
to the cruise ship.
I was Chief Purser.
Never! Now get back
in character, Monsieur Wee Wee.
Someday I'll be the tall guy.
♪♪
All Dad needs to do
is put his stone
inside that circle and they win.
Oh, my God,
Dad threw too hard!
That stone is coming in
like a rocket.
It's gotta be going four,
maybe five miles an hour!
Someone needs to convert
that kinetic energy back
into potential.
(cheering)
Homie, we're going to Vancouver!
Pack your winter coat.
We're going to Canada's
warmest city!
(raspy chanting)
Homer, who's that?
She used to be my therapist.
-(beatboxing-like chant)
-(guttural chanting)
(chanting continues)
(chanting stops)
How can I ever thank you?
Pay your bill!
I couldn't hear
the last thing you said!
Good-bye forever!
Bob Costas at the
2010 Vancouver Games.
For the Beijing Games,
China picked famed director
Zhang Yimou to stage
its Opening Ceremony.
Tonight, Canada turns to
its most famous director:
Ivan Reitman, the man who
brought us Ghostbusters.
ANNOUNCER (over PA):
Who you gonna call?
Albania!
Algeria!
Who you gonna call?
Argentina!
(wearily and hoarsely):
Who you gonna call?
Zimbabwe.
And now, not competing
but observing:
Who you gonna call?
Angola.
(drumroll, cheering)
BOB COSTAS:
And now, in the Olympic
spirit of peace and goodwill,
we release the Canadian dove,
the beaver!
(squeaking)
This was all
preventable!
Hey, Lis, want
to come with?
I'm snowboarding
with my new Canadian friend,
Milhoose.
Hey, Bort, your sister's hotter
than a Calgary brush fire.
Mind if I ask her oot?
Sorry, but I was planning
to stop by
the Olympic Pin Center
to fill in a few small gaps
in my collection.
You know,
just to get me through the day.
She's as loony
as a one-dollar coin.
Hey, hoser,
want some Canadian Club?
Do I?!
-Oh!
-Hoo-hoo!
(to tune of "Old MacDonald")
♪ Oh, a pork bao ♪
♪ A shrimp bao,
everywhere a bao bao ♪
♪ Homer Simpson wins a gold,
sliding rocks on ice, bao bao! ♪
Marge, we need to talk
about your husband.
Oh, my favorite subject.
I'll go first. Isn't he cute?
A little.
But as an Olympic curler,
he's dragging us down
like an anchor
on a bag of toasters.
Hmm?
But Homer tries his best.
We know. That's
why we're positive
he'll never
get any better.
I had one Olympics ruined
by a bald, drooling idiot,
but it's not gonna
happen again.
I was not bald.
My fontanel was covered
by lanugo.
Whatever.
We want Homer
off the team.
Well, who made
you the coach?
The hat
makes me the coach.
Well, Homer's my soul mate,
and you don't dump a soul mate.
Oh, my God,
I'm holding back the team.
But our marriage is based
on curling.
Oh, what am I gonna do?
Hmm...
Hmm.
Mm.
(gaping in awe)
(gasps)
Oh, my gosh.
It's the mascot
from the 1924 games in Chamonix.
That's right.
It's Ennui, himself.
I must have him.
Um... can I have it
on account?
On account of I want it?
(laughs)
You've heard that one, huh?
No, it's just not
funny the first time.
But if you want to
trade, I could take--
uh, oh, I don't know--
those pearls you're wearing.
My pearls?
These were a gift from my mom
when I could first read
at a twelfth grade level.
You want to yak, or
you want to trade?
(whimpers)
Just take them.
(laughs)
(jazzy saxophone music)
I saw you grooving to the beat.
You got to pay for that.
Lis, what's going on?
You're not normally
this interesting.
Nothing's going on.
Just sharing my music
with the good
people of Vancouver.
A dime?!
What do you think I am--
a pay phone from 1980?!
Are you sure
you're okay?
I'm fine.
Fine, fine, fine, fine,
fine, fine, fine, fine.
What's that noise?
Your dress is covered
with pins.
There is no dress.
It's just pins.
(crying)
Help me?
(explosion)
-What are you doing?
-I like to warm up.
by sweeping behind
the snack bar.
Boo yeah!
Well, no matter
what you do,
it won't make up
for Sir Slip-a-lot over there.
(grunting)
Uh-oh.
Yes, it will.
I'll just sweep harder
than anyone's ever swept before.
Because without Homer,
I'm a broom without a stone.
No use for anything.
Wow. That's
love, Seymour.
I'm glad you saw it
once before you died.
BOB COSTAS:
If Homer Simpson doesn't land
this stone in center house,
the only gold
they'll be going home with
is Lisa's pin collection.
That tidbit courtesy
of our highly paid intern,
Tom Brokaw.
I love to learn about Lisa.
COSTAS:
Oh, my, that delivery has
less juice than Sunny Delight.
(audience sighing)
Marge Simpson is sweeping fast
and clean,
but it won't be enough.
I've never seen this before.
Marge Simpson is trying
to restart a stone.
-Come on, baby!
-She did it!
She pulled off
an impossible move,
just like the time I shaved off
Larry Bird's mustache
while he was napping.
(soft grunting)
-(loud pop)
-Aah!
(cheering)
Team U.S.A. heads
to the Gold Medal Match.
But wait a minute.
Marge Simpson looks hurt.
This is the sort
of bittersweet melodrama
Olympic coverage feeds on.
I admit it.
We're vampires
who suck on shattered dreams.
That's my Marge!
-High five.
-Hold on a sec.
Marge, let me look
at that shoulder.
-(winces)
-Hmm. Sorry, but
I'm afraid
she'll never curl again.
That looks like the end
of team USA's dream.
It appears team Sweden
will clinch the gold,
and they are over the moon
with joy.
Joy is but the shadow
pain casts.
(grunting and grumbling)
Can I help you
with that?
I'll do it myself.
When we do things together,
they always turn out badly...
for me.
Ooh, you're hot
when you're horny.
I'm not horny. I'm mad.
Ooh, you're mad
when you're angry.
(angry grunt)
Marge, you're really good
with your left hand.
I should be. I'm left-handed.
I've been using my right hand
all these years
'cause I didn't want
to seem unusual in any way.
Hmm.
Lisa, I know everything
about addiction
that you can learn
from watching Dad.
The first thing
you have to do is get clean,
so give me your pins.
-All of 'em.
-What is this, tough love?
Uh, it's a little more
like soft hate.
I said, all of them.
(sighs)
Oh.
And now, just put
your pearls back on,
and we'll go get some coffee.
It's not that easy, Bart.
I...
traded away my pearls.
Oh. (cries)
Without them,
I'm just a big Maggie.
(sobbing)
What'll you take
for the pearls?
Nothing you got,
Junior.
Really?
Not even this first-ever pin
from the 2014 Winter Olympics
in Sochi, Russia?
His name is Fatov.
He represents the Russian spirit
of sloth and alcoholism.
Ah. Fatov.
("Lara's Theme" from
Dr. Zhivago plays)
All for you.
(laughs)
We'll return
to sudden-death overtime
in the gold medal hockey game
between Russia
and the U.S. in a moment,
but first,
the Forfeiture-signing Ceremony,
where the injury-stricken
U.S. mixed curling team
is about to concede its chance
at gold to Sweden.
Team Captain Seymour Skinner
is preparing to sign.
There's been some question
as to whether
he'll use his middle name.
I guess we're
about to find out.
Okay, here comes the pen.
The ink appears to be blue.
No surrender!
Let's give the
Olympics a miracle.
But this time, on ice.
(cheering)
Oh, look
at that broom work.
Ah, they shouldn't be playing
Quidditch at all.
Not while four of the seven
horcruxes are still unfound.
Sacre bleu.
Sacred blue.
It's okay, son.
You did your best.
Really, Mother?
Y-You mean that?
I do.
Before now, I never knew a
mother could love her child.
Win or lose, I'm taking you
out for pizza and ice cream,
and we can sit at
the same table.
(happy grunt)
COSTAS:
The U.S.A. has won
Demonstration Gold.
Our first and only medals
of these entire Olympics.
Kids, open your history books,
tear out the pages
and put this indelible
Olympic moment in.
U.S.A.! U.S.A.!
Oops.
(crowd cheering)
(The "Star-Spangled Banner"
plays)
How's this for
a date night?
Wonderful, Homie.
Take that,
Sweden!
Tell me
how my ice tastes.
(Russian Dance
from "Nutcracker Suite" plays)
Shh!
Enhanced by Fotokem