♪ The Simpsons ♪
D'oh!
-Ahh!
-(tires screeching)
...which, if true
means death for us all.
And now, Kent's people.
Tonight's inspiring story
is about Frank Grimes,
a 35-year-old
Springfieldite
who's earned everything
the hard way
but never let adversity
get him down.
Abandoned by his parents
at age four,
Frank never got to go
to school.
He spent his childhood years
as a delivery boy
delivering toys
to more fortunate children.
Then, on his 18th birthday
he was blown up
in a silo explosion.
During his long recuperation
he taught himself to hear
and feel pain again.
As the years passed
he used his few
leisure moments each day
to study science by mail.
And last week
Frank Grimes--
the man who had to struggle
for everything he ever got--
received his correspondence
school diploma
in nuclear physics...
with a minor
in determination.
(screeching)
That's the kind of man I need
on my team, Smithers.
A real scrapper--
a self-made man like me.
Bring this
Grimes fellow to me.
I want to make him
my executive vice president.
Yes, sir.
Smithers,
I've just seen
the most heroic dog
on television.
He pulled a toddler from
the path of a speeding car
then pushed a criminal
in front of it.
Find this dog.
I want to make him
my executive vice president.
Uh, yes, sir.
I-In the meantime,
here's Frank Grimes.
The-- The self-made man?
What? Oh, yes, that fellow.
Oh, just put him somewhere
out of the way
and find that dog!
Yes, sir.
Ahh.
Chair goes round,
chair goes round...
Hey, Homey,
you busy?
Yes.
Hey, there's a new guy
at the plant.
Maybe we ought to say
"hi" to him.
I don't know.
I'm kind of dizzy.
I should probably go home sick.
Hm. Hmm.
Mm-hm.
Hm.
(scrunching)
You new?
Yes. My name is Frank Grimes.
I'm Lenny.
This is Carl and Homer.
-I'm Lenny.
-How do you do?
Wow. You got pencils
with your name on 'em
just like a pencil
company executive.
I'd give anything
for one of these.
Any office supply company
can have them made up for you.
-Can I have this one?
-No.
-Can Lenny have it?
Oh, that's my degree
in nuclear physics.
I'm sure you all have one.
Oh, yeah. Carl and I
each have a master's.
'Course old Homer,
he didn't need a degree.
He showed up the day
they opened the plant.
I didn't even know what
a nuclear panner plant was.
Um...
(chuckles)
Yeah. Well, listen,
I'm sure we all have
a lot of work to do.
BOTH: Hm.
Hey, you seem like a great guy,
so I'll give you a little tip:
If you turn that
security camera around,
you can sleep,
and no one will ever know.
Uh, I don't think
we're being paid to sleep.
Oh, yeah, they're always
trying to screw ya.
Huh.
"Marge" is already taken?
Mm, how about "Marjorie?"
(keyboard rattling)
-Oh, sorry, ma'am.
-Mm...
How about... "Mitzi?"
(keyboard rattling)
Uh-uh.
Uh, you can have "Nitzi."
Hmm... "Nitzi..."
I'm outta here.
MAN: Ladies and gentlemen,
our next lot is number 751.
How much am I bid
for item 751?
Seven-five-one?
Nothing.
No bids for item 751?
A buck!
I have a buck.
I have one dollar...
(extended auctioneer patter)
Sold! For a buck.
Cool. What'd I buy?
35 Industry Way.
Looks like my
years of hard work
have finally paid off.
(Homer gulping)
Hiya, Stretch,
what's the good word?
My name is Grimes,
uh, Simpson.
Frank Grimes. I took the trouble
to learn your name.
The least you can do is...
learn mine.
(chuckling)
Okay, Grimy.
Uh, you're eating
my special dietetic lunch.
Huh?
(chuckling)
Oh, gee...
Oh, I'm sorry.
The bag was clearly marked.
Please be more careful
in the future.
Check.
(gulps)
(humming)
Mmm
Ugh...
Simpson, do you know
who chewed my--
(snaps)
Wow.
It's filthy, and it's mine.
(laughs)
(clanks)
-(hissing)
-Whee!
(squeaking)
(Bart groans)
So, how's it going,
Grimy?
I-I'd appreciate it
if you'd stay out of
my office, Simpson.
(laughs)
I wish I had a nickel
for every time I heard that.
(makes obnoxious sounds)
♪ Take me out
to the ball game ♪
to the ball-ah... ♪
So... what's new, Grimy?
(beeping)
Simpson, you've got
a 5-13.
No, a 5-13!
In your procedures manual?
A 5-13?
Look at your control panel.
Oh!
A 5-13.
I'll handle it.
(buzzing)
That got it.
(whistles)
Hey, Milhouse!
You want a job
in my factory?
You don't have a factory.
Hey, I'm a busy man.
You want a job or not?
Okay.
(crunching)
God, he eats like a pig.
I don't know.
Pigs tend to chew.
I'd say he eats
more like a duck.
Well, some kind
of farm animal, anyway.
And earlier today
I saw him asleep
inside a radiation suit.
(chuckles)
Can you imagine that?
He was hanging
from a coat hook!
He had three beers
at lunch.
That would make
anybody sleepy.
I've never seen him do
any work around here.
W-What is his job?
Safety inspector.
That irresponsible oaf?!
A man who, by all rights
should have been killed
dozens of times by now?
Eh, 316 times,
by my count.
That's the man who's in charge
of our safety?
I-It boggles the mind.
It's best
not to think about it.
(grunts)
You idiot!
You nearly drank a beaker
full of sulfuric acid!
Acid, eh? Gee, that
would have been stupid.
(laughs)
Boy, would my face
have been red.
(laughing)
Stop laughing,
you imbecile!
Don't you realize
how close you just came
to killing yourself?
Who did this to my wall?
He did.
Is this true?
I, well, uh, technically
it is true, sir, but--
Come with me.
He likes you.
(barking)
BURNS: How dare you destroy
my valuable wall
and spill my priceless acid?!
Did you think you were
going to get away with it?
-GRIMES: I wasn't--
-BURNS: Silence!
I'm going to give you
one more chance...
at a reduced salary.
So straighten up
and fly right.
GRIMES: But, sir,
if I could--
(barking and growling)
Hi, Grimy, old buddy.
I'm not your
buddy, Simpson!
I don't like you.
In fact, I hate you.
Stay the hell
away from me!
Because from now on...
we're enemies!
Okay.
Do I have to do anything?
(groans)
Oh, I can't believe it.
I got an enemy.
Me. The most beloved man
in Springfield.
Ah, it's
a weird world, Homer.
As hard as it is
to believe,
some people don't care
for me neither.
No, I won't
accept that.
No, it's true.
I got their names
written down right here
in what I call
my, uh, enemies list.
Jane Fonda, Daniel Shore,
Jack Anderson--
Hey! This is Richard Nixon's
enemies list.
You just crossed out his name
and put yours.
Okay, give me that.
Give me it back.
Barney Gumbel.
Oh.
Oh, what'll
I do, Moe?
Well, why don't you
invite him over to dinner?
Turn him from an enemy
into a friend.
Then, when he's
not expecting it--
Bam! The old fork
in the eye.
Do you think
it might work
without the fork
in the eye?
There's always
a first time.
This dinner has to go
absolutely perfect
if Grimy and me are
going to be friends.
Lisa, be perfect.
-Okay.
-Marge, perfect.
Bart, perfect.
Other kid, perfect.
I only have five lobsters.
Are you sure
he's not bringing
anyone with him?
No, no. He doesn't know
he's coming to dinner.
I didn't think he'd come,
so I called and said
I have something
really important to tell him
and that I could only
tell him about it here.
-(doorbell rings)
-It's him!
(singsongy) It's him!
It's him! It's him!
Calm down.
Homer, calm down.
Answer the door.
(gasping)
Welcome
to the Simpson residence
or casa de Simpson,
as I call it.
Yeah, what did you want
to see me about, Simpson?
This better
be important.
It is. It is.
But first, let me
introduce you to my family.
My perfect family.
This is my
wife, Marge.
Hello.
HOMER:
And our beautiful baby.
My daughter Lisa
I.Q.-156.
Hi.
HOMER: See, and
my son Bart.
He owns
a factory downtown.
How do you do?
Look, Homer, I'm late
for my night job
at the foundry
so if you don't
mind telling me...
Good heavens!
This is a palace.
How in the world
can you afford to live
in a house like this, Simpson?
I don't know. Don't ask me
how the economy works.
Yeah, but look
at the size of this place.
I live in a single room
above a bowling alley
and below another
bowling alley.
Wow.
I'm sorry, isn't that--
Yeah, that's me
all right.
And the guy
standing next to me
is president Gerald Ford.
And this is
when I was on tour
with the Smashing Pumpkins.
Oh, and here's a picture of me
in outer space.
You... went
into outer space?
You?
Sure.
You've never been?
Would you like to see
my Grammy award?
No! I wouldn't!
God! I've had to work hard
every day of my life
and what do I have
to show for it?
This briefcase
and this haircut!
And what do you have to show
for your lifetime
of sloth and ignorance?
-What?
-Everything!
A dream house, two cars,
a beautiful wife,
a son who owns a factory,
fancy clothes, and--
(sniffing)
Lobsters for dinner!
And do you
deserve any of it?
No!
(gasps)
What are you saying?
I'm saying,
you're what's wrong
with America,
Simpson.
You coast
through life.
You do as little
as possible
and you leach off decent
hardworking people
like me.
If you lived in any other
country in the world,
you would have
starved to death long ago.
He's got you there, Dad.
You're a fraud.
A total fraud.
It was nice
meeting you.
(door slams)
MILHOUSE:
Wow... adding machines.
Industrial waste.
What should we do
with all this stuff, Bart?
I think we both know
the answer to that.
(sighs)
(knocking)
Get to work.
(stairs squeaking)
BOTH: Wacky shack!
Better be
careful, Bart.
Look at those
warning signs.
Solve your problem,
Milhouse?
Yup.
(stairs squeaking)
Hm?
(knocking)
Homer.
Homer, why aren't
you at work?
The car won't start.
I don't feel
very good today.
I am at work.
You're afraid to go to work
because Frank Grimes
will be there, aren't you?
That's crazy talk.
You're crazy, Marge.
Get off the road.
(honks horn)
You'll have
to face him sometime,
and when you do,
I'm sure he'll be
just as anxious
to make up as you are.
No, he won't.
He hates me.
He doesn't hate you.
He just feels insecure
because you're getting
through life so easily,
and it's been
so difficult for him.
Yeah. Yeah.
That's his problem.
He's a nut.
It's not about me being lazy.
It's about him
being a crazy nut.
Well... maybe.
But I'll bet
he would be less crazy
if you were just
a little more,
mm...
professional in your work.
(gasps)
Just a little more.
Then he won't have any reason
to resent you.
I'll do it.
To professionalism.
Good morning, fellow employee.
You'll notice that I am now
a model worker.
We should continue
this conversation later
during a designated
break period.
Sincerely,
Homer Simpson.
(beeping)
Can you believe that guy?
He's in his office
making a pathetic attempt
to look professional.
Hey, what do you got
against Homer anyway?
Are you kidding?
Does this whole plant
have some disease
where it can't see
that he's an idiot?
Look here.
Accidents have doubled
every year
since he became
safety inspector.
And meltdowns have tripled.
Has he been fired? No.
Has he been disciplined?
No, no.
Ah, everybody
makes mistakes.
That's why they put
erasers on pencils.
Yeah, Homer's okay.
Give him a break.
No. Homer is not okay.
And I want everyone in this
plant to realize it.
I would die a happy man
if I could prove to you
that Homer Simpson
has the intelligence
of a six year old.
So, how you doing?
(groans)
Hmm?
Uh, here we go.
Mm-hm.
Ahh.
Design your own
power plant, eh?
This is my chance
to show everyone
how professional I am.
Lenny, tell Mr. Burns
I've gone home
to work on the contest.
(chuckling)
Oh, God!
(power tool grinding)
(Homer shouting, indistinct)
Ow!
(shouting)
Can I go downstairs
and see what Dad's doing?
I wouldn't
bother him, honey.
He's making some kind
of model for a contest.
He says it's really
high-tech stuff
that we wouldn't
understand.
Marge, do we have
any elbow macaroni
and glue-on sparkles?
-(banging)
-(grunting)
(whistle blowing)
Oh, boy! Quittin' time!
Just a minute, Van Houten.
Somebody needs to guard
this place tonight
so it doesn't get trashed.
How'd you like to be
night watchman?
But I'm sleepy.
Oh, no problemo.
Here's a nickel
for the coffee machine.
(squeaking)
So this is my life.
At least I've done
better than Dad.
(whistling, gasps)
Aw, geez!
Milhouse, how could you
let this happen?
You were supposed to be
the night watchman.
I was watching.
I saw the whole thing.
First, it started
falling over,
and then it fell over.
Wow.
I wonder where all the rats
are gonna go.
(rats squeaking)
MOE: Okay, everybody,
tuck your pants
into your socks.
And the bold new ideas
these tiny tykes
unveil for us today
could make thousands of jobs
like yours obsolete!
(scant applause)
Our first little genius
is Ralph Wiggum.
It's pretty
good, sir.
Hot tub?
Media room?
It's supposed to be
a power plant
not Aunt Beulah's bordello.
Thank you.
Get out.
Next.
WIGGUM: Uh, Ralphy,
get off the stage, sweetheart.
Behold!
The power plant
of the future... today!
(moans)
Too cold and sterile.
Where's the heart?
But it really
generates power.
It's lighting this room
right now.
You lose. Get off
my property.
Let's have the next child.
Look, everybody!
Simpson's in a contest
with children!
Hey, shh!
You're making us
miss the contest.
Could you explain
your model, young man?
What's to explain?!
He's an idiot?!
LENNY: Pipe down!
Well, basically,
I just copied the plant we have now.
Mm...
Then, I added some fins
to lower wind resistance.
And this racing stripe here
I feel is pretty sharp.
Agreed.
First prize.
-What?!
-Way to go, Homer!
You're number one, Homer!
But it was a contest
for children!
Yeah, and Homer beat
their brains out!
(cheering)
CROWD: Yeah! Yeah!
I can't stand it any longer.
This whole plant is insane!
Insane, I tell you!
(screams)
I can be lazy, too!
Look at me!
Hi! I'm a worthless employee
just like Homer Simpson!
Give me a promotion!
Ooh, I eat like a slob,
but nobody minds!
(gobbling loudly)
I'm peeing
on the seat!
Give me a raise!
Now I'm returning to work
without washing my hands!
But it doesn't matter
because
I'm Homer Simpson.
I don't need to do my work
'cause someone else
will do it for me.
D-ohh, d-ohh, d-ohh!
Hey, you okay, Grimy?
I'm better than okay.
I'm Homer Simpson.
You wish.
Oh, hi, Mr. Burns.
I'm the worst worker
in the world.
Time to go home
to my mansion
and eat my lobster.
What's this?
"Extremely high voltage."
Well, I don't need
safety gloves
because I'm Homer Simp--
(zapping)
LOVEJOY:
Frank Grimes,
or "Grimy,"
as he liked to be called,
taught us that a man
can triumph over adversity.
And even though Frank's
agonizing struggle
through life
was tragically
cut short...
I'm sure he's...
(snoring)
Change the channel, Marge.
(laughing)
That's our Homer!
Shhh!!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.