May I sample the Mango Mayhem?
Now you're gonna scream
for ice cream,
John Wick Four!
Actually, it's...
gelato.
[muffled screaming]
The violence Mom won't let me
watch is the best.
- [tires screech]
- [crashing outside]
Damn it!
Whoa.
Live violence!
[Marge] Homie, wake up.
There's been a car crash!
[yawns] What's happening?
There's been an accident!
Ooh, let's go gawk!
- [grunts]
- Yeah! [giggles]
Marge, are you using
a charger cord as a robe belt?
Uh, well, I lost my belt
and Bart lost this phone, so...
What's that mark on your sleeve?
I used it as an oven mitt.
My Milhouse buys me a new robe
every Christmas.
Ralphie bought me
this chenille beauty
with his tooth fairy money.
Don't you like any of the robes
your kids bought you?
They've never bought me a robe.
- The quintessential mom gift!
- [gasps] - Un-frigging-believable.
[both groan]
My kids give me homemade gifts,
like hand turkeys
and macaroni-covered...
[stammers] stuff.
Sounds like they're just giving
you their art class crap.
Feel this.
I like the thoughtful,
artistic gifts my kids...
[gasps]
Oh, my God, that's plush!
[gasps] My robe is fine.
It's just a little worn
in spots.
Uh, one big spot in the back.
Aah! The top of my crack!
[gasps] Oh! Here! Come here!
Ooh! Mm.
[gasping]
♪ ♪
It's magical.
But it smells like
burning flip-flops.
[gasps] Ow! My flip-flops!
Careful!
Live wire on the ground!
Whoa. Thank you, Homer.
Aw, you da man.
Did you hear that?
Kirk said I was da man.
I mean, it sounded stupid,
the way he said it, but still...
Well, uh, if you want
to be "da man" for everybody,
you should post a warning about
that live wire on Alarmist.
It's this app that alerts
neighbors to local dangers.
Downloading now.
[Lenny] You film
dangerous stuff and post it.
You know, traffic accidents,
nighttime animals out
during the day.
Uh, hello.
This is Homer Simpson.
Username, uh...
The Simp.
There's a live wire sparking
on Evergreen Terrace.
Risk of electrocution,
1,000%.
♪ ♪
[gasping]
A thousand percent?
My baby could've played
with that wire!
He ain't born,
but he's 'bout to be.
Congratulations, you're now part
of the Alarmy Army.
Hey, I can barely read my name
without my cheaters.
How do I get a bigger font
like these guys?
Um, those are
the top alarmers on the app.
You want your name
in a readable font size?
You better learn
how to spread fear.
I'll do it. I'll get to the top
of this leaderboard
if it's the most useless thing
I ever do!
Bart, we need to talk
about Mom's birthday present.
Finishing it as we speak.
Ta-da!
Uh, it might be time
to retire the pasta art genre.
What?
In my vital bucatini phase?
You heard what those judgy women
said about our presents.
We need to buy Mom a present
this year.
Where are we gonna get money?
Otto stopped paying
for clean urine.
Hmm. Mr. Flanders is generous.
I've sold him
so many magazine subscriptions.
Why Cat Fancy?
His cat isn't even that fancy.
[humming]
Yo, Flan-man. We're trying
to make some scratch
for our mom's birthday gift.
You need any help
cleaning this mess up?
Sorry. I always keep
my grass trimmed.
You know the old saying...
"the lawn is the mustache
of the house."
Aw, we get it.
We just thought
Mom deserved something nice.
But if you don't think so,
mm, that's cool.
Now, well, hold on!
If, uh, you clean those two
leaves on my sidewalk up,
I'll give you...
$44.
- Both leaves?
- [grunts]
- Ow!
- Deal.
This store has everything.
[gasps]
This will make Mom
feel cozy and loved.
And it'll put a sock in the yaps
of those gossipy hens.
I'm gonna ignore
the problematic "hens"
because I support the sentiment.
- Whoa.
Is it a toy?
Yes. But it's also...
gear.
It's got a pen
that's actually a tape recorder,
an eavesdropping device
that lets you hear conversations
from miles away.
And when you get
in a tight spot,
sour gummy cyanide capsules!
This could change everything.
Deep down,
I know I'm the dingus!
[crying]
[crying replays on pen]
Give me your lunch money
or the whole playground
hears you blubber.
You, too, bow tie.
The Eavesdropper
could be so useful.
Okay, the meeting of the cool
girls has been called to order.
It's been decided
that the new cool thing
is to wear earmuffs
in warm weather,
so don't tell any randos...
- [gasps]
- Hey, guys!
[chuckling knowingly]
[gasps] Now Lisa's cool, too!
And there's nothing
we can do about it!
[crying]
[chuckles] Yes.
Cry, Sherri, cry.
Okay, just thinking out loud...
this kit is the same price
as the robe...
[gasps] Are you suggesting
- that we...
- You know I am!
[sighs] Say yes. Come on, Lis.
I need two keys
to launch this missile.
Mom has never really been
a gift person.
True.
She's more into stuff like hugs
and seeing us happy!
But we can't just buy a spy kit
for us and nothing for Mom.
[stammers] Bart?
Bart, we can't do this.
Would you like to apply
for a Bullseye credit card?
I'm eight.
Yeah, you won't get it.
But if you apply,
you get a free Bullseye
ironing board cover.
[gasps] We could buy the spy kit
and give Mom
the ironing board cover!
That's like giving her
a whole new ironing board!
Give me an application!
We'll give her
two ironing board covers!
[group]
♪ Happy birthday ♪
♪ To you! ♪
Uh, open my present first.
I got to hit the streets.
I have citizens to alarm.
Another charm
for my charm bracelet!
That bracelet was
the smartest investment ever.
No matter what the occasion,
I always know what you need...
another charm.
You know me so well.
I better
after however many years.
Open mine next!
Oh. An ironing board cover.
Yeah, 'cause,
you know, you iron.
I sure do.
Open mine.
It's in the Bullseye bag!
Hmm. Such clever wrapping.
[chuckles]
Ah, it's another
ironing board cover.
What do you get for the woman
who has only one
ironing board cover?
Thank you. Both of you.
I love them.
I got to hit the road.
If I find just three more things
to warn people about,
I'll move ahead of Cautionary
Gale and Cry Wolfcastle
on the leaderboard.
We'll help clean up!
[grunts]
No! I'll do it.
You guys have...
done so much for me.
[sighs deeply]
[groans]
Enjoying your present, huh?
Don't play with it all day!
[grumbles]
We'll know soon enough
who broke this va...
[gasps, groans]
[Bart] Yellow Sparrow, this is Slingshot.
Prepare
for face-to-face discussion.
Roger that. Face is prepared.
This spy kit is great!
All the secrets of this house
are being laid bare.
And Mom loves her present.
She can't stop muttering
about it.
We rule. Over.
Roger that. Over.
Inappropriate billboard
near Noiseland Arcade.
Guaranteed danger of corruption.
Keep children away!
- [phone chimes]
- Hmm. Whoa, whoa.
Thanks for warning us
about the vulgar wordplay, Simp!
"Itch, please."
Wait, I get it!
"Itch" rhymes with "bi..."
Uh, Mom hates that word.
Trust me.
One more post
and I'll be top five.
Homer.
Religious fanatic
running through town.
Possibly from murder scene.
Avoid outdoors.
[phone chimes]
- I did it.
- Fanatic!
I'm number five!
I'm better than everyone!
♪ ♪
- [static] - [Frink] Uh-uh-uh.
Your name is not "Frink."
You are "Frink's Monster,"
you see?
[Frink's Monster]
[growls] Frink sad.
[Frink]
No, Frink's Monster is sad!
What is wrong with you?!
[Moe] All right, one of youse
rats has been eating pool chalk
and leaving chalky pellets
all over the place.
No, no,
don't look at each other!
Look at me! Hey! Steve!
- [static]
- [Flanders] Oh, hey, Marge.
- [Marge] Hi, Ned.
- Ooh, that's Mom!
What a party yesterday.
I don't usually take my water
on the rocks.
I was buzzing all night.
Yeah. It was... fun.
- [crying]
- [Lisa] Oh.
Whoa. I didn't mean
to bring on a peeper-puddle.
What's wrong?
[Marge]
It's silly. I-I'm embarrassed
that my feelings were hurt
by a stupid birthday gift.
[Flanders]
Oh, now, feelings aren't stupid.
Some of them are evil,
but they're not stupid.
It's just... on my one day,
I'm barely an afterthought.
It's like they don't think of me
as a person.
[sighs]
I don't get it.
Why is she so sad?
Bart, she's feeling unseen.
What? I always see her.
She's in my phone contacts
three times...
under "Mom," "Mommy"
and "Sandwich."
She does so many things
that we take for granted.
Imagine how we would feel
if she...
half-tushied our birthdays.
What? I'd be fine if she only...
[groaning]
[sighs]
We suck. Over.
Roger that. Over.
As of this morning,
I am number one on the
leaderboard of the Alarmist app.
[gasps] Look at that!
What? The broken sprinkler?
We need to warn people!
It could cause a sinkhole
or activate a gremlin!
This is your number one Alarmy
with a warning that a geyser
of water is pouring onto...
- [phone chimes]
- Wha...?
Hey! Someone named Silver Bullet
already reported a...
"vertical tsunami at the park."
Whoa! That's good mongering.
I got scooped?
Silver Bullet
is now Alarmy number one.
What?! Who is this guy?
Those fat fingers are too slow
for the Silver Bullet!
Silver Bullet,
your days are numbered!
Tell me something
my doctor hasn't.
You smell like old lady.
So do you.
I smell like a lot of things.
We have to
get Mom a new present.
Something meaningful.
So, let's make a list
of everything we know about Mom.
Yes. Great idea.
Mm...
Hmm. Her first name is
actually Margaret.
Good. Write that down.
Hmm.
Ooh, I know. She loves coming
to my jazz recitals.
Uh, no, she doesn't.
She hides a copy of
People magazine in the program.
Oh. Ugh!
Why is this so hard?
We should know the woman
who gave birth to us.
Maybe she's unknowable.
What if we just give her
the spy kit
and breakfast in bed
for the rest of her life?
Or, you know that trunk
where Mom keeps all her
memories and stuff?
What if we use the spy kit
to break into it?
Ooh, welcome to the dark side.
♪ ♪
[Lisa]
Huh.
[gasps] Here we are.
I don't know
if these lock-picking tools
are even going to work.
I mean, this is just a toy...
[gasps]
Oh. Now I'm concerned about
those gummy cyanide capsules.
Mom's birth announcement.
Oh, her name is Marjorie,
not Margaret.
We officially
know nothing about her.
Hmm.
Mom had a parrot named Petey?
Oh, they were best friends, like
me and Santa's Little Helper.
- [whining]
- Not now, boy. Busy.
[gasps]
Look at this one.
[Bart] Oh, Mom's parents
must've given Petey away.
Hey, we just learned something
about her.
Grandma was a jerk-ass.
Wait. Parrots live for,
like, 80 years.
Maybe we could find Petey,
and then reunite Mom
with her long-lost friend.
That would be like
getting her a robe
that tells you
it wants crackers.
How do we find this lady?
[Lisa] Well, we need to go
to North Townsburg.
Oh, that place is sketchy.
Milhouse's dad was a sign
spinner for a meth clinic there.
But let's do it, for Mar-ge-dy!
- Marjorie.
- Whatever.
Oh, Townsburg is
three hours away?!
Fine. I'll just kick
the seat in front of me
until that little screw
falls out. [grunting]
That is so rude.
[grunting]
Well, you have to get closer
to the screw, like this.
[both grunting]
Great.
[both groaning]
Oh, this place is depressing.
Isn't that the corner
where Nic Cage went crazy?
Yep. There's the statue.
[gasps]
There's the mechanic's shop.
Let's do this.
Hey, grease stains,
seen this bird?
Yeah, I remember him.
That's Krista's bird.
He in some kind of trouble?
We'll ask the questions.
What's the skinny on
this Krista character?
Well, she owns the craft store
down the block.
She also sells liquor and weed.
- Let's go.
- Don't leave town.
But my niece's wedding
is tomorrow.
I said don't leave town.
Fine. Hey, Shirl, it's Vince.
I can't make it.
I don't know, some kid
told me I can't leave town.
I've got to get back
to being Alarmy number one.
Gotta warn people about...
something.
[gasps] Death from above.
Falling branches
in Springfield Park!
- Stay away.
- [phones chiming]
- We have to get out of here!
- I did it.
I'm Alarmy number one!
Not for long,
you toad-faced beanbag.
I will cut you into tiny pieces
like my son's pancakes.
I'm going to eat you up
and crap you out
like my son's pancakes.
[grumbles]
The air at Springfield Park
is full of pollen.
Individuals with lungs
should avoid the area.
[groans]
Lifeless bodies at the park.
Possible gas leak.
Demented man throwing objects
at the duck pond.
Chemical air attack
at the play yard.
UFOs hovering over picnic area.
String-guided dragons, most
likely time travelers attack...
I saw the kites first,
ya big galoot!
[rumbling]
[both cry out]
What happened?
The earth couldn't support
your giant ass.
Maybe Satan heard your voice
and decided to fast-track you
to hell.
Okay, we both got one in.
How are we getting
out of this sinkhole?
I dropped my phone.
Do you have yours?
No. Just start shouting.
Someone will hear us.
- Help!
- Down here!
Save me, not her!
[girl]
Hurry, the dragons are coming!
Oh, yeah, Petey.
He was smart as a whip.
Could imitate anything:
political figures of the day,
the "You Lose" horn
from Price Is Right.
So many times I thought
contestants lost
when they hadn't.
Why are you talking
about him in the past tense?
Oh, I left his cage open
by mistake and he flew away.
Last I heard, he joined
a flock of wild parrots.
Oh. I guess we came
all this way for nothing.
Stay in town.
But my daughter's wedding is...
[sighs]
Shirl? Bad news.
We failed Mom again.
We are losers.
[voice imitates
The Price is Right horn]
Bart, it's Petey!
How can we lure him down here?
Uh, uh, I've got it.
[Marge's voice] Bart,
are you secretly recording me?
I'm on hold to talk
about our water bill.
I'm sorry, no,
I'm not talking to you.
I'm talking to my annoying son.
- Yes!
- Got him!
[Petey] Annoying son.
[squawks]
[Agnes] Hello?!
Can't any of you
idiots hear us?!
There's no one to save us.
We scared everyone away.
- Isn't that ironic?
- I guess.
No, I'm asking.
I don't know what ironic means.
Why did we get so crazy?
I was doing a public service.
I warned everyone
that broken sprinkler
would cause a sinkhole.
Bull-scat. You were trying to
move up the leaderboard.
- We both were.
- Now we're stuck down here.
[sighs]
I miss the surface world.
Hey, you gotta share that!
We both need strength
to fight off CHUDs.
Hell no.
My Werther's, my choice.
- [grumbling]
- [choking]
Yeah, yeah,
you got candy in there.
Stop showing off.
Are you choking?
Hang on, I'll save you.
Wait, is this irony?
Ow. Ow! Okay, I'm doing it.
[grunts]
[gasps] I can breathe!
[sighs]
Simpson,
instead of mongering fear,
you mongered...
Life itself.
- Thank you.
- [gasps]
This is the feeling I was after.
Not some stupid leaderboard.
I'm gonna help you
get out of here.
Step in my hands,
I'll boost you up.
[grunts]
Oh, there's so much
to grab on to.
I'll tell everyone
you're down there.
Which will make me
Alarmy number one. Suck it!
Hairless ground hippo stuck
in sinkhole.
She's horrible.
Mom, we have one more
birthday surprise for you.
Oh. Really?
We tracked down
your best friend.
- Petey?
How-how is this happening?
How is this happening?!
Aah! Get it off!
Get it off before he... Oh!
- Ew.
- Ugh.
- Ow! Ow!
- [Lisa] Bart, do something!
[grunts]
Sorry.
We thought he loved you.
This is how he shows love.
By grooming me
and regurgitating on me.
I could never have friends over,
he was so possessive.
Mine!
[squawking angrily]
So why did you even get him?
I didn't.
I wanted a kitten.
Our neighbor was
giving away their parrot.
Since Petey can meow, my dad
decided he was close enough.
[Petey] Meow.
- You're nothing like a kitten!
- [all yell]
Don't worry, we'll
take him back to Townsburg.
He's part of a wild flock there.
You went all the way
to Townsburg?
We wanted to get
you something, you know,
personal for your birthday.
Yeah. We did not make friends
on the bus ride home.
Petey is kind of racist.
Well, that's just...
[crying]
We're sorry.
We didn't mean to
re-traumatize you
with your childhood
nightmare bird.
My wonderful babies!
You went to all that trouble
for me.
I wasn't an afterthought,
I was a thought.
Well, yeah, 'cause... you know,
we see you as a person.
We really do.
Our favorite person.
Oh, that is so...
- [crunch]
- Ow!
You little...
Who wants to help Mommy
abandon Petey in Townsburg?
[both] We do!
Captioning sponsored by
20th CENTURY FOX TELEVISION
and FOX BROADCASTING COMPANY
and TOYOTA.
Captioned by Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
- [tires screech]
- [crashing]
[concerned murmuring]
Marge, what a beautiful robe.
Is that terry cloth?
French terry, from the Terry
province of France.
[excited murmuring]
My kids got it for me.
I just threw it on to see
what that noise was.
I think it came from over there.
Look at the fullness
in that sleeve.
What was that sound?
I don't see anything.
Well, it's a mystery.
We may never know.
- Look at how it moves.
- Poetry in fabric.
You better work.
[Bart laughs]
Mission accomplished. Over.
[both] Roger that. Over.
Shh!