CHORUS: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(theme song playing)
(bell ringing)
(whistle blows)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
(honking horn)
D'oh! (screams)
(tires screeching)
(alarm blaring)
Fire! Fire! Fire!!
(gasps) Oh, no!
What do I save?
Trophies, trophies... (panicked gasping)
Attendance!
Don't panic! Don't panic! Don't panic!
Get in! Move it! This is not a drill!
Good work, everyone.
We're sure to be
first in line for Duff Days.
You set off the smoke alarm
to rush us to a beer festival?
(laughing) I know, I'm a character.
Now a little beer music
to get in the mood.
-(polka music playing)
-(panicked gasping)
Looking for these?
(hums mockingly)
(sighs)
(playing polka music)
Drink Duff... (whispers) responsibly.
Now, which one of you
is our designated driver?
(Homer grunting)
-(yelping)
-Twist off, damn it.
I guess I'll be driving.
Right this way to the Duff
designated drivers' rockin' fun zone.
Rockin' fun zone?
That sounds fun...
I don't see the need for razor wire.
Ooh, there's Ulysses S. Grant,
Babe Ruth... (gasping) Ben Franklin.
Early to bed... (hiccups) early to rise.
(slurred) You think... You think you're
better than me? Huh?
Ee...
OK, kids, who wants to see
what it's like to get drunk?
Ooh! Ooh! Uh, uh, uh!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
(moaning)
Now you're charming.
You don't know me.
This guy here...
This is the guy. (laughing and groaning)
ANNOUNCER: All right,
Springfield, belly up
for the Duff Beer-Tender
of the Year Contest.
-(all cheering)
-Now, fresh from his appearance
before the House Subcommittee
on Teenage Alcoholism,
Duffman!
Are you ready for some Duff love?
-(all cheering)
-All right!
Today we're going to find out
which of these bartenders
has the right stuff to dispense Duff.
♪ Oh, yeah... ♪
From the Green Potato Pub at
O'Hare International Airport,
-Michael Finn.
-(all cheering)
From Juggernauts in Hollywood, California,
-Titania.
-(raucous cheering)
And now, the local lug who fills your mug
with the drug you chug. Oh, yeah!
Give it up for Moe Szyslak.
Hello, Springfield, how you...
-(gasps) Ooh!
-(cheering and applause)
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
OK, our first event
qualifies for course credit
at Dartmouth College,
Trick Pouring.
♪ For goodness sake ♪
♪ I got the hippy hippy shake ♪
♪ Yeah, I got the shake ♪
CARL: That spells Duff.
Go, Moe! Boo, everyone else!
I think we know who wins this round,
-Titania!
-(cheering and applause)
Duff beer is brewed from hops, barley
and sparkling clear mountain what?
-(buzzes)
-Goat.
-Close enough.
-(cheering and applause)
Ah! You can really taste the goat.
Now, our final round
which counts for 98% of the total score,
making the previous rounds
a complete waste.
(cheering and applause)
Don't forget, today's winner will be
immortalized on our new Duff calendar.
All right, guys, one, two, three...
"Moo?"
Lenny, you were supposed to be "E."
See what happens when you skip rehearsal?
All right, bartenders, toss your drunks!
(grunts) And stay out!
(moaning)
Ew! You said if I slept with you,
I wouldn't have to touch the drunk.
Duffman says a lot of things. Oh, yeah!
(grunting)
-(screaming)
-(panicked grunting)
And the winner, Moe szyslak!
(cheering)
Aw, that's great. Thank you, thanks a lot.
Uh, I just want to say that
it was an honor for me to compete
with the Mick and the chick
with the rack there.
-Yeah, all right, Moe!
-That's my Moo!
And now, to take
your official calendar portrait
Duff's vice-president in charge
of calenders and fake I.D.s.
Phil Angelides.
(all cheering)
-both: Ugh!
-That's a mug you don't want to chug.
Knock it off, Larry.
We can't put this face on our calendar.
(grunting)
When I get home, there are going to be
a lot of open pickle jars.
That one.
Kids, would you like a balloon?
Yeah, right, Mom. Then I'd like
a rattle and a wowwipop.
Actually, I would like a wowwipop.
Those balloons won't biodegrade
for 10,000 years.
And if Bart gets a wowwipop,
I want a wowwipop.
Ah, Maggie wants a balloon
and daddy will take a hand
stamp so he can get back in.
-(groaning)
-Just kidding.
Remember my face.
Oh, boy! Uh... (groans)
-(groans)
-Moe, the new Duff calendars are out,
the ones with your picture!
Oh, boy! Move over, liquor license.
Hey, Moe, this license expired in 1973,
uh, and it's only good in Rhode Island,
and it's signed by you.
Yeah, yeah, I've been meaning to get
that updated, uh, for this state and real.
Now, let's see the poster boy
for the new Moe-lennium.
(stammering)
They put a sticker over my face.
Hey! "Viva La... Kiss..." What?
Aw, for the love of Jeff!
-Ugh... Oh! Am I really that ugly?
-Moe, it's all relative.
-Is Lenny really that dumb?
-(gasps)
Is Barney that drunk?
Is Homer that lazy, bald and fat?
Oh, my God, it's worse than I thought.
(crying)
See, this is why I don't talk much.
I can't believe they put
those stickers over my face.
(sighs) I must be the ugliest man alive.
Oh, Moe, there's lots of people
uglier than you.
Like, you ever been to White Castle?
Oh, boy, Pigtown, U.S.A.
Aw, come on, look at me, I'm a gargoyle.
What with the cauliflower ear
-there and the lizard lips...
-Little rat eyes.
-Caveman brow.
-Don't forget that fish mouth.
OK! I get it. I ain't pleasant to look at.
-Or listen to.
-Or be with.
Come on, Moe, don't feel bad.
There's too much emphasis
on looks these days.
That's why they won't let Bill Maher on TV
before midnight.
Hey, Moe, if you're
tired of being an eyesore
Why not get some plastic surgery?
Plastic surgery, huh?
Yeah, maybe they can dynamite Mount
Crapmore here and carve me a new kisser.
Oh, I don't know. Plastic surgery might
make you look good on the outside,
but you still might
feel bad on the inside.
But I'd look good on the outside, right?
Yeah, but you'd feel bad inside.
Plastic surgery it is!
Carl Carlson, you just saved my life.
-(cash register ringing)
-Hey! Get out of there.
-(gurgling happily)
-Look at her.
It must be great to be a baby
and be so easily amused.
Yeah, I wish I could be entertained
by two cents' worth of rubber
shaped like some colorful animal
dancing and twirling...
Dancing and twirling...
-Hey! Give me that!
-(grunting) That's mine!
(squealing unhappily)
The door!
Oh, no!
(gurgling unhappily)
OK, don't panic, I'll get the bikes.
I hope they're hover bikes.
Oh, man, that would be so awesome.
(groaning)
Mm-hmm... Yeah.
Hmm...
(imitates bomb whistling)
(imitates explosion)
It's hopeless, ain't it?
No, no, no, I love a challenge.
First, we must install buttocks.
Nah, nah, nah,
no luxury items, just a face.
OK, I'm going to move this up, this wider.
We're going to lose that.
I've never even seen one of these.
Can the medical mumbo jumbo.
-Can you fix me or not?
-Well, we'll see.
You know, most faces
need a little remodeling,
but this is a total tear-down.
Let me clean up this mess I made.
Hey, hey! Hey, that really burns there!
Oh, stop it, you're worse
than Faye Dunaway.
(Bart grunting) We've got to get closer.
Oh, I'm trying!
Can't I get on your shoulders?
I'm not riding a girl's bike.
Hey, it's getting away!
Step on it! Hyah! Hyah!
-Stop kicking me!
-Hyah!
Oh, boy! What a mug!
Yeah. You should see his genitals.
Would you like to see them?
I'm awake here.
Uh-oh. This isn't anesthetic.
It's new car smell.
Oh, sorry, Doctor.
♪ Oh, silver bells, silver bells... ♪
It's going into that building!
Nice suit, Jeeves.
Daddy, I'm stealing! I'm stealing!
Oh, that's my little dude.
We need a symbol. Something that says
we're gay and Republican.
A little on the nose, don't you think?
(panting) Excuse me.
We just came to get our balloon.
Here you go. And have a bumper sticker.
Thank you.
"A Gay President in 2084"?
We're realistic.
Hurry. Hurry up! I have to pee!
-Beautiful.
-OK, now do Moe.
Well, Moe, now we see
if you go on my wall of fame
or my blooper reel.
-Oh...
Oh...
-(both gasping)
-What? I'm a monster, right?
I knew it. I guess I'll just crawl back
to live in the sewer,
periodically emerging to sue you.
(gasps) Is that me?
Oopsie! We've got some leakage.
Let me just cauterize that for you.
(Moe screaming)
-Bye, Moe.
-Don't be a stranger, handsome.
Bye-bye.
Homer, did you hear that?
She called me handsome. Me!
It's like I've gone to heaven.
Wait a minute. I died on
the operating table, didn't I?
(laughing) Yeah, but just for a minute.
It's a funny story.
I'll tell you sometime.
So this is all real?
Oh, you dear, dear man.
You're one of us beautiful people now.
And your new life begins today.
A new life.
A second chance... for revenge.
That brown patch needs a little H2O!
Oh, yeah!
Hey, Duffman, let's see
how you like a sticker
on your face! Yeah!
Duffman can't breathe!
Oh, no! Ooh!
-Hello.
-Yeah, hello, yourself.
I'm Moe Syzslak. Back in high school,
I asked you to the Springtime
Pumpkin Dance and you turned me down.
Well, I just wanted to show you the face
-that you could have been kissing.
-HOMER: Yeah!
Oh, I was just a stupid kid back then
and I feel terrible about hurting you.
Will you accept my apology?
Apology?
Uh... Geez, I wasn't expecting that. Uh...
Run!
Man, that felt great!
OK, last stop, Channel Six.
You going to get even with that lottery
guy that never picks our numbers?
Nah, nah, nah. This is personal.
It all goes back to my acting days.
I was auditioning for the role
of Dr. Tad Winslow
on the hit soap, It Never Ends.
-Angela, I'm afraid I--
-Woman: Thank you. Next!
-What were you thinking?
-Well, you said you wanted "gritty."
In other words, "ugly."
I wanted "Mary Ann
on Gilligan's Island" ugly
not "Cornelius on
The Planet of the Apes" ugly.
"TV" ugly, not "ugly" ugly.
I've been called ugly,
pug ugly, fugly, pug fugly,
but never ugly ugly.
Well, it's time to get some closure.
Extreme closure.
But I've been Dr. Tad Winslow
for 25 years.
It's time I got a raise.
Oh, shut up, you windy, old hack.
And another thing. You have
to stop calling me that.
Remember me? Twenty-five years ago,
you said I was too ugly
to play Dr. Tad Winslow.
I did? Well, that's why
pencils have erasers, hon.
You're our new Dr. Tad Winslow.
Really? You mean it?
But there can't be two Dr. Tad Winslows.
That's going to... Oh.
I've been waiting
all my life for this moment.
-(laughing)
-Homer, whoa, whoa, Homer.
Change of plans.
Whatever.
MAN (on TV): Like the cleaning of a house,
It Never Ends.
With Gabriella DeFarge
as Gabriella St. Farge
Allegra Hamilton as Sister Bernadette
and Roxy Monoxide.
And as Dr. Tad Winslow,
Moe Szyslak.
I don't know if I'll be able to accept Moe
as Dr. Tad Winslow.
Well, I'm going to keep watching
as long as they have shocking story twists
and endless pillow talk.
Cleo, Cleo...
You've brought music to my heart,
but this relationship can never work.
I'm a doctor and you're
a 5,000-year-old mummy
I brought back to life.
But I love you, Tad.
And together, we can burn
all the cities of the Earth.
It's against
hospital regulations, damn it!
And Clive Dancer's
just waiting for me to slip up.
So, Lenny, how are things working out
with you and that girl next door?
Ah, it's over. She got a window shade.
-ALL: Wha...
-Whoa, whoa,
if you must grope me, ladies.
Please, a little softer.
(chuckles) OK, now, harder.
Hey, there are women in our bar.
Hey, Moe, beer me.
I'm a little busy, Homer.
Uh, you can pour it yourself.
Hmm. This isn't nearly as complicated
as Moe made it seem.
(acreaming and sputtering)
(gurgling)
I didn't bring you back to life
so you could make
a fool of me at the club!
You don't love me!
The only thing you love is
your ear, nose and throat pavilion.
I've dedicated my life
to diseases of the head hole,
but the one hole
I've never been able to fix
is the one in my soul!
That was amazing, Moe.
I'm actually a little turned on.
Yeah. Hey, I got a gift.
As a child, I was bitten
by the acting bug.
Then it burrowed under my skin
and laid eggs in my heart.
Now those eggs are hatching, and I...
The feeling is indescribable.
I know what you mean. Our dog had that.
-(knocking at door)
-DELIVERY BOY: Excuse me.
I got a delivery here for the producers.
"Top Secret Storylines"?
Uh, I'll sign for it.
Eh, might as well have a little peek...
(chuckles)
Hmm... Hmm! Looks like my character
gets back together
with that evil Contessa.
-The one with the amulet?
-Precisely.
Then I get in a skydiving accident
and have to be rushed to the... graveyard?
They're killing off Dr. Tad Winslow!
What? Let me see that.
"Interior coroner's office.
Close-up on Dr. Winslow's mangled corpse.
"CORONER: Let's get
that brain out and weighed
and call it a day."
Yep. That does sound kind of bad.
Well, if they're going
to stomp on my dreams,
the least I can do is go out
in a blaze of sour grapes.
I never used to trust you, Contessa,
but now you seem so nice.
Why don't we celebrate
your newfound trust in me
by taking a skydiving lesson?
Well, how could I say no
to such a captivating--
-HOMER: Ding dong.
-Whoa! It's the door!
(ghostly voice) Dr. Winslow.
Why, who are you?
I am an angel from the future.
-Angel?
-What the fudge?
-Should I cut him off?
-No. Let's see where this is going.
And what do you have to tell
us, oh, angel of the future?
You're going to die
in a skydiving accident.
How tragic! Tell me more.
Gabriella's baby shower
will be invaded by terrorists,
with sexy results.
Ooh, that's unexpected. What else?
Well, Sister Bernadette
will leave the convent
and start a softball team,
with sexy results.
What's Dad doing on the show?
Who cares? He's dishing out the dirt.
And only then do we find out
that Professor Gallaway's half-sister
is plotting to take over
International Perfume and Wine.
Ah! He just gave away
a year's worth of story lines!
Cut him off... now.
(both laughting)
-Yeah.
-Yes!
What the hell are you doing?
Sticking it to you
for killing off my character!
-(laughing) Whoo!
-Yeah!
You idiot! Dr. Winslow was
only going to die in a dream.
-What?
-Pink pages always mean a dream.
I thought dreams was on goldenrod.
No. Goldenrod is for coma fantasies.
I see.
So, uh... what time tomorrow?
(laughing)
Escort these men out... now.
Get your hands off me. Get off!
I don't need your stinking show, anyway.
With a mug like this,
I can get on any soap in Springfield.
(grunts and scoffs)
Ahhh...
Oh! Oh, my face!
I'm not supposed to put weight on it!
-(all gasping)
-What? What?
-Sorry about your face, Moe.
-Nah, it's just as well.
That handsome face was nice,
but it was too much maintenance.
I had to wash it,
rub it with Neat's foot oil.
You did me a favor, Homer
And to think I was about
to sell the bar to hooters.
Yeah. You were... D'oh!
Well, I guess that wraps it up.
Hey, there's one thing
I don't get, though.
When my face was crushed,
why'd it go back to my old face?
I mean, shouldn't it have turned into some
kind of third face
that was different?
(chuckles) It don't make no...
(theme song playing)
-(murmuring)
-Shh.
Oh, yeah!
Captioned by
Visual Data Media Services