(SlNGlNG) The Simpsons
(TlRES SCREECHlNG)
D'oh !
(SCREAMlNG)
(TlRES SCREECHlNG)
ANNOUNCER: WeIcome back to
Promiscuous ldiots lsland
on Fox, the home of
Promiscuous ldiots.
Last week on Pll,
our billionaire bachelor
gave five IoveIy Iadies
a rose of continuation.
And he hurled a rock
of rejection at anyone
dispIaying inteIIigence,
character, or ethnicity.
(GRUNTS)
Tonight, we reveaI
a shocking secret.
Ladies, when you
were selected,
you were told
that you'd be dating
a billionaire on
his private island.
Well, l'm afraid
we misled you.
(GASPlNG)
Get ready, skanks.
Here comes the truth train !
This isn't an island.
lt's a peninsula.
(DRAMATlC MUSlC PLAYlNG)
(GASPlNG)
This was supposed
to be about trust!
(SOBBlNG)
l just want
to get on that boat
and go home!
Well, you don't need a boat
because you can walk.
(WAlLlNG)
Yeah.
What do those women expect?
When you sign
a contract with Fox,
you know you're gonna be
betrayed and humiliated.
Quiet! The commercial's on !
lf we don't watch these,
it's like we're stealing TV.
Do you Iove that sweet smeII
of Farmer BiIIy's bacon?
Do l ever?
WouId you Iike to
see how a pig goes
from Ioving Iife to
your fork and knife?
Would l?
WeII, if you open up
one of these here packages
and find a goIden ticket,
you get a tour
of Farmer BiIIy's
bacon factory.
(COMMERClAL ANNOUNCER READlNG)
FARMER BlLLY:
You'II see the hoof grinder,
the marrow sluice,
and of course,
the five-story pig shredder
bIessed by three popes.
If you Iike bacon,
you're gonna Iove it.
And if you don't Iike bacon,
weII, then the heII with ya!
l'm going to find
that golden ticket
and win that tour!
The only thing
that can make bacon
more delicious
is seeing how it's made!
Okay. Farmer Billy's
slow-killed bacon.
Farmer Billy's
bacon-fed bacon,
Farmer Billy's travel bacon. . .
Mr. Simpson,
if you really want to
kill yourself,
l also sell handguns.
Nope. Just looking
for that golden ticket.
Nope. Nothing. Nope. Nada.
(GASPS)
The golden ticket!
At long last!
(KlSSlNG)
Mr. Simpson, please!
l fear your smooches
are premature.
This, in fact,
is a silver ticket.
Huh?
"This silver ticket
entitles you
"to judge
the pig competition at the
Springfield County Fair."
Hmm. Judge a pig competition?
But l'm no super genius.
Or are l?
(CHUCKLlNG)
(BLUEGRASS MUSlC PLAYlNG)
These giant vegetables
are amazing.
Hmm. . .
How about a bite of
the world's biggest
Brussels sprout?
Ew.
(WHlSTLlNG NONCHALANTLY)
This song is about
a country I Iove.
You may have heard of it.
lt's called America.
Hey, l know that country!
(SlNGlNG) I couId pIease
Miss Barbra Streisand
By spitting on the fIag
Or strangling a bald eagle
On the cover of some mag
But I Iove this country
To me, she has no sins
If you don't buy my record
Then al-Qaeda wins
USA! USA!
Of all the days
for you to get a zit.
Comely. Succulent.
(SCOFFS)
Clearly had a snout job.
Ugh ! Too '80s.
Let's see how
your sister's doing
in the place-setting
competition.
Place-setting?
How is someone so lame
related to a hot tamale
like me?
JUDGE: Hmm.
Check it out! Dribble glass,
rubber knife, whoopee salad !
(FARTlNG)
(CHUCKLES)
And finally the breakaway
wine bottle. . .
Did not arrive. (MOANlNG)
My theme is "lf Music
be the Food of Love."
The setting
features tuning forks,
champagne flutes,
and of course, chopsticks.
And for dessert,
Ella Fitz Jell-O.
Lordy, girl.
Your entry stinks like
the south end of
a northbound mule.
What's wrong with it?
Well, your
place-setting thinks
it's better than it is.
Like a yard dog that
sneaks into the house.
Zing !
Did l do anything right?
Well, you did
put it on a table.
(CHORTLlNG)
Lookee here, it wobbles.
Wobble, wobble, wobble. . .
This table's about
as solid as your
underlying concept.
(LAUGHlNG)
(SOBBlNG)
No one does that
to my daughter!
One more
felony assault, Simpson,
and you're going down.
l didn't know
l could fit in a bubble.
l must be losing weight.
Oh. . .
But l gotta do something !
l'll need a disguise.
(SOBBlNG)
Aw, there, there,
little darlin'.
Dry those tears with this!
(LAUGHlNG)
HOMER: Hold it right there!
(ALL GASP)
You've hurt
your last feeling !
(LAUGHS)
(ALL JEERlNG)
We all know pi-R-squared.
But today, pie-are-justice.
l welcome it.
Thank you,
mysterious stranger.
Where did he go?
Where were you, Homie?
You missed all
the excitement.
Shall we ever
see Springfield's
costumed protector again?
Oh, l have
a funny feeling we will.
Wherever people
are mistreated,
the Pie Man will strike!
(CHUCKLES)
What you doing, sweetie?
l'm drawing a picture
of my newest hero. Pie Man !
Gee, l thought l had a bigger
package than that.
That's really sweet, honey.
(BART GROANS)
Aw. Hey, let's turn
that frown upside down.
Oh, Dad ! l feel like
l'm gonna throw up!
All right.
What's wrong, Son?
Comic Book Guy
made me pay for these
comics he said l smudged.
But l didn't even touch 'em !
LISA: Richie Rich
Incorporates in DeIaware.
Easy to BeIieve TaIes.
Supergirl vs.
The Glass Ceiling.
The Green Listener.
He was just
trying to unload these
crappy comics on
a helpless kid.
Somebody oughta
take him down a peg,
or should l say "down a pie"?
No, l think
the expression is "peg."
Maybe you're right, Lisa.
Maybe you're pie.
Pie be you're pie.
This magazine
you sold me isn't
Fantastic Four,
it's Fantastic FIoor.
My family can't put
in floors. We rent.
Sorry. No refunds.
(DOOR CHlME RlNGS)
Oh, brother.
Why do we get all
the weirdoes here
at the comic book store?
Comic Book Guy,
don't do the crime if
you can't do the key lime!
(EXCLAlMlNG)
How could this be
any more humiliating?
Hello. l'm Nichelle Nichols
of Star Trek.
Oh ! You finally accepted
my invitation for tea
and chit chat.
Ew. Listen,
l said it to Shatner
and l'm saying it to you.
There is no way
l'm going to be dating
a man with pie on his face.
(SOBBlNG)
(ALL LAUGHlNG)
There's a note!
(READlNG)
Finally, a superhero
that kids can love.
What about Fist Face?
Fist Face? Who's Fist Face?
Why won't you tell me
who Fist Face is?
l demand you reveal
the identity of Fist Face!
lt's you !
(GRUNTS)
You can tell by the way
the pie tin sits on his face
that he's very good-looking.
Oh, l think you'd
find his filling
extremely hot.
Ooh ! l bet he's Ned Flanders.
Flanders?
He's not man enough
to trim my crust!
l mean Pie Man's crust!
l'm not Pie Man.
Pie. PopuIar pastry,
tricky math thing
and now sword
of righteousness.
A masked avenger
has been giving
Springfield's scoundrels
their just desserts!
This is for your
show's sIight decIine
in quaIity over the years!
KENT: In an attempt to
curb copycat pie-ings,
the poIice have organized
a pie-for-guns exchange.
The pies were immediateIy
detonated by the bomb squad.
(EXPLODlNG)
Aw! Those poor innocent pies.
Some days you just
don't want to be a cop,
you know?
I'm gonna go
turn the siren on.
That aIways cheers me up.
(SlREN WAlLlNG)
(LAUGHlNG)
That's good footage.
Where will the Pie Man
strike next?
Perhaps at the Springfield
Children's Hospital,
which is tossing out
aII its sick youngsters
to make way for a new
cosmetic surgery cIinic.
Who will treat
my whooping cough?
(HACKlNG)
Search me.
Come back when you
want a giant rack.
(CROWD CLAPPlNG)
(HACKlNG)
Okay, Lou.
The minute Pie Man shows up,
we spring our trap.
Hey, what do you got
against this pie guy anyway?
He's giving jerks
their comeuppance.
Yeah, but he's skipping
the hardest part
of being a cop.
Bike safety lectures.
Oh, come on, Chief.
No, no one ever
wants to hear about
the importance of
pants clips, do they?
Well yeah, but. . .
(lNTERRUPTlNG)
That's why
Pie Man is going down.
Thanks to this clinic,
we will no longer
be terrorized
by the spectacle
of women aging naturally.
(CACKLlNG)
Not so fast,
old-time liberal.
Get him !
(CROWD MUTTERlNG)
Pie Man, no! lt's a trap!
No trap can hold
Homer Simpson. . .
But l'm not Homer Simpson !
l'm the Pie Man !
Homer Simpson away!
l mean, the Pie Man !
Shoot to kill !
(GUNS FlRlNG)
(ALL SCREAMlNG)
(GRUNTS) Oh ! Damn it!
Oh, way to go, Lou.
You hit him !
What? You sound
like you're surprised.
l'm trying to
give you positive
reinforcement, jerk.
What, and that's positive,
calling me a jerk?
Well, you are a jerk.
(PEOPLE SCREAMlNG)
(GRUNTS)
l'm not being trampled.
What gives?
Uh, listen. l'm married.
(SlGHS)
l'm looking up your nose,
but l feel like
l'm staring into your soul.
(THUNDER CRASHlNG)
(STRAlNlNG)
That was
so exciting yet familiar,
like Coke with lemon.
(MUTTERlNG HAPPlLY)
(MOANlNG)
(GRUNTlNG)
Let's see.
Cartilage. Cartilage.
Muscle. Nerve.
Artery. Bullet!
(SlGHS lN RELlEF)
Dad?
Pie Man is not your father,
little girl.
l murdered your father.
Dad, please.
lt's obvious you're Pie Man.
We've been getting
his mail for weeks.
We shall continue
this conversation
in the Pie Cave.
Watch it. One more step.
Welcome to my secret lair.
Dad, this is the basement.
Here's the iced tea
l left down here
this afternoon.
So it would seem.
Anyhoo, l bet this
is all a pretty
big surprise, huh?
Mild-mannered
Homer Simpson. . .
You're not mild-mannered.
You're often
liquored up and rude.
Honorable men can differ.
Now what brings you
down here?
l want you to stop this, Dad,
before you get killed.
All right, l'll stop.
What'll l do with these pies?
Well, l know
one thing you could do.
(CHUCKLES)
l was in so deep
l forgot pies were food.
(WHlSTLlNG)
Simpson, you're late,
bald, and stupid.
l'm docking you a day's pay.
What?
l'll show him.
No, l shouldn't. Or should l?
l'll keep my promise, honey.
No Iooking at
pictures of Ioved ones!
Mr. Burns. . .
Bald-headed little. . .
Kill you, you. . .
No angry grumbIing
under your breath!
(WHlP CRACKlNG)
Eat faster! Faster!
Swallow on your own time!
(EXCLAlMlNG lN PAlN)
Won't someone help us?
Who will stand up
for Carl and Lenny?
Hey, Homer, throw me
at Mr. Burns.
No, throw me!
l'm old and stale!
l might just kill him !
(CACKLlNG)
Don't do it, Homer.
You made a promise to Lisa.
Since when do
l listen to cakes?
Tell you what, Homer.
You make one last hit
and then you're out of
the business forever.
Lisa would understand.
You're all so wise.
l wish l could eat each
and every one of you.
Aw, we wish
you could eat us, too.
Hey!
Attention.
While you've
been showering here,
l sold all your clothes.
(ALL GROAN)
Again?
l've run out of
pie-related puns!
(ALL LAUGHlNG)
He won't escape, sir.
(SNORlNG)
Behold, Smithers,
your so-called Messiah.
Sir, l never. . .
l am the Pie Man. . .
l am Pie Man.
To the employee prison !
(EXCLAlMS)
Now let's see
what we have here.
(GASPS) Simpson !
You'll rue the day
you took that pie tin,
poked holes for eyes,
and attached a rubber band
around the back!
lt's not a rubber band,
it's a scrunchie.
Silence!
Or l'll chop you into suet
for my murderous
gerbils and hamsters!
(GROWLlNG)
Wait! l have a better idea.
You'll work for me now.
l already work for you.
ln addition to working
in your normal capacity
at the plant,
you will also serve
as my personal hit man.
Do l get two paychecks?
No.
(SHRlEKS)
Here's your first assignment
to prove your loyalty.
But l promised
my daughter. . .
Do as l say!
Or l'll tell the police.
You'll do so much
community service.
No! Not community service!
l can't stand helping others!
l just can't!
Now open the folder.
lt contains your next victim.
(GASPS) No, not him !
Anyone but him !
l've had
my problems with him.
Everyone has.
But like every monster,
he just wants to be loved.
Oh. . .
Come on.
lt's cobblering time.
(GROANlNG)
l can't sleep.
l keep thinking
about the Pie Man.
Oh, me, too.
What if he started
pie-ing good people?
Not because he wanted to,
but because he was being
blackmailed by his boss?
Homie, are you the Pie Man?
No, l'm not. And here's
a picture that proves it.
See?
Well, whoever he is,
the Pie Man
would never cave
in to blackmail.
(GROANS SADLY)
Now on a different subject,
kiss me hard !
You know, l'm not Pie Man.
l don't care.
(DOORBELL CHlMlNG)
Girl Scout cookies!
HOMER: Oh, come on.
She's a little girl !
MR. BURNS: Grow a spine on
your own time, blimpo!
Just one second, sweetheart.
Now pie that Brownie,
fruitcake!
Sorry.
Sir, my baby wants to play
Patty Cake, now!
(lMlTATES BABY COOlNG)
Your assignment.
HOMER: (GASPS)
The Dalai Lama?
That's right.
All his talk of
peace and love is really
honking off
my red Chinese masters.
Now, Smithers,
walk me around the park
until l fall asleep.
l'm feeling fussy.
As Springfield's
youngest Buddhist,
l am deeply
honored to introduce
the Dalai Lama.
Oh, l can't do this
in front of Lisa.
Why does she have
to believe in things?
You have no choice.
Pie him or l'll
reveal your secret
to the world.
And now, please welcome
the Elvis of Enlightenment,
the lean,
serene chanting machine:
the Dalai Lama!
(HORNS PLAYlNG)
Greetings, fellow travelers
on the path to enlightenment.
(ALL GASPlNG)
Please forgive me,
talking llama.
No, Pie Man ! Don't do it!
Come on, Pie Man, hit him !
That's the only
reason anyone came
to this stupid thing !
Oh ! No, l won't!
There's only
one way l can escape
from this nightmare!
(ALL GASP)
Homer Simpson?
lt was him all along?
Homer Simpson is
the Pie Man? lmpossible.
He's never thrown away
a pastry in his life!
His brain
isn't large enough to juggle
two contrasting personae!
Yeah, and Homer's a dumbass.
No offense, Homer.
You dumbass.
l'm telling you
l'm the Pie Man.
No, you're not.
The Pie Man could fly.
And spit acid.
And animals did his bidding.
(MUTTERlNG lN AGREEMENT)
Well, that closes
the book on Pie Man.
Wait a minute.
What?
lf it wasn't Simpson,
who was it?
lt's gonna be you
if you don't shut up.
Dad, l think
you created a hero
that even you
couldn't live up to.
(CHUCKLlNG)
Yeah. Let's go home, honey.
On to my next engagement,
Buffalo, New York.
l know one person
who believes you're
the Pie Man, Homie.
Me. l've known it all along.
Was it the kiss?
No. lt was clearly
you in that suit.
You'd have to be an idiot
not to see it from the start.
So, Pie Man,
why don't you show me
your super powers?
Pie Man?
Wherever injustice
shows its ugly face,
l will be there!
For l am the Pie Man !
And wherever Pie Man is,
the Cupcake Kid
will not be far behind.
MARGE: While you two
are up on the roof,
why don't you take the leaves
out of the gutter!
(BOTH GROANlNG)
English - US - PSDH