Gentlemen, I'd like to introduce
our youngest and brightest star.
He was very helpful during
our recent operation in Prague.
Only 11 dead.
- Excellent. Huzzah!
- Bravo.
Barely double digits.
He will now be taking over
our most critical assignment.
I am on the hunt
for a turned American
now working for Russia
code‐named Grey Fox.
In World War II, he served
with the fabled Flying Hellfish,
the only unit that served
in the Pacific, European
and Grauman's Chinese Theatres.
Now Grey Fox lives
in a small American town
containing a nuclear plant,
stealing their secrets.
This is a map of all
nuclear plants in America,
and these
are all the nuclear plants
with bad security.
I will go to each city,
and in no time at all,
I will have flushed out
Mr. Grey Fox.
Even if it takes me a fortnight.
Oy, what's a fortnight?
Nobody knows.
Goodbye, chaps.
I shall find this man
with English speed
and efficiency.
No, sir.
I haven't found him yet.
Yes, I know it's been 50 years.
But I've called you
because the dots
have finally connected,
and I'm off to prove it.
If I'm wrong, my entire life
has been a waste.
Except, of course,
for the reading.
And now to flush out the fox.
Oh, my God.
That's Louise's room.
Yes, it's terrible.
Did she...?
Her family took her back home
to live with them.
I hate to lose them that way.
I sure am gonna miss Louise.
She had a great smile.
- Oh, yeah, I loved her smile.
- Yeah, she sure did.
She had a great room.
- Oh, what a room!
- That was the best.
- It has a window!
- That opens.
Her call button actually works!
I want it, I want it, I want it.
- I want it.
- I said... I want it.
- It's mine.
She was my friend!
I should get it.
Louise hated your guts.
She hated your guts.
Now, now,
she hated all your guts.
So she let someone else know
the room was available,
and they put down
a huge deposit.
For this
I'm taking lucidity meds?
Who am I?
It is an emergency.
You've got to see
how I got cheated
out of the only good room
in the place.
Come on, Dad.
You love your room.
How would you know?
You never come to visit.
You don't know
a single thing about me.
Yes, I do.
What's my greatest fear?
Cocktail olives and fascism.
Everyone's afraid of that.
Those olives look like eyes.
Look at this closet.
It's got
a nice new light fixture,
not a naked bulb that leaves
nothing to the imagination.
Hello, boys.
Sorry to startle you.
Sorry. I'll be okay.
Ah, thanks.
How nice of you
to welcome me to my new room.
I'm Terrance.
What are you looking at?
It is so good
to finally meet you.
You're real.
You do exist.
Would you...! Hey!
My face was wrinkled
just the way I like it.
Oh, you stay away from me,
fella.
Unless I need companionship.
But don't hold your breath.
We should talk.
Yeah, you seem interesting,
but I can't stand old people.
Ah, just a minute.
I think I know how to tempt you.
I've studied your family.
I know your habits,
your personal pleasures.
Now, what might work here?
Oh, yeah.
Can I buy you a...
- Drink?
- Yes.
- And maybe have pretzels?
You know everything.
So, pal, where you from?
A little bit of everywhere,
really.
I was born in Bristol.
Caught cod off of Cardiff.
Fed pudding
to a terrier in Yorkshire.
And I know who you are.
You work at the nuclear plant,
are married to Marge
and have three children.
No, I only have tw...
Wait a minute, you're right.
That's amazing.
You're making the hair stand up
on the back of my neck.
This is it.
The moment when I say it all.
There's a lot.
I'm gonna exhaust you.
Anyone who's interested
in hearing a life story,
gather round.
I'll buy you a drink
for your troubles.
I'm calling my sponsor.
Get over here.
They're giving out free drinks.
Wow, those three hours
just flew by.
I want to hear more
about Terrance.
I am a spy.
- No!
- Oh, yes.
My father was an awful spy.
A blundering spy.
Sir, I've figured out
how the Russians
have stayed
one step ahead of us.
Lucky guesses.
You fool.
They've planted a mole
at the top
of our secret service.
Not possible.
I've asked everyone
if they were a mole,
and they all said no.
I became a spy
to redeem my father's name.
I was top of my class.
A real‐life spy. You must
know your way around women
and disillusionment.
Ah, yes, I certainly do.
Always the same.
She saves your life,
you fall in love,
you hold her in your arms,
then some bugger
shoots her dead.
You hunt the killer,
you track him down,
he captures you,
he tortures you,
you kill the killer.
And round and round you go,
boys.
That's amazing, Moe.
So, did you restore
your father's good name?
No, but I will
when I apprehend my target.
How long you been at it?
50 years.
Are you paid by the project
or by the hour?
No amount of money
could wipe away
the shame I feel.
Are you supposed
to be telling us all this?
Sure.
Nobody retains a word you say
when you're a man
of a certain age.
50 years
of serving queen and country.
Just the one queen, actually.
She really hangs in there.
But I have nothing
to show for it.
Until now.
But...
I shan't get into that just yet.
- Whatever happened to your father?
- Oh, he was
banished to Tipperary,
making his way back
to my mother, who had left him.
Do you by any chance know,
It's a Long Way to Tipperary?
Up to mighty London
came an Irishman one day
It's a long way
to Tipperary
Damn it!
Everybody sings it that way.
It was written
to be sung faster.
It's a pop song.
It's a long way to go
It's a long way to Tipperary
To the sweetest girl I know
Oh, Daddy, I'm so sorry.
Aw, he's miserable.
- He fits right in.
- Homer.
You were supposed to be home
three hours ago.
Oh, please, don't get up.
No, my dear.
Once you start this,
it's best to go ahead with it.
Ah, charmed.
Homer,
this is the nicest man
you've ever gotten
sloppy drunk with.
You must be Marge.
When's the last time
you told Marge you loved her?
Let's see.
It was...
When I figured out
how to stuff a porkchop
with another porkchop.
Thank you for asking.
Nice drinking free with you.
Maybe I'll see you again.
Oh, you will.
Once more, boys. With feeling.
It's a long way to Tipperary
Every time you sing a song,
it's $5,000 in damage.
Aw, come on!
What?
2:00 in the morning.
Don't answer it.
So, you want to snuggle?
I'm not gonna be romantic
with you
while the phone's ringing.
Hello?
Oh, hi, Terrance.
Yes, it was a pleasure.
Oh, give me that.
Y'ello?
If you want to know
the awful truth
about your father,
come see me now.
All right.
I've spent half my life
hunting a Russian agent
known as Grey Fox.
But now I believe I've found him
in this very home.
Your father, Abe.
What? My dad is not a spy.
So you say.
Ask yourself a few questions.
What did your father do
for a living?
I don't know.
Yet he always had money.
More than I expect.
Does he hate this country?
Well, he doesn't like
any of our political parties,
he says Grand Canyon
sarcastically,
he thinks
The Star‐Spangled Banner
is impossible to sing,
he calls Uncle Sam, Uncle Scam,
and he doesn't like
people who are different,
so I'd say he's as American
as Apple Watches.
Well, I'm about
to show you otherwise.
Let me ask you this...
Have you ever wondered
how it was
that you got a job
at a nuclear plant so easily?
How you retained that job
even though you screwed it up
time after time?
Answer me that!
This is insane.
What if Grampa's not the man
I think he is?
What if his name
isn't Grampa at all?
Listen, I understand
you need absolute proof.
If you really want to learn
the truth about your father,
meet me today at Springfield
Harbor at 10:00 till 2:00.
Okay. I'm in.
But I have one question.
Anything.
Your voice, it's so great.
Can you do Churchill?
Never was so much owed
by so many to so few.
Amazing!
I feel like I'm at a movie
I would fall asleep in.
He's not here.
Of course he's not.
He's just another crazy coot
from the old folks' home.
Don't get between me
and the pigeons, dearie.
Get away from me, lady.
Homer, you fool.
It's me.
What? Prove it.
Oh, my God. That's amazing!
An Englishman dressing in drag!
Never mind, now.
Hide behind that newspaper
and sit down.
Grey Fox is here.
Each Wednesday,
at precisely 2:00,
Grey Fox comes
to this boardwalk.
He finds an excuse to sit
on the very first bench he sees.
Hey, why is that woman talkin'
like a bloody Englishman?
I'm not English.
I'm Scottish.
And if you say different,
I'll rouge your fat behind!
You sound just like me ma.
Well, why don't you mind
your own business,
you red‐haired baboon?
Oh, it's like a letter
from home.
God bless ya.
Now, watch closely.
The second man
is gonna put down his cane.
Now see which cane
your father takes.
No, Dad.
Don't switch canes. Don't.
Don't. Don't. Didn't.
Don't. He did!
Oh, no!
It's called a dead drop.
He's receiving instructions
from his handlers,
hidden in the cane.
Oh, that
definitely proves he's a spy.
He took the wrong cane!
Now we're gonna see him
get his payment.
My dad would not spy for money.
He would only do it
because he hated his country.
Just look through these.
This is the worst thing
I've ever seen!
Okay, third worst thing!
I can't believe it.
Got my secret envelope
Will I say what's in it?
Nope!
No, no.
There, there.
A reveal takes time
to get used to.
I should've known.
He was a lousy dad.
He never took me
on a Ferris wheel.
I'd have been proud
to have a boy like you.
I've only known you a few days,
but I believe
everything you say.
Let me buy you a cotton candy.
Pink one, Daddy!
You can't bring
that cup of wine with you
on the Ferris wheel, sir.
It shall be gone
before you finish tightening
the safety arm.
Look at all those blurry
little dots down there.
Sir, you haven't gotten
on the ride yet.
Balance me with a cannonball
and start her up.
Okay.
So my father's a spy.
What happens now?
There are two ways this can go.
Here's the better one.
Your father trusts you,
so you're the only one
who can bring him in safely.
Then I'll deliver him
to justice.
I promise he'll be treated as
well as he is in the home now.
I prefer
he be treated slightly better.
Deal.
Brush your teeth after.
You didn't say with what.
Dad, we have to go.
Go where?
You don't have to lie
to me anymore.
I know who you really are.
That's good. Who am I?
No more games! I'm sorry,
but the only thing I can do
is turn you in.
Don't worry.
They promised me you'll be okay.
Is this one of your tricks
to get me to see
- the butt doctor again?
- Please!
Terrance will be here
any second.
No! I can't do it!
I'll take you somewhere far away
where they can't find you.
But we've got to leave now.
Say your goodbyes, quick.
You know,
goodbye is a contraction
of the farewell phrase
God be with you,
while farewell is a
contraction of fare thee well.
Shut up and let's go!
Sorry, gentlemen.
I'm afraid
there's been a change in plans.
Get in the car.
I call shotgun!
Thank heaven
I lost all feeling years ago,
so this won't be difficult.
Do you even have a license?
Just a license... to kill.
You idiot!
Someone tells you I'm a spy
and you immediately believe it?
No, I believed it
because I saw you do spy stuff.
What spy stuff?
You switched canes in the park.
I'm always takin'
someone else's somethin'.
I have two Jell‐Os every lunch,
and I'm not even supposed
to eat Jell‐O.
Well, what about the envelope
from the Russians?
Those were
Canadian blood pressure meds.
I got high blood pressure
from trying to pay
for my American pills.
I know you always think
the worst of me,
but how could you believe this?
Wait a minute.
Even though you suspected
I was a traitor,
you wanted to save me.
Of course I did.
Which means...
you love me.
Apparently.
I love you, Dad.
I love you.
Oh, and I love you.
And I love you.
And I love you more
than you love me.
Oh, no.
We're here to see Terrance.
My husband went to see him last
night and he never came back.
Not here.
How 'bout our grandpa?
Also not here.
Do you see anything
that goes on here?
Your father and
grandfather left with Terrance.
Your father‐in‐law was mouthing
the words help me,
but I'm trained to ignore that.
Excuse me,
are you friends with Terrance?
I'm his daughter, Hazel.
Your father took my husband
and his father away.
Homer left me this phone message
last night.
Marge! I'm...
locked in a trunk!
And not in a good way!
I got to...
What's going on?
Have you heard anything
from your dad?
He never remembers to call.
Especially when
he's killing people.
Killing people?!
But that's when he was a spy.
Now he's retired
and a bit delusional,
bless his moldy melon.
Good thing
he couldn't get hold of a gun.
In England.
Gun delivery for Crazy Terrance.
Didn't give a last name.
Just said he was workin'
for a foreign government.
What about the waiting period?
Oh, I waited for him
to hand me cash.
Period.
We're on a gravel road
and we're slowing down.
Not a good sign.
This is it, Dad.
I forgive you for everything.
You too, son.
If he asks me
to dig my own grave,
I'm totally not gonna do
a good job.
Well, this is
a wild goose chase.
There's no one in the car.
Open the trunk.
Well, I'll be.
I solved a case.
How did I do this?
I tracked my father
with my cell phone.
Show‐off.
I'll put out
the bulletin, Yanks.
Damn it. I mean...
Guys!
Dad, I know that's you.
Move yo' ass, sister.
I'm workin' here.
I heard someone's been
a little naughty.
A bit kidnappy.
Oh, my God, you're right.
I've mucked it up again.
Officers, I hope you never know
what it's like
to face a lifetime
of failing at your duty.
Never happen, my friend.
Cuffs. Cuffs.
Oh, who's got the cuffs?!
I'm nothing.
I'm a failure.
I'm worse than my father.
I'm just a hopeless bag
of useless...
Can't even kick myself.
Poor fella.
Nothin' to show
for 50 years' work.
But who does except for Tom Jones?
That guy loves not being dead.
But I could help this guy.
By being the Grey Box.
Or whatever.
You know what?
You got your man.
I did spy for the Russkies.
I am the Grey Fox!
Really?
Yep. I always knew
you'd be the one to get me.
Good show, me!
I have to admit, I did doubt
myself a couple of times.
Well, now you can retire
a happy man,
watch Fox News and feel
your brain turn to angry mush.
Congratulations.
Marge, may I give you a hug?
Of course.
No! It's happened again!
No, no, no, she's fine.
I was just shootin' off the top
of a soda can.
Yeah.
Homer, why don't you ride back
with Terrance?
Okay.
No, no. Up front.
Up front! Like a grown‐up!
It's a long way
To Tipperary
Faster! Come on!
It's a long way to go
Tiddly pom
It's a long way to Tipperary
To the sweetest girl I know!
- Dad, come here.
- What is it?
Korova govorit mu.
Koza govorit ba.
It's Russian.
What's going on in here, missy?
Osel govorit
hee haw, hee haw.
Made in Russia?
Oh, that's why that thing
only cost three bucks on Amazon.