Come on, Maggie.
Hi. Sorry we're late.
This is Maggie.
We're here for our first day.
Hello, Maggie.
And who will be picking her up?
After she falls down?
No, at the end of the day.
Wait, I don't stay with her?
Research shows
pre-toddlers learn best
in a parent-free environment.
Unless you want to stunt
her growth, which is great.
We're not supposed to judge.
No, no, it's not that.
I just don't want Maggie
to feel abandoned.
So, we'll see you at 4:00.
Okay, then.
Now what will I do
with the rest of my day?
I know.
I'll ask my favorite mommy blog.
Now turn that resistance
all the way up!
Come on! I want to see
you bitches suffer!
Am I the only one
who heard that?
I love it.
It's like being coached
by the voice inside my head.
Spin yourselves to death,
you land manatees!
Paint harder,
you sausage-fingered no-talents!
Sex-prise
your man at work.
What are you doing here?
Maybe you could give me
a safety inspection.
Oh, my God, I can't believe
this is happening.
I'm so sex-prised!
There's security
cameras everywhere,
so we'll have to
snuggle under the desk.
On top of the desk, please.
Thanks, Jerry!
Nice. Real cool.
Now how do I fill the day?
What's Well Plus Good?
It's pronounced Well and Good.
Why is everyone
talking to me?
Well, if all these people
want to work here,
maybe I want to work here.
All right, go to tablet seven
to take your pre-application
ethics assessment.
Cool hair, by the way.
You think that my hair is cool?
Well, thank you, Lauren.
Oh, by the way,
your name tag is upside down.
Thank you.
You're the only person
to mention that.
Ooh, major mom vibes.
She's perfect.
I always never lie.
Two.
I sometimes always never lie.
If I never found a wallet,
I would always give it back.
What color is the wallet?
Marge Simpson.
There was never a test.
Except there always was.
- There wasn't?
- And you passed.
Welcome to
the Well and Good family.
The rest of you can go.
Your résumés will be deleted.
I'm the only one you hired?
You're the only one
we partnered with.
Okay, so I work here now.
I never asked what we sell.
I can figure this out.
Candy? Bath bombs?
Blowtorches?
$30 bottles of soda?
Excuse me.
Do you recommend
the tincture or the oil?
The tincture
is more expensive, I guess.
Look, this is about you.
And taking care of you.
I think.
So you have
to put yourself... first?
Well, your no-frills,
fumbling sales pitch
has won me over.
I'll take both. Yes...
Wow, girl, you just made
a hundred-dollar sale.
You're gonna fit in great here.
Thing is, what does here sell?
Is this what RadioShack is now?
No. We're a high-end
cannabis boutique.
You sell pot?!
Technically, I check ID's.
You sell pot.
I'm a drugs dealer!
Cannabis is legal
in this state now.
Well, so is water-skiing,
but that doesn't mean
I have to sell it!
I'm sorry.
Marge, don't leave, seriously.
Like, I'm asking.
Drederick Tatum!
I own your countertop grill.
Oh, take care not to use
metal utensils
on the non-stick surfaces.
But anyway, after
my boxing career ended,
I was in a lot of pain.
Specifically,
in my punching hands
and my blocking face.
But following a regimen
of CBD oil
and medicinal hits
from a Pikachu bong,
I was able to enjoy life again.
Which inspired me to create
Well and Good Healing Emporiums.
But pot is for Cheeches...
and Chongs.
Marge, it's not about
getting high.
It's about wellness.
And that's why I've hand-picked
the perfect team here.
I'm an expert in cannabinoids
and cutting-edge
delivery systems,
aka infusers, decarboxylators,
transdermals
and pet suppositories.
And I'm super hot.
And what do you need me for?
Marge, people know
you want to help them,
that it's safe here.
Not some place
for Cheeches and Chongs,
as you so recently put it.
I'm sorry.
I don't think this is really me.
Good luck with your lifestyle.
Oh, it's a shame there's no drug
for hurt feelings.
Oh, wait, there totally is.
You know, in some families,
they go around the table
and everyone says
one thing they learned that day.
Okay. I learned that.
Well, I learned that
the former heavyweight champion
of the world
owns a marijuana store.
And he offered me a job,
which I turned down.
Wait, what?
I mean, the people
were really cool,
and they thought I was cool,
which made me feel stoked.
But I'm not going to be
a reefer saleslady.
Well, I guess there's nothing
wrong with it.
Cannabis is legal in this state.
Yeah, it's basically
the same thing
as working in a liquor store.
You can work in a liquor store?
Stay with us, big guy.
I thought you'd be
opposed to it.
People are stressed out
these days.
Scurvy is back,
there's, like, 60 wars going on.
Whales are eating
our precious ocean plastic.
Maybe people want
to smoke a doob for that.
Oh, yeah, everyone's
selling crap to stoners now.
Have you seen the new
Krusty Burger commercial?
When you've got the munchies,
for some reason...
wink, wink,
you crave weird.
A deep-fried rib-wich
served on a warm doughnut.
Or a spaghetti-filled
grilled cheese sandwich
drizzled with ranch pudding.
Krusty's Munchie Mouthfuls.
It's high time you tried it.
Get it? Get it?!
Get it?
I get it.
Well, Mr. Tatum
did personally choose me.
He said I was helpful.
Honey, you're the most
helpful person I've ever met.
Now go sell the safe
legal drugs
our kids should never, ever use!
Especially Bart!
Is this an Apple store?
Everyone keeps asking that.
I dropped my phone
because of my arthritis.
We can't fix your phone,
but I can sure help
with that arthritis.
Try this amazing
pain-relieving lotion.
It tingles.
Not like Jergens.
I hate Jergens!
You seem stressed.
Why not try some yummy gummies?
Marge, thank you.
When Mother's happy, I'm happy.
Or at least,
much less miserable.
This big shot here
is the principal
of a whole school!
Show her your key ring.
Oh, I love it.
I want to buy some pot.
All right,
pump the brakes, Jhorts.
Got to ask
a few questions first.
Now, do you want a body high
or a front-of-the-face buzz?
I don't know.
Just hook me up.
I have the perfect strain
in mind.
But be warned, boo,
the couch-lock is strong
on this one,
but there's, like,
zero mind-race.
What are you saying?
I just want...
weed.
Okay, almost there.
Almost there. Now listen.
Do you want this in flower...
shatter, topical...
edible, nasal mist...
- ear drops?
- Look, I just want to score a bag of shwag
from some dude who may
or may not be a cop.
I'm a cop.
Have you tried this?
Nothing makes sense anymore!
Give me a beer.
It doesn't make my hair
smell like anything!
I dreamed my whole life
of legalized weed.
Turns out it's a real buzzkill.
Ain't that the truth?
Times have changed.
The romance of alcohol
is fading into the past.
Stoners will never know the joy
of sitting on the toilet
and barfing into
your own underwear.
Or picking a fight with a guy
twice your size
because his leg
touched your car.
Yeah. I miss the old days too.
When buying pot was scuzzy.
I'd pay anything
to turn back that clock.
You know what'd be popular?
If one of those legal places
made it feel like
you were scoring weed
from your old-school
pot connection.
That's a great idea,
and we should do it.
Those tie-dyed bong monkeys
will cough up big-time
for the full dirtbag shebang!
I'll alert the bong monkeys.
Afternoon, gernts.
You need some suds?
Duffman knows it's always time
for a refreshing Duff!
Yeah, that being said,
sometimes Barry is looking
for a little herbal refreshment.
Know what I mean?
Right this way, fellas.
So you guys friends of Moe?
Yeah. These guys are cool.
Whoa, tight.
Come on in, gentlemen.
Oh, wait.
Here's a disclaimer, man.
This is a legal dispensary,
compliant with all laws
and statutes.
As part of the experience,
cast members may pretend
it's illegal.
All right. Shall we?
Crazy bird,
rusty free weights,
everything smells like
a damp swimsuit...
I'm home.
Who are you supposed to be?
I'm the weird friend
who never acknowledges you.
I was that guy
for my old roommate Scott.
Just stick it
in the Band-Aid can.
It's all stems and seeds.
Thank you.
So, with the success
of the Well and Good brand...
which, you know, thank God...
I'm so pleased to present
our latest venture...
Werk.
This is The Drederick.
It's a fully realized
cannabis resort and spa.
Now, for our launch event,
we'll be inviting marijuana
influencers from Dave Chapelle
to Harrison Ford, who is
flying himself, by the way,
so you know, fingers crossed.
Marge, I was thinking
that you would be
the hostess
of this launch party,
acting as the de facto face
of the Well and Good brand.
Oh, my God. Why me?
Well, Marge,
'cause people trust you.
Also, my face
is the intellectual property
of the artist
who created this tattoo.
So, you know, I'm out.
Oh, I'd love to.
This is so exciting, I...
Wait, wait, no.
I wanted to ask you.
But unfortunately, there was
a fly in the CBD ointment.
Your husband Homer
is selling weed, Marge.
That's terrible.
Wait, no, so am I.
We all are.
We are trying to elevate
the image of cannabis.
This is what he's doing.
Oh, he knows how much
self-esteem I get
from selling bud.
And that's our good frisbee.
I'm afraid that you cannot
continue with this company
while your husband is taking pot
back to the dark ages of 2018.
- I'm very sorry.
- Oh, no. No, no, no.
Please, please don't fire me.
I want to be your face.
When Homer realizes
how much this is hurting me,
I'm sure he'll understand.
I don't understand.
We're doing the same thing,
except you dress like a doctor,
and I dress like a cool toddler.
Don't you get it?
I'm a healer,
and you're a dealer.
You need to quit.
I can quit whenever I want.
I just don't want to.
What happened to the quitter
I married?
I quit quitting!
- What's going on?
- Mom and Dad are having a drug war.
- It's not different!
- And you spent $1,000...
I make CNN much funnier!
Homer wouldn't quit.
Here's my smock,
my key to the hash register,
my business card
reading associate.
Instead of being
the face of the company,
my face will just be me.
Wait, Marge. There is one way
to save your job,
but it would entail the betrayal
of your husband,
which I would never
ask you to do.
Well, I mean,
it doesn't hurt to ask.
With your help, we can get
the government to shut him down.
The FBI? The DEA?
The County Health Department.
I don't understand.
What crime is Homer committing?
Pot's legal.
Yes, but he isn't
licensed to serve
non-psychotropic edibles,
aka food.
If he offers snacks
to his customers and they eat
even one bite,
we go in and take him down.
So we need you to bait the trap
with these.
Are you in?
Nailed it.
You're the son I never had.
Hey, Homer.
Look who's stopped by over here.
I am so sorry
about our little tiff.
Will you accept this apology
gift for you and your friends?
Oh, honey.
You're always in my corner.
I have the most loving,
supportive, loyal wife
in the world.
If Simpson keeps
eating like this,
he'll hit bottom dust
before anyone takes the bait.
Come on, you fat bastard, offer
the customer some cheese balls.
And the whole floor
is an air hockey table,
so moving furniture...
is like...
Homer!
Give your friends
some cheese balls.
Would anyone care to partake?
Code Orange. Go, go, go!
Stop eating!
Health Department.
This is a raid.
We got to get rid of the stuff.
Oh, no! Come on!
Oh, God!
We got everything we need.
You're shut down, pal.
You, you knew.
- You...
- Set you up.
You're coming with us, scumbag,
to pay a $25 fine.
Marge, darling,
everything is so perfect.
I hope your husband
wasn't too upset
about the, you know,
the treachery.
Oh, well, Homer is very
easygoing, so...
Excuse me,
can any of these oils or goos
help me with a knife wound?
I have been stabbed,
in the back!
How did you get in?
This is by invitation only.
I said I was
Kevin Smith's father.
No one questioned me.
Homer, control yourself.
You're upsetting
the influencers.
They're very easily influenced.
That guy is on alcohol.
Please don't ruin this.
This is cannabinoid health,
and I am its face.
Cabana boy health.
If it's so good for you...
why have you never
tried pot, ever?
Well, does a doctor
need to try insulin
to know that it helps diabetes?
Yes. I think she should.
Surprise! The doctor's a woman.
Sexist!
- Good point.
- That is sexist.
Look, I don't have
a problem with pot.
I can start any time I want.
I'll do some right now.
Perfect. Serenity.
See? Nothing.
I'm probably one of those people
it doesn't work on.
I feel like I'm on an elevator
that's going up and down
at the same time.
Something's wrong. You said
this was about wellness,
but I feel high.
Okay, okay, listen.
What you need to understand
is this, I'm high too!
I'm Serenityed out of my gourd.
Yeah, baby.
I've got to come down.
I've got to eat something.
That was
a chicken pot pot pie.
Oh, no. I ate an eatable.
And you just wiped your mouth
with a Hash-nap,
the most potent thing here.
Is this how I always walk?
What do I do with my arms?
Okay, got it.
This is normal.
Honey, it's me.
Homie.
You're gonna be okay.
In two hours
that will seem like 12.
You're so sweet.
And I ratted you out.
No, I get it.
You found a place
that made you feel special,
and you didn't want
to lose that.
I still feel weird.
Maybe you'd feel less weird
if I were weird too.
Here, I'll smoke
one of your futuristic joints.
That's not a doobie!
Oh, man, Dad, what did you do?
Hemp clothes burns like paper!
All wrong, all wrong, all wrong!
- Oops.
- Be cool.
Cheer up, neck face.
If there's one thing I know,
it's life is nothing but pain.
People will always need guys
like you and me
to get them wasted.
Yeah, thanks,
monster man hallucination.
Your words are
a great comfort to me.
We'll get through it somehow.
Well, can I come with...
In reaction to the destructive
Drederick blaze
which also destroyed the
Sign Language Monkey Sanctuary,
the town council has passed
an emergency ordinance
outlawing the sale of cannabis.
Without that tax money,
Maggie's pre-education center
will have to close.
Aw, man, they were
teaching her Mandarin.
Well, it's probably
for the best.
Even though they say
something's not addictive,
you can still get hooked.
And you don't want that.