(SlNGlNG) The Simpsons
(TlRES SCREECHlNG)
D'oh !
(SCREAMlNG)
(BRAKES SCREECHlNG)
lt's too nice a day
to be outside doing chores.
Come in and watch TV.
Mom finally stopped caring !
Don't go inside!
lt's a trap!
Yes, she must
have some kind of
super-chore in there.
Like getting the rat
out of Maggie's room.
l'm not fooling
around, people.
Park your keisters
in front of that TV!
Now!
(LlSA SCREAMlNG)
(EXCLAlMlNG)
This counts as a bath !
(CHUCKLlNG)
The irrepressibIe
1 00-year-oId skydiver
will be buried as soon
as his body is found.
Now, it's time for
the Channel 6 Oops Patrol!
This week,
one eagIe-eyed viewer
spotted this
hilarious headline.
Mayor unveiIs
erection to cheering crowd.
This week's
Oops Patrol T-shirt
goes to...
Whom? Whom?
Mrs. Marge Simpson
of Springfield!
Ta-dah !
Mom made the Oops Patrol !
Hot damn !
Bart, you're not at school,
don't swear.
What an amusing
T-shirt, Marge.
l'll trade you
for a tote bag
that says "Prozac."
No, thanks.
l'm wearing my cure
for depression.
Come on !
Give me that shirt!
l'll put you at the top of
the heart transplant list.
My heart is fine.
lt could always
be a little better.
Honey, this is your
moment in the sun.
And l couldn't
be more pleased
for your happiness.
(WHlMPERS)
Why was l born?
(STRUGGLlNG)
Oh, T-shirt,
bless the loom that
fruited you.
(GASPS) Homer!
Win your own T-shirt!
(GROANS)
HOMER: Gotta win a T-shirt.
Gotta win a T-shirt.
Okay, get ready to laugh.
"Cranford man missing."
What's he missing?
His pants? A train?
Gimme a break!
Too soon, huh? All right.
"Drought threatens to turn
west into dessert"!
Yum, yum. l think l'd like
some whipped cream
on my Wyoming.
Dad, the word's "desert."
And those farmers
are suffering.
From what?
Too much hot fudge?
(LAUGHS)
Come on, Bart.
Show me some love.
Don't drag me down
with you, old man.
(ELECTRlCAL SOUNDS)
This is what
happens when l go for
six hours without sleep.
(READlNG)
(LAUGHS)
No.
(READlNG)
l'll put that in the "maybes."
l gotta get that T-shirt.
"World's biggest pizza"?
Oh, my God !
Marge, wake up!
The newspaper's
talking to me!
Oh, relax.
l'm sure it's just
your brain going crazy.
l wish ! Look at
this headline!
Someone or
something knows l love
oversized food and
short punchy articles.
So they hid a message
in the first letter
of each line. See?
"Homer, meet me 4th street
overpass midnite."
Wait a minute.
This is today's paper!
That meeting is tonight!
Don't tell me
you're actually going.
Marge, l don't know
what this is.
But sometimes
you've just gotta
go with your gut.
You always go
with your gut.
This time, why don't you
listen to your brain?
All right, l will.
(UKULELE MUSlC PLAYlNG)
That's why l don't
listen to my brain.
And away we go!
(GROANS)
Psst. Hey, pal.
Hey, buddy. Wake up.
You want to go on an
adventure with your old man?
No.
You have no choice.
There's coffee
in the thermos.
This is boring.
Can't we go home?
This overpass
smells like urine.
They all do.
Fresh urine!
Hey! The bathroom's
a block away!
(ZlPS PANTS)
MONA: Homer Simpson?
(BOTH SCREAM)
(HOMER SCREAMlNG)
MONA:
Still my little crybaby.
l'll save you, Dad ! Karate!
Grandma!
Oh, Bart.
Are you still
a little hell-raiser?
Yes'm.
Mom, you're back!
Just like you
were back before.
Then you left me again.
l love you so much !
But it's so hard
for me to trust you.
What the heck.
Give me a hug, you.
Homer, you're hugging a bum.
l know. l'm working
my way up to you.
Hey, gimme back my wine!
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
Sorry about all
the cloak and dagger, Homer,
but the government
is still after me
for what l did in the '60s.
They're probably
tapping your phones
and reading your mail.
l think the government has
better things to do
than to read my mail.
Most people write
letters to movie stars.
This Simpson guy
writes to movies!
"Dear Die Hard, you rock!
"Especially when that
guy was on the roof.
"P.S. Do you know Mad Max?"
To reach you,
l called up my friends
in the liberal media
and planted that story
about the giant pizza.
You sure know me, Mom.
Pizza was the first food
he choked on.
Aw...
So why are you back in town?
l saw this
macaroni pencil holder
Homer made me,
and l realized how
much l missed him.
l made this when l was five.
l had to do something.
Your pencils were
all over the place.
Hey, it was the '60s.
(ALL GASP)
ls that fugitive radical
Mona Simpson?
Yeah. And that's Tokyo Rose
mopping the floor.
Hey, Joe!
Your girlfriend
sleeps with Tyrone Power!
Chief, l think
we've got a match here.
All right.
Let's check it out.
But if you're wrong,
you and Lou have
to kiss each other.
Hey, Chief,
l checked with the union.
You can only do that once.
Oh.
Cora, is there
a back way outta here?
Not for someone who tips 9%.
Fine!
Right through there,
Santa Claus.
Mom, l swear on
your eventual grave,
l will never
ever let the police
get their hands on you !
Uh-oh.
You guys are damn lucky.
All you destroyed
were bricks, mortar
and attorneys.
Remember me
as a drain on society.
Captured '60s radical,
Mona J. Simpson,
goes on triaI today
on decades-oId charges
of sabotaging
the C. Montgomery Burns
Germ Warfare Lab.
For those of you
too young to remember
the '60s,
here's our stock montage.
(ALL ALONG
THE WATCHTOWER PLAYlNG)
You bet your sweet bippy.
What a shrill,
pointIess decade.
During her years on the Iam,
Simpson led an exemplary life
working as a crossing guard,
oral historian,
reader for the blind,
listener for the deaf
and reacher for the short.
Yet local villain,
Montgomery Burns, seen
here terrorizing chiIdren
in a 1 9th century woodcut,
insists that she stand trial.
Kent, I want everyone
in your radio
picture audience to know
that this woman is a menace
to decent peopIe
and germ warriors everywhere!
End communication.
(GAVEL SLAMMlNG)
Now, Lisa,
would you agree that your
grandmother is a sweet,
harmless woman
who could
hardly be considered
a menace to society?
Definitely. lf you ask me,
she's far less dangerous
than Bart.
lf it please the court,
l would like to go
ape on my sister.
l object.
Judge, sidebar?
Very well.
Judge, do you
have a little sister?
Yes.
She used to call me
"Fatty Boomalatty."
l'll allow an lndian burn.
Thank you, Your Honor.
LlSA: Ow!
Your Honor,
can you please focus
on the case at hand?
l'm sorry.
My wife left me this morning.
Now, l'm not a man
who's good with words.
You gotta say something.
She's looking at 20 years!
And my legal license
expires in 1 5 minutes.
l barely know my mother.
And every time l see her,
she's taken away again.
And when a man
doesn't have his mother,
he winds up like me.
ALL: Aw. . .
l mean,
l'm due back in this same
courtroom three times today.
Hell, l torched a blood bank!
One cookie, my ass!
Please, please give me
back my mommy!
(CRYlNG)
Your Honor, there is no way
we can find this
defendant guilty!
Although l will miss
the jury room cold cuts.
And the Quality lnn
more than lived
up to its name. . .
Case dismissed !
. . .business center,
workout room,
an honor bar l was
honored to use. . .
That's enough.
And Peggy in the coffee shop,
what a pistol.
A mere nod
in her direction,
and the refill
was in the mug !
The jets in the whirlpool
anticipated my every move
when it was working.
And $3 for a local call?
They should be
the ones on trial !
Oh, Mom, l'm so happy!
l never want to let you go!
Mom, l never
want to let you go!
l'm not your mother.
Look, lady.
Just keep hugging
till we get to Mexico.
Mother.
Go hug your floozy.
Mother, she's right here.
She knows l'm kidding.
l'm not kidding.
Curse that groovy granny!
This is America!
Justice should favor
the rich !
Sir, maybe you
could use a few huffs
from your ether bottle.
(lNHALES DEEPLY)
Oh, man, that's good E.
Well, now that l'm free,
l intend to be
a better mother to my son.
Woo-hoo!
l can be a little boy again !
A boy who gets
some on the side.
Baby! Now you're free
to come back to me.
Dad, you testified
against her.
l read a book that
said women like jerks.
But the mother
and child reunion
Is onIy a motion away
Oh, little darling of mine
l can't for the life of me
Remember a sadder day
Look, Mom !
Look! l'm riding by myself!
(CAR HORN)
(SCREAMlNG)
(GRUNTlNG AND GROANlNG)
Homer, this really
isn't necessary.
You weren't around
for the birth
of your grandson.
And l want you to see it.
(MlMlCKlNG BABY CRYlNG)
Ain't l cute?
You owe me a dirt bike.
Hey, guys. l brought my mom.
Lenny Leonard?
l haven't seen you
since you were this high.
l can jump off the high dive!
Carl Carlson.
l remember when you,
Lenny and Stevie McGregor
were like
"The Three Musketeers."
Yeah. Poor Stevie.
They never found his head.
Mrs. Simpson,
when you took off,
you left a hole
in Homer's heart
that he's been trying to fill
with alcohol for 20 years.
God bless ya.
Welcome to your room, Mom.
l want you to
stay here forever.
Homer, it's perfect.
Doesn't this armoire
belong to Mr. Flanders?
You stole this entire room
from Ned Flanders' house!
Oh, well,
you snooze, you lose.
But could l have
my photo albums back?
Now get out of my house!
And so in
the spirit of fence-mending
and grudge-not-bearing,
l hereby rename
the Burns Germ Warfare Lab,
the Grandma Simpson
Peace Museum
and Kid-teractive
Learnatorium.
Grandma Simpson,
will you be the first
to sign
the museum's guest book?
lt'd be a real pleasure.
You know,
when l was on the run,
l always had to
sign a fake name,
like when l
visited a state park.
lndeed, how about
a national park?
Why yes.
l've got it all
on this dictabelt.
Move in, boys!
What's going on?
Supplying false information
on a national park register
is a federal offense,
which you've committed
at every national park
from Acadia to Zion.
You're going away
for a long time,
Mrs. Simpson.
Or should l call
you "Anita Bonghitt"?
No! l can't lose
my mother again !
Don't take her away!
(TlRES SCREECHlNG)
Stop messing with him.
The man lost his mother.
Just one more time.
Okay, it is pretty funny.
(TlRES SCREECHlNG)
Mother, you had me
But I never had you
I wanted you
But you didn't want me
Dad, l'm just
as sad as you are.
What happened to Grandma
is an outrage.
How do you figure?
She was acquitted !
Then they
put her back in jail
on a technicality!
You're right.
People should only
be let out of jail
on technicalities.
Well,
they're transferring Grandma
to a federal prison tomorrow.
l say we hit 'em
where they live
with a candlelight vigil.
Candlepin bowling?
That's a great idea.
We'll play right after
l break your grandmother
out of prison.
(SlNGlNG) I fought the Iaw
and the law won
Now just the innocent!
I fought the Iaw
and the law won
Now just the really innocent!
(LAUGHlNG)
l hope this bus ride
never ends,
'cause l'm getting
executed when l get off.
Okay, boy.
Flip through
those highway warnings
till we find one
that'll stop that bus.
Next.
Pass.
Boring.
Aw...
Ha-ha, loser!
Geez, pal.
Will you look at that?
(TlRES SCREECHlNG)
(GUARDS COUGHlNG)
Homer, what on earth
are you doing?
Mom, l love you.
l can't let you go to prison.
Who's the wheelman, granny?
lt's my son, Homer.
ALL: Aw. . .
Oh, isn't he darling?
He's a big one.
Oh, stop it.
Take care, ladies.
l'm sure you can
make it back to
the prison on your own.
We will.
You're all right,
Donut Breath.
You're like
the son l never killed.
Mom, l'm gonna hide
you where there's no one
around for miles.
Disney's California
Adventure.
(SlRENS BLARlNG)
BOTH: D'oh !
Homer, get out now
and no one will ever
know you're involved.
No! You're my mother,
and l won't leave you !
lf you stay here,
you'll be abandoning
your family
the way l abandoned you.
Yeah.
That did mess me up
pretty bad. But l'm
not gonna leave you !
l see
you've made your choice.
l love you, Homer.
(ELECTRlCAL ZAPPlNG)
That's lucky.
(SCREAMS)
Brambles! Briars!
Nettles! Thorns!
Granny to the Man.
This is "the Man."
"l think it'd be a gas if you
turned that magic bus around
"and kept on
truckin' to our pig pad."
l don't know
what you're saying.
But l am not turning back.
Then listen to me, lady.
The only way
you're getting off
this mountain is in a box
or a funicular.
What about
a hot air balloon?
Pipe down, Jules Verne.
Go, Mom ! You can do it!
No!
There's still air
in that bus.
So for the next five minutes,
this is a rescue mission.
(EXPLOSlON)
Make that a salvage mission.
(RUMBLlNG)
Okay, everyone take
some free time,
and we'll see you
tomorrow at 1 0:00.
Grandma, you'll always be
an inspiration to me.
You taught me a criminal
can evade the law
well into old age.
Thanks for
the meatloaf recipe,
l claim it as my own.
Mona, l'll always remember
raspberry trolley cars.
Because my mind is shot.
Your last act as a mom
was to make me a better dad.
But at least now,
l'll never lose you again.
(TlRES SCREECHlNG)
Look out!
(EXCLAlMS lN FRUSTRATlON)
Homer,
it's 2:00 in the morning.
l couldn't sleep
because l thought
there might be
a sign of my mom
in one of these articles.
They never did find her body.
Then what was in the coffin?
Last week's garbage.
l missed the pickup date.
But it doesn't matter,
because my mom is alive! See?
l am o. . . Kay.
Get it? "l am okay."
Okay, Homie.
lf it makes you feel better,
l think your mom's
all right, too.
Hey, as long as
we're thinking about her,
Grandma's still alive.
Come on, big guy.
This'll help you
get to sleep.
MONA: Homer, your mother
Ioves you.
I escaped from
the bus the moment
before it pIunged
off the cliff.
l then hitched a ride
from a nice young coupIe.
We had lunch at
a IoveIy diner.
They had cIam chowder,
Rhode IsIand-styIe.
l never knew there
was such a thing.
And the crackers
kept on coming.
English - US - PSDH