CHOIR: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(theme music playing)
(exclaims)
(school bell ringing)
(burps)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-(tires screech)
-(grunts)
Hmm.
♪ ♪
(Strauss' "Also Sprach Zarathustra"
playing)
(clacking)
-(alarm wailing)
-HOMER: Uh-oh.
-(alarm stops)
-HOMER: Sweet.
-(gulping)
-Whoo-hoo!
-Simpson.
-Uh-oh. The boss.
Do you know what you've done?
You won the "count the buttons"
in the button jar challenge.
Thanks to him,
you all get the rest of the day off.
(chuckles) Go home.
Live your lives. Don't look back.
Smithers, the bodies.
(beeping)
♪ ♪
I had a great day, and I really
want to celebrate with the boys.
So don't wait up for me, my sweet,
wonderful bartender, Moe.
Yeah, all right, but who's the boys?
Marge's boobs. See ya. Mm-hmm.
(rapping) ♪ I'm so happy ♪
♪ Bursting with joy,
my day's been spectacular ♪
♪ Improving my vernacular,
eating Cracker Jack-ular ♪
♪ It's a perfect day so far... ♪
Patty and Selma's car?! D'oh!
Homie, stop dropping rhymes
and get dressed.
We're going to
the 38th annual DMV Awards.
Aw, there are too many award shows.
People don't deserve so many awards.
People suck.
They should just be grateful to be alive.
Get your coffin suit out,
'cause you're goin'.
-(groans)
-You're at table one,
next to the bathroom,
furthest from the bar.
Patty and Selma are producing
the Surlys this year.
Hamilton's gonna win everything.
Fred Hamilton. Window six.
He can make every person in the room
feel like their number
is the furthest from being called.
(laughing)
-(light crackling)
-(dog barks in distance)
You know, Selma,
James Bond has a license to kill.
HOMER: Stop forcing banter!
But a lot of people would kill
for these licenses.
HOMER: Heckle! Heckle!
For Funniest Vanity Plate,
the nominees are I Heart Heart Doctors,
from the writing team of...
Oh, team?!
♪ ♪
BOTH: Beep-beep, beep-beep.
Objects may be sexier than they appear.
(growls)
That's it. I'm leaving.
-Take me!
-You'd slow me down!
Lisa Simpson here,
covering the Surly Awards
for Springfield Elementary
School Radio, WSES.
Ooh, here comes
an audience member now.
One guy in the "In Memoriam" reel
was alive when it started!
Don't forget your gift bag!
HOMER: It's just a coupon
for a dollar off at the car wash,
but if you don't have one,
the lady at the car wash
will give you one from out of a drawer!
-(tires screech)
-Homer, come back!
You're the next presenter!
HOMER:
The winner is me 'cause I'm leaving!
Stomach filled with rage.
Must quench with French fries.
(tires screech)
Five Krusty Burgers. No tomato.
Sorry, sir.
We no longer serve Krusty Burgers.
But it's your name!
It's as if Macy's didn't sell Mace!
Our corporate parent in Kumamoto, Japan,
has instituted the following fun
and nonnegotiable changes...
-(traditional Japanese music playing)
-Hey, hey!
Try our Buttermilk Sriracha Sandwich,
Kobe Shiitake Ciabatta Explosion,
and Hanoi Honey Barbecue
Banh Mi Pho-furter.
Get 'em quick, before they're Sai-gone!
(laughs)
Oh, I just want a one-pound burger
that a snake couldn't fit
its mouth around.
Sorry.
We no longer sell the Python Buster.
Would you like some Kombucha
Kimchi Mini Tacos instead?
Just give me a cup.
That's beet aioli.
No!
-(tires screech)
-People! Beware!
The crap you love to eat
has been replaced by food!
(tires screech)
♪ ♪
Heavenly Father, I know
you're a friend of the eating man.
You created Sunday so we can have brunch.
Please, O Lard,
shower me with your divine grease
and deliver me some egg rolls.
Or pizza or hot dogs.
Whatever I can eat while driving.
For thine is the flower
and the gravy forever.
A menu...
would be great.
♪ ♪
(gasps) Thank you.
-Help you?
-Um...
what's the healthiest thing
in this place?
Whoo-hoo!
Chewie, we're home.
Chewie is what I call my mouth.
I really don't care
what you call your mouth.
(tires screech)
Ah.
Just in time for breakfast.
Hi, guys.
So, Homie, I'm sure
you have a good explanation
-for where you were.
-The best.
I was eating hot dogs.
Hot dogs? (scoffs)
-That is so stupid it must be the truth.
-It is.
I bet you're picturing me
as a hot dog right now.
Absolutely not!
-Oh...
-(chuckles)
And these weren't just any hot dogs--
they were Deuce's Caboose Chili Dogs!
We were worried sick!
What do you think we are, man?
Take that.
Ow! No fair!
She nut-butted me.
(chuckles) Deuce's Caboose, eh?
We used to take you there
when you were a boy.
I don't remember any of that.
Well, you were young then,
and you're stupid now.
Your mom and me dropped you off
there every Wednesday afternoon
while we tuned up our marriage.
-Turn here.
-Oh, you just love to tell me what to do.
We come here every week,
and you get lost.
Please stop fighting.
Oh, you would just love it
if we did that, wouldn't you?
He'll take a small soda
and sit there for 50 minutes.
(grunts)
Hey, kid, have a chili dog,
on the house.
If we split up, no one gets Homer!
("The Flower Duet" playing)
(monitor beeping rhythmically)
That's when I started eating my emotions.
Oh. You poor guy.
Fat-man begins.
Well, it taught me a great coping skill.
Eating is to me what drinking is to me.
(chuckles) I just wish I had
something aggravating in my life
to make me hungry now.
-Hello!
-(gasps)
Uh, Homie, Patty and Selma
lost their jobs at the DMV,
because they spent too much
on the award show.
We went over the $43 budget.
By $100,000.
To save money,
I said they could live here for a while.
And don't forget,
we have a baby and an iguana.
And they both have
different sleep schedules.
What they do have in common is diarrhea.
And we forgot to bring diapers.
Hey. You remember me as a kid, right?
No, sir.
But you called me
your Little H-Dog, remember?
Look, man, I'm getting up there.
I can barely remember the starting lineup
of the 1961 Chicago Blackhawks.
Uh, Bobby Hull, Al Arbour,
Ed Litzenberger, captain,
Stan Mikita, and... that's all.
Also, Dollard St. Laurent.
But not you.
I'm sorry, sir.
(moans)
Okay, people, what have you got?
We're being killed in the ratings
by the morning announcements.
SKINNER (on P.A.): Attention,
the bus that took 30 kids
on a "field trip"
was not from this school.
If anyone's mom can pick up
30 students in South Springfield,
it would be much appreciated. Ow!
Why didn't we break that story?!
Damn it, we're even being beaten
by Jimbo's podcast.
Today on Left, Right and Center,
we'll discuss whether
to punch someone in the left,
right, or center.
Our special guest today
is upside-down nerd,
Milhouse Van Houten.
Thanks for having me back.
Aren't we just supposed to do
the stories we want
and not worry about ratings?
That's kindergarten talk.
This is professional fourth-grade radio.
(knocking)
Meeting's over.
I've got to put the balls back in.
I'm the smartest ball in the bag.
(crow caws)
You could be replaced,
and it wouldn't be hard.
A cinder block with a stretched-out belt
-would do the trick.
-(yells)
(tires squeal)
("The Flower Duet" playing)
No one's eating at my place.
No one!
I'm a self-hating chew.
♪ Hot dog ♪
♪ Life is tasting pretty good ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ Hot dog ♪
♪ 'Cause you love me like you should ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ So put some mustard on my roll ♪
♪ 'Cause you're barking up my soul ♪
♪ Hot dog ♪
-♪ I like to see you walk ♪
-♪ Beef log ♪
-♪ I like to hear you talk ♪
-♪ Food blog ♪
-♪ I really relish you ♪
-What rhymes with relish?
-♪ Who could embellish you? ♪
-Whoo-hoo!
BOTH: ♪ Hot dog ♪
-♪ Hot dog ♪
♪ Hot dog ♪
-♪ Don't know what's inside of you ♪
-♪ Hot dog ♪
(laughter)
Ah.
I still don't remember you, man.
LISA: Here at Springfield Elementary,
detention has many names.
Prankatraz, The Skinner Sheraton,
Spitball Alley, The Bully Pen,
Three Elevenworth, Little Devil's Island,
and Dead Man Chalking.
And I am here with the legendary
nurple purpler Nelson Muntz.
-Yo.
-Nelson, let me get right to it.
Haw haw!
Where did that come from?
Um... wow.
First of all, great question.
I guess I just saw a jerk
doing something lame,
and I wanted to make the dope
feel like a dingus.
Well, Mr. Muntz,
I just happen to have
one of those "dingi" right here.
Milhouse, how does it feel
to get a full Nelson?
The first "haw" isn't that bad.
But the second one is devastating.
Wow! Wow!
Sorry, Lisa.
Funding has run out
for our radio station.
I'm, uh, gonna have to
take back your hat.
-What?!
-Jeff and Becky broke up!
Just before the story of the year!
(Homer humming)
Hmm?
What's wrong, sweetie?
They took away my radio station,
which was the only source of news
in a 50-foot area.
You could come with me
to the hot dog stand
and do the word search
on the kids' menu.
Do they have diagonals?
Diagonals!
That's where "race car" was hiding.
Oh, no, the hot dog stand is closed!
The place I forgot for 30 years is gone!
(whimpering)
There's always a weak link.
There's always a weak link!
(groaning)
We should help that man. He's choking.
I remember when you used
to help me when I was choking.
Why don't you ask the girl
at the hiking store?
I gave her my number
because I was ordering boots.
Don't let it be forgot
that on this shining spot
was a place I really ate a lot.
I don't see how you can
blame a man of 97 for retiring.
-I thought we were the same age.
-So did I.
Well, I hope you didn't
sell it to some clown.
(Krusty's theme playing)
Here's a check.
Welcome to the Krusty Burger family.
And since we're family, we don't talk!
Next problem.
Oh! What else are you gonna change?
We're going to keep everything
that makes Deuce's Caboose great.
Like the hot dogs and the caboose?
No. God, no.
We're already talking to C-list actors
about playing the owner in commercials.
We're trying to find
a cheap Garrett Morris.
-(creaking)
-(engine starts)
Hot dogs,
come with me if you want to live!
(engine revving)
Somebody, stop them!
(Krusty's theme song plays in reverse)
That better be
a monkey's tail I'm feeling.
Uh, chimps have no tails.
Chimps have no tails?!
Dad, what are we doing?
I'm saving a precious childhood memory!
You realize this will be
my childhood memory,
and maybe not so precious?
-That's a problem for grown-up Lisa.
-All right, then.
("The Flower Duet" playing)
I certainly hope that isn't
your father's hot dog caboose.
I have no end game!
Oh, Lord!
He's on the news so much,
he has his own theme music now.
♪ Go, Homer, go ♪
♪ Never know what he's gonna do ♪
Kent Brockman with you.
You're watching Channel 6
Super Team coverage
of Chili Dog Day Afternoon
Wiener on a Roll.
Indeed.
Basically, I'm just watching it
like the rest of you.
I guess you'd like some kind
of commentary or perspective.
I don't have any,
but I'd like you to remember
you're watching Channel 6--
the one that doesn't cut away
when somebody dies.
(siren wailing)
Chief Wiggum,
maybe I can defuse the situation.
De-fuse? Huh.
Well, there's a first time
for everything.
Can you hand me your mic?
Every police regulation says no,
but do you know what says yes?
-What?
-Your eyes.
Aw.
This is Lisa Simpson,
a name you can trust,
and I'm with Homer Simpson,
a man who just stole a caboose.
My father is on a quixotic quest
to save a greasy spoon from being licked.
I have to save
that caboose full of hot dogs,
which is what my father called me.
(excited chatter)
This aggression shall not stand, sir.
Let us ride!
Say, Colonel, which army were you in?
Never you mind which army I was in
and which courthouse we surrendered at.
I said let's ride!
I guess that's it--
the one freeway chase
that ends in failure.
No, it has not!
We shall overeat!
(dramatic music playing)
ALL: Aw.
-ALL: Yay!
-D'oh!
I'm sorry, Dad. It's over.
No, it's not.
(all gasping)
Krusty, run regular.
I forgot how! (grunts)
(Homer grunting)
(screams)
-(creaking)
-Oh.
-(gasps)
-So that's what it's for.
No! I can't let my Little H-Dog die!
(gasps) You do remember me.
I never forgot you. How could I?
-(creaking)
-You were such a sweet,
sad little boy, and I failed you.
-No, you didn't.
-Yes, I did.
You needed a father,
and all I could give you
was steamed tubes
filled with chicken asses.
But I love those chicken asses!
I love... you.
(both crying)
Your chili dogs didn't get me
through my childhood. You did!
Suddenly this hot dog-covered
locomotive seems like a joke!
Take my hand, son.
It's strong from turning a can opener.
Your chili was store-bought?!
I didn't say I paid for it.
(explosion)
-Mmm!
-Ooh!
-Oh!
-Oh, yeah.
You're a hero, Dad!
They're calling you
Public Elephant Number One!
Well, I guess that's better than
"Local Man Cut Out of Dressing Room."
It sure is, Dad. It sure is.
Chief, why are you letting him leave?
He just committed a series
of serious crimes.
Forget it, Lou. It's Chili Town.
(Chinatown theme music playing)
Why does the moon need sunglasses?
Ah, same reason cops wear 'em--
to be cool.
Gentlemen, I'm-a so tired
of all of the bad blood
between our companies.
Can't we have a-piece... of pizza?
What are you doing?!
You fools!
I'm a real person in here!
(Chinatown theme music playing)
-(crowd murmuring)
-Shh!
Subtitled by Melissa Roland