♪ The Simpsons ♪
D'oh!
-Ahh!
-(tires screech)
(gasps)
Ahh!
-(horn honks)
-(tires screech)
(whimpering)
Run, Daddy, run!
Open the door, Maude!
I don't have time
for the secret knock!
MAUDE:
Oh, I'm panicking, Neddy.
I can't work the knob!
Ahh! Ahh! Ahh! Ahh!
This is Kent Brockman
with a special report from
the Channel 6 news copter.
A large bear-like animal,
most likely a bear,
has wandered down from the hills
in search of food
or perhaps employment.
Please, remain calm.
Stay in your homes.
(growling)
(laughs)
Looks like bad news for the...
Impson family.
Let's all calm down.
Everyone's going to be just fine
as long as I've got
enough beer.
(screams)
All right,
that does it.
If I'm going to be trapped
inside the house
I got to go out
and buy some beer.
(growling)
Now to drop gracefully
through the windshield.
Ahh!
I got you, Dad!
(siren wails)
Sweet dreams, Smokey.
Oww!
Animal tranquilizer!
Ohh...
Smooth.
(belches)
Book 'em, Lou.
One count
of being a bear.
And one count
of being an accessory
to being a bear.
(men grunting)
(grunting)
Oh, Marge,
it was horrible.
We were trapped
in the house all afternoon
and... well...
we had to drink
toilet water.
Well, things were
bad everywhere.
I'm sick of these
constant bear attacks!
It's like a freakin' country
bear jamboroo around here.
Well, now,
realistically, Homer,
I've lived here
some 30-odd years.
This is the first
and only bear I've ever seen.
Hey,
if you want wild bears
eating your children
and scaring away
your salmon,
that's your business.
But I'm not gonna take it!
Who's with me?
ALL: I am!
HOMER:
We're here! We're queer!
We don't want any more bears!
ALL:
We're here! We're queer!
We don't want any more bears!
Hey Homer,
that's a pretty catchy chant.
Where'd you learn it?
Oh, I heard it
at the mustache parade
they have every year.
ALL: We don't want
any more bears!
Sir, there's an unruly
mob to see you.
Does it have
an appointment?
Uh... yes it does.
I phoned ahead.
Mr. Mayor, I hate
to break it to you
but your city
is infested with bears.
And these ones are smarter
than the average bear.
They swiped my
pic-a-nic basket.
Think of the children.
Very well.
I promise swift
and decisive action
against these
hibernating hucksters.
(cheering)
(chuckling)
(siren wailing)
Ahh, not a bear in sight.
The bear patrol must
be working like a charm.
That's specious
reasoning, Dad.
Thank you, honey.
By your logic,
I could claim
that this rock
keeps tigers away.
Oh, how does it work?
It doesn't work.
-Uh-huh.
-It's just a stupid rock.
-But I don't see
any tigers around here.
Do you?
Lisa, I
want to buy your rock.
Woo-hoo!
A perfect day--
Zero bears
and one
big fat hairy paycheck!
Hey!
How come my pay is so low?
"Bear Patrol Tax: $5..."
What?!
This is an outrage!
It's the biggest tax increase
in history!
Actually, Dad, it's the smallest
tax increase in history.
Let the bears
pay the Bear Tax!
I pay the Homer tax!
That's the Home-owner Tax.
Well, anyway,
I'm still outraged.
ALL:
Down with taxes!
Won't you think
of the children?
Are these morons
getting dumber or just louder?
Dumber, sir.
They won't give up
the bear patrol
but they won't pay taxes
for it either.
Ducking this issue
calls for real leadership.
People, your taxes are high
because of illegal immigrants!
That's right--
illegal immigrants!
We need to get rid of them!
(overlapping chatter)
Immiggants!
I knew it was them!
Even when it
was the bears
I knew it was them!
Oh, won't somebody
please think of the children?
In one week, the town will vote
on a special referendum--
whether or not to deport
all illegal immigrants
from Springfield.
It shall be known
as Proposition 24.
(cheering)
Hey, German boy,
go back to Germania!
I do not deserve this.
I have come here legally
as an exchange student.
Young man, the only thing
we exchanged for you
was our national dignity.
(laughter)
You want to
pick on immigrants?!
-Then pick on Willie!
-Willie, please.
The children want to pick on
someone their own size.
Ach...
(eating loudly)
I don't see how you can support
Proposition 24, Dad.
Open your eyes, Lisa.
Our schools are so
jam-packed with immigrants,
kids like Bart have
lost the will to learn.
There's no
denying it, sis.
But immigration is
what America is all about.
Even the Simpson family
immigrated to America.
Right, Grampa?
Okay, you
twisted my arm.
The Simpson story begins
back in the old country.
I forget which one exactly.
My father would drone
on and on about America.
He thought it was
the greatest thing
since sliced bread--
sliced bread having been invented
the previous winter.
See this, son?
That's where we're
going to live.
Maybe not today,
maybe not tomorrow...
but someday.
Later that day,
we set sail for America.
There it is.
Our new home.
Whee!
I love America!
Abe! Supper's on!
We had to move out once we'd
filled the head with garbage.
The end.
Yeah, when those immigrants
get deported
there'll be
a lot more elbow room
for regular Joes
like you and me, Apu.
Ah... Mr. Simpson,
it may astonish you
to learn
that I am
an immigrant.
You? Pfft.
I don't believe it.
No, in truth
an illegal immigrant, sir.
If Proposition 24 passes,
I shall be forced
to leave this country.
Oh, I wish...
Oh, I wish I could have stayed
just one more year or two.
There was so much
I wanted to see
and to do
and to have done to me.
Oh, my God.
I got so swept up
in the scapegoating
and fun of Proposition 24,
I never stopped to think
it might affect
someone I cared about.
You know what, Apu...
I am really,
really gonna miss you.
(whistling)
You know what really
aggravazes me?
Is them immiggants--
They want all
the benefits
of living
in Springfield,
but they ain't
even bothered
to learn themself
the language.
Yeah. Those are exactly
my sentimonies.
(babbling incoherently)
Yeah,
you said it, Barn.
Make the protesters go away
and I'll give you
the entire bottle.
Oh, thank you goodness.
My first customers
in a week.
It's hard to believe someone
so close to our family
could be an illegal alien.
Alas, it is true.
I came here shortly
after my graduation
from Cal Tech--
Calcutta Technical Institute.
As the top student
in my graduating class
of seven million,
I was accepted for
graduate study
in the United States.
Wherever you go
and whatever you do,
we will always love you.
Make us proud, son.
Never forget
who you are.
I won't, Mother,
and I won't
forget you, Manjula.
I'm so sorry
our arranged marriage
will not come to pass.
Farewell, my beloved.
I enrolled at
Springfield Heights
Institute of Technology
under the tutelage
of the brilliant
Professor John Frink.
Well, sure, the Frinkiac 7
looks impressive--
Don't touch it.
But I predict
that within 100 years
computers will be
twice as powerful
10,000 times larger
and so expensive
that only the five richest kings
of Europe will own them.
Could it be used
for dating?
Well, theoretically, yes,
but the computer matches
would be so perfect
as to eliminate the thrill
of romantic conquest.
(mumbling)
Nine glorious
years later
I completed
my Ph.D. thesis.
200,000 precisely
ordered punch cards
comprising the world's
very first
tic-tac-toe program.
Only the top human
players could beat it.
Hey, what's this one for?
Ohh!
So, Apu, why didn't you
go back to India
when your Student Visa
expired?
I did not feel
right leaving
without paying off
my student loans.
Mm-hmm.
So I took a job
at the Kwik-E-Mart.
When my debts were wiped clean,
I was all set to go,
but by then, I had made
so many friends here.
What you're saying
is so understandable
and really, your only crime
was violating U.S. law.
Oh, you are one
of the good ones.
You know what?
I'm going to vote "no" on 24.
Mom, you're the greatest.
Can I have this licorice?
Uh, good evening, young man.
My name is Charles Norwood.
Furthermore, to this beer,
I would also like three
of your finest, cheapest cigars.
Here's my I.D.,
which confirms my adultivity.
Hm.
Hey, Kearney, this fake I.D.,
it is truly excellent.
Say, if you tell me
where you obtained it,
I will overlook
the ice cream sandwiches
concealed in
your armpits, eh?
Deal.
Okay, here are
your fraudulent documents
Mr. Nahasapeemapetilan:
your U.S. Passport,
Social Security card
birth certificate
and your death certificate.
Just hold on to that one
in your safe-deposit box.
Most humble and grateful
thanks to you.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa.
Can the courtesy.
You're an American now.
Remember: you were born
in Green Bay, Wisconsin,
your parents were Herb
and Judy Nahasapeemapetilan,
and if you do not wish
to arouse suspicion,
I strongly urge you
to act American.
(American accent)
Hey there, Homer.
How's it hanging?
Low and lazy.
So...
Hey, say something again.
Oh, you're just noticing
the way I'm talking
to you now.
You see, it turns out
I am an American citizen
after all.
Apparently, I just
plumb forgot about it.
(phony chuckle)
Say, let's take a relaxed
attitude toward work
and watch
the baseball match.
The NY Mets are my
favorite squadron.
Hey, you got rid of that goofy
sacred elephant statue.
Oh, yeah.
What was I thinking
with that?
(accent slipping) Who needs the infinite
compassion of Ganesha
when I've got Tom Cruise
and Nicole Kidman
staring at me
from Entertainment Weekly
with their dead eyes?!
Look at me!
I've betrayed my Indian
heritage, sir.
What would my parents
think of me now?
(gasps)
APU'S FATHER:
Make us proud, son.
APU'S MOTHER:
Never forget who you are.
Don't make
the same mistake I did.
(gasps)
Oh, forgive me, Mother, Father.
I failed you.
(sniffling)
Who am I kidding?
I am no citizen.
Th-This passport
is a cheap forgery.
A cheap $2,000 forgery.
I have brought shame
to my parents,
to my homeland and to myself.
Don't forget Ganesha.
I cannot deny my roots
and I cannot keep up
this charade.
I only did it
because I love this land
where I have the freedom
to say and to think
and to charge
whatever I want.
I want to stay,
but as the real me,
not as some yahoo
from Green Bay.
(sobbing)
Wow. You must
love this country
more than I love
a cold beer
on a hot
Christmas morning.
Darn it, Apu.
I'm not gonna let them
kick you out.
(grunting)
I never should have
bought this button.
Can I have
my three dollars back?
Store credit only.
HOMER: Hey, Marge.
Look who I brought home.
Oh, Homer. Are you
rounding up immigrants?
(laughs)
No, Marge.
Apu convinced me
that Proposition 24
is a big mistake.
All right!
Now you've got
all the Simpsons
behind you, Apu.
That's nice--
although three of you
are below voting age.
And I'm not registered.
I do appreciate
your concern, really,
but it is hopeless.
The latest poll shows
a whooping 85% support
for Proposition 24.
Hey, Apu,
why don't you just
marry some American broad
then dump her after you
get your citizenship?
(touch tones)
Hello, Selma?
Selma, my dear,
how are you?
Uh-huh...
uh-huh... uh-huh...
Listen,
shut up for a second.
How would you like
to marry Apu
so he doesn't get deported?
I'd rather eat poison.
My name's already Selma Bouvier
Terwilliger Hutz McClure.
God knows it's long enough
with Nahasapeemapet-whatever.
From now on,
I'm only marrying for love...
and possibly
once more for money.
Oh, it's hopeless.
Oh, poor Apu.
Hey! The government
don't control the sky.
What if you lived
in a balloon?!
-LISA: That's it!
-Did you hear that, Mom?
She's as dumb as me.
No, not what he said,
what he is!
Grandfather,
as in "grandfather clause."
Apu, how long ago
did your Visa expire?
Seven years, but I don't--
(gasps)
There was an amnesty declared
for people who've been here
as long as you.
That means you can take
the citizenship test!
(gasps)
But Apu, the vote
on Proposition 24
is on Tuesday.
You'll have to pass
the test before then.
Oh, no! That is not
nearly enough time
to learn over 200 years
of American history.
Oh, it can't be that many!
Come on, Apu!
I'll be your tutor.
(ominous chords blare)
Please identify
this object.
It appears to be the flag
which disappeared from
the public library last year.
Correct.
Now, we all know the 13 stripes
are for good luck,
but why does the American flag
have precisely 47 stars?
Because this particular flag
is ridiculously out of date.
The library
must have purchased it
during the brief period
in 1912
after New Mexico
became a state
but before Arizona did.
Uh, partial credit.
Now, they may ask you
to locate your town
on a map of the U.S.,
so let's do that.
Uh... Springfield,
Springfield... um...
-right here.
-LISA: Dad!
You're not pointing
anywhere near Springfield.
It's over here, Apu.
Hey, whatcha doin'?
Studying?
Oh, I'm so confused.
I don't even know where
I'm getting
kicked out of anymore.
Whoa!
Sign's floating
away, Chief.
Executive, legislative,
and, uh... judicial.
No, no, and no.
(groans)
Maybe we should start all over
with the electrical college.
Please, Mr. Simpson,
my brain needs sleep.
The test is in six hours
and many of these facts
you speak of
are completely new to me.
Sleep is for the weak, Apu!
Now I'm gonna go to bed
while you look over
my notes from
ninth grade history.
Okay, Apu.
Stay awake and stay focused.
Cotton Mather...
(snoring)
Oh, no! I fell asleep!
I have forgotten everything
that Mr. Homer taught me!
Perfect.
Let's roll.
(crowd clamoring)
Hm.
Hm!
Hmm.
(gasps)
All right, men.
Here's the order
of deportations.
First, you'll be
rounding up your tired,
then your poor,
then your huddled masses
yearning to breathe free.
Breathers. Got it.
All right. Here's
your last question.
What was the cause
of the Civil War?
Actually,
there were numerous causes.
Aside from the obvious schism
between abolitionists
and anti-abolitionists,
economic factors, both domestic
and international, played a significant--
-Hey, hey.
-Yeah?
Just-- Just say "slavery."
Slavery it is, sir.
Yes! I am a citizen!
Now which way to
the Welfare office?!
-What?
-I'm kidding,
I'm kidding!
I work, I work.
Thank you.
I want to say "thank you"
to everyone.
From this day forth
I am no longer an Indian
living in America.
I am an Indian-American.
(cheering, applause)
MAN: Here, here, here.
You know, Apu,
in a way,
all Americans
are immigrants,
except Native Americans.
Yeah. Native Americans
like us.
No, I mean
American Indians.
-Like me.
-No, I mean--
-(tapping)
-Hi, everyone!
If I could just say
a few words...
I'd be a better
public speaker.
(laughing)
Now that you're all relaxed--
(clears throat)
most of us here
were born in America.
We take this country
for granted;
but not immigrants like Apu.
While the rest of us are
drinking ourselves stupid,
they're driving the cabs
that get us home safely.
They're writing the operas
that entertain us every day.
They're training our tigers
and kicking our extra points.
These people are the glue
that holds together the gears
of our society.
If we pass Proposition 24,
we'll be losing
some of the truest
Americans of all.
-(cheering)
-MOE: You said it, Homer!
When you go
to the polls tomorrow,
please, vote no
on Proposition 24.
ALL (chanting):
No on 24.
It's a landslide!
Yes on 24.
The Proposition passed
with a record 95%...
When are people going
to learn--
democracy doesn't work.
Please don't knock
the land that I love.
(gasps)
Jury duty!
Oh! Today I am truly
an American citizen.
(sighs)
Oh!
Just thank heaven
everything worked out
for the people
we care about.
(foghorn blows)
Ach. Ingrates.
♪♪
Shh.
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.