CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
(whistle blows)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
(tires screeching)
D’oh!
(screams)
HOMER:
Hey! Don't shove!
Oh, man, I love
Oktoberfest.
Oktoberfest!
(plays resonant note)
Sorry, sir, this is a harvest
festival-- no alcohol.
I’m gonna have to
confiscate those steins.
(low, sad note)
Springfield squash--
the most fibrous variety
of yellow squash.
We drove 50 miles to look at
a stupid pile of vegetables?
That’s it, buster.
You just
bought yourself
ten minutes watching that
man make a wagon wheel.
Yes’m.
Wagon wheels were
the Internet
of the 19th century!
Really?
No.
Hmm!
This winning cornucopia
is magnificent.
Styrofoam?
(gasps)
You stuffed
your horn?!
What? Everybody does it.
(nervous laughter)
No, no, no, no-- noooo!
-(screaming): Noooo!
-I can testify at the trial.
Ain’t gon’ be no trial.
Ooh, look! Pine
cone first ladies.
Where the hell
is Abigail Adams?!
Oh, there she is.
Where the hell
is Mary Todd Lincoln?!
Oh, she’s right there.
Where the hell is
Ida Saxton McKinley?!
Oh, I see.
-Where the hell is...?
-Dad, look.
-A corn maze!
-(crow caws)
"Betcha can’t solve our maze."
Puh! I didn’t come here
to be insulted.
We’re leaving!
Mm!
Sure is a lot of corn
in this parking lot.
Dad, we’re
in the maze.
(suspenseful music)
D’oh!
(groans)
Dad, why don’t you
throw me in the air,
and I can see
which way is out?
-Hip!
-Corn.
Hip!
More corn.
Another kid getting
thrown in the air.
Witch’s coven.
Seattle Space Needle.
Amateur production of
You Can’t Take It With You
Oh, I’m getting dizzy.
And corn again.
Maybe we should
split up.
Split up?!
Marge, no! We can
fix this marriage!
No, no,
I didn’t mean...
Fine, you want out?
Then go!
I can make it on my own!
Before I met you,
I had friends and dreams!
I was talking
about...
Oh, please
take me back.
The dating scene
is a nightmare.
I’m begging you!
I just meant we should split
up to get out of this corn maze.
Deep down, I...
I guess I knew that.
Now there must
be a way out!
Of our marriage?!
I don’t want to live!
(shrieking, blubbering)
(distant):
I don’t want to live...!
(Marge growls)
HOMER:
Hey, this maze is made of corn!
(panting)
I’m so sick of being lost.
To hell with maze etiquette!
I’m walking straight outta here!
(screams)
(whimpers)
Damn it!
(moans)
How come things that
happen to stupid people
keep happening to me?
Finally!
I knew we could
solve that maze
using Tremaux’s
algorithm.
Told you.
No, you didn’t.
Your plan was to
burn the corn.
That was never my plan.
HOMER (echoing from distance):
I’m lost and I’m starving!
Eat some corn!
I don’t have
any holders!
Now, don’t worry,
ma’am.
We’ll send a member of
our elite canine unit in
to find your
husband’s corpse.
(gasps)
Uh-- living corpse.
Say hello
to Officer Jaws!
(weak growl)
Chief, I’m afraid Officer
Jaws is guilty of littering...
and here’s the litter!
Okay, everyone--
puppy party at my house!
(crowd cheers)
Oh!
Don’t worry! Our dog
will find my dad!
We need you, boy!
(whimpering)
Good boy!
Now go find Homer!
(questioning bark)
He needs something
with your
father’s scent.
Maybe there’s something
in Dad’s backpack.
A sports bra?
He just needs it for
walking upstairs.
(barking)
(squawks)
(synthesized voice):
This maze is too hard for me.
"To my wife Marge.
In case I don’t make it,
here are my Oscar picks
for next year--
Best Sound Effects Editing:
the team from..."
Huh?
Ahh...
-Dad!
Your dog’s
quite a tracker.
Say, has he ever thought about
A career in law enforcement?
(whimpering)
Um, I don’t think
he’s ever thought
about anything.
Santa’s Little Helper
would be an awesome
police dog.
Can he, Dad?
Can he?
No, and never bring it
up again!
-Please, can he?
-All right.
Boy, it is going to be so cool
when you’re a police dog.
(gasps)
(growling)
(gasping)
(whistles)
(screams)
Good boy!
Now, transform.
(laughs)
Cool.
CHIEF WIGGUM:
All right, listen up.
For the next two weeks,
I’m gonna be your worst enemy,
except this Thursday
is the Fourth of July,
so we’ll take Friday off
as well.
Well, I guess Wednesday
everybody’s going to be thinking
about the long weekend, so...
eh, what the hell?
Why don’t we just take
the whole week off?
Why did you let me do that?
We are so far behind.
(dogs growling)
Nice work, canines.
Bring in the next group.
(whinnying)
(barking)
Uh, should I get this blow
back to the cage, Chief?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
"Blow? Cage"?
You’re in uniform,
Lou.
Don’t slang it up.
It is my privilege to welcome
this fine group of animals
into the Springfield
Police Force.
And now to give your
commencement address,
the most famous mayor of
New York
since Caleb Smith Woodhull,
Rudolph Giuliani!
(clears throat)
Friends, parents, Chief Wiggum.
What?
And of course graduates!
Who’s a good boy?
You’re a good boy!
Look at that tail.
Waggy waggy waggy!
Who’s got a fuzzy tum-tum?
You got a fuzzy tum-tum.
Who wants a treat?
You wants a treat.
I wish someone had
told me that at my graduation.
Listen to me, rook, these
streets are hard.
It ain’t like Air Bud V:
Strong Arm Of The Paw.
Attention all units:
domestic disturbance in progres
at Rural Route 27.
Domestic disturbance?!
You’re gonna have one hell
of a first day, boy.
Squeak ’em
if you got ’em.
(toy squeaking)
You gave that hog
a day of beauty,
and I didn’t get nothing!
Manicure...
pedicure...
exfoliation!
(startled bark)
Don’t worry, boy,
she just knocked
a few fleas off you.
You’re gonna be okay.
We need backup now!
Cletus, you coward!
Is you man or turtle?
Here’s your answer.
Skittle, skittle,
scurry, skittle.
Okay, since the dog’s not here,
I’m gonna take you for a walk.
(yowls)
(sighs)
What’s the matter, Bart?
Oh, I miss Santa’s
Little Helper.
I wanted him to be a police dog,
but now he has no time for me.
I even have to eat
my own homework.
(coughing)
(electrical buzzing)
(whimpering)
Hey, could you
set us up down here?
Easy there, pal.
We just started
our shift.
(growls)
(walkie-talkie squelches)
WIGGUM:
Attention K-9 unit.
We got an 866 in progress
at the park. Over.
Chief, why are you using
the walkie-talkie?
I can hear you fine.
Fine. Let’s not use
any of our police equipment.
So, uh, you got
any steroids?
Oh, you know it.
I can make you huge.
(all gasp)
I want to pump my guns.
I want to rip my pecs.
I want to shriv my nards.
"Nards," that’s what
we needed to hear.
Freeze!
(all gasp)
Ha!
Nobody ever freezes.
Might as well just say "run."
Catch me if you can,
little bow-wow.
Ha-ha!
(snarling)
No!
Nice work... partner.
(ducks quacking)
(deep, guttural):
Quack, quack, quack...
You stand accused of giving
hope to scrawny young men.
How do you plead?
Guilty...
of being innocent!
(all laugh)
(snarling)
Well, I’m afraid,
because of this improperly
filled-out police report,
I have no choice
but to let you go.
Case dismissed.
Ho-ho!
Don’t worry, dude,
I’m going straight...
straight to my customers
to sell more drugs.
(growls)
Listen, man, you
got to let it go.
Relax for a couple
days with your family.
Come back fresh on Monday.
(growls)
Boy, you’re back!
Ow! You bit me!
My own dog bit me!
I can’t believe it.
My own dog bit me.
Now that he’s had
a taste of human flesh,
the dog will be a slave
to its succulence.
Look at him eyeing me.
He knows I taste best.
Don’t blame
the dog, folks.
A cop’s life
is so intense,
he has to channel it
somewhere.
Me, I knit
violent imagery.
Pretty grim, huh?
Oh, I love Santa’s Little
Helper, but I don’t know
if we can have him
in our home anymore.
Mom, you can’t
send him away!
He’s a dog,
not Grandpa!
What if Santa’s Little Helper
stops being a police dog,
then he can get a nonviolent
job like barking songs
on novelty Christmas records.
You can do it, boy!
(barking "The Dreidel Song")
No, boy, that’s Hanukah!
Forget it, kid.
He’s a cop now.
Well,
I bet he can’t resist this.
Fetch, boy!
My God! I’ve lost him.
(Homer barking)
Homer!
(chortling)
Oh, relax, Marge.
I’m just messing
with you.
I know
I’m not a dog.
I’m a people, like you.
(water running)
(growling)
Homer, it’s just Flanders.
You know him.
(growling and barking)
You’re going to live
with me now ’cause...
’cause only cops
understand cops.
Hey, Lou, want to party tonight?
Oh, not tonight,
Sharquelle.
I’m hanging out
with my new roommate.
Oh, my God!
A police dog!
Oh, I have a friend
who would love him.
(whimpering)
Okay, but just remember:
They don’t love us.
They just
love the uniform.
All right, now,
who’s going with who?
I don’t want
a new dog.
I want my old dog.
The one who bit me.
Cheer up, boy.
We’ll get you their
most vicious street cur!
He’ll bite your ass raw!
No street curs!
That’s it!
I want a snake!
Oh, no problem, pally.
Our pythons cost
five dollars a foot.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
We’re not made of money!
All right.
(blade whacks)
He is so awesome.
I already love him
more than I love Lisa.
It says here
don’t bother naming them.
Snakes have poor hearing,
and only live to strangle.
I like it. "Strangles."
Hey, Lis, you want
to touch Strangles?
He’s not slimy at all.
He’s scaly.
Eww! He is slimy!
That’s because
I soaked him in slime!
(laughing)
Why, you little...
I’ll teach you
to trick your sister!
(both choking)
Homer, can you breathe?
Well, I can breathe out okay.
(wheezing)
Don’t... give...
snake... attention.
It’s what...
he really... wants!
I’m okay.
After months of practice,
I have trained my rabbit
to hop in perfect tempo
to Mussorgsky’s immortal
Pictures at an Exhibition.
Now for some hip-hop
we can all get down with!
(gasps)
Bart Simpson, you can’t
bring a python to school!
Hey, don’t
ask me to show
if you can’t
handle the tell.
(all laughing)
Well, I’m going to show you
to the principal,
and tell him
all about it.
(laughing)
Mine was as funny as his.
No one’s arguing with you, lady.
Now, can we
just learn something?
Oh!
The snake’s getting away!
(alarm blaring)
(all screaming)
(siren wailing)
(sniffing)
(barking)
The snake
must be in there.
(barking)
(growling)
(playful growling)
You miss him,
don’t you?
Lou, he’s got
to get over it.
I miss Shamrock Shakes,
but they ain’t coming
back till March!
You know, Chief,
Shamrock Shakes
are just vanilla shakes
colored green.
I taste the flavor.
It’s a very mild mint.
Well, maybe, because
it’s a minty color,
your mind
is fooling your tongue.
I know what I taste!
I got to go with
the chief on this one.
Whoa! There’s
a big surprise.
Hey, Lou, what’s your
favorite thing in the world,
so I can dump
all over that?
(all screaming)
Time for a head count.
Children, line up according
to height.
No, weight.
No, the sum total of the letters
in your last name
if each letter
is assigned a numeric value
according to its place
in the alphabet.
Quickly, now!
Deadly toxic cloud!
Bart’s missing.
He must still be
in the school!
(whimpering)
No, boy!
It’s too dangerous!
Let him go, Lou.
He’s not following
his nose this time.
He’s following
his heart.
Sometimes I forget
why you’re chief,
but I remember now!
You follow
your heart, boy!
Here, Strangles!
Strangles?
(woozily):
Oh...
Oh, man, it’s like
some chemicals cut one.
Strangles, you came to save me!
Santa’s Little Helper,
you came, too!
Sorry, but a boy’s got
to go with his dog.
And... saved!
Hero cop saves boy!
Oh, I knew
you loved me, boy!
Now you can be
my dog again.
Don’t worry.
I’ll give ya a home.
That’ll do, snake.
That’ll do.
Shh!
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Enhanced by Fotokem