CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(snoring)
Chief, there's a sniper down
in the warehouse district!
-Let's roll!
-Sniper?
Ah, um,
well, you know how I love to roll,
but, uh, my wife ordered a new
dust ruffle for our bedroom,
and, uh, she had it shipped
to the station.
If I'm not here to sign for it,
they'll take it back
to the package place,
and that is a whole nightmare.
Love you guys.
(sighs)
(grunts)
Uh, yeah, I got a delivery here
for, uh, Clancy Wiggins.
"Wiggins"?
N-N-No, it's Wiggum.
Wiggins?
That's not even a real name.
What's a Wiggins?
No, really, tell me.
Wh-What is that?
Okay, so you're not
Clancy Wiggins
who ordered this, uh,
Skymaster X5000 Jet Pack.
Jet pack?
Of course I'm Clancy Wiggins,
you idiot!
"Chief Clancy... Jetpack."
Wow.
Well, boys,
justice has a new name--
up.
Uh, Chief, it says here
you need to take
a 40-hour training course
and get certified
before you can legally...
I'm not the police anymore.
I'm the Sky Police.
(grunts)
Okay, okay.
I think I got it.
(grunts)
No, I got it, I got it.
WIGGUM: (to tune of "Baby Face")
♪ Sky Police ♪
♪ Chief Clancy Wiggins
is the Sky Police ♪
♪ A floating future cop,
Sky Police ♪
♪ Fly, police ♪
♪ Squash perps on their heads ♪
♪ They won't know why they're dead ♪
♪ Sky Police ♪
♪ In my jet pack,
I'm flying high above the law ♪
♪ I'm just like Superman ♪
♪ Powered by great big fans ♪
♪ I'll kill you all ♪
♪ I'm Sky Police ♪
Oof! Why don't you take
that thing off, Chief?
It's starting to smell.
What, so you can steal it
and be Sky Police?
Oh, no. No way.
I'm Brigadier General Clancy Wiggins.
Apparently a military-issue jet pack
was mistakenly delivered here
while I received
this off-brand dust ruffle.
Um...
oh.
Well, there's only one
floating future cop
who can find
that missing jet pack--
the Sky Police.
♪ This is the end of Sky Police ♪
(screams)
You were the wind beneath my ass.
Stupid church.
Why would Jesus want us
to waste our weekend
on extra boring, no-recess,
dress-up school?
Exactly.
The dude was a carpenter.
And those guys
like to kick back on Sundays.
(chuckles)
And I mean kick back.
Guys, church is good for your souls.
And remember,
God is listening to your prayers.
What percentage of prayers
really come true?
Well, not all of them.
Like, um, 90%?
God doesn't hear my prayers.
If he did, I'd be at home
on the couch playing video games
in a diaper.
Oh, God gets your prayers,
but he just clicks delete
without reading them,
like e-mail updates from LinkedIn.
I hope no one was hurt.
So no church?
(gasps)
My prayers were answered.
-(sighs)
-Boom.
Don't worry, Reverend,
according to your policy,
your church is covered
for everything but acts of God.
But we believe everything that happens
everywhere is an act of God.
By jiminy, you're right!
We're off the hook!
Hey!
Those Cornell men
at the head office are gonna
be doing the Saluki Strut tonight!
Go Southern Illinois!
ALL:
Saluki Strut!
So we have no money
to repair the church.
And developers are itching
to build on our land.
Fast-casual dining downstairs,
live-work lofts upstairs,
and as an anchor store--
a chain pharmacy.
(gasping)
Why, it's a mixed-use nightmare!
This building
is the heart of our community.
We have our weddings here,
our funerals.
Our fun runs begin and end here.
I will not rest until it is rebuilt.
I can't believe it,
but the church is going to have
to ask people for money.
(groans)
Who keeps putting
pickle slices in here?
I think I can help you
get the money that you need.
But you don't go to our church.
Granted,
I do not share your faith,
but the yahoos in this town
need a church
to deliver weekly reminders
not to steal-- from me.
And not to take a life--
my life.
Yar, without organized religion,
I've lost me moral compass.
Also I've, uh,
I've been addicted to Oxy
for a while now... yar.
Yar.
Now,
this is what I have got in mind.
I will whisper even though we are alone.
All right, people,
Marge has brought this heathen
to aid us in our time of need.
Please do not call me a heathen.
It offends Hanuman,
the monkey-headed lord of winds,
who believed
the sun to be a ripe mango...
Okay, I get it. I get why you say it.
Apu thinks we can get the money
at the casino playing blackjack.
(gasping)
The casino?!
Blackjack's for suckers.
My brother?
He used to own three Arby's franchises.
Lost 'em all at the tables
and gave himself
a shotgun tonsillectomy.
But you told me Uncle Stevie
moved to Okinawa.
What I told you was to wait in the car.
No, no, you can beat the house.
By counting cards.
I myself have done it--
when I was a student at MIT,
the Mumbai Institute of Tantric Sex,
where I was recruited
by a card-counting ring.
I won enough money
to buy fake SAT scores
I used to get into the real MIT,
where I failed every class
and was kicked out
and had to move to Springfield.
-Mm-hmm.
-Mmm.
Am I hearing this right?
Is the church council
truly considering gambling?
You know, Ned,
the Bible never explicitly
condemns gambling.
Biblical folks were always
playing games of chance,
like, uh, drawing lots.
(gasps)
Leviticus drew lots.
Joshua drew lots, Nehemiah.
Even the apostles were lot-drawers.
(gasps)
If gambling's okay,
then I'm getting health insurance
for the kids.
Card counting is not gambling.
It is math.
And it's not even against the rules.
Exactly.
If you are caught,
you cannot be charged with any crime.
The worst they will do
is beat you with a phone book
or break some fingers.
But what is a little pain
if your church is to be saved?
It is all good.
Counting cards requires
absolute focus.
You must ignore
all casino distractions.
(slot machines ringing over stereo)
(all coughing)
And beware of cocktail waitresses
with free drinks
and eyeball-height cleavage.
They're not attractive,
but you cannot look away.
FEMALE VOICE (over stereo):
Freshen your drink, hon?
Who had the Scotch and soda?
Cocktails. Cocktails.
-Another one, hon?
-You, what is the count?!
(stammers)
Get your head in the game, Mel!
Now remember, for this
legal-but-frowned-upon scheme to work,
we must have complete secrecy.
Do not tell anyone
what you are doing.
Not even Homer?
(sighs)
Homer is many things,
but not a good accomplice.
If he gets involved
and this scheme fails,
what happens to our church?
(dance music plays)
(all groan)
Oh, even I saw that.
I guess I can't tell Homer.
I'm leaving
for my fund-raising meeting.
Don't wait up.
Why are you church-os
getting together so late?
I'm asking because I'm supposed
to care about things.
Well, to raise money, we're...
putting on a revue.
Well, you can't go wrong
with a revue.
Skits and songs?
(chuckles)
I'm entertained already.
Yeah, so, uh...
I'm going out to rehearse...
the revue.
Go. Go make magic.
You just go.
(chuckles)
Revue.
APU:
Card counting is simple.
We all sit at different tables,
betting low,
playing hand after hand,
counting in your head
how many high cards
are left in the deck.
Ignore all distractions.
(stammering)
When the count is high,
you have a "hot deck,"
and the odds are in your favor.
Then you use a secret signal
to call in "the Closer."
The Closer bets big, wins bigger,
and the casino never suspects
that it has been the victim
of a morally acceptable screw job.
But use caution--
there are eyes everywhere.
Sooner or later,
the casino will catch on.
And that is when you must flash
the "get the hell out" signal.
LOVEJOY:
What a haul.
MARGE:
Ooh.
One more night like this,
and we'll be able
to fix the church in style.
What a rush--
it got my blood pumping
in a way I thought
only quiet reflection could.
Fizzy water for everyone.
I think we can do something
a little harder than that.
Mmm!
Now, that's a marshmallow-y
s'more-garita.
Homer, Homer, we did it.
(mumbling)
Wh-What'd you do?
We're going to save the church.
I feel like celebrating.
B-But... But it's not on the calendar.
Okay, but if I'm sleepy
at work tomorrow,
I get to tell everyone why.
Oh, boy, oh, boy.
1:00 a.m. loving
and 2:00 a.m. steak?
Night-marriage rules!
(sighs)
I guess nothing
gets the heart pumping
like a church revue.
Huh?
Oh, yeah. Yeah, yeah, the revue.
Oh, I got so many questions.
What are the skits about?
Uh, pop culture and current events.
How do you transition
between scenes?
Hard blackouts or spotlight fades?
-Uh, both.
-Nice.
You know,
it wouldn't be a revue without songs.
Tell me about one.
Okay,
uh, there's a song about, um...
how Democrats and Republicans
can't get along.
It's called, "Cats and Dogs."
(laughing)
Oh.
You got yourself
one hell of a show, Marge.
One hell of a show.
(sighs)
Okay, okay, don't get cocky,
you rapture-waiting baby-baptizers.
You had one good night,
but now the casino is on to you.
They're not going to let you
anywhere near those blackjack tables,
unless you wear these.
MARGE:
Disguises?
I'm worried our scam
is becoming dishonest.
Relax, Marge.
If God lets the Jews
have Sunday on a Saturday,
he'll be cool with this.
Why, I bet the Lord
is pleased as punch
that we're using
that dirty casino money
to rebuild his temple.
Our mission is 100% pure.
LOVEJOY:
Where has this been all my life?
(Helen and Mrs. Skinner moan)
I could be Sideshow...
anyone.
I'm telling Mom
about how the school freezer broke
and they had to cook all the Tater Tots
and the teachers took the extra Tots home
in manila envelopes.
I'm telling her!
You never let me tell.
Mom, the freezer broke and...
-Cooked all the Tater Tots,
-Cooked all the Tater Tots.
-and there were too many Tots,
-Too many Tots.
-and there were manila envelopes,
-Manila envelopes.
and the teachers
took them home...
BOTH:
I hate you!
MARGE:
Okay, Mel.
I'll be at the casino by 10:00.
Meet me at the lounge
by the J. Geils cover band.
Mom,
why are you going to a casino?
Are you... a hostess?
Actually, my friends and I
are using a system
to win money to save the church.
I can't believe you're gambling.
It's not gambling.
It's math.
Is Dad in on this takedown?
It's not a takedown.
And I haven't told him about it.
Yet.
But it's okay
for you guys to know
because you're finally
grown-up enough
to be trusted
with adult information.
Yeah, we are grown-up.
I know how much
to tip a waiter.
I go on hikes with my friends
where we talk
about our problems.
I'll tell your dad everything
in the morning
when we have the money.
But until then, I appreciate
you keeping
this very grown-up secret.
(sighs)
♪ ♪
Dump that money on the bed.
I'm taking a Franklin bath.
(imitates gargles, laughs)
Yeah...
Dear Lord,
thank you for granting us the gift
of rationalization
to allow us to scheme and swindle
so that we might honor you.
Amen.
MARGE:
Homie.
Homie, I can finally tell you
how we really got the money.
(chuckles)
Homie?
(phone rings)
Uh, Marge?
Some casino guys have me,
and they want the money
you took from them or else.
(gasps)
This is all my fault.
Just tell me one thing, Marge.
Why did you lose faith in the revue?
I mean,
"Cats and Dogs" writes itself.
♪ Cats and dogs on Capitol Hill ♪
♪ They don't get along
and never will ♪
♪ Cats and dogs,
squabbles never ending ♪
♪ Even with so much
legislation pending ♪
Homie, how did you end up
at the casino?
Well, I was taking a moment
to enjoy my after-dinner night cap...
Dad, Mom trusted us with a secret.
But she hasn't come home yet,
and we're worried she's in trouble.
(burping)
What?!
BOTH:
Mom's counting cards at the casino!
Oh, if anything happens to Marge,
(gasps)
we'll all be orphans!
(gasping)
I'm coming for you, baby.
Have you seen this woman?
Have you?
Have you seen my wife?
This is your wife?
Do you know where she is?
Uh, we'd like to ask you
some questions
in our "beating room."
All right,
as long as it's just questions.
Reverend! Reverend!
They took Homer!
Why are you still dressed like that?
Um, well...
(chuckles nervously)
HELEN:
Oh, Asphodel...
Your corpse bride is getting cold.
Uh, one second, Belladonna.
Helen and I have found that, uh,
these new personas
have been quite liberating.
Was that a woman's voice?
Send her in.
(retches)
If we don't give back
the money we won counting cards,
the casino people
are going to hurt Homer.
Okay, uh...
Tiny snafu.
I've already given the money
to the contractor.
Then we'll just have
to ask that contractor
to give the money back.
(laughs)
Give the money back?
Hey, Jerry, th-they want
the money back.
La dama azul quiere
devolver el dinero.
(all laughing)
Are you gonna put my head in a vice?
We don't do that--
we don't even have a vice.
We just want the money
your wife stole from us.
Stole?
How is counting cards stealing?
Well, it's not really stealing.
Is it even cheating?
No, but it's just not allowed.
I don't get it.
Football players
can do the quarterback sneak
and baseball players can steal bases.
Why can't I just remember
which cards have been played?
I can't take any more of this guy.
Get the vice!
I knew you had a vice.
I knew it.
(grunting)
I... knew it.
I'm sorry, Marge.
Maybe your husband's suffering
was all part of God's plan.
God's plan?
God isn't some video gamer
up there controlling us
like we were Pac-Men and Dig Dugs.
God isn't Sky Police.
God didn't do this.
I lied to my husband.
And made my kids lie, too.
We did this.
She's right.
We thought we could enter
the den of sin
and emerge unscathed,
but we were scathed.
Those free ginger ales
at the casino,
I-I didn't declare them on my taxes.
(grunts)
I'm going to do what I should have
done in the first place.
Put on a revue?
(grunts)
(groans)
MARGE: Dear Lord,
I don't have anywhere to pray anymore,
so I've come
to your new temple-- here.
Um, I don't know if you watch
us all the time,
or if we're just like an ant farm
you got for your birthday
and left on the shelf,
and every once in a while,
you check out what kind
of crazy tunnels we've built.
Maybe we got it all wrong,
praying for you to give us
things we selfishly want.
Maybe prayer is just taking
a moment to tell yourself
that there is good in the universe.
And I'm going to sit here
and focus on that good,
and maybe, just maybe,
I'll get my husband back.
(gasps)
I'm Doug Blattner,
COO of the gaming
and resorts division
of Stuffers Italian Foods.
My family loves your microwave lasagnas.
It's not my division,
but I'll tell Bill Kelley you said so.
Your unsanctioned religious
gathering has caused
a marked decrease
in gambling activities.
HPMs are down...
that's hands per minute.
IAMs, GDCs-- they're all down.
I want my husband back.
Hmm, let me run it by Jennifer Yang.
Oh, wait, she's on maternity leave.
Don't worry-- I'm sure
Chuck Bennett will sign off on it.
We are going to release your husband.
See, Marge, someone up in the sky
did hear your prayers.
They sure did--
casino management.
(grunts)
You are free to leave
as long as your faith-based
card-counting group
never return to this or any other
river or maritime casino.
-No deal!
-But we don't need to come back.
We saved the church.
No! An injustice has gone on here
for too long!
I'm not leaving this casino
until you stop punishing people
for counting cards.
They're just playing the game
by the rules.
(people cheer)
(shouts)
Homie, after all this,
do you still believe in God?
On a beautiful night like tonight,
how could I not?
LOU: Next week on Sky Police...
(chuckles)
♪ ♪
WIGGUM:
Sky Police!
Shh!
Subtitled by Jimmy Boots