CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
♪ ♪
(snoring)
Hmm?
(grunts)
(engine cuts off)
Hey, Flanders.
Gas up your leaf blower much?
(gasps) Chickens?
Since when do you have chickens?
Oh, about six months.
Well, they've been driving me crazy.
-Get rid of them.
-(chuckling) Oh.
Don't let these feathery fellas
ruffle your feathers, fella.
Chickens.
You have yourself a perfectly good coop,
and that's what you keep in it?
(whistles)
Oh, Homer, surely you know
there's nothing tastier
than a fresh-laid egg.
-How do you want 'em, boys?
-BOTH: Coddled! Coddled! Coddled!
(chuckles)
What is it about boys
and their coddled eggs?
Hmm.
Mm-hmm.
Hmm?
Whoa, so orange.
♪ ♪
I'm sorry, I can't eat these.
Flanders has freshly-pooped eggs,
orange as a sunset
over a field of ripe Doritos,
while these--
Look, I'm just gonna say
what we're all thinking--
store eggs are yellow.
They're yellow eggs, Marge. Yellow.
Why do you always think
about what you don't have?
Has anyone ever thought
about what they do have?
-Have you?
-Not that much.
-Nope!
Have you?
Boy, I won't live long enough
to teach you about sex,
but I'll be damned if I don't
show you how to steal eggs.
♪ ♪
Okay, son, stay sharp in there.
If chickens are known for two things,
it's bravery and intelligence.
This is what we're after.
(grunting)
-HOMER: Got it.
-BART: I got one.
-Hurry, fat-ass!
-(chickens clucking)
(both moaning)
How can idiots say there's no God
when a species
that evolved from dinosaurs
feeds us their unfertilized babies?
Oh, if I could lay eggs like these,
I'd never leave my bedroom.
(both grunt)
-(yips)
-(screams) The farmer!
Homer Simpson,
I am going to enjoy
finding it in my heart
to forgive you for this.
-(both groan)
-Well, there's no getting past that.
We may not be able
to steal Flanders' eggs,
but we can steal his idea.
You mean get our own chickens,
feed them,
love them, and eat their eggs?
Check. Mate.
(squawks)
(hammering)
Urban poultry farming is a great way
to reduce our carbon footprint.
Or maybe increase it. I'm not sure.
But they're so cute!
Now, don't get attached.
I'm about to cut them open
to scoop out the eggs.
No, look!
They're already laying.
Now, what lays bacon?
One... two... eggs!
-(moaning)
-Delicious.
(groans)
These don't taste right.
You're crazy, these are
the best eggs I've ever eaten.
No. No, something is missing.
Hmm. (slurps)
(gargles)
(inhales)
Hmm, Bart's right.
They're not as good as the eggs
we stole from Flanders.
The eggs... we stole... from Flanders!
You don't think they tasted so great
because they were stolen, do you?
Only one way to find out.
-(door opens)
-FLANDERS: My potato chips!
Okay, first, a chip from the control bag.
Now the stolen bag.
(both moaning)
It's true. Theft equals flavor.
-(Homer grunting)
-(Bart snickering)
Ah, forget it. Just take 'em.
You can't just give them to us!
They only taste good if we steal them!
-Keep chasing!
-It improves the flavor!
Sure, sure, whatever works for you.
(Homer and Bart laughing)
I guess we don't need
our chickens anymore.
Don't worry,
I've already found a research facility
that will raise them humanely.
I wasn't worried about that.
♪ ♪
(whispers loudly) If you're going to eat
the chickens, don't tell the girl.
Oh, no, these chickens are here
to advance the cause of science.
(Simpsons oohing and ahing)
HOMER: Look at all those lab coats.
At Exploration Incorporated,
our mission is to help humanity
make the next big leap.
That's so fascinating.
When did you incorporate?
We are preparing to launch
the first privately-funded,
manned mission to Mars.
(gasps) You're going to Mars?
That's incredible.
Uh, yes.
How do you plan to solve the problem
of eyeball explosion
when you take off your space helmet?
Uh, you leave your helmet on.
Hmm, these guys seem legit.
This video will explain
our revolutionary vision.
♪ ♪
NARRATOR: Human beings are explorers.
It's what we do.
It's who we are.
But since our world
holds no more secrets,
we must journey... to Mars.
Government agencies like NASA
say it will be decades
before we set foot on the Red Planet.
At Exploration Incorporated,
we're working hard to establish
a human settlement on Mars
ten years from today.
Soon a select group of colonists
will leave Earth forever
and become the first residents
of another world.
Will you be one of them?
Exploration Incorporated.
Never stop exploring.
(gasps)
HOMER:
What about those Mars nutjobs?
Who wants to take a one-way trip
to a barren, lifeless rock?
Yeah, in a couple years,
we'll have a perfectly good barren,
lifeless rock right here.
This guy gets it.
Well, this mission really gives me hope.
I'm tired of nothing but bad news
about the future.
Yes, but to travel to another planet,
knowing you can never come back,
you'd have to be pretty sad.
Aniston sad.
I'm not sad, I'm inspired.
-That's why I volunteered this afternoon.
-What?!
The mission leaves in ten years.
I'll be 18, and I'm going to Mars.
No way, young lady.
We cannot afford to send you to Mars.
-It's free.
-Cheaper than college.
-No.
-No!
You volunteered to go to Mars
and leave your family?
Forever?
This mission could save humanity.
What if I was the first person
to set foot on another world?
I'd never be able to hug
my daughter again.
They thought of that.
They give a virtual hug machine
to every family back home.
That does look pretty snuggly.
(gasps) No!
I think this could be my true purpose.
Just let me try out.
They might not even pick me.
I mean, I'd pick me, but...
Absolutely not. You are grounded.
You are confined to this planet.
And its moon.
(both growling)
HOMER: Uh, honey?
A word before you continue parenting?
What?
In all my years of living
with the female species,
I've learned one thing.
When they want to do something
totally insane,
your only move is to support them 100%.
Oh, come on, that's ridiculous.
Really? Have you ever done anything
just because someone told you not to?
You cannot marry Homer Simpson.
I forbid it.
-Hmm.
-And now you got me.
(humming)
Oh, my gosh.
We both know Lisa's not going to Mars.
It's just a little girl's fantasy.
But if you forbid someone
from doing something,
they'll want to do it more.
So we should just pretend we're cool
with our daughter abandoning us forever?
Exactly.
It's an old relationship move
I call "turning into the skid."
If you just play along,
sooner or later Lisa will lose interest
in her terrible idea.
You haven't used that trick on me,
have you?
No, no.
I learned it from observing
other marriages.
Ones less fantastic than ours.
(garbage disposal whirring)
Hmm, "turning into the skid."
You know, I looked at a map,
and Mars is just one planet over.
If you really want to try out
for this mission, I support you.
Really? Thanks, Mom!
If they choose me to be a colonist,
I could make jazz the dominant
music form of a whole new planet.
That's exactly where jazz belongs.
Way to turn into the skid, baby.
Now watch Lisa lose interest in Mars,
just as sure as you gave up
on opening that G-rated comedy club.
I thought Gentle Jollies
was a great idea.
Oh, not great. Amazing.
Hmm, now that I think about it,
that idea did have a lot of problems.
♪ ♪
Greetings, candidates.
The testing that begins today
will determine
which of you have the necessary
skills to thrive on Mars.
Think of how satisfying it will feel
to stand in the Valles Marineris
and thunder-chug
a Blue Bronco energy drink.
-I'm sorry, Blue Bronco?
-Wait, thunder-chug?
Blue Bronco is just one
of this mission's many corporate partners.
Because this is a privately funded
entrepreneurial mission,
we've teamed up with some
of America's most exciting brands.
We're talking Mega-Charge Batteries,
Fantasy-Lunatics.com,
Trudge-Rite Work Boots, Draft-Pigs.
And who here likes Fig Glutens?
(excited chattering)
What? The fig seeds
get caught in my adult braces.
Oh, I should not have
given away my dog, man.
Oh, God. Oh, God. Oh, God. Oh, God.
Oh, it's hurting my... (gibbers)
Oi! I can't feel my... (gibbers)
(chickens clucking)
Principal Skinner,
what brings you on this mission
to make mankind a two-planet species?
Mars is the ultimate field trip.
And all they sell at the gift shop
is immortality.
Also, I'm drowning in debt.
Well, I hope to establish a planet
of perfect equality-ment.
On Mars, you are my servant.
Uh, well, well,
either way is good, really.
And then, finally,
I got to spend some quality time
with the oxygen reclaimers.
You must've felt like
the belle of the ball.
You said if I supported
Lisa's crazy idea,
she'd lose interest.
Oh, Marge.
You'll never understand the female mind.
We're just getting started.
What more can we do?
I've utilized my male mind
to come up with
a plan so supportive,
Lisa will never want
to do anything again.
♪ ♪
What are you guys doing here?
We're trying out for Mars, too.
We were so inspired
by you being inspired.
A family unit could be perfect
for this mission.
NASA would never have the guts
to shoot a baby into space.
And your father is a former astronaut.
What an honor.
Last time, I almost killed everybody.
And what did you learn from that?
Lessons, I guess.
LISA: Okay. Mom, Dad, and Bart
don't want to go to Mars.
So this must be some sort of
mind-game reverse super-fake-out.
HOMER: Poor Lisa.
She is so faked out.
LISA:
And all I have to do is be patient.
Pretty soon,
they'll get sick of this and quit.
HOMER: I'm getting sick of this.
I think I'll quit soon.
LISA:
It's just a matter of time.
HOMER: I wonder which one of these
two guys is the one I quit to?
PAUL: We will now test your ability
to handle close confinement.
For the next week, you'll be living in
the Martian Habitat Simulator.
I'll man this station.
(zips door closed)
(zips door open)
Okay, Mom.
Since you're so excited to go to Mars,
you'll be thrilled to start on
the hab's daily maintenance procedures.
"Nutrition Zone Sterilization Sequence."
(gasps) That's just kitchen cleanup.
-Fun!
-No, no, no.
Procedures aren't "fun."
Sure, if you call them "procedures,"
they're a bore,
but if you think of them as "chores,"
they can be a blast!
(grunts) They're not chores!
They're science!
Ooh, there's even directions
on how to properly clean this binder.
(humming happily)
Oh, no.
You cannot like this more than me.
(both humming)
(Lisa hums louder)
Dinner is served!
I rehydrated it with love.
And recycled toilet water.
(Homer and Bart moaning)
So good, Marge!
Well, today I tested nitrogen levels
in our atmosphere.
-They were the same as yesterday.
-More toilet carrots, please!
(annoyed groan)
HOMER: Can't sleep.
(grunting)
My sleeping pod's too small.
They have an expansion mode
for morbidly obese astronauts.
(grunts) Hmm.
I know we're just here
to fake-support our daughter,
but you're pretty good
at this space junk.
Moms spend their whole lives
obsessing over unlikely catastrophes.
In space,
that's what you're supposed to do.
(humming happily)
♪ ♪
(whistling)
(humming)
(sighs)
(grunts)
(pants)
(grunting)
(exhales)
BARRY: The hab study is complete.
To all the male participants,
your monumental incompetence
has sullied and cheapened space forever.
-Now get out.
-Good.
It's a stupid idea,
and I hope everyone dies.
-HOMER: You're letting the Martians in!
-(Comic Book Guy exhales)
BART: I'm keeping the jumpsuit.
Marge and Lisa, congratulations.
You've both passed with flying colors
and will be named finalists
in our astronaut search.
Marge, you're a revelation.
Most of our candidates
are of the egghead loner variety.
Bookworms, teacher's pets,
friendless middle children,
that sort of thing.
(growls)
But you display an amazing ability
to perform repetitive tasks
without getting bored.
Even our robotic arm
gets a little cranky.
-Ow!
-That's two, Lorraine!
(whirs softly)
May I talk to you in private, please?
Admit it-- the only reason
you're here is to support me
until I lose interest and quit.
Well, I'm not going anywhere,
so you can quit.
Maybe I don't want to quit.
Do you realize what a big deal it is
to be a space colonist?
Yes! That's why I want to do it!
I think you don't like that
I'm just as good at Mars as you.
Maybe even better.
Ha! Hardly.
All you are is a...
a stay-at-hab space wife!
Hmm.
Well, it looks like the ego has landed.
You're the last person
I would ever want to go to Mars with.
In ten years.
That's too bad,
because I'm going with you.
In ten years.
LISA: On Mars,
that would be a door slam!
Sometimes I feel like Lisa
has no respect for me.
I know, I know.
I'm finally good at something
and she has to make it
into a competition.
That must be really hard for you.
It is.
I'm so sorry you have to go through this.
Thank you.
Mom's always trying to hold me back!
I know, I know.
I can't be her little girl forever.
That must be really hard for you.
It is!
I'm so sorry you have to go through this.
Thank you.
That listening-to-women junk
you taught me really works.
The trick is in the nodding.
Dad, after seeing Mom and Lisa go at it,
I'm glad our relationship
is about physical abuse,
not psychological.
Me, too, boy.
Aw.
This press conference
was originally scheduled
to introduce
our ten Mars mission finalists.
However, our rivals at Space Colony One,
a division of Pepperidge Farms,
just announced that their Mars rocket
is nearing completion.
We made a solemn promise to Fig Glutens
that they would be
the first cookie on Mars.
Therefore, we have moved up
our launch date from 2026 to...
-Thursday.
-(gasping)
-Thursday?
-This Thursday?
Are you all ready to be
a part of history?
I wanted to be someone
who's bravely going to Mars eventually.
I haven't used
my Open Table dining points!
I'm still very much an alcoholic.
Uh, I-I guess we should leave, too.
-I knew it!
-What?
This has all been an elaborate charade.
You never had the guts to go to Mars.
Oh, I have the guts.
I once went to a rock concert
by myself in the rain.
It was Loverboy.
Then let's go. To Mars.
Yeah, let's go!
To Mars.
-Hmph.
Ladies and gentlemen,
mankind's first residents of Mars,
powered by Simmer-Time Dinner Sauces.
Dinner time is Simmer-Time. For sauce.
(cheering)
They're leaving in a week?
Mom's my only good parent.
And Lisa's my only good kid!
Why won't they admit that neither of them
actually wants to go to Mars?
I'm not giving up yet.
There's got to be a limit
to their stubbornness, right?
FLIGHT DIRECTOR:
T-minus one minute to launch.
HOMER: D'oh!
Here we go! I guess.
Yep. We're doing this, apparently.
I'm sorry I doubted you, Mom.
There's no one I would
rather go to Mars with.
I love you, sweetie.
I love you, too.
I don't want to go!
This is the stupidest idea we ever had!
Abort launch!
That's a negative.
I think you're forgetting
the motto of Blue Bronco--
-"Let's do this thing."
-FLIGHT DIRECTOR: 12... 11...
HOMER: This is not happening.
-Do you know how to run the dishwasher?
-Of course not!
Maybe we can use paper plates!
Where the hell do we get those?
-Mom, no!
-Marge, no!
FLIGHT DIRECTOR:
...three... two... one...
ignition!
It's not a real rocket.
It's the outside of a real rocket.
We did plan to build a real rocket.
And that's one thing
they can never take away from us.
That plan is our legacy.
Then why did you move up the launch
if you knew it was fake?
To inspire the next generation.
And to provide a distraction
while we drove away.
-Then why are you still here?
-Our car wouldn't start.
Mom, doesn't it frighten you
that we almost went to Mars
out of sheer stubbornness?
That's what a mother-daughter
relationship is, sweetie.
A series of near-fatal
emotional standoffs.
Okay, but it doesn't have to be that way.
Surely we can learn from this.
One day, we'll figure it out.
On this planet or another.
♪ ♪
(chickens clucking)
It's my life!
If I want to leave Mars
and move to Venus,
you can't stop me!
(annoyed grunt)
Mom's always trying to hold me back.
I know, I know.
I can't be her little girl forever.
That must be really hard for you.
It is.
Nod-Bot is so sorry
you have to go through this.
Thank you.
♪ ♪
BARRY:
Well, that's one for the win column.
PAUL: I can't wait to find out
what we're gonna do next.
BARRY: We should fix racism.
PAUL: Racism is bad for business.
BARRY: And that is racism's fatal flaw.
PAUL: I'm thinking of an app
that would use the best
algorithms in the world.
BARRY:
Algorithms like that would be great
for this idea I've been back-burnering.
It's an ad-supported restaurant.
You get free food,
but you have to watch ads.
If you want a hamburger,
you watch five ads.
Tater Tots are, like, three ads.
Have you tried these things?
PAUL: I've heard about them,
actually, I didn't actually...
-BARRY: They're good. They're really good.
-PAUL: I love everything you just said,
but what if it was a barbershop?
BARRY: Might be a good idea...
if you're interested
in changing the world!
-(crowd murmuring)
-Shh!
Subtitled by A. Vandelay