♪ The Simpsons ♪
-(chalk screeches)
-(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(tires screeching)
(horn honks)
(tires screech)
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
(dog whining and scratching)
(barking)
(growling)
No. No!
No! Bad dog!
Let go!
Bad Santa's Little Helper!
Stop it!
Not the sports section!
D'oh!
(whining)
(Homer growling)
Stupid dog.
(dog sniffing)
No! Stay away.
This is not for you.
This is Homer food.
(jabbering)
Time to get up, Lisa.
It's a school day.
(groaning)
Hmm, Lisa,
you don't look well.
I'll make it, Mom.
Just tape my lunch box
to my hand.
Oh, my,
you're burning up
and your cheeks
are so swollen.
(gasps) I think you have
the mumps.
I'm calling Dr. Hibbert.
HOMER:
Marge, the dog is hungry.
Well, then feed him.
Yes, master.
D'oh!
DOLL: You're my best friend.
(laughing)
You're my best friend.
You're my
best friend. (laughing)
(jabbering, laughing)
(jabbering,
laughing)
You're my best friend.
(voice warbles)
(growling)
Hello, Dr. Hibbert?
This is Marge Simpson.
Not that I'm angry,
but how did you get
my home number?
(chuckles)
I see. Quite ingenious.
Doctor, I think Lisa
has the mumps.
(chuckles) Mrs. Simpson, much
as I'd like to rely on your diagnosis
I think it might be professionally
derelict of me to do so.
Let me check my schedule.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm, 2:00 is fine.
Thank you, Dr. Hibbert.
No way! She's faking!
If Lisa stays home,
I stay home.
If Bart stays home,
I'm going to school.
Fine. Then...
Wait a minute.
If Lisa goes to school,
then I go to school.
But then Lisa stays home,
so I stay home,
so Lisa goes to school.
Lisa, don't confuse
your brother like that.
Have a nice day
at school, Bart.
Get my homework
from Mrs. Hoover.
Homework?
Lisa, you wasted chicken pox.
Don't waste the mumps.
(school bus approaching)
(horn honks)
(whining)
Hey, Bart dude.
Hey, Otto man.
Yo, hairy bro.
Go home, boy.
Go home.
Blah-blah-blah,
blah, blah.
(whining)
(sniffing)
(crunching)
(bell rings)
(bell dings)
You wandering mongrel.
Get out of my mom-and-pop
operation.
(barking)
(squawking)
-(ring)
-Hello?
Simpson?
This is Sylvia Winfield.
That canine of yours
is in my pool again.
I'm calling
the dog warden right now!
Oh, are you?
Well, you go ahead and call
your precious dog warden,
you old battle-ax,
because my dog
is tied up in the backyard.
There's only one family
on this block--
no, on Earth--
inconsiderate enough to let
a monster like that roam free.
D'oh!
Are you losing your hearing,
or are you just stupid?
I am going to explain this
to you one more time,
and then I'm going
to hang up on you.
It is not my dog!
I tied my dog outside myself!
I am looking at him right--
D'oh!
Well, howdly-do, Simpson.
Getting a little exercise, huh?
Good for you, pal.
Oh, look at this old rascal.
He's a wet old baby boy,
isn't he?
You're just a water monster.
Well, well. Mr. Universe
takes a walk. Ha ha.
(chuckles)
Mr. Universe-- I wish.
Look at that getup.
Heavy hands, ankle weights--
that's cute--
and...
(gasp)
Assassins!
Oh, you betcha. You know,
they got the Velcro straps,
a water pump in the tongue,
built-in pedometer,
reflective sidewalls,
and little vanity license plates.
Ohh! Ohh! How much?
How much? How much?
Well, you know, they're not
giving them away,
but sometimes you've just
got to spoil yourself.
-Yeah.
-(beeping)
Oop. My heart rate's
dropping.
Better skedaddly-do.
LISA: Ahh.
HIBBERT: Mm-hmm.
Discoloration
of the saliva glands...
MARGE: Oh, dear.
Swelling of the parotids...
I knew it.
Yeah, looks like little
Lisa has the mumps.
I guess you'll be missing
a week of school, young lady.
Oh no. I don't want
to fall behind my class.
(laughing)
Oh, such responsibility
for such a little girl.
What's your
favorite subject?
-Arithmetic.
-Oh ho, ho, ho...
Arithmetic. Now before you
know it, you'll be back among
your polygons, your hypotenuse,
and your Euclidean algorithms.
Now you get rest
and have yourself a wahwee pop.
(phone ringing)
Yello?
Hi, Lisa.
What's wrong?
The mumps?
Ooh, the kissing disease.
(chuckles)
My little girl is growing up.
(laughing)
Yuck. Quit it, Dad.
So what does
my little girl want?
What? Let me
write this down.
Copies of "Teen Dream,"
"Teen Scream,"
and "Teen Steam" magazine?
Well, okay, you're the sickie.
Good-bye, Lisa.
Hey, Lenny, I need to leave early.
Cover for me, will ya?
Hey, sure thing, Homer.
(contented sigh)
(smacking)
Well, Lisa, here it is--
the Bouvier family quilt.
(sniffing)
Wow! Neat!
It smells historic.
(gasps) Ooh.
For five generations
women in our family
have each added a square to it.
Now it's your turn.
LISA: Oh. But I don't know
how to sew.
Oh, yes, you do.
You just don't know it.
The memory of a
million drop stitches
flows in your veins.
-Ah.
-Very impressive.
-You try it.
-Oww!
You just need
to develop a callous.
(humming tune)
You see?
Now that's
a sewing finger, honey.
Eww.
Oh, man. Two dollars?
Uh, I'll take these three.
-Hmm.
-They're for my daughter.
Sure they are.
Wise guy.
Huh?
Oh.
(gasps) Assassins!
Oh... 125 bucks?
Sometimes you got
to spoil yourself...
spoil yourself...
But I can't afford--
Simpson! I order you
to buy those shoes!
Okay, Flanders,
you're the boss.
MARGE: This one's mine.
"Keep On Truckin'"?
What does that mean?
MARGE: I didn't know then
and I don't know now.
Here's your
stupid homework.
Ooh, phonics, functions,
vocabulary...
remedial reading?
Oh, do your own
homework, Bart.
-D'oh!
-Here's your magazines.
How many of these guys
are named Corey?
Eight. Thanks, Dad.
-Whoa! Assassins!
-Yep, read 'em and weep.
Those are
very elaborate sneakers.
They better be
for 125 big ones.
-D'oh!
-$125?
-Bart!
-Ahh!
-Homer!
-D'oh!
I thought we agreed
to consult each other
before any major purchases.
Well, you bought
all those smoke alarms
-and we haven't had a single fire.
-(growls)
A manhunt-- or should I say
a woman hunt-- is on...
You know, Joe, yours is
the only show I'll do.
♪♪ (jingle music playing)
As an actor, my eyeballs
need to look their whitest.
♪♪ (jingle music playing)
It's a penalty kick for--
(whining)
(screaming)
(gasping, whimpering)
Shoe lace...
(Homer whimpering)
-No!
-(howling)
(dogs barking)
(whimpering)
Well, Homer,
there seems to be
a lot of good
obedience schools here.
Oh, school, right. Yeah, that's
your answer for everything.
MARGE:
Hmm.
Oh.
(groaning)
Oh, this one
looks very reputable.
-(barking)
-(blows dog whistle)
(thick British accent)
What lovely handwriting. Have a toffee.
Such a neat dog.
Have at them.
Well done.
Oh! Aww...
Now, if I could borrow
Satan's Little Helper.
Santa's Little Helper.
Ladies and gentlemen,
most of you already know
that with a little love
and compassion,
any puppy will grow up to be
a cuddly little bundle of joy.
Stuff and nonsense
taught by charlatans
and learned by bloody twits.
Let me tell you the two
most important words
you will ever hear
in your life.
Choke chain.
You raise a dog the same way
you would raise a child:
with simple,
authoritative commands.
Lay down!
-Followed by immediate correction.
-(yelps)
How can we tell if we're doing
this maneuver effectively?
The dog's eyes will cross,
and his tongue will protrude
and change color,
ever so slightly.
Is my dog dead, ma'am?
Ha ha! You don't know how
often I am asked that.
Choke chain is a misnomer.
Trust me, they are
always breathing.
WOMAN (on TV): Jack, I think
the baby might be yours.
Oh, I'm sure it is,
doll face,
but I'd like to see
you prove it.
-You treat me like garbage.
-(laughing)
That's because that's
the way you love it, baby.
Gee, is it always this good?
Mmm, I don't know.
I just step in and out.
I'm only watching today
because Brandy is
coming out of her coma
and she knows the phony prince's body
is hidden in the boathouse.
-(barking and screeching)
-Oh, that dog!
Bad dog!
Don't worry, Snowball.
Blah, blah, blah, blah.
(cat screeches)
Mom, what will we do
if Santa's Little Helper
doesn't learn anything
in obedience school?
I don't know.
Father McGrath,
I thought you were dead.
I was.
♪♪
There are two ways for a dog
to relieve himself:
One is like a faithful friend
and partner for life.
The other is like a hose
without a fireman.
Which way do you think
that was, Mr. Simpson?
Like a hose,
your wrinkled highness.
Hyah!
Uh, I changed my mind. I decided
I don't want these shoes.
Hey, wait a minute.
What happened here?
Well, my faithful dog
was bringing me my shoes
and they fell apart
in his mouth.
I'm sorry, sir.
Our warranty doesn't cover
fire, theft or acts of dog.
(gasps)
Big cookie!
-Aloha.
-Well, aloha.
-Would you like a free sample?
-The price is right.
Mmm.
Ooh. Macamacdamia nuts.
If you'd like to buy some,
they're only a dollar each.
Oh, so that's your little plan.
Get us addicted,
then jack up the price.
Well, you win.
Property of...
Hom-er...
J....
Simps-on.
Hands off!
(snarling)
Look, Mom,
I finished my patch.
It depicts the two greatest
musical influences in my life.
(coughing)
On the left is Mr. Largo,
my music teacher at school.
He taught me that even
the noblest concerto
can be drained
of its beauty and soul.
And on the right
is "Bleeding Gums" Murphy.
He taught me that music
is like a fire in your belly
that comes out of your mouth
so you better stick
an instrument in front of it.
-Hmm...
-And look.
-Oh.
(lapping up water)
♪♪ (spooky music)
(growling)
Come on, Homer.
I want you to see what
your sick little girl did.
(screaming)
My quilt!
Six generations, ruined!
(crying)
Now, Marge.
Honey, honey, honey.
Come on. Come on.
Don't get upset.
It's not the end
of the world.
We all loved that quilt, but
you can't get too attached to--
(screams)
My cookie!
(sobbing)
This is not happening.
This is not happening!
Everybody in the kitchen!
We're having a family meeting.
We never had
a family meeting before.
We never had a problem
with a family member
we can give away before.
MARGE:
Homer, what are you saying?
I'm saying...
(jabbering)
No way!
You can't give my dog away.
I'll set fire to my hair.
I'll rip up all my clothes.
-I'll put sugar in the gas tank.
-Bart!
I've suffered
as much as anyone
at the paws of this dog.
But when I look
into his vacant brown eyes,
I just can't bear
to let him go.
I'm sure Mom agrees with me.
No, I'm afraid I agree
with your father.
You do?
♪ Ha ha ha ha ha! ♪
Homer, please.
It's not just the quilt.
He's a nice dog,
but he chews up everything.
He doesn't obey.
He's not even housebroken,
and we've spent all this money
on an obedience school,
and I don't see
any improvement.
Alright, alright.
If Santa's Little Helper
studies real hard,
and passes his finals
and becomes
a perfect dog,
-can we keep him then?
-No!
-Dad!
-This is our pet.
We can question
his integrity and disposition,
but we can't question
his heart.
Are you trying to teach us
that the way to solve a problem
with something you love
is to throw it away?
(crying)
Oh, Lisa.
If they're ever going
to pull the plug on me,
I want you
in my corner, honey.
Oh, all right.
If he passes obedience school,
we can keep him.
-All right.
-Yay.
(coughs)
BART: See, boy,
it's not so hard.
Here, roll over.
Roll over!
Like this.
Congratulations, Sonny.
You've earned a toffee.
Oh, thank you.
(quietly)
You moldy old maid.
Homer, can't we place this ad
after the dog
fails his test?
No. We have
to commit ourselves.
Now take this down.
Free to loving home,
world's most brilliant dog.
Says "I love you"
on command.
-(grumbling)
-Type, type.
Now!
Sit!
I said, "sit."
Um, take a walk.
Sniff that other dog's butt.
See? He does exactly
what I tell him.
HOMER: Oh, no.
We'd never give him away
but we're moving to another country
where dogs are forbidden.
You're what?
Oh, sure.
Come here, boy.
Put that prowler down.
Come here. Come on, boy.
(panting)
Say it, boy. Say "I love you"
for the nice man.
(panting)
I ruv ru.
Good dog!
Good doggie.
Isn't that amazing?
See you soon.
Woo-hoo!
A lot of you think your dogs have
mastered the "stay" command.
Let's see if they can "stay"
away from this Beef Wellington.
Now, stay.
(panting)
Stay, boy!
Stay! Stay!
Stay!
(chomping)
Oh, he'd be very happy
at my farm.
People think only mules
can pull carts.
Impatient people think that.
-But patient people know better.
-(yelps)
HOMER:
He can pick him up tomorrow.
Mrs. Winthrop,
I was thinking.
-Ah! Oh!
-Oh, dear.
Since you get paid either way,
would it be a big deal
to just let my dog pass?
I see. Rubber stamp, thank you
very much, next in line.
-Is that it?
-Yeah.
Heavens to murgatroid.
But!
Perhaps I cling to the old
ways like a well-chewed shoe,
as the traditions I was
weaned on are put to sleep
or neutered one by one.
But my time has not passed yet!
The world does not need
another college graduate
who doesn't know how to sit!
He'll sit, he'll sit.
Come on, boy, sit.
Sit.
Blah-blah, blah-blah.
-Pull the chain.
-Huh?
-Correct the dog.
-I don't wanna strangle my dog.
Pull the bloody chain, boy!
(yelping)
(whimpering)
I'm sorry, boy.
You can't help being dumb.
Hmm, what are
you doing, dear?
Sewing a new quilt.
You know, it's one thing
to be a link in a chain.
It's another
to start one of your own.
Aw...
This patch commemorates
the destruction
of the old quilt.
Well, you certainly
captured the moment. Mwah!
Come on, boy.
Sit.
Sit... sit...
Sit!
Oh, come on, sit!
Oh, man.
Bart, he's not going
to learn it now.
Don't spend your
last hours together
tormenting
the poor creature.
Have some fun.
Frolic with him.
Go get it, boy!
(sighs)
-(growling)
I'm gonna miss you, boy.
I thought we were going
to be pals forever.
But we're going to
have to say good-bye,
because you don't understand
a single word I say.
If you just knew how important
it was to learn...
blah blah sit.
Wait a minute, you did it.
Blah blah blah
blah blah blah blah.
Lay down.
Shake hands?
Stay.
-Speak.
-(barks)
All right!
Good boy!
Roll over.
You son of a bitch.
Good show!
(cheering)
Alright. Yay.
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.