CHORUS SINGS:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(squawks)
(shrieks)
(school bell ringing)
(belches)
(whistle blows)
(yells)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
(tires screeching)
(bike horn beeping)
D’oh!
(all sigh)
(glass shatters,
electrical crackling)
(humming)
(chuckles)
Milhouse, watch me
make a loser lose it.
(door opens,
bell jingles)
Oh, customers,
how I hate them.
Excuse me. I just heard that
before Spider-Man was a movie,
it was a comic book--
is that possible?
What the...?
(groans)
Suffering Steve Ditko!
How can you not know
that Spider-Man first appeared
in 1962’s classic
Amazing Fantasy #15?!
(exclaims)
Ooh, 12 cents!
I’ll take eight.
What the...?
You idiot!
Mint condition copies are,
like, $40,000 each!
Must lie down
on pile of unsold Hulk Hands.
ELECTRONIC VOICE:
Hulk smash.
-Hulk smash.
-Hulk smash-smash.
Hulk smash.
(laughs)
Huh? What’s this?
MILHOUSE:
"Everyman"?
He’s not a hero
from Marvel, DC,
Image or WildStorm.
"It was a typical day
for delivery man Avery Mann
until..."
Help! Bank robbers!
Shut your yap.
(blast of gunfire)
MANN: Time for this average man
to disappear.
(both laughing)
Look at that fat guy--
beatin’ it like an egg.
Yeah, he’s scramblin’
like an egg.
(laughing)
-Egg.
Laugh while you can.
NARRATOR: Everyman absorbs the
powers of every superhero
whose comic book he touches.
Power-Absorption Power...
Absorb!
It’s just a flyin’
fatso-- keep robbin’.
Good afternoon, gentlemen.
(hearty laughter)
(shudders)
Put me in Sing Sing!
It’s safer!
Ooh.
Hey!
Hmm...
Perfect.
Plastic Man powers--
Absorb!
Going somewhere?
Everyman will stop
every crime every time.
And I... am... Everyman.
Put my comic down.
You made this?!
Shut up.
No one is interested
in the critical judgment
of a worthless child...
Actually, I like it.
You what now?
Everyman is awesome.
Reading it, I escaped
from my troubles.
Now they’re back
in spades.
Have you shown
this to anyone?
No. If copies got out,
it would be ridiculed by
the online community--
Son of Spock, The Dork Knight,
and I killed Kenny 6475.
Don’t be afraid of them.
They’re just lame-o’s
like yourself.
Two of them are me.
Very well.
I... shall...
self-publish.
How many issues
have you written?
Oh, uh, just 335, including
the controversial number 289,
featuring the death
of Marmaduke.
(Bart and Milhouse
groan sadly)
Comic Book Guy’s been
writing these for years.
Who knew a troubled person
could be creative?
Yeah, still waters
run deep.
(humming
"Eine Kleine Nachtmusik")
(orchestra takes over, continues
(grunting)
I’m so rich.
All right, what’s our next big
summer franchise? Come on.
You want an original idea?
Yes. Let your imaginations
run free.
Something that’s never
been a movie before,
but feels like it has.
-Extension cords.
-Mixed nuts.
-Car keys.
Eh, we’ve already
made everything
that could possibly be a movie
into a great movie.
There’s nothin’ left.
Dad, can we go?
I’ve watched all the DVDs
in the Bentley.
Jonah, what’s that
in your hand?
Oh, big surprise that you
don’t know what this is.
It’s only Everyman,
the coolest comic book ever.
What are his powers?
All of them.
That’s it.
Our next big summer movie
will be Everyman.
Uh, Marv? Ginormous Pictures
bought the rights
to Everyman three weeks ago.
Damn it!
We at Ginormous Pictures
are incredible fans
and think Everyman would
make a fantastic movie.
Oh really? The way
you thought "Stratego"
would make a good movie?
You’d expect us to believe
that a red scout
would date a blue general?
Gu... ffaw.
Hey, don’t blame us--
Brett Ratner had final cut.
I’m well aware
of who had what cut.
(cracking)
(slurping)
Let me get to the point:
It is not money I am after,
or women--
I know that is impossible.
What I want is to pick the
actor who will play Everyman.
No can do.
(sing-songy):
Thank you.
-But we never give...
-(sing-songy): Thank you.
They’ll laugh us
out of Hollywood.
I repeat--
(sing-songy): Thank you.
(heavy sigh)
Fine. You got it.
(normal voice):
Thank you.
(happy sigh) I played hardball
with Hollywood.
The closest I will ever come
to playing a sport in my life.
"Wherever there’s
a crime to be solved,
I will be there to solve...
...it."
And there’s more,
but my fax machine ran out
of ink, so I can’t read it.
Do you know where
you can buy ink
for an Amiga brand fax machine?
Thank you, that was great.
You want to see it
any other way?
Like sad...
or Brooklyn,
or Richard Nixon voice?
Pass.
But I already
bought a boat
with the money you
were gonna pay me.
(sobbing)
Come on, Comic Book Guy,
you’ve gotta pick someone.
We’ve already
read three people.
Don’t you latté-sipping
leeches understand?
I’ve seen enough of these
Hollywood super-hunks.
We need a dumpy, unappealing
loser-- an everyman.
(door opening)
Can you help me out?
I need change for a dollar.
Oh, I also need a dollar.
♪♪
(thunder crashing)
You... are... acceptable.
Great. Do you want
to see me naked?
-Oh, there’s no nudity
in this movie.
-What movie?
Let’s go around the table,
and everybody say
one amazing thing that
happened to them today.
Lisa?
Well, I qualified for
the National Math Bee--
Great. Marge, go.
Guess who the garden club
elected president?
You? Awesome. Next.
No. I lost.
Eh, they can go
to Hell. Bart?
Dr. Hibbert found out my thyroid
isn’t pumping out enough--
Time’s up. Okay, Maggie: "suck,
suck"-- that takes us to... me.
(humming fanfare)
Some Hollywood idiots hired
me to star in a movie.
No kidding?!
Whoa!
Homer, we have
a problem.
Fine. I’ll give back the Oscars
I stole from the lobby.
Do you want the Golden Globe?
(laughing):
No! No...
But we have a bigger problem.
Homer, my brother and I
showed this picture of you
to a cross-section
of typical moviegoers.
Not one thought you
looked like a superhero.
Several people
stared at the sun,
attempting to blind
themselves.
Stared at the sun.
Against every animal
instinct they had.
We need you to slim down, muscle
up and become the Everyman
people want to be instead
of the one they actually are.
I don’t know if I can.
I’m a yo-yo dieter:
"Yo, hot dog man.
Yo, peanuts."
(laughing)
Why aren’t you laughing?
Don’t you know
what "yo" means?
Maybe I can help.
Lyle McCarthy.
Finally, the answer
to my problem.
What do you do?
He’s the trainer
to the stars.
Here’s what Brad and Angelina
looked like before they met me.
HOMER:
Mm!
They look good with a
little meat on their bones.
Come with me.
Take my hand, Homer,
and wave goodbye
to fat you.
Goodbye, fat me.
You sure that guy who created
Everyman’s gonna like this?
Him? He’s gone Hollywood.
...a lot of people have come
to this town and changed,
but not me.
Now excuse me, I have
to read a story
to my adopted Cambodian orphan.
Nannies, produce
the child and the story.
Hello, Prius--
give Daddy a kiss.
Homer, do you
know why you eat?
Because I’m swallowing
my frustrations
and disappointments?
Something bad happens
and you cope
by cramming a donut
in your mouth.
Yeah, well, you don’t always
have time to (bleep).
I’m gonna teach you
healthy emotional
alternatives to eating.
We don’t have much time,
so we’ll do it in a montage to
the song "Eye of the Tiger."
("Eye of the Tiger" playing)
Oh, that song’s
a little on the nose.
Can we do it to
David Bowie’s "Heroes"?
Eh, it’s your montage.
("Heroes" playing)
Whew... This montage sounds
really exhausting.
-How about I just do a
walking around sad montage?
-No.
A montage of me turning
a ragtag Little League team
-into state runners-up?
-No.
Me using funny modes
of transportation
like a hot air balloon
and a camel,
and finally a pickup truck
full of chickens?
Then I get out of the truck
and go to thank the driver,
but then I see the
driver is a chicken?
Let’s just skip ahead a month.
10,001... 10,002...
and... fit.
(phone ringing)
I gotta take this.
Tobey! Cider House Rules!
(whispers):
Total wuss.
Seabiscuit, you keeping
off the sugar cubes?
(whispers):
I hate this guy.
I love this guy!
Tobe, Tobe, Tobe,
we talked about this.
If the rice ain’t brown,
don’t chow down.
Look, I gotta bail--
I’m with Everyman right now.
No, no, no, no, no, don’t worry.
He totally sucks.
(whispers):
I’m only lying to him.
Good-bye!
(whispers):
Bad-bye.
Was that Tobey Maguire?
Hey, Home Town Buffet,
like I told John Travolta,
my client list
is private.
You know what?
Enough chitchat.
Hit the pole!
Stripper up...
fireman down.
And sexy.
Heroic!
Sexy.
And sexy.
Heroic!
Earn that money.
Found this
on the roof.
Well, I think we’ve seen
the last of the Purple Pariah.
Thanks, Everyman.
Don’t thank me.
Thank Captain America
for giving me the patriotism
to want to save
the president’s life.
And thank Wonder Woman
for giving me the boobs
to distract the guards.
And... cut.
What’d you think, kids?
That was awesome!
Although there were
a few holes in the story.
That’s the problem when
you have 17 writers.
But don’t worry, we have
two fresh ones working on it.
Ooh, Homie, take
your shirt off again.
Oh! There’s less
of you to love,
but I love you even more!
Aah! What was that?
Your other hand.
(chuckles)
Oh...
(gunfire)
(explosion)
Cut! Terrific.
Bring in
the next helicopter.
Awesome performance,
Homer.
I smell Oscar.
Oscar, take a shower,
or a tomato bath or something.
Please!
This life is the greatest--
I get paid a fortune,
I’ve got a closet full
of free sneakers and watches,
and I get to hire
my friends.
At least you get to see
my face-- unlike Carl.
I’m being paid
to do what I love!
(chuckles)
A lot of things
come and go in life,
but not fame and fitness.
Homer! Homer Sapian, can
I have a word with you?
I know this is a bad time, but
I’m leaving for another gig.
Is that all this temporary
job was to you, a gig?
Don’t take it
personally, Home Team.
But how will I keep
from overeating?
Just remember
what I taught you.
But you taught me
the only people
who can stay thin
are those who can
afford $5,000-a-week
nutritional consultants!
(quietly):
I’ve taught you well.
Goodbye.
(fierce yell)
He’s gone.
One cheese cube couldn’t hurt.
Ooh! This other cheese cube
stuck to the first one.
Well, that still
technically counts as one.
Mm, it’s bad luck to eat an
uneven number of cheese cubes.
(chomping, gulping)
(chomping, gulping
continues)
(sobbing):
Don’t look at me!
(chomping)
You, you watch.
Avery, I swear, you’re the
only man in Gothamopolis
who’s never seen Everyman.
Well, one thing’s
for sure:
I’m not Everyman.
-(snap)
-Cut!
(quietly):
This is a disaster.
I’m getting a bad
feeling about this film.
The star’s overweight,
we’re way over budget,
and the grasshopperaptor
we built
seems to have developed
an evil mind of its own.
(humming cheerfully)
(curious grunts)
Oh, Marge, I’m ready
for some lovin’.
Come and get me!
(pop)
(yells)
(groans):
Oh...
Marge! Speak to me!
I think you may have
put on a little weight.
Nag, nag, nag!
Apu, I have
to lose weight now.
Do you have anything
that’ll make me vomit?
Well, I don’t know,
I... might have some milk
that has expired.
Ah, here we are.
A delightful
buttermilk from 1961.
(blows)
Oh, ’61-- everyone was
twisting again like they
did the previous summer.
Whatever you do,
do not chew the chunks.
Uh-oh.
Oh, boy.
Cleanup in aisles in three,
two, one...
And... action!
(groaning)
Ugh. What?
Cut.
-Where’s Homer?
-In his trailer.
-He won’t come out?
-He can’t come out.
Ugh!
This film is an embarrassment
of Jar-Jarrian magnitude!
As the writer, I demand
to express my opinion.
Ooh, I’m afraid that’s
not gonna happen.
I see.
Well, I respect that...
and Vulcan death
grip! (grunts)
Hollywood ponytail yank!
(wailing, shuddering)
My only sin was believing
in George Clooney!
(wailing)
(humming happily)
How you doing, man?
Ooh, I think we have
a clunker here.
And I should know-- I
produced Bad Summer Movie,
the parody of bad summer
movies that was itself
a bad summer movie.
Don’t worry, we fixed
everything with editing.
Editing solves everything--
except my problems with the IRS.
Yeah, how’s that going?
(deep, gruff voice):
Everyman...
(hisses):
show your-ssself.
I’m right here.
I’ve been here all along.
(puzzled grunt)
Half the shots he’s fat,
half the shots he’s thin--
it’s taking me
out of the moment.
Like when you’re kissing
a girl, and she burps.
Who was in charge
of continuity on this picture?
I tried to show them the
Polaroids-- they wouldn’t look.
It’s your job to get
their attention.
Nobody takes
responsibility anymore.
Well, I-I just wanted
to get back into the business
after I had my kids.
Yeah, well, now those kids have
an embarrassment for a mother.
Home Boy.
What happened, dude?
You went from Everyman
to Everywhereman.
What happened is, you left!
Who did you
leave me for?
Tell me--
I can take it.
(sobbing)
Okay! It was Turtle
from Entourage.
I knew it!
(wailing sobs)
Come on, Home Run.
It’s okay, Home Alone.
Look, I’m sorry.
Let me make this up to
you-- I’ll train you,
then leave you again,
then come back and train you.
It’s how I make my money.
Just you and me?
You, me and Turtle.
That could work.
He is a great guy.
(whispers):
He’s an awful guy.
You just said both
those things to me.
I’m sorry.
(whispers):
I’m not sorry.
Look, Comic Book Guy,
about the movie,
we know it’s not great.
Yeah, the projectionist
hung himself at the final reel.
But you created Everyman--
your fans will think
whatever you tell ’em.
If you put the word out
that this movie is good,
we’ll let you direct the sequel.
You would let me direct
Everyman 2:
Rise of the Revenge?
Absolutely!
All you have to do
is tell your army of Internet
dweebs to go see this movie.
Hmm, sell my soul
for Hollywood lucre,
or stay true to my lofty ideals.
Everyman, the motion picture,
is the combination
of a life-long dream,
and I was one of the few
who saw that dream realized
on screen last night.
If there is one fault to find
with this
$200 million production,
it is that this is the worst
movie ever!
And send!
And sip.
(slurping)
ANNOUNCER:
Though legislation was passed
to ensure Everyman was
never seen on screens again,
he remains in the hearts
of every man, woman and child
looking for justice,
or just hoping to see
bad people beaten up.
I’m so cold.
(people talking)
Shh!
Enhanced by Fotokem