D'oh!
Y'ello.
Dad, I'm sleeping over
at Milhouse's
and I can't take it.
Come on, Bart,
read me to sleep.
And do the voices.
I'm ruler,
said Yertle.
Of all that I see.
Could we try that again?
And hit I'm a little harder.
I'm ruler,
said Yertle.
Faster and this time
hit said.
That makes no sense.
Okay, we'll do it your way,
then my way,
and I'll see what works
in editing.
Dad, get me outta here.
Sorry, boy,
you know the rule.
Accept the invite,
stay the night.
Hello, Yertle.
Oh, my God.
I'll be on the next plane.
What's wrong, honey?
My Aunt Eunice is dying.
I have to leave right away.
Oh, poor Marge.
Wait.
She said I, not we.
I don't have to go.
Aw, you love her too.
Sweetie,
do you want to come?
With all my heart.
But the children need me.
Y'ello.
Dad, I am begging you.
Who is this?
Okay.
I made a loaf
of peanut butter and jelly.
You just have to slice it
into sandwiches every day.
- Check.
- I set the Roomba up
to cope with your cleaning.
- Check.
- I made a welcome wagon basket
for our new neighbors
from Eastern Europe.
- Check.
- Not Czech, Slovenian.
Check.
One last thing,
this is very important, Homer.
The new season of Odder Stuff
drops on Netflix tonight.
Something to do.
Do not watch it without me.
What? Why not? I have to see if
my fan theories are correct.
I think it's set in the '80s.
Homer, the nine hours
we binge watch that show
together is our thing.
And we don't have
a lot of things.
But holding hands
in a darkened room
with my head
on your shoulder
has become the glue
that seals our love.
I get it.
I totally get it.
I know I'm not perfect.
Sometimes I forget
our marriage birthday.
- Our anniversary?
- Yes.
And sometimes I forget
your birth anniversary,
but I promise I will not watch
our show without you.
Thank you, Homie.
Thank you girls for coming.
Dearest, you were always
our favorite aunt.
Psst, over here.
When she's gone,
I get the P's,
Selma gets the S's.
You get to notify the utilities.
Can't this wait until
after she's dead?
I'll be too busy grieving.
Yeah. Too busy grieving
I got the salt shaker.
Easy-peasy.
P for salt, S for pepper.
I'm walking towards a light...
with a Post-it on it.
Okay, sweetie, here's a book
that can help you fall asleep.
No, no, no. No, sweetie.
You chew it, like this. Look.
Yummy book.
Hey.
Hey, what?
What's this?
What are you doing?!
You guys can't watch this.
No...
You can't watch this.
We didn't promise Mom nothing.
Children, there are 400 shows
you could watch right now.
Many with Ted Danson.
Wait for me.
This show you can watch.
Too depressing.
No.
Must find place to avoid
pop culture discussions.
I know. The watercooler.
- The Semi-Gorgon...
- So many twists...
- I know.
- Set in the '80s.
And the Guffer Brothers.
My turn to talk about
how much I liked it.
Shouldn't doing something nice
for your wife
feel better than this?
Homer, will you read my
Odder Stuff fan fiction?
I threw it over
Stephen King's fence
but it hit him
on the head.
Why Stephen King?
He's got a low fence.
Don't worry, kids.
Sideshow Mel will be fine.
He has an air bubble.
It's all carbon dioxide now!
This is the last time
I buy a trick
from a magician's widow.
Nobody's watching my show.
What with the downloading
and the streaming,
and the fact that
everything else is better.
Now, you're my writers!
You pay us like interns.
And I'm your niece.
- Hey-hey.
Now I want ideas.
Why don't we do another
live special?
What?
I can't remember lines.
At my last wedding
I wrote I do
on the rabbi's forehead.
You could hide a golden ticket
in some candy like Willy Wonka.
The only children allowed
in my factory
are the ones that work there.
How 'bout we have a contest?
Some lucky kid gets to run
around a Krusty store
for five whole minutes
and take all the toys they want.
It inspires buying,
it's easy to promote,
and it's the third thing
someone pitched.
I'm sold!
Let's see what else
Netflix has to offer.
Because you watched an '80s
show featuring a monster...
Alf, Roseanne, Moonlighting,
The Cosby Show...
They're all too scary.
God forgive me.
No. Only when we're together.
It's our glue.
Homer, I'm Ted Sarandos.
Chief Content Officer
of Netflix.
This can't be a dream because
I don't know who you are.
I'm not a dream. Let's just say
I'm a manifestation
of complex algorithms that know
everything about you.
Well, I can't watch this
because...
I know. I know.
Marge told you not to.
Do you know that
she's been watching
Scandinavian crime dramas
with full nudity without you?
That nudity is story-driven.
Yeah, right.
But Odder Stuff is our thing.
No. Your thing's with us.
She's just along for the ride.
The account's in your name.
Come on, come on,
watch it now.
Because our subscription prices
will triple tomorrow.
Wow. I finally finished
something
I wasn't supposed to start.
That is impressive.
I won't even mind watching it
again with...
Homer?!
The lady from my marriage.
My aunt recovered.
Why are you up at 5:00 a.m.?
Still warm.
You watched it.
I finally learn
how little I mean to you.
Wait.
No.
Marge, I am sorry.
Come on,
it's a stupid TV show.
I don't want to hear your voice.
No. We're staying married.
Enough with the rebuses.
All right, I'll just grab my
pillow and sleep on the couch.
No. You'll sleep
right next to me.
Because I want you to feel
the bitter rays
of ice coming
from my frozen soul.
It's so bitterly cold.
I'm fine.
To enter our contest,
write down, in 15 words or less,
why you love me
more than God and America.
The top three essayists
will earn a chance
to run roughshod through
a Krusty store
and not get tased by security.
Whoever fills the cart
with the most toys
gets to keep them free.
And the other two get the worst
kind of squat, diddly.
Diddly? You can't say
that word on TV.
Employees and monkeys of this
network are not eligible.
Lis, will you write
my essay for me?
What, you can't even
come up with,
I love Krusty because
I'm a class clown
and he's a clown with class?
Perfect. And the best thing is
I'm stealing it from you.
Oh, that'll impress 'em.
Go ahead. But there's one thing
I want you to hear.
When you win by cheating,
eventually you lose.
Wait, sorry,
after you said win,
I started thinking
about dirt bikes.
You cheated on your wife,
Homer.
I waited for Lenny
before I watched.
After this,
we've got a stand-up special
from Chris Rock.
Don't watch that
with your wife either.
Quit sleeping in the garden!
Dad?
Sweetie, everything's fine.
Dad, maybe you should be talking
to someone who's older than me.
Ted Sarandos?
Who's Ted Sarandos?
I was hoping you knew.
Forgive me, Father,
for I have sinned.
My son, what are your sins?
Aside from thinking
our church has confession.
I watched a binge-worthy TV show
without my wife.
Was it The Crown?
Don't tell me how it ends.
Doesn't she become queen?
Oh, go to hell.
What am I gonna do?
I don't know what she wants!
Homer, sorry
to blow my own horn...
but Netflix knows your wife
better than you do.
Do you know what
she watches incessantly
when you're not around?
Usually this thing.
Dance shows! She loves 'em!
Want to win her back?
Learn to dance, my puppet.
I have disappointed Marge
with my dancing in the past.
I'll do it!
Did you guys
all let down your wives?
I'm not that pathetic.
I'm just paying $40 an hour
for basic human contact.
Cha-cha-cha!
Hello. My name is Julia.
Just remember
Julia believes in you.
Julia will always
believe in you.
Julia will stay with you
until you are a dancer.
- What's my name?
- Homer.
- No. My name.
- Julia.
And why are you here?
I need to learn how to dance
to get my wife back.
It's been a long time
since a woman said that to me.
Now we begin.
Zoey B, Zoey T,
you work with these guys.
This man needs one-on-one help.
I don't know how
to tell you this,
but you are a terrible dancer.
It seems like you did know
how to tell me that.
But I am taking you on
as my personal challenge,
and when I take on a challenge,
I don't quit!
Okay, here's the first thing.
When you step on my toe,
it causes me pain.
I'm learning so much.
How's your toe?
Doesn't matter.
I don't quit and neither do you.
Homer, you're getting there.
You're aware of when
the music is playing.
Can't dance.
Marriage over.
Will live on boat.
I'm gonna have to do
something I didn't want to do.
I'm bringing in my partner.
Sweet Sal!
Watch me. With one hand,
you can lead a woman.
- I find that hard to...
- You have to come forward when I do this.
You have to go back
when I do this.
As I push my palm
into your back,
- you're forced to turn here.
- I am. I am.
Back straight! Knees bent!
Feet arched! Eyes merry!
Moe's Tavern.
Moe speaking.
Homer? Nah, sorry, Midge.
I ain't seen him in weeks.
What do you mean?
He told me he's been there
every night.
Oh, Homer Simpson.
Oh, no, I thought
you were talking about,
Homer the blind poet
who wrote the Iliad
and the Odyssey there, yeah.
'Cause he ain't been around
since, like, 720 BC.
Another night at Moe's?
Yeah. I'm beat.
The couch.
Quiet!
Okay, Homer, time to do a lift.
Are you sure?
I'm pretty heavy.
No, me. Just grab my waist
and hold on tight.
I'm doing all the work.
We'll work on that.
Hey, hey!
It's time
for Krusty's Toy Trample!
We have three finalists.
But only the first finisher
gets to keep his toys.
Losers have to pay
the winner's income tax.
We rehearsed this with monkeys,
and everything went great!
Now, to take out these
two losers in two seconds.
Dead Grandma, is that you?
On your marks,
prepare to advance.
Commence!
- No!
Congratulations, kid!
And you also won
a day with Krusty!
Day with Krusty
will actually be
day with Sideshow Mel.
Don't we get anything?
Of course.
You two get the greatest prize
any kid could ask for...
Wooden paddles
with balls on 'em.
Mine's broken already.
Use your imagination.
The ball is a rocket ship,
and the paddle is a...
I don't know. Why am I wasting
my time with this kid?
- Is he dying?
- Not that I know of.
Well, then get him
outta here!
Marge, it's me.
I want to ask you one favor,
and I won't bother you again.
There's a dress in the bedroom.
Put it on and meet me
at 15th and Elm.
Are you going to tell me
where you've been spending
your nights?
All will be made clear.
Marge, go to him.
If you don't,
he'll head off to the war,
and you'll never
see him again.
He's not going to war.
That coward!
He doesn't deserve my daughter!
She's here.
You look beautiful.
Cut it out.
Why are we here?
To dance.
I don't know how.
Marge, all you have to do is
one incredibly difficult thing.
Trust me.
I'm here
Let's dance
My dear
Yeah.
What's your name?
How do you do?
What's the game?
Hallelujah
I saw a girl
I've never seen this.
Mom and Dad
romantically in love.
It's like rebirth.
It cures all the wounds.
Bart, are you seeing this?
I set a new record, 89.
Wha... You missed the greatest
moment in our parents' lives.
89's pretty good.
How
Do you do?
I have not felt this good
since I signed Shonda Rhimes.
You're there
I'm here
Okay, Homer, catch and lift.
But let's dance
My dear
What's your name?
How do you do?
What's the game?
Hey!
Wait, how did you get a toy?
It was a thank-you from Ralph
for writing his essay.
You wrote Ralph's essay too?
It's called
hedging your bets, boys.
Hi-yo, just desserts!
Did someone say just desserts?
Dad, it's just an expression.
Just an expression, eh?
I have to warn you,
we just have desserts.