(SlNGlNG) The Simpsons
(TlRES SCREECHlNG)
D'oh !
(SCREAMlNG)
(BRAKES SCREECHlNG)
(CAMERA MACHlNERY WHlRRlNG)
Oh, boy!
Casino night!
Finally, they'll teach
our kids the dangers of
doubling down on a six.
l really shouldn't be here.
l have a problem with games
of chance.
l played Candy Land
with Maggie and ended up
throwing vodka in her face.
Aw, Marge.
l bet you've gotten
that out of your system.
Bet? System?
Betting system?
God is telling me
to gamble!
(PEOPLE PROTESTlNG)
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Deal. Hit me,
hit me, hit me.
Busted.
(WHlMPERS)
Welcome to Springfield
Elementary Casino Night.
My fee for this evening
goes to victims of
my criminal recidivism.
So relax, have fun
and please God
don't piss me off.
Congratulations,
Mr. Student Body President.
Your Casino Night
is a huge success.
Thanks,
Principal Skinner.
l got the idea
from an episode of
Saved by the Bell.
lt was always on
too late for me.
l'll put everything
on lucky 1 7.
(REPEATlNG) D'oh !
Woo-hoo!
D'oh ! D'oh ! D'oh. . .
D'oh ! D'oh. . .
Woo-hoo!
And the winner
is 1 7!
l win !
This is it, baby.
First thing tomorrow,
we're getting
a PlayStation One.
Ohhh !
l'd like to cash
in these chips.
Give me most of it in cash
and the rest in suitcases
to carry the cash.
Sir, this casino
is for charity.
These chips
are only redeemable
in cafeteria scrip
or a day at the ballpark
with Groundskeeper Willie.
l'll be bringin' sparkplugs
to chuck at people l
don't like, like you !
But l'm up $200,000.
Give me my money!
Think l won't
manhandle
a little boy?
You don't understand.
lt's not real money.
None of these people
have won any money.
What?
Didn't anyone
read the flyer?
lt was sent home
last Tuesday.
(MlLHOUSE SCREAMlNG)
Look at me!
l'm a big man !
But l break just
like a little girl.
Well, this was
a disaster.
l should've known.
The same thing happened
on Saved by the Bell.
Care for a milk?
No, thank you.
Martin, in light
of this fiasco,
you're going to have
to resign as president.
l'll have that milk now.
Easy there.
That's whole milk.
l'm a private citizen now!
l can drink what l like!
You won't have Martin Prince
to kick around anymore!
(SOLEMN MUSlC PLAYlNG)
Well, l guess we're gonna need
a new student body president.
We're from Acme
Amusement Rental.
We're looking for
Principal Skinner.
Uh. Yes, we all are.
Whoo!
(HUMMlNG)
Oh !
Hey, student body
president!
Ah ! l can join
past presidents like
Otto, or Krusty. . .
Nelson, you're running
for president?
l'm not saying
l have all the
answers,
but l do have
all the answer keys
to every test.
(ALL CHEERlNG)
Fractions, dinosaurs,
foreign money,
the first Thanksgiving.
Nelson, what
are you doing?
Real estate
license exam.
My ticket to freedom !
(CHANTlNG) Nelson ! Nelson !
l'm doomed.
(SlGHlNG)
l can't beat Nelson.
Why don't you start a rumor
that he's ding-a-ling-a-ling,
hello!
(GlGGLlNG EFFEMlNATELY)
What a delicious quiche!
l drive a pink Miata!
l can't believe Nelson
is more popular than me.
(VOCALlZlNG EFFEMlNATELY)
Honey, you could be popular.
You've just gotta be yourself
in a whole new way!
No. l'm gonna
stick to my platform
of incremental
policy amelioration.
Fluoridated water fountains,
vegan lunch options.
(LlSPlNG)
My name is Nelson.
l use a salad fork.
La-dee-dah !
l wash my face!
Where did you
get that tutu?
Clothesline.
(GlGGLlNG)
And we deserve
a French teacher who
actually speaks French !
(SPEAKlNG FRENCH)
What is she
yakkin' about?
l rest my case.
(SCATTERED COUGH)
Nelson, rebuttal?
Yo, everyone,
it's me, Nelson !
(ALL CHEERlNG)
(CHANTlNG)
Nelson ! Nelson !
(SlNGlNG) I'm not that cooI
I don't wear jeans
I've poIished
an appIe or two
But every
grade that I grubbed
I grubbed it for you
So call me Bookworm
But I'II never squirm
when there's work to be done
Yes, l'll take
my Iunch at my desk
WhiIe you're aII
outside having fun
Don't vote for me
kids of Springfield
UnIess you want
an effective leader
l'll talk to teachers
l'll handle Skinner
A vote for Lisa
makes you the winner
Vote Lisa!
Vote Lisa! Vote Lisa!
Hey, l've got
a song, too.
(SlNGlNG) I am Iron Man!
(PLAYlNG AlR GUlTAR)
Vote for me!
Ah, screw it.
Lisa. Lisa. Lisa.
Wow, she even
beat perennial write-in
candidate "Skinner Sucks."
Skinner!
l'm worried.
This girl is extremely
popular
and thinks for herself.
She's like a female
Eleanor Roosevelt.
Yeah. The students
will do anything she says.
She's captured their
imagination like a bright
piece of construction paper.
Yes. Well,
we've got to find
a way to control her.
Hey, maybe that escaped
mental patient you've hired
has some sort of
toxin in his shack.
Yes. Hello, Willie.
Well, if you ask me,
a woman's weakness
is her sense of vanity.
Vanity? You might have
something there, Edna.
So when's my
inauguration?
Hmm. Let's see.
When hell freezes
over, tough guy.
You wanted to see me?
Actually, Lisa,
l wanted you to see you.
You're our president now.
But you look like
the First Lady of Yawn.
What would you change?
(SlNGlNG) Eyes, pearIs, smiIe
hair points, dress, voice
shoes, Swatch watch
I may be the new girI
But you can't brainwash me
Just OshKosh B'Gosh me
And then leave me be
To fight for kid power
l must be heard not seen
I have to Iead wiseIy
Not just primp and preen
NaiIs, dimpIes
ears, scrunchie
Purse, lunchbox
teeth, Milhouse
This cuting up suits me
There's beauty within me
So let's Olsen twin me
Give them someone to love
This grownup makeover
Has made me a super tween
For they are my peopIe
and I am their queen
Oh, Lisa.
You look so successful.
Like you're the wife
of a businessman.
l wish l'd married
a businessman.
Then l'd have
nice things.
Well, it's a little
over the top.
But there's no reason
l can't look good
and take back
the playground
from the gypsies.
(PLAYlNG FOLK TUNE)
ls our Frisbee now.
Hey, Lisa!
Can l get a photo
for the front page?
lt'll either be a picture of
you or the drinking fountain
that won't stop running.
Make it snappy,
Milhouse.
l've got an important meeting
in the Teachers' Lounge.
The Teachers' Lounge.
ls it true they make fun
of students in there?
Oh, don't be silly.
WlLLlE: Look at me.
l'm Milhouse.
l tuck my shirt
into me underpants.
(ALL LAUGHlNG)
WlLLlE: l've got no friends.
So l confide in Willie.
(LAUGHlNG LOUDLY)
(GlGGLlNG NERVOUSLY)
Oh, that's good. . .
Oh, hello, Lisa.
We were just discussing
Vasco da Gama.
Well, l have some ideas
for ways we can improve
the classroom experience.
We need to get
teachers more involved.
Have them meet with
struggling kids in the
morning before school.
Fine. l'll come in early
to meet with students.
And l'll have
hypnotherapy when?
Or we could hand out
teachers' home phone
numbers
so kids can call them
whenever they have questions.
l've got a question.
You're crazy.
Look, in the Swedish
public schools,
the students grade
the teachers on
their performance.
Outstanding notions.
Each more implementable
than the last.
lt's a shame you can't stay
to discuss them. Here's your
schedule for the day.
"Photo op
helping kindergartners
take off snow boots."
"Move the brush
fire hazard needle"?
Shouldn't l stay here
and work on school policy?
Lisa, you were elected
to be seen and enjoyed.
Don't hide your light
in a smoky back room
making dusty old decisions.
(GlGGLlNG)
Well, l am proud
of my light.
But just in case you want
to do any more thinking,
l'm proud to present you
with an official key
to the study hall.
(GASPlNG)
Use it anytime you like.
You mean l can come to
the school after hours?
Weekends?
Even during the summer?
Yes. lt's like you're
Harry Potter without
the magic and wonder.
Just sign these
authorization forms and
you can be on your way.
(CHUCKLES)
That little girl should
learn to read things
before she signs them.
Excuse me. l was
wondering if l should
read what l just signed.
No. Just standard key
release boilerplate.
Okay.
Boy, she'll
believe anything.
"Key release boilerplate"?
l find that very
hard to believe.
Mmm-hmm.
And yet there it is.
l'll just
lock this door.
Boy, this key
opens everything.
(GROANS)
And then as school
president, l don't have
to take the hearing test.
l'm so proud
of you, Lisa.
What?
You're like Geraldine Ferraro.
Except you won where
she failed miserably.
Well, l think l can
say with all humility,
l am gonna be
the best school
president ever!
(SLOW APPLAUSE)
(SARCASTlCALLY)
Bravo, Lisa. Bravo.
Oh, isn't that sweet?
Even your brother's
adding his kudos.
l was being sarcastic.
You were?
(SARCASTlCALLY)
No, l was being sincere.
Oh, l'm so confused.
Lise, Skinner is using
you like a pawn on his
unholy chess set.
On my chess set,
the pawns are all
Hamburglars.
(UPBEAT MUSlC PLAYlNG)
(SlNGlNG) I'm so happy
with my eviI pIan
Say goodbye to
music gym and art
Soon we will have
the perfect schooI
Where fun and
excitement never start
l'm so drunk
I can bareIy see
But it heIps me
get through another day
My stomach is fiIIed
with haggis and hurt
I've got to go
puke in some hay
Lisa is a fool
l think the rules are cool
I've faIIen in the pooI
SEYMOUR: Mmm !
Not a cloud
in the sky.
A perfect day to unveil
Operation S. L.A.A.A.M.
So Long Athletics,
Art, and Music.
Care for a t-shirt?
T-shirt?
Why don't you just give me
a sandwich board that says
"male prostitute"?
(EMBARRASSED LAUGH)
Forgive me, sir.
(GASPlNG)
They've taken everything.
Oh, no.
(WEEPlNG)
Look what they've
done to my triangle.
(PANTlNG) l'm doing it!
l'm almost to the top!
Hello, self-esteem !
Repo man !
Ahhh ! Ow!
(LAUGHS)
l love this job.
"All extra-curricular
activities are hereby
canceled,
"to be replaced
by nothing !"
(ALL GASPlNG)
Who would sign
such an order?
"As ordered by
Principal Skinner
"and approved by Student Body
President Lisa Simpson !"
(ALL GASPlNG)
And to think l was gonna
ask you to the dance!
l would've gone
with you.
Well, you still can !
Well, l don't
feel like it now.
Oh ! That's cool.
Stupid, stupid, stupid.
(RUMBLlNG)
Look, they're taking
away the art room !
l'll be cooking
my Lean Cuisine
in your kiln tonight!
(LAUGHlNG EVlLLY)
(SlNGlNG) What have I done?
What they wanted you to
Skinner betrayed me
But a tango
takes two
l almost had a date.
l've gotta tell
Willie about this.
(lN A SlNG-SONG VOlCE)
Lisa is a sellout.
Lisa, what's
a sellout?
With the band gone,
how will l know
who to beat up?
They eliminated
English for Fat Kids!
Okay, you'll do!
Lise, you made this
school even worse.
And it wasn't exactly
San Diego State
to begin with.
They made me
pretty and popular
just so they could
exploit me and ruin
my good name.
Lisa, you've got to
stand up to these guys.
And when you do,
people will
remember you.
Just look at these
postage stamps.
There's Bugs Bunny,
Fat Elvis,
Autumn in New England,
Bats of the Southwest,
all heroes.
Do you want to see
Elvis kiss a bat?
(MlMlCKlNG ELVlS PRESLEY)
Hey, baby, come here.
l want to kiss you.
(KlSSlNG) Squeak, squeak!
No, don't kiss me.
You tricked me
into betraying my
fellow students!
Lisa, student government
is meaningless.
Look at your constitution.
lt's written on the back
of a place mat.
And not a good place mat.
lt's from someplace called
"Doodles."
l see.
Principal Skinner, may l make
an announcement to the school?
l can't see the harm.
l hereby resign
as your president.
And for my last act l call
a general student strike
effective immediately!
Gimme that!
Any student caught striking
will be severely disciplined
unless all of you do it.
Then l'm stymied.
(CHANTlNG) Strike!
Strike! Strike!
Lisa, please help me
lure them back.
l had to do what l did.
Our budget is stretched
tighter than Mother's
sauna pants.
Seymour!
Quit using me
in analogies.
Yes, Mother.
Principal Skinner, l will not
call off this strike until
you bring back music and art!
What about gym?
Meh.
(CHANTlNG) Hey, hey,
Seymour S. Nurture
our well-roundedness!
Sneeze, puke, burp, fart,
we want music, gym, and art!
Why didn't l cancel
Sign Making and
Creative Chanting?
Principal Skinner,
can't you just
reinstate those programs?
Would you be willing
to pay an extra $1 .23
in taxes to fund them?
No way!
l'm saving for
a speedboat.
(CHANTlNG) Strike! Strike!
Lisa, what are you doing?
This is the kind
of trouble-making
l expect from your brother.
You do? Cool.
A blank check
for mayhem.
Mom, l was elected
to make this a better school.
Well, couldn't you just
hang some colorful
crepe paper in the gym?
They've taken away
our crepe paper.
Those Fudruckers!
(SlRENS WAlL)
Oh, no.
They heard me.
Remember, boys.
These are little kids.
So take out
your tiny batons.
(CHUCKLES)
Chief Wiggum,
we're just like
you policemen.
Don't you ever
feel like the mayor
doesn't care about you?
You mean, the mayor
who kept me waiting for
two hours in that restaurant?
l ate so much bread. . .
(SOBS SOFTLY)
Sit down, boys!
We're joining
this strike!
Chief, are you sure the mayor
wasn't at a different
Olive Garden than you?
Well, l can't take that
rattlesnake out of his
mailbox now, now can l?
Yes, Chief,
you could.
Well, let me ask
you this. Shut up.
The Springfield student strike
has entered its fourth day
with no end in sight.
Today professionaI
buttinski Michael Moore
arrived on the scene.
Kids who don't get
to take music and art
are 1 0% more IikeIy
to become chronicaIIy
unempIoyed
and appear in one
of my movies.
Where did you get
that statistic?
Your mother!
The student strikers
have been joined
by other unions
incIuding the
Springfield Goat Milkers,
the Association of
News Room Cue
Card Holders...
Ow.
And the United Federation
of Theme Park Zombies.
Zombie eat brains but zombie
cannot swaIIow this injustice.
At the heart of the strike
is former student body
president, Lisa Simpson.
Her brother
had this to say.
Lisa is a nut.
She has a rubber butt.
Every time she turns around,
it goes putt putt.
lndeed. But that rubber butt
doesn't have much time for
turning around these days.
It's pointed squareIy
in the face of the
administration.
Skinner! We have
got to get these
kids back in school !
Willie, can't you
turn your hose on them?
They are wee children.
l'd sooner turn it on myself.
Well, that's a
good idea, too.
Now see here,
you nose-wiping
hair-combers!
Back in Edinburgh,
we had a coal
miner's strike.
All we wanted were hats
with a wee light on top.
Then one day
the mine collapsed.
No one made it out alive.
Not even Willie!
Skinner!
l don't mean to interrupt
your advice from the janitor,
but l say cut off the head
and the body will die.
You want to get rid of Lisa?
But she's such a good student.
Yes. ln fact, l think
she's a little too
good for this school.
If we stand together,
we are strong!
(ALL CHEERlNG)
Lisa Simpson, you have
just been transferred
to the Springfield
Magnet School for the
Gifted and Troublesome.
Please climb
into the idIing bus.
But, but l. . .
(SlNGlNG) Poor Lisa
Poor Lisa
Don't cry for me
kids of Springfield
You can still reach me
through e-maiI
at Smart Girl 63
underscore back slash
at Yahoo dot com,
at Yahoo dot com
(SPEAKlNG FRENCH)
Oh, this place
is paradise!
Well, l guess this story
has a happy ending after all.
Just like my last massage.
l'm not driving
45 minutes a day!
You can't go
to that school !
But this is my dream.
Oh, why can't you
have a normal dream
like being an Olympic
figure skater?
Okay. Let me
take figure skating.
Are you crazy?
l'm not getting up
at 6:30 every morning
so you can prance around
a frozen pond and think
you're better than me.
LlSA: Well,
what can l be?
HOMER: l don't know.
How about
a horse whisperer?
LlSA: Okay!
HOMER: Over my dead body!
English - US - PSDH