♪ The Simpsons ♪
(chalk screeches)
(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(tires screeching)
(horn honks)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
MARGE: "Barnacle Bill's
Home Pregnancy Test"?
Homer, shouldn't we have
gone with a better-known brand?
But Marge, this one came
with a free corncob pipe.
Okay, let's see.
"Ahoy, mateys.
"If the water turns blue,
a baby for you.
"If purple ye see,
no baby thar be."
Well, what color is it--
blue or purple?
-Pink.
-D'oh!
"If ye test should fail
to a doctor set sail."
Well, I guess I better
go see Dr. Hibbert.
Oh, honey,
do you really think
you're pregnant?
Well, I have the same nausea
and craving for pancake mix
I did with the other kids.
Yeah, and I have the same
tightness in my chest
and profuse sweating
I always get.
Well, I'll let you know.
Hey, Homer, how come mom's
going to the doctor?
-Is anything wrong?
-No, everything's fine.
Your mother, uh...
just broke her leg.
-What?
-I smell a bun in the oven.
Is Mom going
to have another baby, Dad?
Maybe.
-Whoa!
-Hey, all right!
Way to go!
You're a machine, Homer.
Did you hear that,
Maggie?
Another baby
in the house.
Oh, cool.
We can race 'em.
Sure, for you, a baby's
all fun and games.
For me, it's diaper changes
and midnight feedings.
Doesn't Mom do that stuff?
Yeah, but I have
to hear about it.
Were you like this
when Mom was pregnant with me?
Actually Bart, I threw up
more than your mother.
It all happened at the beginning
of that turbulent decade
known as the '80s.
Those were idealistic days--
the candidacy of John Anderson,
the rise of Supertramp.
It was an exciting time
to be young.
♪ When I was young ♪
♪ It seemed that life
was so wonderful ♪
For several years
I'd been dating your mother
and working at
the local fun center.
Homer, you turn
the blades too fast.
The golfers
are complaining. Slow down!
That's better.
Ah, beautiful.
Keep this up,
and someday
you'll be the guy
who hands out
the putters.
Yes, sir!
I was 24 years old
with a beautiful girlfriend
and a job with a future.
Hey! You're supposed
to be listening to my story!
I thought it was over.
You had a problem
turning blades.
You overcame it.
The feel-good story of the year.
It's not our fault
our generation
has short
attention spans, Dad.
We watch
an appalling amount of TV.
Don't you ever, ever,
talk that way about television.
Lousy, ungrateful
can't-keep-their,
what-do-you-call-it...
minds on any, uh...
Where do you think
you're going?
You're going to listen
to my story.
Your mother was living
with her two wicked sisters.
MRS. BOUVIER: Okay, girls,
you can smoke now.
Mmm.
Oh, yeah.
(horn honks)
It's Homer!
I don't know
what you see
in that ugly meatball.
Uh-huh. If you like being pawed
by something fat and lazy,
we could get a cat.
It would leave less
hair on the couch.
(laughing)
MARGE: You don't know Homer
like I do.
He's sensitive and sweet.
(horn honks)
HOMER: Marge,
get your butt out here!
-(honking)
-(groans)
Homer, do you ever think
about the future?
You mean like will apes
be our masters?
No, I mean how you
plan to earn a living.
I can't imagine that your job
of yours is very stimulating.
But it gives me
time to think.
What do you think about?
Well, girls.
I mean boys!
I mean you.
I think about you too.
Wow, what an ending.
Who would have thought
Darth Vader was
Luke Skywalker's father?
(clamoring)
Well, thank you,
Mr. Blow-The-Picture-for-Me.
Marge, you're as pretty
as Princess Leia
and as smart as Yoda.
Oh, Homer.
-Mmm.
♪ You light up my days ♪
♪ And fill my nights ♪
♪ With song ♪
♪ It can't be wrong ♪
♪ When it feels so good ♪
-♪ Right ♪
(giggling)
♪ 'Cause you... ♪
-You.
-No, you.
(smooching)
♪ You light up my life ♪
Our song.
I bet the guy
she was singing that about
was real happy.
Actually, she was singing
about God.
Oh, well,
he's always happy.
No, wait,
he's always mad.
Someday I'll buy you
a real castle.
You don't have
to do that.
Whoo, good.
Homer, maybe
it's the Champale talking,
but I think
you're pretty sexy.
Really?
It must be
the Champale talking.
MARGE: Oh, Homer,
what if we get caught?
HOMER: Don't worry.
This castle
is impregnable.
(alarms and buzzers sound)
Pass the cookie dough.
MAN (on TV): Dust off your
hula skirts, Angels.
I'm afraid there's
been a murder. In Hawaii.
WOMAN:
Hawaii it is, Charlie.
(barking and howling)
(phone rings)
Hello?
Oh, hi, Marge.
I need you to drive me
to the doctor, Homer.
Why, what's wrong?
Well...
that unforgettable night we...
joined The Castle Club.
Oh...
Well, Miss Bouvier.
I think we
found the reason
why you've been throwing up
in the morning.
Congratulations.
(echoing)
D'oh!
Poor guy.
Perhaps this pamphlet
will prove helpful.
MARGE:
"So you've ruined your life."
Mmm.
Son, you've got
to marry that girl.
Because it's the
honorable thing to do?
No! Because you'll never
do any better.
(giggling)
You lucky bum.
The fish jumped
right in the boat.
All you got to do
is whack her with the oar.
Marge, there's something
I want to ask you
but I'm afraid
because if you say "no"
it'll destroy me
and make me a criminal.
Well, I haven't said
"no" to you lately, have I?
Marge, I...
Damn it,
where's that card?
What card?
I wrote down what I was
gonna say on a card.
Stupid thing must have
fallen out of my pocket.
-(grunting)
-(horn honks)
-Is this it?
-What's it say?
"Marge, from the first
moment I saw you
"I never wanted to be
with anyone else.
"I don't have much to offer you
except all my love.
Will you marry me?"
That's the card.
Give it here.
Oh, Homer...
This is the most beautiful
moment of my life.
So, will you marry me?
Yes!
Whoo-hoo! Whoo-hoo!
Yeah, she's gonna marry me!
In your face, everybody!
-Whoo-hoo!
-(car horn blares)
Dad, if the new baby
is a girl,
can we name her Ariel?
I'm sorry,
the baby's name will be
Kool Moe Dee Simpson.
-Ariel.
-Kool Moe Dee.
You know, I had this
very same discussion
with your mother
ten years ago.
MARGE:
Homer, I've been thinking.
If the baby's a boy,
what do you think
of the name Larry?
Marge! We can't do that.
All the kids
will call him Larry Fairy.
Well, how about Louis?
They'll call him
Screwy Louie.
-Bob?
-Slob.
-Luke?
-Puke.
-Marcus?
-Mucous.
What about Bart?
Let's see...
Bart, cart, dart,
eeyart...
Nope. Can't see
any problem with that.
Wow. I'll take that ring.
Yes, sir.
And how will you be paying for it?
I don't know.
HOMER:
Finally, the big day came.
We didn't have much money
so we went to
a quaint little chapel
just across the state line.
WOMAN:
Basic ceremony is 20 bucks.
Here's your license.
Be sure to get this punched
every time.
The tenth wedding
is on the house.
Hey, this marriage is
gonna last forever.
No matter how many times
I hear that
it always makes me laugh.
Cletus, do you take Aileen
to be your lawful wedded wife?
-Yup.
-Done. Next.
♪♪ (cheesy keyboard playing
"Here Comes the Bride")
There certainly are
a lot of stains
on the ceiling.
Marge, I'm sorry.
I wish I could afford
a better place.
Homer, I'd be lying if I said
that this is how
I pictured my wedding day,
but you are
how I pictured my husband.
-I am?
-Well, you may not look
like Ted Bessell
but you're just as nice.
Ohhh.
Dearly beloved, we are
gathered here in the sight of God
and this casino
to join...
-Homer.
-and...
Marge.
In holy matrimony.
Beautiful.
Do you, Marjorie Bouvier,
take Homer J. Simpson
to be your
lawful wedded husband?
I do.
Homer, same question,
names reversed.
I do.
Then, by the power vested in me
by the state gaming commission
I pronounce you
man and wife.
Here's $10 worth of chips.
You may kiss the bride.
Next!
Mmm. What a perfect day.
(sighs)
Our first night together
as man and wife.
Mmm...
PATTY: Hey, love birds,
keep it down.
Look what I got, Marge.
A baby monitor.
Baby to Marge.
Wah! Wah! Over.
Homer, I don't know how
we can afford all these things
on your salary.
Hey, why don't I apply
at the nuclear power plant?
I hear they pay pretty well.
I don't know.
I heard radiation
can make you sterile.
Now you tell me.
We only have
two openings
so I'm afraid one of you
will have to go home
empty-handed--
(sighs) but it won't be
my old frat buddy
Lou Collier.
How you doing,
you old Alpha Tau?
Smithers,
you keg-meister, you.
BOTH: Uh-huh-huh, hey.
Well, hey,
I'm from the Alabama chapter.
Well, I'll be.
(laughing)
Oh well. Let's get on
with the testing.
♪ Roll on, roll on,
Alpha Tau ♪
♪ Tau... ♪
♪ Bow-wow-wow-wow ♪
♪ Bow-wow-wow-wow... ♪
If I didn't know better,
I'd swear he was trying
to moon us.
What would each of you say
is your worst quality?
Well, I am a workaholic.
I push myself too hard.
Well, it takes me a long time
to learn anything.
-I'm kind of a goof-off--
-Okay, that will do.
Little stuff starts
disappearing
-from the workplace...
-That's enough!
Next, there's a problem
with the reactor.
What do you do?
There's a problem
with the reactor?!
We're all gonna die!
(screaming)
MARGE:
Mmm... mmm...
Did you get the job?
Nah, they wanted
someone good.
Story of my life.
Oh, Homie.
Hey, come over here
and feel our baby kicking.
Wow.
Kid, I won't let you down.
I swear to you.
When you come out of there
the first thing
you're gonna see
is a man with a good job.
Yeah. The doctor.
(laughing)
♪ Working 9 to 5 ♪
♪ What a way
to make a living ♪
And when ye tallow hardens,
we remove it from yon mold.
(sobbing)
What a crappy candle.
You've ruined our vacation.
You, gentle sir, are fired.
Oh!
♪ Barely gettin' by ♪
♪ It's all taking
and no giving ♪
Oh, hello, young man.
Good evening, Madam.
You have been selected by
the good people of Slashco
to reap the benefits
of their new never-dull
knife edge.
Here. Shake hands
with the Slashco.
(screaming)
Handle first, handle first.
♪ They just use your mind ♪
♪ And they never
give you credit ♪
Hmm.
(screaming)
I quit! I quit!
I thought you said
you liked dogs.
♪ It's enough to drive you
crazy if you let it ♪
Hey! Who wants
to get rich today?
-ALL: Me! Me!
-Me!
Me! Me! Me!
I said it first.
First, let me assure you
that this is not
one of those shady
pyramid schemes
you've been
hearing about.
No sir. Our model
is the trapezoid
that guarantees each investor
an 800% return
-within hours of your initial--
-(siren blaring)
Uh-oh! The cops!
"Fourth notice."
"90 days overdue."
"We break thumbs."
Homer, what are we
going to do?
-(doorbell rings)
-I don't know. I don't know.
Repo man. I'm here
for the baby's things.
Crib, mobile, monitor--
Oh, and the lady's ring,
I'm afraid.
(gasps)
Oh, dear.
Repossessing stuff is
the hardest part of my job.
Dear Marge,
By the time you read this,
I will be gone.
You deserve all the finest
things in the world,
and although
I can give them to you,
they will be repossessed
and I will be hunted down
like a dog.
Also, it has become clear
that your family
doesn't want me here.
MRS. BOUVIER: Shut up with that
pen scratching down there.
I will send you every cent
I earn for the baby
but you will not see me again
until I am a man.
(sobbing)
That is so sad.
Oh, come on, honey.
You know how it turns out.
After all,
you wouldn't be here today
if I hadn't become
the responsible head
of a household.
Hey Homer,
can we have a can of
frosting for lunch?
Okay.
"You will not see me again
until I am a man."
(sobbing)
Oh, Homer...
Homer!
There, there, dear.
We're all in shock.
I thought he'd two-time you
for a while first.
(gagging and choking)
This taco is
full of hair.
Uh-huh.
There's your
explanation.
(loud slurping)
-Ahhhh!
-Shall we tell Marge where he is?
Nah, let her read about it
in the society page.
Homer?! Oh...
Marge, listen,
we just saw--
-Don't be stupid.
-(grunts)
HOMER:
Dear Marge, XXX
Homer.
Big shots with their
stainless steel lunch boxes.
(honks horn)
(gasps)
They get doughnuts!
That's right.
All the colors
of the rainbow.
Wow.
Marge, what are
you doing up?
You need your rest, dear.
I heard a noise outside,
and thought it might be Homer.
Ay!
What the hell.
Marge, I've got
2 1/2 words for you.
Gulp 'n Blow.
Yeah, what do you want?
My husband by my side.
You want fries with that?
Homer?!
Marge?!
-Homer!
-Marge!
Holy cow, you're
as big as a house!
Homer, come home with me.
No, Marge,
I just can't.
I mean, look at me.
I'm a trainee.
They won't even tell me
what's in the secret sauce.
And I can't buy you
a decent wedding ring.
Any ring is fine,
as long as it's from you.
Marge...
Pour vous.
Oh!
Would you mind
if I took it off now?
The oil
is burning my finger.
Oh, sure.
Homer, do you know
why I married you?
'Cause I knocked you up?
No, because I love you.
Come home soon.
(growling)
MR. BURNS:
That's it...
That's it... come closer...
(laughing wickedly)
Ironic, isn't it?
The hunter
has become the hunted.
(laughing)
Oh, God, Smithers
I feel so alive!
You the boss?
-Yes.
-I'll call security, sir.
Well, listen to me,
Mr. Big Shot,
if you're looking
for the kind of employee
who takes abuse and never
sticks up for himself,
I'm your man!
You can treat me
like dirt and
I'll still kiss your butt
and call it ice cream!
And if you don't like it,
I can change!
Hold the phone, Smithers.
I like your attitude.
Feisty, yet spineless.
Sir, this man not only
failed the aptitude test
he got trapped
in a closet on his way out.
I don't care. I haven't
been this impressed
since I first laid eyes
on a young bootlick
named Wayland Smithers.
-You mean...?
-Welcome aboard, son.
I got the job.
I got the job!
Whoo hoo!
Only in America
could I get a job.
Who was that
young hellcat, Smithers?
-Homer Simpson, sir.
-Simpson, eh?
I'll remember that name.
Marge, Marge!
You're a little late.
She's gone
to the hospital.
The hospital?!
I'll drive you.
Thanks, Mom.
Don't ever call me that.
Marge! Marge,
where's the baby?
Right where you
left it.
-Shut up.
-Hey listen, fat boy--
No, you listen.
This is my wife,
and this is my kid,
and I'm paying for
this delivery.
So if you wanna stay
you better give me some respect.
Homer, does this mean...?
Starting tomorrow,
I'm a nuclear technician!
Good God!
And tomorrow morning,
I'm gonna buy your ring back,
then I'm going house hunting.
Doesn't your job
start tomorrow?
Somebody will
cover for me.
Homer, that's-- Oh!
Step aside.
I'll deliver this baby.
Why don't you
let me handle it, Homer.
Oh, a college boy, eh?
Homer, for God sakes,
let him deliver the baby!
Homie, isn't
he beautiful?
Hey, as long as he's got
eight fingers
and eight toes,
he's fine by me.
Oh, Bart!
Daddy's little angel.
Ah!
Why, you little--!
He did that on purpose!
How could he?
He's only ten minutes old.
Bart, Lisa, come
here for a minute.
You know, son,
the day you were born
I received the greatest gift
a man could have.
As the years went by,
your mother and I
were blessed twice more,
and not a day goes by that
we don't thank God
for all three of you.
Homer!
I'm not pregnant!
Yeah! Whoa! Excellent, Marge!
Yes!
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.