♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
Hey, Bart,
summer's almost here.
Which kind of sprinkler
do you like?
The one that goes
like this?
Sss...
fff...
sss...
Or the one that goes like this?
Fft-fft-fft-fft-fft-fft.
Oh, and there's this one.
Fff-fff-fff-fff-fff-fff.
It's the last day
of school, Milhouse.
Try to show
some dignity.
(truck engines rev)
Gentlemen, start your chimes.
(chimes ringing)
School's out!
Up yours, Krabappel.
Well, I'm glad the rest of you
remembered that summer vacation
starts at the end of
the day, not the beginning.
Here you go, Ma'am.
Hmm, quick work.
How did you know
he was going to run?
We've got someone
on the inside.
(nervous laughter)
Ah, the reward for a year's
worth of toil and sacrifice.
Retrospecticus.
Ugh...
-Ooh.
-Aah.
The leatheroleum covers
were worth the extra money.
Oh... you can
smell the benzene.
Oh, when the kids see
these layouts and fonts,
you're going to be the most popular
girl in school.
You know something, Beezee?
I think you're right.
And so, as Abraham Lincoln sat
in Ford's Theater that night,
John Wilkes Booth entered,
drew his gun and...
(bell ringing)
Well, that's it. Have a
nice summer, everyone.
But what happened
in Ford's Theater?
Was President Lincoln okay?
He was fine.
Go home, Ralph.
In the beginning
of the school year,
each of you received
a colored ticket.
I hope everyone
still has theirs.
-No.
Who died and
made you boss?
Mr. Estes,
the publications advisor.
I edited the whole thing.
If you hadn't done it,
some other loser would have.
So quit milking it.
(cheering)
Hey, will you guys
sign my yearbook?
(sighs)
This is Becky.
She's in
the second grade.
Hi, Becky.
Thanks for coming out.
"See ya."
He writes the way
people talk.
Your daughter
is named Seymour?
Well, I... ye...
I lied. It's for me.
I don't get it.
Straight A's,
perfect attendance,
bathroom timer.
I should be the most
popular girl in school.
(sighs)
Homer, I'm in a rhubarb
of a pickle of a jam here.
I was all set to go off
on vacation
when I get called up
for jury duty.
It's a corker of a case.
Seems a man drove up
onto a traffic island
and hit a decorative rowboat
full of geraniums.
Now they're trying it
as a maritime offense...
So, anyhoo, how'd you like
to use my beach house?
Free of charge.
I only get two weeks
of vacation a year,
and you want me to spend it
in your lousy beach house?
Well... if it will
seal the deal,
I'll take a look
at your septic tank,
see if I can get her
humming again?
Deal. See Flanders? You give
a little, you get a little.
(squishing)
Hello, Mr. Brown Ground.
What you got for me?
MARGE: And you're sure the
Flanderses won't be there?
Well, it sounds great.
Bart, you can
invite Milhouse.
Lisa, you can
bring a friend, too.
Hey, great, a friend...
or a companion...
or, I don't know,
a stuffed animal.
Well, did you call
one of your friends?
Friends? Ha.
These are
my only friends.
Grown-up nerds
like Gore Vidal.
And even he's kissed
more boys than I ever will.
Girls, Lisa.
Boys kiss girls.
Mom, why don't I have
any friends?
We have each other.
When I was
a lonely little girl,
I always dreamed
that someday
my daughter would be
my best friend.
We are best friends, Mom.
But I'm a kid.
I need friends
my own age, too.
Honey, you'll make
plenty of friends.
All you have to do
is be yourself.
Be myself?
I've been myself for eight
years and it hasn't worked.
Look at all these
dorky clothes.
A bathing cap...
nose plugs...
a microscope at the beach?
Ugh, what was I thinking?
Mom, I'm gonna tighten
Milhouse's straps.
He's fidgeting again.
Ow!
-(honking)
-Lisa! Let's go.
Hmm...
Somebody's traveling light.
Maybe you're getting stronger.
Well, I have been
eating more.
Wave bye-bye
to our house, Maggie.
Bye-bye, tree.
Bye-bye, job.
Bye-bye, toothbrush.
Bye-bye, Lisa Simpson.
When the hell are we
going to get to...
Where the hell are we going?
(annoyed grunt)
It's called Little
Pwagmattasquarmsettport.
It's known
as America's scrod basket.
I thought Springfield
was America's scrod basket.
No. Springfield
is America's crud bucket.
At least,
according to Newsweek.
"Wel-diddly-elcome,
Simpsons."
Oh, geez.
He actually
wrote "diddly."
That was thoughtful.
"I left a few helpful
notes around our house."
HOMER: Aw, come on-- Gee--
"Put food in me."
I'll take that.
Well, duh!
With what, Ned?
(annoyed groan)
Nice try, Todd.
(chuckles)
Isn't this fun, honey?
It must be exciting
to make a different set of beds.
I know you're
joking, but it is!
Say, why don't you
put on your swimsuit
and head for the beach?
Well, it's kind of funny.
With all the craziness
and confusion
and mishegoss of packing,
I forgot to pack.
Lisa, that's not
at all like you.
Exactly.
Hmm.
I forgot my swimsuit, too
but I improvised.
HOMER:
Hello.
(siren wailing)
Uh, Mom, I'm kind
of trying to go
for a different
look this year.
Oh, okay.
(gasps)
Ooh!
How about this
adorable sunsuit?
It has a starfish
on the fanny
and it comes
with its own pail.
LISA: Mom, come here!
Bring money.
So, where do you want
to show off your new hip togs?
The Sherbet Shoppe?
The Candle District?
Big Sue's Tap Water Taffy?
Um, if it's okay
with you, Mom,
I'd rather go
find some kids.
Oh.
Okay.
You'll be my friend.
I'm never, never going
to let you get away.
(laughing)
BART: Last one in
is a yearbook editor!
Full speed ahead.
Prepare to dive.
Dive!
(both groan)
It's low tide, boys.
I wonder where
all the kids are.
Hey, a library!
No, I can't.
That's the old nerdy Lisa.
Lisa, read about
my adventures in the south seas
and make me live again.
We've got periodicals
on microfiche.
Won't you join
our tea party?
It would be ever so...
Don't do it, Lisa!
It's a trick. Run!
Run!
Oh, I don't see
any kids at all.
It's like they ditched me
in advance.
BOY:
So, he goes like (snorts).
GIRL: I can totally
hear him going that.
(gasps)
Only kids are that incoherent.
(kids chuckling)
So my Mom tried to take me
to some candle place,
but I'm all, like, "no way."
Like, you know, whatever.
Like, you know,
whatever.
Hey, what's hap...
(screeching)
Okay, okay, okay.
Not your fault.
It's a bird thing.
You don't control the birds.
You will someday, but not now.
-Hi.
-What's up?
-Who's that?
-I don't know. Some kid.
Hey, I like your hat.
A compliment!
Scanning for sarcasm...
It's clean. Go!
Thanks.
Um... you guys skate?
Try to, but cops always
confiscate our boards.
Yeah. And you just know
they're using them
like, five minutes later
down at the station.
Hmm. I think I know
a place you can skate
that's virtually deserted.
Like, you know, whatever.
-Oh, cool.
-All right. Cool.
Hey, this place rocks.
What'd you say
your name was?
-Didn't. It's Lisa.
-I'm Erin.
So how'd you know
about this place?
You into books?
Me? Unlikely.
My goony brother's
always going to libraries.
I usually hang out in front.
Oh, you like hanging out, too?
Well, it beats doing stuff.
Yeah, stuff sucks.
Hey, you up?
You can use my board.
Aah!
Okay. Thanks.
That's very, um...
rad of you.
Hey, Bart, Lisa's skateboarding
with some cool kids.
And she looks like Blossom.
Lisa? With people?
(snorts)
If they're
impressed by her,
I'm going to Bart
their world.
Okay, Milhouse,
you know the drill.
Right. You go over
and wow them.
I hide in the shrubs.
Hot stuff coming through!
My friendship,
you know you want it.
(scoffs) That kid, like,
tries too hard.
Shah. The whole thing
smacks of effort, man.
Pff. That's my dorky little brother,
Bart... tholomew.
(scoffs) Like, who does
he think he is
with that slingshot
in his back pocket?
Dennis the Menace?
-(all laughing)
-Face. What a rip!
Like, Mr. Wilson
or something.
How'd it go?
Are we down with them?
No. They must
have seen you.
(bug zapper zaps)
Oh, why do we have to play
this lousy old game?
Because it was
the only one in the house.
Come on, Homer, open the door
for your mystery date.
Ooh captain of
the football team!
He's a dreamboat.
Don't wait up, Marge.
(chuckles)
Okay, Bart, your turn, your turn.
(Marge laughing)
You got the dud!
Hey, he looks just
like you, Poindexter.
(guffawing)
How come Lisa
doesn't have to play?
Why does she get to hang out
with her friends?
You got friends.
You got the dud right here.
Stand up for yourself,
Poindexter.
Wow, Lisa,
I never appreciated
all this, like,
sea junk before.
Hey, that clam's got legs.
That's a hermit crab.
When she outgrows
her old shell,
she finds a new one
that's a better fit.
Don't be afraid,
little friend.
You'll be the most popular
crab on the beach.
Aww, a gift
from my favorite crustacean.
Um, did you learn that word
from a teacher or something?
No. No...
I heard it
on Baywatch.
(overlapping
affirmations)
Baywatch...
David Hasselhoff, man.
Hmm... I bet this place
sells illegal fireworks.
Just go in and act casual,
like you buy 'em all the time.
Hi.
Um... let me have
one of those porno magazines,
large box of condoms,
a bottle of Old Harper,
couple of those panty shields,
and some illegal fireworks,
and one of those
disposable enemas.
No, make it two.
My apologies, sir,
but the sale of fireworks
is prohibited in this state
and is punishable by...
Follow me.
Any red-blooded,
flag-fearing American
would love the M-320.
Celebrate the independence
of your nation
by blowing up
a small part of it.
All right.
Pretty cool
of your Mom
to let us
hang out here.
Totally. Not
like my Mom.
She'd be
butting in
with Rice Krispie
squares and Tang.
My Dad's all stoked
'cause today's
the fourth of July.
He woke me up at dawn
to take a loyalty oath.
Ugh. My Mom's French
so we only celebrate
Bastille Day.
Well, we could do
something fun.
Um, how about
a beach party?
Oh, great idea, Lis.
I know where there's a beach.
I know where we can
get some baguettes.
Gee, I don't know
what you've got planned
for tonight, Homer,
but count me out.
Didn't you buy any meat?
(chuckles)
This baby's sure
to kill something.
Okay, now, everybody, stand back
while I celebrate freedom.
Bart, give me your matches.
Fresh out.
No lighter? Nothing?!
Oh!
Wait. I got it.
D'oh!
(gibbering)
(gasps)
The beer!
(sighs)
(whistling)
Oh, this is the worst
fourth of July ever.
I hate America.
Come on, Milhouse.
Let's go down there.
I don't think you should.
Let Lisa be alone
with her new friends.
They're my friends rightfully.
She only got them
by copying me.
Don't have
a cow, man.
(all laughing)
See? That's
my expression.
Oh, you haven't said that
in four years.
Let Lisa have it.
It's the principle.
She's got to learn.
No! Now, park your keister,
Meester.
LISA:
Aye, carumba!
(kids laugh)
Hey, Lis, I made
something for you.
It's a friendship
bracelet.
For me?
Wow, my first real
friend... ship bracelet.
(nervous chuckle)
I don't have
anything for you...
except this necklace I made.
Oh, cool.
Thanks.
(sniffing)
Hey, cinnamon dental floss.
I just know we're going
to be friends forever.
So, Lisa has a friend.
We'll see about that.
Bart!
I need my glasses.
Oh, nice doggie.
(giggling)
I'm dizzy!
I'm nauseous!
But I'm popular!
Huh?
What's he doing here?
My yearbook.
No!
Mm-hmm.
Hey, you guys,
you want to see
how cool Lisa Simpson
really is?
Check this out.
"Miss Perfect Attendance."
"Grammar Rodeo--
Head Buckeroo."
"The French table."
Ooh la la.
"Teacher's Pet"?
(sobbing)
(humming)
Hey, Lis.
I guess my little
yearbook stunt
was pretty rough,
but it did
teach you a lesson.
It's important
to be yourself.
(through clenched teeth)
I know exactly who I am.
I am the sister
of a rotten, jealous,
mean little sneak.
You cost me
my only friends.
You've ruined my life.
Hey, kids, there's
a carnival tonight.
Oh, boy, a carnival!
Hmm.
(choking)
Kids, stop that.
Don't make me get the carny.
Hey, Lisa,
make friends with this.
Hey!
MILHOUSE:
Help!
Remember, kids,
there's no need to bump.
Just enjoy the ride.
(bell rings)
(electrical crackling)
(sighs)
Lisa, wait!
Being myself didn't work.
Being someone else didn't work.
Maybe I just wasn't meant
to have friends.
BOY: Lisa is gonna freak
when she sees this.
ERIN: Well, hurry up.
They'll be back soon.
(gasps) Lisa.
Okay, you found out
I'm an overachieving bookworm.
So whatever mean prank
you're pulling,
just finish it up
and send me a Polaroid.
I'm going to sleep.
BOY:
Wait, Lisa, look.
Hmm?
(Lisa exclaiming)
Cool, huh?
Now you can take the beach with you
wherever you go.
Uh, but don't drive
at night.
Does this mean you still
want to be friends?
Even though I tried to
cover up my nerdish leanings?
Look, we don't care
who you were,
and you can't fake the kind
of good person that you are.
Yeah. You taught us
about cool things like nature
and why we shouldn't
drink sea water.
This is the most thoughtful
thing anybody ever--
HOMER:
Sweet merciful crap!
My car!
(sea gulls shrieking)
Mmm. The polite thing to do
would have been to clean
the shells first.
Shoo. Shoo.
I guess I should
give this back to you.
I showed it to your friends again
before we left.
Bart!
Look inside.
Oh, thanks, Bart.
I signed it, too.
(goofy laughter)
Uh-huh.
Well, get a last look
at the beautiful
ocean scenery, kids.
♪ Sittin' in my car
outside your house ♪
♪ Sittin' in my car outside
your house ♪
♪ Remember when you spilled
Coke all over your blouse ♪
♪ T-shirts, cut-offs,
and a pair of thongs ♪
♪ T-shirts, cut-offs, and
a pair of thongs ♪
♪ We've been havin' fun
all summer long ♪
♪ Won't be long till
summertime is through ♪
♪ Summertime is through... ♪
♪ Every now and then
we hear our song... ♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.