(theme music playing)
CHORUS: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
(whistle blows)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
(jazzy solo)
(chimes)
(tires screeching)
(honking horn)
D'oh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
ALL: Ah, ah, ooh, ooh...
Ah, ah, ooh, ooh. Hmm!
Here's the mail, Dad. That'll be
three dollars for on-couch delivery.
And three makes three.
This isn't real money. It's printed
by the Montana Militia.
It'll be real soon enough.
Ooh, my first issue of Self-test Monthly .
Finally I get to find out
what makes me tick.
-I'm betting it's hunger and rage.
-Yeah, but in what ratio?
"Are you a good driver?" Hmm. Yes.
"Are you a good lover?"
Yes. Oh, I'm doing great.
Dad, those are just
the names of the quizzes.
You're supposed to open the magazine.
My way is easier.
Why don't you be the quiz master
and ask other people the questions?
Ooh... Quiz master, yes.
That would entertain me briefly.
OK, Flanders,
your love quiz score is... 61.
That makes you a "Frigid Frieda."
I took off 30 points
for all that crying you did.
(sniffling) Well, it was
a little insensitive giving me a sex test
seeing that my wife just passed away.
-No way! When?
-Six months ago.
You were at the funeral.
You fell into the grave.
(chuckles) Oh, yeah.
I saw a gopher. What a day.
-(crow caws)
-OK... last question.
"Who is your favorite Backstreet Boy?"
Oh, the little rat-faced one.
No, no, no. Nick.
He's so good to his mother.
According to this, you're both idiots.
Hey, thanks. What do we owe you?
OK, "There's black widow at your door,
a rattlesnake at the window
and a scorpion on the phone.
Do you... A, none of the below,
B..."
Homie, for God's sakes, it's 02:00 a.m.
Fine. I'll take the next quiz.
"How long will you live?"
"In an average week, how many braised ribs
do you eat?"
Marge, do you think
that counts honey-braised?
MARGE: I don't know!
I'm trying to sleep!
OK... "non-smoker... add eight years."
Hmm.
So according to this, I'll live to be...
Forty-two? Oh, that's horrible!
I won't even live to see my children die.
(sobbing)
Now what's wrong?
I've only got three more years to live.
Maybe you added it wrong. Let me have it.
(mumbling)
See? And these quizzes
are never wrong, Marge.
They're put together
by the finest scientists
in the magazine business.
Oh... Honey, don't panic.
If you just made a few
lifestyle changes...
No! (sobbing)
Can't sleep. Gonna die.
We're back with legendary
producer, Robert Evans.
Now before you did The Godfather
there was Love Story .
-Tell us about that.
-Ah, Love Story...
The little picture that could.
Was Paramount chomping
at the bit to make it?
(chuckles) You better believe
they weren't.
But once that tear-jerker
hit John Q. Popcorn,
it was boffo, boo-hoo box office
all the way. (chuckles)
And the critics loved it, too.
I remember Vincent Canby said...
"I'm going to kill you, Homer."
-You are so dead.
-(shrieks)
Now, Chinatown was a classic.
But you had problems
with the sequel The Two Jakes?
Oh, boy, disappointed?
I had the blues like Chasen's had chili.
I said to myself...
"Evans, you forgot
Hollywood rule number one...
-Kill Homer Simpson."
-(shrieks)
Hey, what's all the screaming?
Some of us have grammar school
in the morning, you know.
Maybe you should see a doctor, Homie.
A head doctor.
I'm not crazy. It's the TV that's crazy!
Aren't you, TV?
The crisis? Charlie Bludorn's birthday.
The solution? A snappy banner.
Out comes the phone, in flies Bobby Towne
and six drafts later,
I had myself a party.
You see? Gibberish. All gibberish.
(crow caws)
So tell me,
are all you government inspectors
so handsome and strapping?
Well, we've got a solo flex down at HQ.
Anyway, everything looks great, Mr. Burns.
I can't find a single violation
or employee acting strangely.
You got to hide me! Death is after me!
And I don't entirely trust these cowboys.
Is this man an employee?
Oh, of course not. He's just...
a harmless maniac here to remind us
of the precious gift of sanity.
(sputtering) Oh, God, what's he doing?
That's it, that's it. A mother can't die.
And I'm a mother, see?
(nervous Laughing)
(Homer whimpering)
-You hate your father, don't you?
-Sometimes.
But the guy I really hate is your father.
I shouldn't have brought that up.
I was just venting.
Any-hoo, I think your fear
of death is causing your insomnia
which is provoking your erratic behavior.
Why isn't my baby gaining weight?
-Because it's made of plastic.
-I see.
What you need is a good, long rest.
-I suggest Florida.
-Florida?
But that's America's wang.
They prefer "The sunshine state."
Mom, Bart's sitting next to me.
-Mom, Lisa's growing.
-Quiet, you two.
You know your father's had a breakdown.
My pockets hurt.
OK, honey, we're almost to Palm Corners.
There'll be nothing to do
but lie on the beach and relax.
(chattering, cheering)
(tires squeal)
(crowd chanting) Spring break,
spring break, spring break...
Oh, no. We came during spring break.
(gasps)
Take them off the glass!
This looks like a terrible place to relax.
We're going to get you to a... (gasps)
-(Homer Laughing)
-(cheering)
(grunting)
(groans)
Party! Woo-hoo!
♪ Hey, boys it's the wild weekend ♪
♪ We did it then and we'll do it again ♪
♪ We're having fun
and we just got started ♪
(music fades out)
This is terrible.
The whole point of coming down here
was for you to get some rest.
-Show us your boobs!
-Not now.
(Home yawns)
Well... (yawns) enjoy your sightseeing.
I promise I won't leave this bed.
I trust you, honey.
Sweet dreams.
HOMER: Uh... could you just shut off the--
Party! Party! Party!
Party! Party!
Party?
Now, this is living.
Whoo! Sepulveda here doing a veejay thing
for the most out-of-control
spring break ever!
And since it's my birthday,
we'll party extra hard.
(beeping)
(gasps) No. Not yet. I'm only 25.
(grunting)
What up, chew toys? Cienega here...
tightening the hose clamps
for you bad girls.
We got Kid Rock coming up
for all you mosh monkeys.
Woo! I like music!
Yo, yo, straight out of Detroit, y'all.
It's the J-O-E to the C.
Let's rock the party with Kid Rock.
Oh, no. It's a lost child.
Don't worry, folks... I'll tackle him.
(grunts)
(rock music playing)
Yo, Rock, tell spring break
what your name is.
My name is Ki...
Kid Rock!
♪ Bawit daba, banana fana ♪
♪ Ooga chucka, fa with the falun gonga ♪
♪ Pa tee dana mana onga... ♪
And if you look to your left,
you'll see another endless
stretch of stagnant water.
Oh, well, look who turned out
to greet us, folks.
It's our town's most famous
resident, Captain Jack.
Look at the size of that gator.
-Is he a man-eater?
-Only convicts and hobos.
Do you have any hobo chunks
we could throw to him?
(chuckles) Afraid not.
Now, years ago, Captain Jack
helped build Palm Corners
by dragging sticks and stones
from the swamps.
Legend has it, he designed the town flag.
Say hello, Captain Jack.
ALL: Aww...
Ah. He can crawl up
through my toilet any day.
(raucous cheers)
Thank you!
It's the pimp of the nation
Kid Rock tearin' it up
at spring break, y'all.
Now, what we'd like to do next
is bring it down for a minute.
HOMER: Bring on the rappin' granny!
MAN: What?
What? She's hilarious.
You know, a lot of my homies
didn't make it to the party
and we're gonna give props
to the fallen by pourin' a 40 on the curb.
(reverent murmuring)
But this ain't no 40-ounce curb.
So we're going to need 40 gallons, y'all.
(cheering)
-All for Homer.
-(crowd booing)
All for Homer.
-What the...
-Hey, who's that fool?
Yo, let's waste that biatch.
"Biatch"? Moi?
KID ROCK: Son of a...
♪ We built this city on rock and roll ♪
Uh-oh.
We'll give that punk a Joe C. Section.
Let's do this thing.
All right now, boys, that's enough.
Kid Rock, that's not like you.
And, Joe C., would your mama want you
stretching out that sweatshirt like that?
No, sir. Please don't tell Mama.
They called you a pig, sheriff.
Well, I don't care what they call me
as long as they play "Fists of Rage."
That's a good song. (laughs)
(groaning)
Oh, thank goodness. Where were you?
Guess how many boobs I saw today, Marge.
Fifteen.
(groans)
Ohh! I hope he didn't cause
too much trouble, sheriff.
Oh, boys will be boys.
I reckon he was just
blowing off a little steam.
(laughing) Doesn't he talk funny?
(yawning)
My insomnia. It's gone.
Check it out, Marge.
I'm sane again.
And I owe it all to...
Spring break!
Whoo!
I'm an animal!
Huh?
Hey, where is everybody?
Spring break is over.
It's time to get back to our studies.
The world looks to us,
the college students, for leadership.
Fine. Be nerds.
I'll find some people who know
the true meaning of the words
"par-tay."
♪ Louie Louie ♪
♪ Oh, no, we gotta go ♪
♪ We built this city ♪
♪ This kick-ass city ♪
♪ What kind of music built this city? ♪
♪ Rock and roll ♪
Dad, look out!
♪ Look out for what? ♪
-♪ The giant gator ♪
- ♪ The giant... ♪
(gasps)
-Oh, no.
-(siren wailing)
You killed Captain Jack.
You in a heap of trouble, son.
You'll have to catch me first.
(shrieking)
OK, I'll go quietly.
(siren wails)
Did you really have
to handcuff the children?
No, ma'am, I did not.
You seemed so understanding before.
What happened to "Boys will be boys"?
You see, during spring break,
the beer companies pay me
to look the other way.
The rest of the year, I'm a real hard-ass.
OK, sweet pea, you're next.
Whoa, looks like we got
a teeny Houdini here.
(all laughing)
Well, don't you worry, darlin'.
I got some baby cuffs in the station.
Look. This is our chance.
(grunts)
Let's go.
You can't drive, Dad.
He's got your license.
I'm going to try anyway.
-(engine starts)
-It worked. It's a miracle.
(tires squealing)
Ah, dang it.
Now, why does that only happen
when nobody's looking?
(squawking )
(siren wailing)
-Pull over!
-There's no good place!
There's lots of good places.
What about over there?
-No shade!
-(gunshots)
-(train whistle blowing)
-(gasps)
(bell clanging)
-Perfect.
-Homer, No. You'll kill us all.
Or die trying. (grunts)
-(tires squealing)
-(whistle blowing)
(kids screaming)
(siren stops)
Dang!
(sighs)
-D'oh!
-(all shrieking)
Dad, what'll we do?
The only thing we can do.
Sit tight and try to get some sleep.
(snoring)
(whinnying)
(metal screeching)
(all snoring)
(yawns) Hey, where's Dad?
(grunts)
-Rise and shine, everybody.
-You went to the snack car?
Yeah. But first, I talked to the engineer.
He said there's a procedure
for dealing with events of this nature.
(grunts)
(all screaming)
HOMER: Oh! OK, now,
am I the only one on fire?
Good.
(screaming)
Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh!
This family has hit a new low.
We're on the run from the law.
Totally lost, no car, no money
No clean clothes, and it's all your fault!
I love being married.
-A diner?
-It's perfect.
We can hide out here until the heat's off.
You took the signs out of the window?
That's pretty presumptuous.
How do you know I'm going to hire you?
Sorry. I just want
to be a broom boy so bad.
I like your attitude. You're hired.
How about you, missy?
-You want to be a mop girl?
-Not really. No.
I like your honesty. You're hired.
And you two haven't said a word.
I like that. You're hired.
-Woo-hoo!
-Hey, keep it down.
Y'all can stay in this trailer.
-Now, it ain't Buckingham palace...
-Ohh...
But I raised eight young 'uns,
three chill-uns and a baby here.
-(electricity crackling)
-LISA: Eww...
Oh, it's so cozy.
You're insincere. I like that.
(country music playing)
-Can I top you off, hon?
-No, thanks.
-More hash browns, sugar?
-No, I'm good.
ANNOUNCER: This just in...
Authorities in Six-Toe County
are on the lookout
for a family of fugitives.
-They're charged with Gatorcide...
-(gasps)
...and defrauding an Amtrak snack bar.
Trouble with the law, huh?
Well, I'm not one to judge.
The way I see it,
we're all sinners, and...
(humming)
Y'all just lie low here.
You'll be safe with ol' Velma.
-Stop that!
-But I was just--
-Scat!
-Going to try to--
-Go on now! Just quit.
-Knock you out.
♪ Jimmy crack corn and I don't care ♪
♪ Jimmy crack corn and I'm not there ♪
♪ We built this city on rock 'n' roll ♪
♪ Something something day ♪
Wow! Look at all
the stars you can see here.
Those noxious gasses from the swamp
must magnify them.
I'm getting used to this country life.
Teacher says I'm whittling
at a tenth-grade level.
And y'all hardly ever bicker anymore.
Too hot to bicker, I reckon.
You know, killing that gator
was the best decision I ever made.
-Got that right.
-Darn tootin'.
Boy, howdy.
Yep, this place is great.
Someday, when Lisa and Bart get married,
it'll all be theirs.
-BOTH: Yuck!
-You mean, when they marry other people.
OK, but I ain't paying for two weddings.
(all snoring)
-(car engine starting)
-(yawns) Hey, wake up! We're moving.
(siren wailing)
You just relax.
I'll have you in jail by supper time.
You'd better.
Hey, you're stealing my trailer!
I like that.
(gravel bangs)
Well, first up is
The state of Florida
vs. The Simpson family.
Your honor, I'd like to represent myself.
Drunken hicks of the jury...
(gasps)
(clanking)
(grunting)
We'd be much better rock breakers
if we weren't all chained together.
-(whip snaps)
-Ow!
No talking.
You know, you catch more flies
with honey than with vinegar.
Ow! I'm beginning to dislike
the man with the whip.
(siren wails)
Afternoon, folks.
Got a new assignment for you.
The judge is having a little soiree
and he needs some help.
-Ow!
-No listening.
You hear me?
Uh... No.
-OFFICER: You just don't learn, do you?
-Ow!
(crowd chattering)
Champagne, madam?
-(whip snaps)
-Ow! Son of a...
-And the gentleman?
-Damn it!
Simpson, we got a problem.
The jazz pianist didn't show up.
Well, what am I supposed to do?
(off-key )
(groaning)
Ow!
(playing beautifully)
OK, Bart, I'll sweet talk the sheriff
while you grab his keys.
What should I do?
Restock the possum bar.
-We're almost out of claws.
-Oh...
My goodness!
What a lovely suit, Sheriff!
Is that Seersucker?
Nah. Not on a civil servant's
salary. It's Nearsucker.
Well, the fabric really brings
out the red in your neck.
Yep. It's coming along, huh?
You should see it in August
after the horseflies been getting at it.
Hoo, man!
Dang, I wish I could, but in August
our chain gang has to dig for tar.
Well, now, I might could switch you to
dead animal pickup.
-Hey!
-Run!
(panting)
Huh? (groaning)
(whimpering)
-Hey.
-Ooh.
Nice try. I guess we just haven't been
whipping you enough.
-(Whimpers)
-Sake's alive!
(growls)
Our beloved Captain Jack
isn't dead after all!
(excited murmuring)
Well, don't that beat all!
I guess you folks just stunned him.
That's what we've been trying to tell you.
Well, looks like you folks are free to go.
But don't you set foot
in the state of Florida again.
Fine, there are plenty of other states
that are happy to have us.
Well, we're still welcome
in North Dakota and... Arizona.
Arizona smells funny.
(groans)
North Dakota, here we come!
I've always wanted to see Mount Rushmore.
That's South Dakota.
Oh.
(rock music playing)
♪ Bawitdaba da bang a dang
diggy diggy diggy ♪
♪ Said the boogie
said up jump the boogie ♪
♪ Bawitdaba da bang a dang
diggy diggy diggy ♪
♪ Said the boogie
said up jump the boogie ♪
♪ Bawitdaba da bang a dang
diggy diggy diggy ♪
♪ Said the boogie
said up jump the boogie ♪
♪ Bawitdaba da bang a dang
diggy diggy diggy ♪
♪ Said the boogie
said up jump the boogie ♪
(echoes) ♪ Love ♪
♪ And for the hate ♪
-(murmuring)
-Shh!
Captioned by
Visual Data Media Services