♪ The Simpsons ♪
D'oh!
(screams)
Did you hear
about Miss Hoover?
She drank a bottle
of drain cleaner by mistake.
I heard she fell down
a well.
Ahh!
-(sobbing)
-Come on, now.
My God,
she's been dumped again.
Children,
I won't be staying long.
I just came from the doctor,
and I have lyme disease.
Principal Skinner
will run the class
until a substitute arrives.
-What's lyme disease?
-I'll field that one.
Lyme disease is spread
by small parasites called ticks.
When a diseased tick
attaches itself to you
-and begins sucking your blood,
-Ohh.
malignant spirochetes
infest your bloodstream,
eventually spreading to your
spinal fluid and on into the brain.
The brain.
Oh, dear God.
(class chatters)
Come on, Elizabeth.
Come, come.
Well now, children,
here we are.
Open your primers to page 32.
Ah, subtraction.
(screaming from above)
Bart Simpson!
I know it's you.
And here comes snowball two.
This is the one we kept.
KIDS:
Eww!
We were gonna keep the gray one,
but the mother ate her.
KIDS:
Eww!
Mrs. Krabappel,
he's traumatizing
the children.
As usual,
I agree with you, Martin.
Bart, shut that off
and take your seat immediately.
Oh look, this is really cool.
When you hit reverse,
I can make 'em go back in.
(screaming)
No, children,
you're not seeing things.
This, my little friends,
is a schwa.
-(cap guns firing)
-(cries ouit)
-Are you the substitute?
-Yes, sir.
-Yes, I am.
-Are you insane?
No sir, no I'm not.
It's my way of getting their attention.
Well, all right.
Uh, play friendly
with your new teacher,
children.
Howdy. I am a Texas cowboy.
The year is 1830.
You young'uns ask me
any questions you like.
Can we play kickball instead
of science after lunch?
Kickball? Son, there ain't
no kickball in 1830.
Any other questions?
Shoot, it's awfully quiet
on the plains here.
Well, how about this? Everybody?
I want to see two eyes
on every single person
staring right at me right now.
There are three things wrong
with my costume.
Anybody names those three
things will get my hat.
I believe I know the answer.
-What's your name?
-Lisa Simpson.
-Well, go ahead, Miss Simpson.
-Um, one.
Your belt buckle says
"State of Texas,"
but Texas wasn't a state
until 1845.
-Very good.
-Two.
-The revolver wasn't invented until 1835.
-That's excellent.
Three. You seem to be
of the Jewish faith.
Are you sure I'm Jewish?
-Or Italian.
-I'm Jewish.
And there weren't
any Jewish cowboys.
Very good. That's excellent.
I'm also wearing a digital watch,
but I'll accept that.
Here you go, little lady.
And for the record,
there were a few Jewish cowboys,
ladies and gentlemen.
Big guys who were great shots
and spent money freely.
I'm Mr. Bergstrom. Feel free to
make fun of my name if you want.
Two suggestions
are "Mr. Nerdstrom"
and "Mr. Booger-strom."
(class laughing)
Boys and girls, today we will begin
selecting a class president.
I'm not allowed to vote,
but I strongly suggest
you elect Martin. Martin?
As your president,
I would demand
a science fiction library
featuring an A-B-C
of the overlords of the genre:
Asimov, Bester, Clarke...
-What about Ray Bradbury?
-I'm aware of his work.
Thank you,
and keep watching the skies!
Excellent! Excellent! Martin!
If you're through
with your pemmican,
why don't we sing a song
about cowboys?
Now, this one's not
very accurate,
but we can fix it up
as we go along. Okay?
♪ Home,
home on the range ♪
(quietly) Actually, the range
was far from home.
It was a very desolate place
where danger and disease
rode tall in the saddle.
♪ Where the deer
and the antelope play ♪
(whispering) But unlike
the efficient Indians,
cowboys used only the tongue
of the antelope,
and they threw the rest away.
♪ Where seldom is heard ♪
-♪ A discouraging word ♪
- (giggling)
♪ And the skies are
not cloudy all day. ♪
Hey, what's this?
Did you do it?
No, it wasn't me. I would never do
anything like that.
It was just one of those immature people
who, instead of building themselves up--
It's neat.
Can I have it?
Yes, but I didn't do it.
Are you sure you didn't?
It's good.
No, but I'm starting
to wish I had.
(chuckles) Ladies and gentlemen:
The Singing Dork.
(whispering)
Lisa.
(snickering)
Any other nominations?
TOGETHER:
We nominate Bart Simpson.
Speech! Speech!
I had a speech ready,
but my dog ate it.
-(kids laughing)
-Children!
Good. Bart, I need
someone very reliable
to deliver an important message
to the principal's office.
-Would you do it for me?
-Why Mrs. Krabappel,
how would I know where
the principal's office is?
-(laughing)
-(clapping and cheering)
People, what have I told you
about encouraging him?
When Bart wins approval for making a fool
of himself, it makes him think that--
-Yay, Bart!
-(hysterical laughing )
(chanting)
Bart! Bart! Bart! Bart!
Whoo! Whoo! Whoo! Whoo!
Whoo! Whoo! Whoo!
"Nobody...
"of the hundreds of people
that had visited the fair
"knew that a gray spider
"had played the most
important part of all.
No one was with her
when she died."
(crying)
Come on, Janey!
Everybody has a talent.
I want to see yours.
That's all.
-I don't have a talent.
-You can not talk like that.
There has to be something that
you can do better than anybody else.
Well, I can do this.
Yes! Great.
Okay. How about you, Ralph?
Wonderful! Chuck.
Oh, that's disgusting.
I love it.
Lisa! Come on,
you're holding out on us.
-I see a saxophone over there.
-I can't.
Come on, Lisa.
I bet you're good.
No, really, I can't.
Sure, you can.
Just try.
Please don't make me do it.
All right, you owe me
something special.
(bell ringing)
(laughing and chattering)
So... while I'm technically
still married,
there really hasn't been
any marriage to speak of
since Mister Krabappel moved
into his little love nest.
This profession can put
a lot of strain on a marriage.
Since he's been gone,
I've been looking
for a substitute
to teach me a lesson
I sorely need.
Mrs. Krabappel,
you're trying to seduce me.
(chuckles)
Well?
I'm sorry,
Mrs. Krabappel.
You're very nice,
but it's the children I love.
(sighing)
Oh...
(saxophone playing the blues)
When I fall asleep,
Mr. Bergstrom is
the last thing I think of.
And he's my first thought
when I wake up.
I feel that way
about your father.
No, no. You don't understand.
When Mr. Bergstrom smiles,
you only see these teeth.
But when you really make him laugh,
you can see these two teeth.
I think they're called
the eye teeth?
I don't know if he had
orthodontic work or what,
but they're absolutely perfect.
I notice little things
about your father too.
No, Mom. This is different.
I mean, this man makes you feel
like there's nobody better.
Your father does that to me.
Mom, are we going to talk,
or are we going to talk?
Lisa, we can talk, but first you have
to accept the fact
-that I feel that way about your father.
-Fine.
Yesterday he read us
"Charlotte's Web"
and cried at the end,
never trying to hide his tears.
-(laughing)
A book made him cry?
-Boo-hoo!
-Waaaah!
(groaning)
Mr. Bergstrom: Remember,
nobody, and I mean nobody
gets back in after lunch
without one igneous rock--
that's volcanic--
and one sedimentary,
and that is layered.
Lisa, can I see you
for a minute?
Yes! Yes, Mr. Bergstrom?
Lisa, your homework is always so neat.
How can I put this?
Does your father
help you with it?
No. Homework's
not my father's specialty.
Well, there's no shame in it.
I mean, my Dad--
-Not mine.
-You didn't let me finish.
Unless the next word
was "burp, "
you didn't have to.
In a sample taken
in this very classroom,
a state inspector found 1.74 parts
per million of asbestos!
That's not enough.
We demand more asbestos.
More asbestos!
(kids chanting)
More asbestos! More asbestos!
(camera shutter clicks)
Wow! You made the front page.
Aw, Dad, it's just
a popularity contest.
Just a popularity contest?
Excuse me, what's more
important than popularity?
Now, Bart, do you really
think you can win?
-Sure. Why not?
-Whoo-whoo!
All right. I always knew
you had personality.
The doctor said it was hyperactivity
but I knew better.
President Simpson.
Has a nice ring to it,
doesn't it, boy?
Hmm... yeah.
-Now, go get 'em!
-(growling)
He says there aren't
any easy answers.
I say he's not looking
hard enough!
(kids cheering)
(kids chanting)
Bart! Bart! Bart! Bart!
(laughing)
(cheering)
(kids chanting)
Bart! Bart! Bart! Bart!
(kids cheering)
(sighs)
Oh, you'll never go broke
appealing to the lowest
common denominator.
You're gonna miss
your brother's antics.
-When?
-When? When your life takes you places
the rest of us
have only heard about.
Places where my intelligence will be
an asset and not a liability?
Yes. There is such a place.
Believe me, it's true.
I believe everything you say
with your words,
your body language,
and your Semitic good looks.
"Dear Miss Hoover,
You have lyme disease.
"We miss you.
"Kevin's biting me.
"Come back soon.
"Here is a drawing
of a spirochete.
-Love, Ralph."
-Oh, that's great, Ralph.
-(bell ringing)
-Hey, kids!
I've learned
that in two weeks,
the Springfield
Museum of Natural History
will be closing forever
due to a lack of interest.
I urge you to see it
while you can.
(slurping)
Hmm. Lisa needs to go
to the museum tomorrow,
and I think
you should take her.
-The museum? Tomorrow?
-Mm-hmm.
Oh, Marge, I'd love to,
but I was planning on...
(thinking) Sleeping?
Eating a big sandwich?
Watching TV?
Spending time with the boy!
Spending time with the boy.
The boy needs attention, Marge.
Homer, I've been talking
to Lisa,
and I'm concerned about
your relationship with her.
Me, too, Mom.
-I think they're drifting apart.
-Shut up, boy.
-Homer, please!
-Marge, you don't understand.
I can't do it because--
You're trapped.
If you were smarter,
you might think of something.
But you're not.
So you just might as well--
All right, all right,
I'll take her.
Lousy brain.
Hey, what do you mean
by "suggested donation"?
Pay any amount you wish, sir.
And what if I wish
to pay zero?
(chuckles)
Well, it's up to you.
Ooh, so it's up
to me, is it?
-Yes.
-I see.
And you think that people
are gonna pay you $4.50
even though
they don't have to
just out of the goodness
of their--
(laughing)
Well, anything you say.
Good luck, lady.
You're going to need it.
-Mr. Bergstrom!
-Hi, Lisa.
Hey! you don't have to pay.
Read the sign.
-And this must be your father.
-(sighs)
His teeth had jagged edges
to rip through your body,
but he could've
swallowed you whole.
-Wow!
-Actually, Mr. Simpson,
they do know a great deal about
the process of mummification.
First they pulled the brain out
through the nose with an iron hook.
then stuffed the insides
with sawdust and onions.
-Eww! Gross!
-Ooh! Pretty creepy.
Still, I'd rather have him
chasing me than The Wolfman.
Oh, Lord.
Mr. Simpson, I am going
to be presumptuous.
I have noticed
that Lisa seems to feel
she has no strong
male role model.
-She said that?
-Well, no, she didn't say it,
-but, you know, she--
-But you can tell, right?
She looks around and sees everybody
else's dad with a good education,
youthful looks,
and a clean credit record
and thinks, "Why me?
What did I do to deserve
-this fat, old piece of--
-Mr. Simpson,
you have got to be
a bigger man.
There is a wonderful girl's
future at stake.
Well, if she's so wonderful,
give her an "A."
I am giving her an "A."
Great, but don't tell her it was
a favor to me. Tell her she earned it.
Mr. Simpson, she did earn it!
You are smooth.
I'll give you that.
He ruined the one chance
I had of getting
to know Mr. Bergstrom
outside of school.
Well, I'll tell you what.
Why don't we invite
Mr. Bergstrom to dinner?
Oh, Mom, that's wonderful!
Can I find out
his favorite dish
-and help you make it?
-Sure!
-Can I wear your jewelry?
-Can I get my ears pierced?
-No.
-Can I dye my shoes pink?
-Yes.
-Can I paint my nails?
-No.
-Can we have wine? Can I have wine?
-Yes. No.
- Does Bart have to be there?
- Yes.
Can we do it this week?
"Mr. Bergstrom,
May we request the pleasure
of your company..."
No.
"Mr. Bergstrom, if you're
not doing anything
this Friday..." No.
"Mr. Bergstrom,
Do you like pork chops?"
Oh, no,
of course you wouldn't.
(gasps)
Good morning, Lisa.
I'm back.
You see, class, my lyme
disease turned out to be...
ahem, psy-cho-somatic.
Does that mean you're crazy?
No, that means
she was faking it.
No, actually,
it was a little of both.
Sometimes, when a disease
is in all the magazines
and on all the news shows,
it's only natural
that you think you have it.
-Where's Mr. Bergstrom?
-I don't know.
Although I'd sure like
to talk to him.
He didn't touch my lesson plan.
What did he teach you?
That life is worth living.
(gasps)
(crying)
The polls will be open from
now until the end of recess.
Now, just in case any of you have
decided to put any thought into this,
we'll have our
final statements.
Martin?
I don't think there's
anything left to say.
-Bart?
-Victory party under the slide!
(cheering)
(buzzing)
Mr. Bergstrom!
Hey! Hey!
He moved out this morning.
He must have a new job--
He took his Copernicus costume.
Do you know where
I can find him?
Uh, I think he's taking
the next train to Capital City.
The train, how like him.
Traditional,
yet environmentally sound.
Yes, and it's been
the backbone of our country
since Leland Stanford drove that
golden spike at Promontory Point.
-I see he touched you too.
-(both sigh)
-Thanks for your vote, man.
-I didn't vote. Voting's for geeks.
Well, you got that right.
Thanks for your vote, girls.
BOTH: We forgot.
Well, don't sweat it.
Just so long as a couple
of people did.
-Right, Milhouse?
-Uh-uh.
-Lewis?
-No.
-Somebody must have voted.
-What about you, Bart?
-Didn't you vote?
-Uh-oh.
-(school bell)
-(screaming)
(cheering)
I demand a recount.
One for Martin.
Two for Martin.
-Would you like another recount?
-No.
Well, I just wanna make sure.
One for Martin. Two for Martin.
(chuckles)
This way, Mr. President.
MAN (on P.A.):
Now boarding on track five...
Mr. Bergstrom!
Hey, Mr. Bergstrom!
Hey! Lisa!
Hey, Lisa, indeed.
What? What is it?
Oh, I mean...
Were you just going to
leave, just like that?
Aw, I'm sorry, Lisa.
You know, it's the life
of the substitute teacher.
He's a fraud.
Today he might be
wearing gym shorts,
tomorrow he's speaking
French or pretending
to know how to run a band saw,
-or God knows what.
-You can't go.
You're the best teacher
I'll ever have.
Aw, that's not true.
Other teachers will come along.
-Oh, please!
-No, I can't lie to you, I am the best,
but, you know, they need me over
in the projects of Capital City.
(nearly whispering)
But I need you too.
That's the problem
with being middle class.
Anybody who really cares
will abandon you
for those who need it more.
I... I understand.
Mr. Bergstrom,
I'm going to miss you.
I'll tell you what.
Whenever you feel
like you're alone
and there's nobody
you can rely on,
this is all you need to know.
Thank you, Mr. Bergstrom.
MAN: All aboard!
So, I guess this is it.
If you don't mind,
I'll just run alongside
the train
as it speeds you
from my life.
Good-bye, Lisa honey.
It'll be okay.
Just read the note!
(train whistle blows)
HOMER:
Bart didn't get one vote?
Oh, this is the worst thing
that could ever happen to us.
All right, all right,
spilt milk, spilt milk,
spilt milk.
-What are you so mopey about?
-Nothing.
Lisa, tell your father.
Mr. Bergstrom
left today.
-Oh?
-He's gone forever.
-And?
-I didn't think you'd understand.
Hey! Just because I don't
care doesn't mean I don't understand.
I'm glad I'm not crying,
because I would hate
for you to think
that what I'm about to say
is based on emotion.
-But you, sir--
-Huh?
-...are a baboon!
-(gasps) Me?
Yes, you! Baboon! Baboon!
Baboon! Baboon!
I don't think you realize
what you're saying.
(screaming)
Baboon!
-(crying)
-Whoa.
Somebody was bound
to say it one day.
I just can't believe
it was her.
Did you hear that, Marge?
She called me a baboon!
The stupidest, ugliest,
smelliest ape of them all.
Homer, you're not allowed to have
hurt feelings right now.
There's a little girl upstairs
who needs you.
Her confidence
in her father is shaken,
and no little girl can be happy
unless she has faith in her daddy.
(groans)
Oh.
(reading)
"Go away."
(sobbing)
Lisa, don't hold
anything back.
You can tell me.
Are you crying because
you called Daddy a baboon?
-No!
-Nuts.
D'oh!
-This isn't going well at all.
-Look!
-If you just want me to forgive you--
-No, no, no.
I just wish
I knew what to say.
(melancholy music playing)
Although,
maybe this music will help.
Now, you lost someone
special, and it hurts.
I'm lucky, because I never
lost anyone special to me.
Everyone special to me
is under this roof.
-Oh...
-It's true.
Now, you'll have lots of special people
in your life, Lisa.
There's probably someplace
where they all get together,
and the food is real good,
and guys like me are serving drinks.
Oh, well, maybe
I can't explain all this,
but I can fix
your dollhouse for you.
At least I'm good
at monkey work.
You know? Monkey?
-You know what I mean?
-Yeah.
Bet I can hold these nails
in place with my tail.
-(both chuckle)
-(imitating monkey)
(laughing)
You're so silly.
-Give me a banana.
-I don't have any bananas.
Come on, you're
holding out on me.
(both laughing)
I'm sorry I called you
a baboon, Dad.
Think nothing of it.
BART: President prince,
president princess,
president priss...
Hey, what's the matter, son?
Aw, Dad...
If just me, Milhouse,
and Louis had voted.
Hey, son,
would you have gotten
any money for being
class president?
-No.
-Would you have to do extra work?
-Yeah.
-And, is this Martin guy
going to get to do
anything neat,
like throw out the first ball
at the World Series? Huh?
-Well, no.
-So let the baby have his bottle, huh?
-That's my motto.
-(both laughing)
Hey, thanks, monkey man.
Holy moly,
talk about parenting.
-(fussing)
-Uh-oh.
Sleep well, Maggie.
Ah. Three for three.
Homey, did you straighten
everything out?
Ah, bup, bup, bup, bup!
Don't say anything, Marge.
Let's just go to bed.
I'm on the biggest roll
of my life.
(switch clicks)
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.