CHOIR: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(groans)
D'oh!
-(tires screech)
-(grunts)
(alarm blaring)
(Paul Engemann's
"Push It to the Limit" playing)
♪ Push it to the limit ♪
♪ Walk along the razor's edge ♪
♪ But don't look down,
just keep your head ♪
♪ Or you'll be finished ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Open up the limit ♪
♪ Past the point of no return ♪
♪ You've reached the top
but still you gotta learn ♪
♪ How to keep it ♪
♪ Welcome to the limit ♪
♪ The limit ♪
♪ Take it maybe one step more ♪
♪ The power game's still playing ♪
♪ So you better push it to the limit... ♪
♪ The limit, the limit, the limit,
the limit, the limit ♪
Damn reruns.
-(music stops)
-(squeaking)
(theme music playing)
(indistinct shouting)
"Even then, a wish, I mind its pow'r,
A wish that to my latest hour
Shall strongly heave my breast,
That I for poor auld Scotland's sake..."
(shouts)
All right, you little monsters!
You've awakened Scotland's shame!
(playing bagpipes)
(screaming)
(grunting)
Willie, you know you can't play
that torture trumpet to kids.
I'll just use it to vape, then.
(laughs)
Class, I would like you to meet
your new teacher,
retired Air Force Sergeant
-Ms. Berrera.
-BART: Ay, caramba!
-Air Force?
-Sergeant?
A woman?
(Spanish accent)
Good morning, crew.
I am proud to be here
educating my country.
(students gasping)
For you, teacher.
Because if there's one thing
I learned in combat,
it's that the most powerful weapon
is knowledge.
What's the second most powerful weapon?
Shoulder-mounted anti-tank missile. Duh.
Did you ever American Sniper someone?
Uh, that's really
not appropriate for me to say.
How many hospitals did you help build?
Negative three.
BART: Oh, my God,
I've got a cool teacher.
What am I doing?
I'm sitting up straight,
and my hands are folded like a nerd.
-I've got to fix that.
-Yes?
(gasps) Now one's up in the air.
Okay, let's show
this innocent young veteran
what happens when you call
on Bart Simpson.
Ma'am, my name is Bart,
and I just want to say
how delighted I am that you're here.
What the hell?
Thank you, Bart.
(gasps) A neck tat?
Milhouse, have you ever thought
a teacher was cute?
Oh, yeah.
I thought Krabappel was smokin'.
I kept every issue of
the Fourth Gradian she was in.
Great lady.
(to tune of "Easy Lover")
♪ Pretty sober ♪
♪ I've only got one beer inside me ♪
♪ Pull me over ♪
♪ My blood alcohol is .03 ♪
Oh, I like it when the drivers sing
their blood alcohol level.
♪ Not so sober ♪
♪ So drunk I'll eat gas station sushi ♪
Homer, don't forget to pick up milk.
-Oh.
-And not just any milk--
healthy milk, without any hormones.
I won't forget.
Aw, they sell ads in thought bubbles now?
(whoops) I'm running a basic errand.
Homer Simpson buying a healthy product?
Now I have seen all of the things
that there are to see.
-(beep)
-That will be $16.
And can I interest you in any,
uh, milk insurance?
$16?!
Oof, another case of the rich cows
stickin' it to the little guy.
Okay, don't worry.
We're going to get you into a milk today.
Hmm.
I like it's in a plastic bottle
that'll be around for millions of years.
But is it good for my kids?
I know you have concerns.
But this video will gloss over
all of your questions.
It'd better.
Hmm.
-How's that milk, Jimmy?
-Boring.
Now, we could engineer a new Jimmy
who is less of a brat,
but we'll just use science
to jazz things up.
(jazz playing)
We used to feed boring old grass to cows.
That might have been fine
for Farmer Brown.
But we brought in a next-gen blend
of phenyl ketamine,
ketyl phenamine, and a healthy
sprinkling of transuranic elements.
But don't worry, we still get the milk
from good old-fashioned cows.
That's the best milk I've ever had.
(chuckles) You said "milk."
We can't, legally.
I'm not the kind of guy
advertising works on,
but I'll take 20,
no questions asked.
(Marge humming)
-Hmm?
-(humming)
-Bart, you're up already?
-Don't want to be late for school.
Hair combed, face washed?
-I thought I'd shake things up.
-(humming)
Morning, Marge. Morning, Bart.
What the... Ooh, la, la.
Is it a court day today?
Hmm, let's see.
(muttering) Nope, today we're off.
The courthouse is closed
because the judge is becoming a citizen.
-What gives, boy?
-Nothing's going on.
Some days a boy just wants to look
like he's going to church, okay?
I'm the last one to breakfast?
(gasps) You guys are planning
my birthday, right?
'Cause last year's was kind of lonely.
Boy, that's when I realized just how big
a bowling alley really is.
Can we please get a move on?
I do not want to miss any school.
Ooh, could this punctual
Bart possibly be connected
to your cute new teacher?
Oh, do I have a cute new sexy teacher?
I hadn't noticed.
♪ Bart likes his teacher,
Bart likes his teacher ♪
Hey, nothing can turn a boy's life around
like a cute teacher.
Like what Michelle Pfeiffer
did for Coolio.
In fact, to be supportive,
I'll drive Bart to school.
Are you just trying to see
how cute the teacher is?
Or how handsome he is, Marge.
(quietly) Not a he, right, boy?
-No.
-(whoops softly)
Hmm?
Even my dad came back for this!
That's right, son.
But, uh, right after this,
I have to go get some cigarettes.
Last time, you never came back.
(sobs)
Oh, don't cry, Norman.
-That's not my name!
-Oh, right.
-That's my other abandoned son.
-I have a brother!
And just what are you doing?
Putting the first new coat of paint
on this school in 30 years.
(chuckles)
It's always good to have a joker
in the platoon.
Bart, according to your folder,
you need some extra help.
Can you meet me after class?
No problemo.
I can move my 3:30 freeze tag.
Ugh, just cancel.
Bart, I'm glad that you're trying,
but I am worried that
you're starting from a place
far behind most students.
It's because I am so troubled, ma'am.
Vulnerable.
I need a firm but pretty hand.
Oh. Would you like Martin Prince
to tutor you?
No! Last time he was at my house,
he talked about bird-watching all day.
Even my mom got bored,
and she loves boredom.
Well, I guess I could see you
Tuesdays after school.
(sighs)
♪ Tuesday ♪
♪ Afternoon ♪
♪ I'm just beginning to see ♪
♪ Now I'm on my way ♪
♪ It doesn't matter to me ♪
♪ Chasing the clouds away ♪
SKINNER: Uh, Ms. Berrera?
(clears throat)
I was, uh, wondering
if you needed any help,
uh, pulling your maps.
You have to give 'em a snap.
Otherwise,
they just get longer and longer.
BART: Oh, my God, he loves her, too.
SKINNER: Oh, my God, he loves her, too.
HERRERA: (American accent)
Oh, my God, they love me, too!
That's right.
In my head, I sound like this.
LISA: No! No, no, no, no!
BART:
What happened? Did jazz die?
Look at me!
Acne? But she's only eight.
Somehow I'm becoming
a squeaky-voiced teen!
(voice cracking)
Do you want fries with that?
What am I saying?!
BART: I, too, was visited
by the Ghost of Puberty Present.
I've got a starter 'stache.
Next, I'm a loser,
then I'm a creep, then I'm a perv.
I've got to buy a van.
(crying) This isn't fair.
I'm not ready for my awkward years.
This is my happy childhood,
for crying out loud!
Aw. Beep, bop, boop.
Dialing for pizza.
-(grunts)
-Ow!
Somewhere, another mustache
is in tremendous pain.
It must be precocious puberty.
It's a thing.
I just read about it in Thing Magazine.
Homer, I'll fix Lisa up,
and you teach Bart to shave.
You got it. But there will be blood.
And there, there, and there.
The cream looks delicious,
but don't eat too much.
And there.
See how it's done, boy?
Dad, aren't you supposed to take
the little plastic thing off the blade?
Really?
I always wondered about that.
Hmm.
(humming)
(gasps) Well, hello, Billy Zane.
(purrs)
Sweetie, every kid goes through this.
That's why proms are dark.
Just stick some carrots in there
three times a day.
So we won't see your sweet little face
for ten more years?
(crying)
Mom, the inside of this hoodie
is covered in tears.
Let me try some makeup.
(whimpering)
-Cruelty-free?
-Oh, yes.
I'll be very gentle.
Marge? Marge, you got to see this!
Oh, what is it?
D'oh!
I actually have two different PTSDs.
The kind we combat veterans know.
And also parent-teacher-student dilemmas.
No!
(squeaking, grunts)
(gasps) Bart!
Do not worry.
I am certified as a paramedic.
Oh! Teacher, could you kiss my owie?
Boy owies can only be kissed by Willie.
(panting)
-Where's the owie?
-I'm fine. I'm fine.
Whoa, Lisa, you look great!
Beautiful and mature.
Like a sideline reporter.
Oh. R-Really?
Didn't know you were so cool.
Well, um, uh, well, duh.
LISA: Oh, my God, I'm popular!
Hope this doesn't go to my head.
It went right to my head! Aah!
So when you're done with this page,
you will learn how tectonic plates
rub against each other
till something gives deep down.
-(laughs)
-You do not have to tutor this boy
under the new One Child Left Behind law.
But he needs help, and he's not
going to be a child much longer.
He's got a mustache coming in.
Yeah, so beat it, bald lip.
-(cell phone chimes)
-Oh, my God!
I just got invited
to my first third-grade party!
Are the parents gonna be home?
-Yes.
-(scoffs) Lame.
Guys, I need to sharpen my mustaches.
Which is better--
A or B?
A... or B?
-A... or B?
-B.
-A.
-N.
Ugh! I'm tired of my son
having a mustache like a pool boy.
Hey, those pool boys
pull in some sweet jingle.
Plus, they get to work in flip-flops.
Homie, it's time we figured this out.
Maybe milk will help us think.
How would milk do that?
It's from cows who are smart enough
not to get turned into hamburger.
Hmm.
Oh.
I never looked closely
at this milk before.
Is it made by a soda company?
They don't just make soda, Marge.
They also make industrial foam.
(belches loudly)
Homer, it's the milk!
-Oh.
-Hey.
I'll call the help hotline on the carton.
(touch tones sounding)
(phone ringing)
Talk to me.
Yes, I need a milk refund.
Right. Um, address, please?
Wait, wait. Hold on.
742 Nevergreen...
Oh, Evergreen Terrace.
Sorry. Our system's a little slow.
(indistinct chatter)
(whistling)
-Aw!
-(both moaning)
Ew! I mean, cool!
I just turned a big corner, Bart.
(humming)
(laughing) Oh, Simpson,
I called you here to gloat.
(scoffs) Yeah, yeah,
I know about you and Berrera.
You know about me and Carol?
(gasps) You know her name?
Oh, first and middle, and I know more.
Her favorite salad bar item
is little shredded cheese.
(scoffs) Everyone likes that.
Oh, I know a lot more than that.
She's never seen an episode of Friends.
-Not even "The One With..."
-No, not one.
And she has a cat
with different color eyes.
His name is Bowie.
No!
Face it, Simpson,
you can't compete with me.
I can rent a car.
How can I derail his happiness?
I got a delivery of live class pets here.
Interesting. Excuse me.
-I have one question.
-Yes.
When you're in the shower,
do you shampoo your mustache?
Of course. It's a must-stache,
not an if-you-feel-like-it-stache.
All right, have a good day.
Dickory doo.
(both moaning)
I brought you some candy, Carol.
Not from CVS, not from Walgreens.
From the airport.
And I wasn't even going anywhere.
-Oh!
-Ah.
Your candy's filled with chupacabras.
We've been pranked or possibly punked.
I know who your prankster is.
The Simpson lad.
Were you watching us make out?
I was watching you try.
Mom, could you please, please,
please stay within the lip liner?
A week ago,
you'd never even worn makeup.
Now you're an expert like Ace Frehley.
(groans)
Sherri. Terri. (laughs)
I usually don't see double
until an hour into the party. (giggles)
(thunder rumbling)
LISA: It's going to rain,
and rain washes off makeup,
and then they will see me as I truly am--
imperfect, blemished,
a social mess in a lampshade dress.
(thunderclaps)
Okay, all right.
Lisa, you were never popular,
so you're playing with
the house's money.
Attention, party!
I'm not like you.
What I'm saying is,
I gave my Christmas money to NPR.
I have a chemistry set... that I've used!
MAN: Is there a point to this?
And beneath all this makeup,
I have... problem skin.
KIDS: Ew!
What are you talking about?
Your skin is fine.
Really? The bad milk wore off.
So, uh, admitting you're not cool
is probably the coolest thing
you can do, right? (laughs)
(kids murmuring)
I will see myself out.
(groans)
You look ba-lonely.
I feel ba-lonely.
-You want to be friends?
-I do.
Um, how clean is that hand?
Mmm... mah!
Cleaner now.
Okay.
A fish says, "Moo!"
(quietly) This isn't gonna last long.
I still take baths in the sink.
Okay, it's over. Sorry, Ralph.
I'll be eating crayons for one.
Oh, the plan is perfect!
I just have to get Skinner to hold still
while I slip a firecracker in his butt.
LISA: Come on, give it up.
Bart, I realized what's been going on.
We've been operating
under the influence of hormones.
Hormones? Sounds far-fetched.
(in deep voice) Very far-fetched.
Well, it's true, so give Skinner a shot.
Everyone deserves happiness.
Even wieners.
Hey, Dad, how much does
the Mustache Fairy pay?
Hmm, three bucks.
When you asked me to go skating,
I really thought you knew how.
Uh, I thought I could learn
by watching YouTubes this morning.
All right, Simpson, I'm here.
Do what you do best-- your worst.
Look, Seymour, I'm not gonna do a thing.
Carol, he's all yours.
Wow. The first war I've won.
Uh, Carol, all that's left is for you
to meet my mother,
and, uh, up she skates now.
My son, I just want to say,
I wish the four of you the best.
Four of us?
You, her,
your model planes and nudie books.
Sorry, Seymour.
Now I can't look at you
without picturing it.
Oh, my room's not that bad.
I'm talking about your mother.
(cackling)
Hey, listen, want to roast marshmallows?
-I'd like that.
-Great, man, great.
You're buying.
(saxophone playing)
Thank you, Simpson.
That does feel better.
Fire looks like it's dying down.
BART: Thanks, man.
Well, I guess a lot of women
leave their men
to go back and serve in Afghanistan.
No one drives 'em away like you, Seymour.
(saxophone playing)
Well, no more makeup for me. Ever!
What about when you're blowing
your stupid horn at Carnegie Hall?
(gasps) If you say it out loud,
it won't come true!
Carnegie Hall. Carnegie Hall.
Carnegie Hall.
(both grunting)
Looks like someone's
still drinking the milk.
(both grunting)
(saxophone playing)
(jazz playing)
-(crowd murmuring)
-Shh!
Subtitled by Jimmy Boots