CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
D'oh!
(tires screeching)
(grunts)
(whirring)
Mmm. Paper jam.
Okay, Dad, I'm ready for
Take Your Daughter to Work Day.
How come there's never
a Take Your Son to Work Day?
'Cause boys are already on track
to get all the good jobs.
The Dirty Dozen? All guys.
Twelve Angry Men? Uh, men!
The X-Men?
Mostly men.
-Good one, Dad.
-Yeah.
Well, despite all that,
today's going to be fun, Dad!
Will there be lots
of other girls there?
Just a few. For some reason,
there's been a lot
of infertility
at the nuclear plant.
After we show you the wealth
of jobs in the steno pool,
a hearty luncheon of bison
with lake beaver will be served.
GIRLS:
Ew!
And upon leaving,
you will each receive
a piece of orangewood
to bite down on during childbirth.
(chuckles)
Excellent.
(person applauds)
It's getting harder
and harder
to maintain my sunny disposition,
Smithers.
Oh, you're always
my ray of...
Shut up.
Dad, what does that do?
-I don't know.
-Who's that guy?
-Where do those pipes lead?
Not sure.
Is it called the cooling tower
because there's...
-Not my department.
-How many kilowatts are...?
Look, sweetie,
would you like to go
to the cafeteria
and get some ice cream?
-How many kinds are there?
-Twelve.
Curse that Elon Musk!
Thanks to that Earth-smooching
buttinski,
I'm on the verge of bankruptcy.
All I have left
are the clothes on my back
and the clones in my freezer.
43 is missing again.
I had to replace my beloved hounds
with teacup poodles.
It's pathetic. Watch.
Release the hounds.
(barking)
(chuckling)
Aw.
No. Help. Oh, stop.
Oh, spare me.
And all I got from Mr. Musk
was an electric car,
which I charge by stealing power
from my nosy neighbor.
Hey, dippily-do, neighbor-oni!
Stupid Branson.
But I have a new scheme
that will undo the terrible damage
done by my other schemes.
I have an appointment
with a Nigerian King
to negotiate a uranium deal
that will put me right back on top.
Nothing can stop you, sir.
But, uh, not that you're not
at the top of your game.
Uh, what if you
don't get the deal?
I'll just have
to sell everything
and move
to the South Pacific with you.
What a grim fate
that would be.
And with your omelet,
would you like the fried potatoes
or the mixed berries?
I'll have the berries.
Ah.
A terrible fate indeed, sir.
Oh, no. My almond milk
leaked all over everything.
Dad, do you have anything
I can eat?
Hmm?
Oh, uh, I will turn this corn chip
into a wonderful meal,
using my greatest skill--
lunchroom trading!
Shut your eyes.
("The Thieving Magpie"
by Rossini plays)
Pretty impressive, Homer.
But what about
the presentation?
The eyes taste first, then lips,
then palate.
Then the body's harshest critic--
the colon.
(Rossini's "Thieving Magpie" plays)
Okay, sweetie,
open those baby blacks.
(gasps)
Wow, Dad.
(giggles)
Thank you. Ooh.
Welcome, Your Majesty.
Mr. Burns, I don't know
what you have heard,
but I do not eat monkey brains
from a skull.
Oh, this is for me.
Before we begin,
I have a favor to ask.
My daughter is traveling with me.
Hello.
She is my true treasure.
During our complicated
negotiations,
I need someone
to look after her,
keep her out of trouble.
Hmm.
That man is the perfect choice.
What?!
Sir, that's Homer Simpson.
You forgot that
he's the most incompetent...
(both laughing)
Homer Simpson
would be perfect.
Simpson, all you have to do
is babysit the princess--
keeping her in this hotel room
during the negotiations.
Babysitting, eh?
What do I know about kids?
Homer Simpson, I give you
Princess Kemi of Nigeria!
Watch that girl like a hawk.
(screams)
Princess, why'd you put on
that coat?
You're obviously cold.
May I escort you
to the radiator?
No. I want to go out.
I'm 25 years old.
(phone ringing)
Uh, just a second.
Hey, Marge.
Yeah, I'm working late.
Yup, special project.
Lenny said you
were babysitting,
and if you are babysitting,
why can't you do some at home?
I could use a night out.
Sorry, Marge,
but I am the royal babysitter.
If I start watching commoners,
the tongues of the court
will be awag.
Really? Awag?
Really?
Well, if you think that...
-(beeps off)
-I want to go out
and see the America
whose greatest cities
I've only seen
destroyed in movies.
I see. You want excitement.
Princess, have you ever heard of
Studio 54, CBGBs, the Roxbury?
Yes! I've dreamed of...
All gone.
But in their place, we have
500 channels of television.
All awesome.
Sit down, and I'll show you.
So, all these concubines belong
to this one tyrant?
He's called "The Bachelor."
Please let me go out.
All right, Princess.
I'll take you to a place
that's fun with a capital "F."
(grunting)
Moe, this is Kemi.
She's an honest-to-God princess.
Ah, really?
Hey, tell me something.
I heard that Queen Elizabeth in person
is actually not that funny.
I am from Africa.
Wow, Africa.
I had a good friend
who really wanted to go there.
So, uh, you speak
English there?
I speak five languages.
(sputters)
Nobody does.
(speaking Portuguese)
(speaking French)
(speaking Spanish)
(speaking Japanese)
Uh, which means what?
"I don't wish to show off."
Yeah, that's pretty good there,
uh, but don't expect me
to bow and scrape.
Uh, well,
I'll give you one scrape.
Yeah, that's it, Majesty.
Notice I didn't say "Your."
(laughs)
Oh, they don't make them
like you in Nigeria.
Nigeria?
Homer, can I speak to you
in private?
(grunting)
Can I try it?
Ah, you got to be mad
at something.
Well, I'm mad I'm not doing it.
Okay, I'll tell you why I'm mad.
A few months back,
I got an unsolicited e-mail
from an actual Nigerian prince.
♪ ♪
The prince needed to transfer
$40 million out of the country.
He offered to split that with me
if I paid the five grand
for the transfer fees.
HOMER:
And you gave it to him?
MOE:
Yeah, I did.
I was sure the guy
was on the level
because of his bad spelling
and grammar.
Now, guess how much
of the $20 million I saw?
-$8 million?
-Ze-ro.
Get out of here!
If Kemi there
is a Nigerian princess,
her brother just might be
the Nigerian prince
that took my money!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Listen, Moe, I'm Kemi's guardian.
She and I are going back
to the hotel now!
(gasps)
She's gone!
And she trashed my bar!
Oh, no, wait.
She actually cleaned up a little bit.
Yeah, good for her.
(panting)
Chief, thank God!
I was drinking at Moe's,
and I lost an African princess!
Lost African princess, eh?
Well,
lucky for you, she just happens
to be in the back of my cruiser.
Yes! The prayer I forgot to say
has been answered.
What the...?
You're going straight
to the drunk tank, rummy.
"African princess."
(distant gunshots)
Chief, I just saw someone
robbin' the Kwik-E-Mart!
Oh, now African princesses
are robbing the Kwik-E-Mart, huh?
Get in the car, booze bag.
Chief, I have been shot
in the shoulder!
In the car!
What is this, St. Patrick's Day?
Why, this is terrible.
Can't even think of anything
to mumble to myself.
That's how upset I am here.
Hello. First of all,
I wanted to pay.
Also... maybe...
I wanted to talk more to you?
Really?
Okay there, Moe,
you got to get to the brother,
because he knows what
my PIN number is, and I forgot.
Yeah, duly noted.
Uh, so, Your Tootsieness,
tell me about your family.
Got any aunts, uncles,
cousins, sisters...
brothers?
I have a brother.
Yes. One.
I see.
Now, Moe,
don't jump to conclusions.
A lot of people have brothers.
-Does he have a computer?
-Yes.
MOE: It's him!
HOMER:
Guys,
thanks for bailing me out,
but I still have
a huge problem.
Well, till we find her,
maybe we could get somebody
to pretend to be her.
You know, get a nice wig
and a dress.
Oh, no, I am not dressing up
like an African princess.
I am not! I am not! I am not!
Thank you for listening
to my objections.
Well,
you were really vehement.
(phone ringing)
Uh, hello, Simpson.
Just checking up.
May I speak
with the princess?
Um, yeah, sure. Uh...
(high-pitched Southern accent)
Hello, this is the princess.
I'm with Homer Simpson,
and I do declare he's wonderful.
Oh, that's right,
I'm from South Africa.
Fiddle-dee-dee.
Well, sounds like everything's
going just the way I want it.
Yeah, so all my money's
tied up in this "jernt."
Can't even afford
elocution lessons
to teach me how
to pronounce "joint."
I guess I could do it online,
but, uh, what's the "pernt"?
(laughs)
What-What's so funny?
I thought my English
was perfect,
but you make me feel
even better about it.
(chuckles)
Eh, usually people that tease me
get thrown out on their ass.
But, uh, your sayin' it
made me feel good.
Geez, I sound like one
of those guys in them rom coms
that play at the theaters
next to the theater I'm in. Heh.
So, uh, what's a "princessess"
like you, uh, do all day, huh?
A lot of spinning wheels
and witches treating you like crap?
I read. Are you familiar
with the books
by my countryman Chinua Achebe,
Things Fall Apart and No Longer At Ease?
Hey, you guys got real
optimistic literature there.
(giggles)
Fair comment.
(yawns)
I haven't eaten all day.
Well, don't eat those eggs!
Uh, we don't know
what kind of bird
they turn into.
But there's
a string cheese or something
in the fridge in the back.
Uh, help yourself.
All right, after she eats,
I'd better close up.
(yawns)
Oh. Come on, pal.
(grunts)
Come on.
That's really stuck there good.
Ah, I can't be mad
at her no more.
Good night, moon.
Good night, broom.
Good night, jukebox
that won't play a tune.
Good night, eggs.
Good night, dregs.
Good night, bugs
crawlin' up my legs.
Good night, beer.
Good night, mice.
Good night, princess
who treats me nice.
Yeah.
(yawns)
So my offer
for one ton of your uranium
is a goat.
Will you stop offering me that?
I come from a modern nation
of 90 million people.
-Two goats.
-You are starting to insult me.
All right,
let's cut to the chase.
My board has given me permission
to go up to 12 goats.
(grumbles)
-How about here, sir?
-Looks good to me.
I'm so sorry
I pretended not to be gay
for all those years.
Well, better an old queen
than never a queen at all.
(chuckles)
Pay attention.
My last offer:
20 million goats.
Okay, but no dogs
disguised as goats.
Oh, great,
here comes the haggling.
Well, well, look who's up. Heh.
Uh, Princess, I'm gonna
do something for you
I've never done for anyone in this bar.
Call you a cab.
No. I want to spend time with you.
I want to see this town.
Do you mind
ridin' a cute little scooter
with your arms around my waist?
I don't.
To the scooter store.
♪ ♪
And after you eat the soup,
you can eat the bowl
or you can put "kerns" in it.
What, uh, whatever you like.
I have a confession to make.
This is my first montage.
Just relax and enjoy the music.
Moe Szyslak.
This is the part of the fairy tale
where the princess
goes back to the hotel
and watches TV.
Come with me.
So where are we headed, dude?
Just go and go fast.
Okay, um,
usually I do kind of a funny take
on an airline pilot
greeting the passengers.
You know, like,
"Hey. Thank you for flying Air Kevin.
If you look out to the left
of the pedicab, you..."
Just move the pedals.
Whoa, sounds like the tower
has cleared us for takeoff.
We're tryin' to escape that guy.
Well, dude, as long as he can run,
he can beat us.
D'oh!
So, anyways, the place that
I really feel the pedaling?
It's my legs.
Okay, all right, we're safe.
Actually,
I wanted to go back with him.
I don't want to get
my father mad, O.
Go back? But I didn't
show you the place
where Dave Grohl got mugged.
I have to leave,
but I still had a wonderful day.
MOE: Thank God I shaved
my forehead this morning.
-(shutter clicks)
-(gasps)
A paparazzo?
Please don't send that.
If my father sees it,
it will ruin my life.
Well, thanks for making it so easy.
And you have
the 20 million goats?
Two, now.
19,999,998
on delivery.
-Very good.
-Um, shouldn't we
see how the princess is doing
before you sign,
Your Majesty?
What are you talking about,
Smithers?
(phone dings)
(gasps)
I can't even trust you
to watch an impetuous adult
who does what she wants?
The deal is off.
SMITHERS: Wow.
After spending my life serving others,
I'm finally gonna get what I want.
Uh, sir, there may be a bright side.
There's never a bright side.
SMITHERS:
(chuckles) He's almost mine.
Yes, you've torn that up,
all right.
Father, I want to explain.
I was a young woman
who wanted to see the world,
and this kind man
has shown it to me.
And stolen your heart.
Eh, well, that's what I do.
Uh, sorry, but there ain't
no off switch for this.
(laughs)
He has not stolen my heart.
Wha?!
Why has he made the ancient
tribal sound of confusion?
I think he is a sweet,
sweet man.
But when I kissed him
on the forehead,
it was not romantic.
More like when
Snow White kissed Dopey.
Oh, no, no,
not this comparison again.
I'm sorry, Moe.
I don't love you.
But I really like you.
Well, daughter, even though
you have done nothing seriously wrong,
first I will tear this contract
one more time.
(grunts)
And as for you,
your punishment will be...
Uh, may I speak to you,
Majesty,
father to father?
A woman has allowed you
to sire her children?
There was beer involved.
I have two daughters.
And I've learned you have
to let them go their own way.
Even the one-year-old.
Majesty.
And the older one,
I can't tell her what to do.
-And she's only 12.
-Eight.
See what I mean?
Always an argument.
Hmm.
But the thing you
have to remember is
that you have to let
them be who they are
because you love them.
I am not convinced.
Uh, because you
want them to grow.
Still not convinced.
Then because you can't
strangle a girl.
That makes sense.
-Oh...
-Come here, Daughter.
Oh, Father.
Little girl, let me
give you some advice.
Never dream big, because
it will blow up in your face.
You're talking to the girl
who wants a career in jazz.
Oh, poor thing.
So the good king's
cheap uranium will
allow me to sell you
expensive nuclear power.
Everyone wins.
Yes, yes. Princess.
Can you tell us about
the man you kissed?
Uh, yeah, I'll field that.
Uh, yesterday,
a local man
"may or may not"
have given a tour
to a certain princess,
who, uh, one assumes,
turned all his thoughts
of revenge
to love and then
love to respect.
And yesterday,
a certain princess
may or may not have seen
much of your world
with a certain man,
and she certainly
might be eternally grateful.
Oh, this is vague stuff.
Vague stuff!
I did not think this through.
Moe, before I left,
I just wanted to give you
these examples
of our most beloved,
albeit depressing, literature.
Ah, some nice bedtime readin'.
Fun premise.
I'm laughing already.
Really not
cheerin' me up here,
but, uh, let me offer you
the only literature
in this bar--
sure works for me, though.
This coaster.
I will treasure it.
Well, I guess you'll pine forever
for a man who doesn't care,
while I just grow old
here in this bar.
Yeah.
Here's to suffering in silence.
Oh.
Mm. Can't wait to see those numbers
hanging from my rafters.
(sighs)
I can't believe it's been
three years since Smithers left.
Man, have I been aging badly.
But I guess I can finally
wash this forehead.
Oh, divine.
(doorbell ringing)
Oh, God, what do you want?
Well, neighbor, now that
your streak of rum luck
is at its end,
I have a favor to ask.
It involves charity.
I've set up
the Virgin Earth Challenge,
a $25 million prize
to eliminate
greenhouse gases,
that I was hoping
you would add to.
Where are the hounds
when I need them?
They're on a free Virgin Galactic flight
around the world.
Can you go five blasted minutes
without saying the word "virgin"?
That's another Virgin Challenge
that I will not be Virgin taking.
Virgin.
-(crowd murmuring)
-Shh!
Subtitled by B. Everdene