CHORUS: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(theme music playing)
(bell ringing)
[alarm sounding)
(beeps)
(playing the blues)
(jazzy solo)
(clinks)
(horn honking)
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
(screams)
(yelling)
ANNOUNCER: Okay, FDR is
in the White House,
an ice cream cone
costs a nickel,
and a hot new tune
by Benny Goodman
is hitting the charts.
-The year is 1939.
-(snoring)
19... 1939!
Oh, my God.
I've gone back in time!
I've got to warn everybody
about Hitler!
And get to the ice cream store!
Hey, Homer,
what's all the hubbub?
Let me guess-- you travel
back in time again?
Shut up.
You haven't even been born yet.
Easy, Homer,
I'll bring you back.
(tuning radio)
("The Safety Dance" playing)
Oh, boy, am I glad
to see you guys.
MARTY:
That was Men Without Hats.
Or as they're known today...
Men Without Jobs!
(laughing)
BILL:
Hey, don't go there, Marty.
MARTY:
I'm not going anywhere.
I'm staying right here
at P. J. O'Harrigan's!
We're broadcasting
live from P. J. O'H's
and this place
makes Animal House
look like
Terms of Endearment!
We're kicking off our
35th consecutive happy hour
with no end in sight.
-So come on down.
-(cheering)
Man, that sounds like
a swinging shindig.
Yeah, too bad we got
to work, huh, Homer?
Homer?
HOMER: Woo-hoo! Let's party!
Wake up, Homer.
Eh?
Come on. Move your butt.
You're blocking traffic.
(honking horn)
That's no way to address
Sir Drinks-A-Lot.
(groans)
Come on.
Let's get you inside
and scrape the gum
out of your hair.
Okay...
Hey, Marge,
what's your
favorite radio station?
-Well, Marge...
-What?
What's your favorite
radio station?
Okay, Dad. We're ready.
Hey, that's super.
See you later.
Dad, don't you remember?
It's our special Saturday.
You agreed to spend
one Saturday a month
doing something with the kids.
Oh!
Oh, quit complaining.
It's half the work
of a divorced dad.
Yeah, but it's twice as much
as a deadbeat dad.
Homer!
They know I'm kidding.
(both moaning)
Okay, Bart,
it's your turn to pick.
Where are we headed?
Bowling? Demolition Derby?
P. J. O'Harrigan's?
Isn't that a funny name?
Huh? Huh?
Hysterical. But I traded my
turn to Lisa for her dessert.
-No! We did a Lisa thing last month!
-MARGE: (grumbles)
(laughing)
And I'm glad we did.
But now I think
we should do something
normal people would like.
Why do you assume that I won't
pick something fun?
Let's see.
-Oh, this looks very educational.
-Oh!
Well, this could be
quite enlightening.
-Oh! Oh!
-Fine. How about--
She didn't say it yet.
-Go ahead, sweetie.
-The book fair?
Oh, no.
I'm not falling
for that again.
If it doesn't have
Siamese twins in a jar,
it's not a fair.
Oh, this is perfect.
We're going to go
see Marmaduke?
No, the Smithsonian
Traveling Exhibit.
It encapsulates America
and makes history come alive.
What? And Marmaduke doesn't?
Sorry, Dad.
My mind is made up.
This is your fault
for trading away your turn.
Just for that,
no dessert tonight.
Trade you my next turn
for your dessert.
-Deal.
-D'oh!
Hey, how come the Smithsonian
needs to be sponsored
by a cell phone company?
I can answer that.
Uncle Sam needs
to spend our tax dollars
on the essentials.
Anti-tobacco programs,
pro-tobacco programs,
killing wild donkeys,
and Israel.
Good old government.
Yeah, but corporate sponsorship
cheapens our nation's
treasures.
Actually, they're Omnitouch's
treasures now.
We bought them during
the last budget crisis.
(gasping) Look, they have
Lincoln's hat.
Thank God for grave robbers.
Oh, America's greatest citizen
summed up in one piece
of clothing.
HOMER (gasping):
Fonzie's jacket!
Who's Fonzie?
"Who's Fonzie?"
Don't they teach you
anything in school?
He freed the squares.
How can they put a prop
from a TV show
next to the Bill of Rights?
So what's so great
about the Bill of Rights?
It guarantees all
of the basic freedoms.
Speech, religion,
the right to a speedy trial...
HOMER: Where?
I don't see that.
(gasping) Dad!
Don't do that!
-(alarm buzzing)
-(guns cocking)
Get out of
Archie Bunker's chair! Now!
Relax. I'm just boning up
on the old constitution.
Oh, you're going
to regret that, pinko.
Oh, I am so sick of people
hiding behind
the Bill of Rights.
Look, he got chocolate on it.
I didn't mean to. Look...
Mm-hmm. You just
licked off the part
that forbids cruel
and unusual punishment.
(chuckling)
Beautiful.
Really? That much?
It's going to cost $10,000
to repair that document.
What?
Of course, Omnitouch
understands
that real money doesn't grow on trees.
Not these days.
Finally, a company
that understands my needs.
We sure do.
It's called caring.
So, we're even then?
Not by a long shot.
But I have a solution
that'll work out for both of us.
Especially you.
I don't want
a cellular transmitter
sticking out of my roof.
We prefer to think of them
as "keep in touch towers."
It's called caring, Marge.
Plus, you've increased
Springfield's roaming
capabilities 64%.
You've got to admit, Marge,
that's a lot more roaming.
Oh, I guess.
Hey, this is pretty
comfortable.
That Andy Capp
was on to something.
Ugh. That antenna is an
eyesore.
Just pretend it's a tree,
honey.
Or as we say at Omnitouch,
a "progress tree."
Yeah, well, I hope
it doesn't hum too loud
'cause I have a ton
of homework to do
and if don't finish it by...
(screams)
My room!
What? I heard a yell.
Did you touch a wire?
What happened to my room?
Nothing. They just
needed a place to put
all the electronic gizmos
and I know much you like that
science-y stuff, so I decid--
You gave away my room?
Come on, Lisa,
try and see this
from the Omnitouch
Corporation's point of view.
Your father's right, Lisa.
Cellular service is about
communication and unity.
Community.
Hmm.
Oh...
I can't believe
you did this, Dad.
Why didn't you put
that thing in your room?
Hmm, that thought
never occurred to me.
Funny how your mind works
in a crisis.
It's just until we pay off
Daddy's desecration
of a priceless artifact.
I thought I'd never
have to say that again.
Uh. But where am I
supposed to live?
Lisa... what's
your favorite movie?
Until you taped over it,
The Little Mermaid.
That's right, The Odd Couple.
So meet your comically
mismatched roommate,
Bart Simpson!
(hums "The Odd Couple" theme)
I'm going to make your life
a living hell.
Uh-oh.
(humming continues)
Dad!
Whoa.
Okay, if you're going
to live in my room
you're going to obey
my rules.
One, I am Bart, thy god.
If I am out,
the Krusty doll is thy god.
If the doll's with me,
you will worship
the Night-light.
Should the Night-light
be unable to fulfill
its duties...
-Shut up.
-You shut up.
Oh, this is not going to work.
No, you shut up.
(groaning) Oh...
(electric current crackling)
-PRINCIPAL SKINNER: Hello, Mother?
-(gasping) Maggie?
MRS. SKINNER:
Seymour, you were supposed
to call me three minutes ago.
Sorry, Mother, I was driving
through a tunnel
and my cell phone
wouldn't work.
I don't want you driving
through tunnels.
You know what that symbolizes.
But, Mother, it cuts 90 minutes
off my drive.
MRS. SKINNER: No tunnels!
Homer, we're picking up
cell phone calls
over the baby monitor.
Whoo! Anything spicy?
Oh, that's not the point.
We should report this
to an Omnitouch care rep.
People's privacy is at stake.
Great. I'm going
to eat mayonnaise.
(groans)
(chair squeaking)
Bart, stop it.
-Stop what?
-Squeaking that chair.
Hey, that's what I do
in my room, Lis.
I squeak my chair.
-(squeaking faster)
-Argh!
Oh, quit it, quit it,
quit it, quit it!
Well, well, if it isn't
Frick and Frack,
Jack and Jill, Fred and Ethel,
the three...
Dad, will you please tell Bart
to stop squeaking his chair?
I'm trying
to do my homework.
Bart, stop squeaking
your chair.
If you've got to do
something, click this pen.
(clicking)
No!
-Hey, that looks like fun.
-Race you.
You're on.
Lisa, you play winner.
(rapid clicking)
Come on, come on!
-I'm gaining on ya!
-(both laughing)
Oh, honey, you missed
a great race.
Bart was winning,
but then he said,
"this is stupid,"
and he stopped and I won.
Dad, I am trying
to do my homework.
Hmm. Hey, you're mad at me.
That wasn't
your mayonnaise, was it?
Dad, why did you have
to take away my room?
Maybe you'd feel better
if we watched
some TV together.
(groans) I just want to study.
-That's no fun.
-It is to me.
-No, it's not.
-Dad!
Oh, here's something
you'll like--
"When animals attack
magicians."
MAN: Pick a card, any...
-(baboon screeches)
-(man screams)
-(chuckling)
-That's awful.
-Awful entertaining.
-(stomach gurgling)
Oh, my stomach hurts.
Hey, it's Krusty.
I need you to get me
out of another jam.
I picked up this chick
last night.
At least I thought
she was a chick.
(laughing)
Showbiz is so fascinating.
Uh, Mom,
I don't feel so good.
(groans)
What is it, honey?
My tummy really hurts.
Somebody wants mommy
to change baby's diaper.
Is that somebody you, Homer?
Yes, it is.
Okay, then you can take Lisa
to Dr. Hibbert's.
Great. Maybe on the way back,
we can swing
by the Demolition Derby
and have a nice talk.
Oh, sounds great.
-(gurgling)
-Lisa, I'm afraid
your tummy ache
may be caused by stress.
Well, that's a relief.
(chuckles) Yes. Anyway,
when it comes to stress,
I believe laughter
is the best medicine.
You know, before I learned
to chuckle mindlessly,
I was headed
for an early grave myself.
(chuckling)
Give it a try, honey.
(half-hearted chuckling)
Oh, now,
you call that chuckling?
Come on, child, force it.
I'm really not
the chuckling type.
It's true. I'm always making
clever noises
and she never chuckles at 'em.
Well, I could prescribe
some harsh antacids,
but I think Lisa
would benefit more
from some herbal teas
or aromatherapy.
Yeah, you know,
some of that all-natural stuff
is really very...
Oh, no, you don't.
Screw that touchy-queery crap.
We'll take the harsh antacids.
Nothing's too good
for my little girl.
I sure settled his hash.
Imagine that quack
thinking you'd try
one of those crazy
new-age cures.
They're not all crazy, Dad.
Sure they are, honey.
You know, just because
you say something is crazy
doesn't make it so,
and just because you think
museums are boring
and demolition derbies are fun
doesn't make that true, either!
I'm sorry, Lisa.
Oh, it's not your fault.
I know we love each other, Dad,
but we're two
very different people,
and, much as I hate to say it,
as time goes on,
we'll probably just drift
further and further apart.
HOMER: Oh, Lisa, honey,
I won't ever let that happen.
Oh.
Dad, you don't have to go
to a new-age store just for me.
I know you think
this stuff is stupid.
Nah, you must be
thinking of your mother.
I'm always exploring
alternatives
and expanding my horizons
into realms of...
Can't we just go in?
(bell ringing)
Oh, good...
I've been meaning to buy a...
"dream-catcher"?
Give me a break.
I just wish
you could keep an open mind
about other cultures.
Other cultures are fine.
I'm just saying
I can get along in life
without a... "toothbrush."
Namaste.
And, uh, ooga-booga to you, too.
May I tell you
about our white-light specials?
Absolutely not.
My little girl's tummy hurts.
Do you have anything
to stop her complaining?
Dad!
Here...
try this wheat grass juice.
(slurping) Blah!
Well, your tongue works.
Mm-hmm. Hmm...
Let's try some oil of Lorenzo,
and, uh, what's keeping
Joan Rivers alive?
Fetal grindings,
but I have a better idea.
Oh, no, no freezing.
No, Mr. Simpson,
this is
a sensory-deprivation tank.
It blocks out
all the external distractions
-that bombard our souls.
-Can you pee in it?
-I'll take two hours.
-Me, too.
You're about to take
a journey into the mind.
You may see
and experience things
that are strange
and frightening,
but remember,
they can't physically harm you,
though they may
destroy you mentally.
HOMER: So what?
LISA:
Ah, this is kind of relaxing,
but it's so hard
to turn off my brain.
I have to stop thinking,
starting... now.
Hey, it worked.
Oh, no, that's thinking.
HOMER: Boring.
(over radio)
Lenny, how you doing? It's Moe.
I got some
class-three gossip here.
LENNY: Well... dish.
MOE: Groundskeeper Willie,
you know,
the guy in the skirt?
He bought himself
a mail-order bride,
but he was too cheap
to pay the C.O.D. Right?
So she's still in the crate
down at the post office.
-You want to go...
-Ooh, this sounds juicy.
Hmm...
Hey, Milhouse,
want to have some fun?
Uh...
Okay.
How am I supposed to
hallucinate with all these swirling colors
distracting me?
Hey...
Oh, it's a ball of yarn.
That's funny.
I feel like batting it around.
Wow, I have a paw!
Oh, my gosh.
I've entered the body
of our cat.
(sucking)
Ah! Maggie!
Hey, hey,
get your sticky hands off me.
Ow!
(hisses)
Oh, bad cat. Leave her alone.
(grunts)
LISA: (screams)
Wow, my mind just created
that out of nothing.
This tank is releasing
the full potential of my brain.
♪ Ooh-eee ooh-ah-ah ♪
♪ Ting-tang,
walla-walla-bing-bang ♪
♪ Ooh-eee ooh-ah-ah ♪
♪ Walla-bing-bang
ting-ting, too... ♪
Come on, come on,
I need some gossip here.
Where is everybody?
Does this town
shut down at 5:00?
Frankie, it's me, Killer.
I just busted out of prison
and the cops are after me.
Ooh, talk to me, baby.
Okay, I think I lost them.
-(mooing)
-Uh-oh, a cow.
Eat lead, bossy.
Listen, Tony,
I need someplace to hide.
Oh, this place looks good--
"742 Evergreen Terrace."
-(gasps)
-Now, to open the door
and kill whoever's inside.
I'll start by turning the knob.
(laughing)
Got you, Mrs...
(groans)
Oh, my God.
BART: (laughing)
Oh, Mom, you are
a prankster's dream.
(laughs)
Wow, you really
clobbered him.
That was a horrible trick
to play on your mother.
Yeah, well, it serves you right
for eavesdropping.
Hmm.
Well, I guess we both learned
a lesson...
But, if anybody asks,
you hit him.
(groaning)
CLERK: But you can't just
repossess our merchandise.
The I Ching said I had
six months till bankruptcy.
Hey, channel somebody
who gives a damn.
Can't we discuss this
over some sympathy tea?
Sorry, the teas are
already on the truck.
There's only enough room
on the truck for this one.
We'll get the other one later.
(both grunting)
Hey... this piece of junk
is finally doing something.
(laughs)
Oh, man, this is heavy!
You should lift
with your legs.
Yeah, aw, screw it.
I got health insurance. Oh!
Abracadabra.
The crystal says,
"Your baby shall be a girl."
Shut up!
(tires squealing)
(crashes)
Whoo!
Sensory deprivation kicks ass!
-(brakes squealing)
-(gasping)
Oh, Neddy, you almost hit
that coffin.
(gasping) Leapin' Lazarus!
Is this what passes
for eternal rest these days?
Rod, go get Daddy
his burying shovel.
Yay!
You sure buried him deep,
Daddy.
(laughing) Not so deep
the Lord can't find him...
and judge him.
This is the best birthday
I ever had.
Okay, I'm ready
to get out now.
Yoo-hoo, hippie lady.
Hippie lady?
Hey, hippie lady!
(yelling)
Oh! What's going on?
Oh! Ow! Oh!
This inner-peace stuff is tough
on the old coconut!
(grunting)
Hippie lady,
I want to get out.
Oh!
(humming)
Hmm? Look, Daddy,
a whale egg.
Oh, geez, I am so sick
of companies dumping their crud
in our ocean
without a permit.
It's not like
those permits are hard to get.
You're going right back
where you came from.
But, Daddy,
you're on vacation.
Crime doesn't take a vacation.
Hey, hey, hey, careful!
You'll pop it!
Wow, I've been a cat,
a tree, and Cokie Roberts.
(gasps)
It's happening again.
I wonder where
I'm going this time.
What's that? Oh, yuck!
That sandwich is full of meat!
There's... bacon...
Canadian bacon...
Mexican bacon...
(loudly salivating)
LISA: (as Homer)
And a mouthwatering veal chop.
(slurping)
Oh, no. Now I'm Dad.
Oh... and I'm
at a stupid, boring ballet.
(yawning)
(snoring)
Dad! Wake up!
Your snoring is disturbing
the dancers.
Hmm.
How can you embarrass me
like this?
Ooh, you won't sit
through anything
that doesn't have car crashes.
I'm sorry, honey.
Jeez, why's she so mad at me?
I only came to this dump
so I could be with her.
And what happened
to my big sandwich?
(snoring)
(sighs)
(groans)
Boy... I can really be a pain
in the butt.
-(creaking)
-Gee, I should cut Dad some slack.
After all,
he did take me to the ballet
and the Smithsonian Exhibit.
In fact, he takes me
lots of places he hates.
HOMER:
♪ I told the witch doctor ♪
♪ There's tightness in my chest,
bom-bom-bom-bom-bom ♪
♪ I told the witch doctor
he had to run a test... ♪
Hi, sweetie.
Hi, Dad. How was it?
I went on a wild ride
without ever leaving
the building.
How was yours?
Pretty cool,
but now what do you say
we go do something
we'll both enjoy?
Oh... like what?
(screeching)
(crashing)
Whoa, look at that car burn.
Does it get
any better than this?
Not to me, Dad.
(screeching and crashing)
Oh!
(laughter)
(siren wailing)
ANNOUNCER: (laughs)
Here comes the ambulance.
(theme music playing)
Shh.
Captioned by
Visual Data Media Services