CHORUS: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
(whistle blows)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
(tinkles)
(honking horn)
(tires screeching)
D'oh! (screams)
Hello! I'm Kent Brockman.
(polite applause)
And I'm teen sensation, Britney Spears.
(wild cheering)
And I'm Kent Brockman.
With Britney Spears!
And we're here to present the...
-...sixty-fifth...
-...Annual...
-...Spring...
-...Field...
-...Pride A-
-wards.
Tonight, we'll be recognizing
outstanding members
-of...
-The...
Springfield community!
This is my year, Marge.
Everyone knows I'm what
makes this city great!
I don't know. There's a lot of buzz
around Lenny.
Our first Springfield Pride Award
goes to a local legend.
A man who brings laughter and joy
to the children of Springfield.
With his big red nose and baggy pants...
-BROCKMAN: Krusty the Clown!
-Hey, hey!
-(applause)
-What?
-Who are you?
-Seat filler.
Aw...
Everyone gets an award, but me.
I can't help it if I donated
the most blood.
Oh, I'm feeling kind of woozy. (groans)
Oh, why won't anyone give me an award?
You won a Grammy.
I mean an award that's worth winning.
You know, Kent, in today's
youth-obsessed culture,
we sometimes forget that
older people are still alive.
I told ya!
Well, sorry !
And that's why our final award
honors a man
who's lived in Springfield for 108 years.
Our oldest resident,
-Cornelius Chapman!
-(applause)
SPEARS: Cornelius Chapman
built the first log cabin
in Springfield
and introduced the toothbrush
-to our fair city.
-(people exclaiming)
BROCKMAN: For years, he was Springfield's
only basketball player,
but he still managed
-to entertain the crowd.
-(cheering)
SPEARS: In the market crash of 1929,
he helped people jump out
of windows to avoid disgrace.
You're doing the right thing.
Oh-oh, out you go!
-Oh!
-(chuckling)
My! You're a big one!
No-no. No turning back now.
Off a tall building!
That's a great way to do it!
And in 1935, our honoree
took a bullet for Huey Long.
(groans)
-No!
-(groans)
And now, Springfield's oldest citizen...
He is, like, totally venerable.
-Cornelius Chapman!
-(applause)
-Mwah!
-(gagging)
(all gasp)
Well, guess we should've
expected that.
Well, this award has to go to somebody.
Would everyone, who is 60 or older,
please stand up?
Over 80?
Ninety?
One hundred years old?
Homer, sit down!
-What's that, sonny?
-(growling)
(cheering)
Well, this is all so sudden.
Ah! Don't give me that kiss of death,
you black widow!
Argh! Ah! Boy, he didn't want
to let go of that!
OK, let's see.
I don't have a speech prepared,
but, uh...
Abracadaver!
"Thank you all so much.
I love Springfield
from the cuddliest infant to the...
(whispering) puppies, patriotism...
bluebirds."
I'm not reading this drivel.
This speech is over.
(sparse applause)
(grunting)
Well, that was a great night for us all!
That's not an award.
That's part of the set.
Nothing you can say
will diminish this honor.
(grunting)
(sighs) Now that I'm
the town's oldest man,
I'm starting to realize
I'm not a young man anymore!
I'll have to start taking
better care of myself.
You know, I haven't had
a medicine-o checkup in ages.
Sir, you deserve the finest
doctors in the world.
I'm taking you to the Mayo Clinic
in Minnesota.
Very well, but I'll need someone
to watch my house.
Who's that fella who always
screws up and creates havoc?
Homer Simpson, sir?
Yes! The way I figure it,
he's due for a good performance.
(groaning)
Now, if the house catches fire,
I want you to call this number.
Uh-huh. The fire department.
Yes. They're new, but they're good.
Sir, we should get going.
Don't worry about a thing.
We'll take good care of your house.
HOMER: Look at me!
I'm a billionaire!
(yelling)
I forgot my...
(chuckling)
Good Lord!
This bedroom is as big as our house.
And the bed never needs to be made.
Check it out.
(chuckling and gasping)
Hmm. Seems a little wasteful.
Wasteful and practical.
A mechanical dressing dealy.
Watch this, Marge.
(gears grinding)
Oh! Oh! Ow! Oh, no! Oh!
(bell dings)
Now I'm ready to hit the town.
Hmm.
(chuckles)
(tumblers click)
-Close that door.
-(Bart screams)
Wow! He's got every Nancy Drew.
Even the controversial Clue In The Clock.
Tsk-tsk-tsk, so many swears.
(panting)
I'm Al Unser Jr.!
-I'm Princess Margaret!
-(horse neighing)
I'm drunk!
(groaning)
It's nothing serious.
Just lay off the chili
-and you should be fine.
-(laughing)
Don't you laugh, Fidel.
I've been in the car with you.
Let's see. Social security number:
Naught-naught-naught... Naught-naught...
Naught-naught-naught-two.
(whispers) Damn Roosevelt!
Cause of parents' death, got in my way.
Mom, Bart's making faces at me!
-I think.
-Look how loud I have to yell!
This all seems a little elaborate
for sloppy joes.
Hmm. I know what
the other 11 forks are for,
but what do you do with this one?
Why, Marge, I believe
you're supposed to scratch
your ass with it.
Homer, watch your lang--
Oh! That's a lifesaver!
Man, this is living!
Hmm. Stop that!
Cigars are for rich people
and legendary comedians,
like Bill Crosby and David Letterson.
(humming)
Oops! Forgot to swirl it.
Homer, did you jimmy open
Mr. Burns's liquor cabinet?
"Jimmy" is such an ugly word, Marge,
Unless you're talking about Jimmy Smits.
(sexy growl)
But house-sitting is a sacred... Hey!
MARGE: Stop swirling, Homer.
Listen, I worked long
and hard for this place,
and no one's going
to take it away from me.
Not you, not its rightful owner,
not anybody.
And another thing, if I ev--
Operator, get me Thailand.
T-I... And so on.
Homer, who are you calling?
Everybody. I found Burnsy's address book.
I called the New York Yankees
and told them to bunt.
And then I called the Queen of England
and asked her
how it was going. And then, I--
Well, don't run up Mr. Burns' phone bill.
Just a second, Marge. Hello, Thailand?
How's everything on your end?
Uh-huh. That's some language
you got there.
And you talk like that 24/7, huh? Hey!
Homer, you've got to stop
pretending this is your house.
You're not a billionaire.
Geez, way to burst my bubble, Marge.
All I'm saying is don't get
too comfortable.
Mr. Burns will be back tomorrow.
Marge, you're right.
We do have to have a party.
Party? No. No parties.
What about "partays"?
No partays, no shindigs,
no keggers, no hootenannies,
no mixers, no raves,
-no box socials.
-Damn!
And I looked so good on that bike.
Now, doctor, I want you to test me
for everything...
Every disease on this chart.
Fine. We'll just start
by drawing some blood.
Well, isn't that odd? It's like poking
-through meringue.
-Oh, try this arm.
I saw some blood in there the other day.
Come on, keep blowing.
OK, 12 centimeters. Excellent!
I'm a big boy!
(machine whirring)
-There's your problem.
-(growls)
(snarls)
(Moe humming)
Having a party, Moe. I'll need four kegs
of your finest imported-sounding beer.
How about Tuborg,
the beer of Danish kings?
Mm! Danish.
Now, you know I can't sell you
no beer till 2:00 p.m.
on account of it's Sunday.
Huh? If you can't sell beer,
what are Lenny and Carl doing here?
Huh? Oh, we're just watching
the sun move across the sky.
When it gets to here, we can drink again.
But I need that beer now.
Sorry, 2:00 p.m.
Or you can steal a boat
and sail out to international waters.
-Huh!
-What's that, a theme park?
No. The ocean.
Once you get 12 miles out,
there's no laws. That's where they held
the Tyson-Secretariat fight.
HOMER: He-he. They were so drunk.
Gentlemen, get off your knees.
Your rich uncle, Homer,
is throwing the wildest Box Social
the high seas have ever seen!
And you're invited.
Yeah! All right!
(yelling)
Oh, no, you don't.
I'm not going to let
you trash Mr. Burns' yacht.
Marge, you know I normally listen to you,
but I got to seize this opportunity...
Just in case I never become
a real billionaire.
Oh, Homie, I don't care
if you're a billionaire.
-I love you because...
-Hey, there's another way
-to get on the boat!
-Whoo-hoo!
(laughing)
Propellers... spinning!
Turn... left!
Boat go... there!
(all cheering)
Don't worry, Mom. I'm sure he'll be OK.
The boat's going sideways.
-HOMER: Chips ahoy!
-(all cheering)
Well done, Mr. Lenny! Well done.
Homer, have we hit
international waters yet?
Because, uh, things are getting real ugly.
I can't sell you beer
till we cross the line!
Legally, you could give us free beer.
Ow!
Could you give us rubbing alcohol
for our wounds?
Hey. Ha-ha-ha. Sucker!
Ow!
We made it, son!
International waters,
the land that law forgot.
-(music playing)
-(laughing)
Yee-haw!
Yahoo!
(bull bellows)
Wow, you can do anything out here!
That's right.
See that ship over there?
They're rebroadcasting
major league baseball with implied
oral consent.
Not expressed written consent.
Or so the legend goes.
Darr... I now pronounce ya...
man and cow.
(glass breaking)
Please accept these
illegal fireworks
with my blessing.
(chuckling) Yarr...
There are no laws.
We can do anything we want. Anything.
Ow! Ow!
Oh, real mature, Lenny.
Well, doc, I think I did pretty well
on my tests.
You may shake my hand if you like.
Well, under the circumstances,
I'd rather not.
-Eh?
-Mr. Burns I'm afraid
you are the sickest man
in the United States.
You have everything.
-You mean I have pneumonia?
-Yes.
-Juvenile diabetes?
-Hysterical pregnancy?
-A little bit, yes.
You also have several diseases
that have just been discovered... in you.
I see. You sure you just haven't made
thousands of mistakes?
Uh, no. No, I'm afraid not.
-This sounds like bad news.
-Well, you'd think so,
but all of your diseases
are in perfect balance.
I-If you have a moment, I can explain.
-Well!
-Here's the door
to your body, you see?
And these are over-sized novelty germs.
Uh, that's influenza, that's bronchitis.
And this cute little cuddle bug
Is pancreatic cancer.
Ah! Here's what happens when they all try
to get through the door at once.
(imitates the Three Stooges grunts)
Move it, chowderhead!
We call it "Three Stooges Syndrome."
So what you're saying is...
I'm indestructible.
Oh, no, no. In fact,
even a slight breeze could--
Indestructible.
Why are we cleaning this room?
I don't think we were even in here.
Honey, we want Mr. Burns
to find this place
exactly the way he left it.
(humming)
(gasps)
-(music playing)
-(all laughing and cheering)
Look at those poor saps back on land
with their "laws and ethics."
They'll never know the simple joys
of a monkey knife fight.
Give it to him boy! Give it to him!
-(monkey chattering)
-(all encouraging)
MOE: Thrust! Parry!
Stab, stab, stab, stab!
-(Moe laughing)
-(thud)
Oh, he ain't pretty no more.
-(ship bell ringing)
- Hey, coast guard!
Try and stop us now,
You lousy Americans!
MAN: We can't hear you.
Come 300 feet closer.
Nice try. You're not gonna nail us.
MAN: But we just want to party.
Oh, really?
Then, play some rock music.
(man imitating "China Grove" guitar riff)
♪ Doo-doo-doo-doo, doo-doo
doo, doo-doo, doo-doo ♪
Come on, Bart. The coast guard's
covering the doo.
♪ A-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo ♪
♪ A-doo, doo-doo, doo-doo... ♪
Who's the greatest billionaire
in the world?
ALL: You are!
Looks like another homosexual party boat.
They always have such nice things.
Perhaps we should pay them a visit.
A deadly visit?
Well, let's play it by ear.
-("China Grove" playing)
-(all laughing)
(laughing)
(gasps)
♪ China Grove... ♪
(shrieks) Pirates!
Are you friendly pirates?
Uh, not really. No.
Then what have you done
with my party guests?
(yelling)
They got my bus pass.
They got my bus pass!
Whoa! They're poking
every nook and cranny.
Well, every cranny, anyway.
So far, the nook is relatively...
Oh, no! No, it isn't!
Set a course for hidden pirate island...
a.k.a. Hong Kong.
Aye, aye, Captain.
Help! Pirates!
MAN: Navy SEALs are on the way.
Oh, bless you!
MAN: How about a tactical nuclear strike?
Oh, that would be just...
Oh! You're just yanking
my chain, aren't you?
MAN: Perhaps this foghorn
will answer your question.
(horn blows cartoon sound effect)
Enough! Get in the net.
I don't want to!
(Homer grunting and parrots squawking)
Aha! Prepare to die!
You, too.
(yelling painfully) Rope burns!
Ooh, ooh, Charley horse! Charley horse!
(yells painfully)
My mouth! (groaning weakly)
In the net, right?
Some party, Homer!
Shut up, net face.
Hey, you're in the net, too.
I said, "Shut up, net face."
Aw, we're going to die,
and I never tasted cantaloupe.
Ah, you didn't miss much.
Honeydew is the money melon.
And now, we will cut you loose.
For liability purposes,
it is the ocean
that will kill you, not us.
(all screaming)
Hey, what do you know? It floats.
That was my plan all along.
Now, relax and the currents
will take us home.
What about the people on the bottom?
They're the greatest heroes of all.
Hey, something's clawing at my leg.
OK, it stopped.
It looks great!
I can't believe we scrubbed
that old-man smell out of 137 rooms.
Smithers, old chum, there's nothing like
coming home
with a clean bill of health.
Oh, and sorry about your news.
-Thank you, sir.
-Do they know how many eggs
it laid in your brain?
I prefer not to know.
Frankly, one is too many.
Ugh!
The foul stench of youth.
Well, let's see.
Ming vase on narrow column
not knocked down.
Priceless coins not used
in vending machine.
Yes, not bad.
Uh, Mr. Burns,
pirates got your yacht!
What?
Well, I suppose some mishaps
are unavoidable.
(monkey chattering)
(metal clangs)
(gasping) Furious George!
What have they done
to your beautiful face?
Oh... There, there.
Smithers, this monkey's going
to need most of your skin.
(groans)
Ah! It's good to be home.
I don't know. After living
like a billionaire,
this place is kind of a dump.
Ah, it's not so bad.
Here we can spit on the floor.
Bart, stop that!
Now, we may not have antique furniture
or priceless artwork,
but we have everything we need right here.
That's right.
Just because we're not rich
doesn't mean that we don't have...
(sobbing)
Oh, I can't even finish.
I want to be rich...
(sobbing)
Like these guys!
(sobbing aloud)
And look at all these rich people here.
Not as rich as they should be, of course,
but still rich.
(sobbing continues)
Look at all the big money.
Look at all the names got all the money...
and have lots of money.
(sobbing continues)
Oh, he's bored.
But look at all the other people.
Oh! Look at all the people
who can buy and sell me.
I should send a list
of these names to the I.R.S.
I'm taking them all down. (sobbing)
Oh, look at all the rich people.
-Oh! Oh, look at the rich.
-WOMAN: Shh!
HOMER: Don't shush me, you rich bastard!
Captioned by
Visual Data Media Services