CHORUS: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(theme music playing)
(bell ringing)
(whistle blowing)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
(honking horn)
(tires screeching)
D'oh! (screams)
(thud)
♪ The Itchy and Scratchy show ♪
Um.
(clicking tongue)
(sobbing)
He was so young.
(sobbing) So sad.
(gulping)
Ooh!
-(clattering)
-Hey!
(tittering)
-Eh!
-Ah!
-(raucous laugh)
-(thud)
-(gunshots)
-(yelling)
(sawing)
(banging, clanking)
(banging)
(beep)
(sawing, banging, whirring)
(screaming)
(raucous laughter)
(laughter continues)
OK. Here goes.
Cloning is a troubling issue.
I like the ones where
the mouse kills the cat.
What's in the box, Mom?
This box?
Oh, nothing.
Are you sure? You sound nervous.
Well, anyone would be nervous
with all the economic turmoil
you read about in the-- Huh!
Get her! She's doing something!
-(door slamming)
-(grunting)
-(banging)
-It's the goodwill truck!
-(gasping) She cleaned out the attic!
Our junk!
And the exits are sealed.
Go to plan B.
(grunting)
Good God! Come on!
(panting)
(gasps) Go! Go!
-I'm trying!
-(engine starting)
Stop yelling at me!
(engine roaring)
Oh, no. You don't!
(grunts)
Oh, precious heirlooms.
Daddy would never let them take you.
(continuous grunting)
(groans)
Ooh! That was scary.
We came this close to losing
our spare Christmas tree stand.
You monster!
Look. Here's the box
from my Pitch Back.
If I still had it, I could
put it in here.
(sighs) I'll never get rid
of this useless junk.
Useless? This flashcube
has two flashes left.
You guys never use any of this stuff.
Look at these. You bought them after
the Nagano Olympics and never skied once.
If you would just stop
being so impulsive, maybe--
Hey, let's go skiing right now!
Yeah, Dad. Let's go skiing!
(all clamoring)
No!
OK, here it comes.
Keep your eyes on the chair.
Look, Dad, it's the drummer from Bread !
(gasps) Where? Stop!
(laughing)
(frightened yell)
(chattering scream)
(grunts)
Wow, this chair lift sure goes high.
Oh, finally.
(Marge gasps)
Some gentle rocking will relax you, Mom.
-(creaking)
-(moaning)
-Stop it!
Uh. See, Mom? You conquered your fears,
-and now you're ready to--
-I'm sorry!
Hmm, "The Widowmaker."
Oh, that one's for the ladies.
"Spinebuster." Boring.
Ooh, "Colostomizer."
(grunts) Don't hurt me. Here's my wallet.
(laughs) Hi-diddly-ho, schuss-in-boots.
(gasps) Flanders!
That suit's a little revealing, isn't it?
Well, it allows for maximum mobility.
Feels like I'm wearing nothing at all.
(shrieks) Quit it! Must wash eyes!
Uh-oh. Ooh.
OK, don't panic. Remember
what the instructor said,
"If you ever get into any trouble,
all you need to do is--
Feels like I'm wearing nothing at all--
Nothing at all-- Nothing at all!"
(gasps) Stupid, sexy Flanders!
Ow, my legs!
This is the worst pain ever.
(continuous grunts)
(forlorn sobbing)
(groans)
Single.
(chuckles)
(panting) So hard,
but so rewarding. (chuckles)
Downhill skiers missing. Fun.
Oh, who am I kidding?
Wow! What a perfect scene.
This was so worth it.
(gasps) Don't worry, little friends.
I won't hurt you.
(snarling)
Eep!
-(snarling)
-(yelling)
(panting, grunting)
(snarling)
Leave those deer alone.
But they were trying to eat me.
(chuckles) Those deer?
-But they--
-Come on. I'll drop you off at the lodge.
(hissing)
Whoa! Flat 540!
I'm getting aggro on this kicker.
Stomp that pickle revert.
Excellent. Your lingo
is progressing nicely.
-Can I go to the bathroom?
-(grunts)
Say it in "Snowboard."
Um, I got to blast a dookie.
Dook on!
Snow Fox at 5:00.
♪ Move it in, shove it out, Disco lady ♪
-Is this seat taken?
-I think that's an armrest.
So, do you party?
You mean, like, uh, hats and noisemakers
kind of party?
Sure, baby. Whatever your trip is.
Disco Stu wants you to be comfortable
while he does his thing.
Who's Disco Stu?
-Hey, Mom!
-Hi, pumpkins.
Kids?
♪ Back away, not today Disco lady ♪
Have you been in here all day?
You missed all the fun.
Skiing fanny-first into a crevasse
isn't my idea of fun.
The only risk I'm taking is
running out of marshmallows. (laughs)
-(grunts)
-Somebody get a doctor.
-(panting)
-Aw, man, another clock accident.
No wonder. Look at this.
(straining)
-That ought to hold it.
-(creaking)
I want my wife to get the best treatment
money can buy.
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Don't go nuts.
Nah, better than that. Perfect.
-(engine starting)
-(siren wailing)
Yeesh. I can't believe
she went home with those guys.
Well, as you can see,
it's a compound fracture.
The leg must remain motionless.
Otherwise, a hunk of bone
could zoom right to her brain. (chuckles)
I can't be in the hospital.
Tomorrow is laundry day,
and I've got to de-meat Lisa's bologna.
We'll be fine, honey.
The main thing is for you to get better.
And don't worry.
All the laundry and dirty dishes
will be there when you get back.
No, they won't.
We'll all pitch in on the housework.
Right, guys? Guys?
-(chuckles) Take that.
-(grunts) Hey! Hey!
Sweetie, it's nice that you want to
take charge around the house.
But don't be a hero.
Just make sure your father
eats all his meals over a tarp,
but not the good tarp.
I want you to get married on that someday.
Oh, Mom, I've seen what you do
around the house,
and I can handle it.
Maybe, I can even
make things more efficient.
Oh, really? Well, knock yourself out.
Just don't expect
any miracles from those two.
BART: Got you! Got you!
Good Lord! You're wasting
thousands of dollars
worth of interferon.
And you're "interferon"
with our good time. (chuckles)
(spits)
Well, I'll be.
That cured my canker sores.
(yawns)
-Morning.
-Dad, where are your clothes?
I don't know.
Don't tell me Mom dresses you.
I guess, or one of her friends. (munching)
OK, now, we're going to draw jobs
from the chore hat.
Come on, bikini inspector.
"Scrub toilet." OK, that was a practice.
Practice. Practice.
OK, here we go. "Feed fish."
-I'll supervise.
-You know, the reason for the hat--
Oh, it's a great hat.
No one's questioning the hat.
Will you at least do the dishes?
Lisa, I'll do the dishes
when I pick it out of the chore hat,
and it's not a practice.
See? There it is.
But that was a practice.
The system works.
-Come on, eat, you lazy fish.
-(honking)
Oh! You're going to be late.
Here are your lunches, and no trading
your fruit for firecrackers.
Oh, but Lenny just got
some bottle rockets.
You stay away from Lenny.
Where's your sweater, Bart?
It unraveled on a nail.
That's not true. He left it on the bus.
-You're dead, squealer.
-(grunts) Lisa, help!
Those boys of mine.
Mrs. Simpson! What are you doing?
I couldn't sleep knowing
that window had a smudge on it.
You're here to rest.
If you want the window cleaned,
just push the call button.
Oh, I don't want to be a bother.
Wouldn't bother us.
It just turns up your morphine.
Oh, so it does.
Stop pushing that!
Mr. Sakamoto is here for your acupressure.
Now, Mrs. Simpson,
just lie back and relax.
Mr. Sakamoto wants you to be comfortable
while he does his thing.
Oh, I don't think I need any--
Ooh... Oh, wow!
OK, guys, dinner's ready!
-(footsteps)
-(eating noisily)
The cheese isn't quite melted.
Let me just pop it back in the...
-(growls)
-Here you go.
Hmm. (gasps)
Slivered almonds for the green beans.
I'll be right back.
(clattering)
(loud belch)
(sighs)
-So, how was your day?
-(gurgles)
(groans)
(flies buzzing)
Bart, you were supposed to scour the pans.
They need to soak.
You said that four days ago.
Look! They're rusted through.
-It's an illusion.
-No, it's not.
-I got the groceries.
-Good.
(sniffs) Maple soda?
A cell phone full of candy?
Astronaut bread?
It's the bread of astronauts.
I didn't know Aerosmith made a cereal.
Dad, I gave you a list.
Oh, yeah.
(chuckles)
You were way off.
(growls)
Hello, lollipop island.
There's a little girl here
who had too many sour balls.
-(frustrated sigh)
-Anyway, where were we?
Hello? Hello?
They hung up.
(phone rings)
Talk to me.
Hey, Mom, how's the leg?
Leg? Oh! Oh, that.
It's pretty great.
How are things at home?
Oh, couldn't be better.
-Marco.
-BART: Polo.
(cat mewing scared)
-HOMER: Marc...
-(crash)
-BART (chuckles): Polo.
-So, Mom, you think you'll be
getting out of there soon?
I don't know, honey.
I've got a lot of therapy left.
I really thought
I could handle this, but--
I think so, too. Bye.
-(dial tone)
-(groans)
RICKY (on TV): Lucy?
(Lucy crying)
FRED: You hit her pretty hard there, Rick.
(laughing)
(TV sound)
(groaning, growling)
Will you guys turn that thing down?
Sweetie, if we didn't
turn it down for the cops
what chance do you have?
(Lucy crying on TV)
HOMER (laughs): He hit her again.
(grunts)
(grumbles, mumbles)
LUCY: Losing your marbles, huh, kid?
(shrieks)
-Lucy?
-Lucy McGillicuddy Ricardo Carmichael.
(coughs) And I think there's some more.
What are you doing here?
I came from heaven to help you
get revenge on these bums.
Is there an ashtray around here?
-Will this do?
-Thanks, doll.
Now, we need a scheme
to teach those slobs a lesson.
You mean like when you hid inside
the Congo drum to scare Ricky?
Hey, stay away from the drums.
That's my bit.
(snaps a finger) I got it!
Here's what you do.
Wait until they fall asleep,
then you sneak into their rooms
and make sure
they're fast asleep because...
(snoring)
(soft chuckle)
(Homer screams)
BART: My skin! My beautiful skin!
(chuckles)
-HOMER: Lisa, help!
-(both grunting, crying)
(whining) What's wrong with us?
(gasps) I don't like the looks of this.
You don't? 'cause that's what I said.
-Tell her, Bart.
-Shut up! Shut up!
We better check with a doctor.
Welcome to Virtual Doctor ,
from the makers of Dragon Quest
and Sim Sandwich.
Enter symptoms now!
Let's see.
-Crusty sores.
-Yes.
Horrible wailing.
Yes... Yes!
Any exposure to unsanitary conditions?
Duh! We're pigs!
OK, and... diagnose.
You've got leprosy.
BOTH: Leprosy!
-(both scream)
-BOTH: Unclean!
Help us, Virtual Doc !
Look at me, I'm on my knees.
Good-bye.
-(whimpering )
-Excellent.
Leprosy? I can't believe it.
That fortune cookie was right.
Why would God punish a kid?
I mean, an American kid.
Now, guys, leprosy thrives
in filthy conditions.
So your only chance
is to clean up the house.
-I'll get you a couple of mops.
-Mops?
The cure sounds worse than the disease.
At Sunday school, they said, the lepers
were cured by some bearded dude.
-Jesus?
-Yeah, that sounds right.
Oh, I think we're on the outs with him,
but I know someone
who's even holier than Jesus.
(doorbell rings)
Hi-diddly-ho, I've-- (grunts)
(both crying)
Maude, come quick!
The Simpsons are covered with cooties!
-Help us!
-We're diseased!
Oh, no! That's leprosy!
Remember those scary lepers in Ben-Hur?
You saw Ben-Hur without me?
We were broken up then.
-Well, that's no--
-(both yell)
BOTH: Brains!
Use your brains to help us.
Your delicious brains.
-(Bart groaning)
-Oh, those poor souls.
What's the Christian thing to do?
Oh, thank you! Thank you, thank you,
you wonderful man!
(kissing)
All right! Food!
-(eating noisily)
-(both crying)
Bart! Leave some for Rod and Todd.
Here you go, lad.
-MAUDE: Todd, no!
-(sucking sound)
Uh, listen, Homer, we'd love to help you,
but we're not really set up for lepers.
So you're shunning us?
No, no, no, no, no.
I'm just thinking, we could
send you to a better place.
You know, a place where they could
really take care of you.
Oh, thank you, good sir!
-(kisses)
-(groans)
-(sucking sound)
-(sneezes)
Ooh, that smarts.
Boys, get the alcohol-free alcohol.
Well, I shall just get this cast off,
and you can go home to your--
Oh, my Lord!
Well, it has been a week.
Code blue! 1,000 cc's of leg wax, stat!
Lazy, no-good lepers.
Making me clean everything myself.
(phone rings)
MOE: Hey, is Homer there?
No, he isn't.
-I don't know where he is.
-I'm a little worried.
He usually stops in for an eye-opener
on the way to work.
He told us he'd been going to the gym.
(chuckles) Wow!
Anyway, you don't think he could be
at another bar, do you?
Because I couldn't take that.
I-I just couldn't. I--
(sobbing)
Don't hang up on me!
MARGE: I'm home, everybody.
Gee, the house looks great.
Mom, I lost Dad and Bart.
Lost them? What do you mean?
I tricked them into thinking
they had leprosy.
Hansen's disease.
You know, like that horrible cream soda?
Well, Dad and Bart ran away,
and no one seems to know where they went.
OK, OK, calm down.
They couldn't have gone too far.
Molokai?
You mean, Hawaii?
Uh-huh. That's the one.
They've got a top-notch
leper colony there,
so we shipped them right off.
(gasps) Ooh, cost us a bundle, too.
I guess we'll have
an imagination Christmas this year.
BOTH: Yay! Imagination Christmas!
I got a Pogo stick!
I got a hula hoop!
(tires screeching)
Here.
Whoa! This is a hospital?
That it is.
We'll take the cure, bag a few lobsters,
then watch some gay guys get married.
Ah, you must be the Simpsons.
Howdy. And thanks for not
recoiling in horror.
Thank you for the friendly "howdy."
Do we get a room with a view?
Oh, you'll have a great view
of the whole beach
from the electric needle room.
Really? The whole beach?
Yes, from the electric needle room.
Electric needle room?
(dolphins twittering)
-(electrical zapping)
-(Homer screaming)
(screaming continues)
Glad it's not me.
-(bell rings)
-Time to turn over.
Here they are.
Oh, thank God you're all right.
Dad, Bart, I played
a horrible trick on you,
and I'm really sorry.
You don't have leprosy. It's just oatmeal.
Yeah, we know.
I figured it out after
I ate one of my chest sores.
Well, then let's get out of here.
No way. We scored
a free Hawaiian vacation.
This place is a blast.
All we have to do is endure
two hours of blinding pain.
Then, it's nothing
but shopping and surfing.
Tonight, we're gonna put
our fake sores back on,
then jump the fence at club med
and scare the normals.
Well, it all sounds lovely, but--
Come on, loosen up. This is paradise.
MAN (on PA system): Number one,
report to the dermabrasion hut.
That's me. (humming)
HOMER: ♪ Aloha ♪
-(electric sander grinding)
-(Homer screams)
♪ Aloha ♪
(screams)
♪ Until we meet a-- ♪
(sander grinding)
(theme music playing Hawaiian style)
-(murmuring)
-Shh.
MAN: You hit her
pretty hard there, Rick.
Captioned by
Visual Data Media Services