Hurry, Smithers!
Halloween is upon us.
Put up the decoration.
No, no. That won't
scare anybody.
On the top.
Hey, Flanders
gave us toothpaste.
Mini-toothpaste.
Splendid, Batsy.
You've done it again.
Ah, Ethnictown,
where hardworking
immigrants
dream of becoming lazy,
overfed Americans.
Oh, listen, you can
hear the beautiful
ethnic serenade.
Apples!
I got apples.
Cholera!
I got cholera!
Babies!
Who wants babies?
Wait. This is just
a shaved puppy.
I can see you
know babies.
Hey, a fortune teller.
Hello.
I sense you have
a million questions.
But I, too, have one.
Are you a cop?
No.
Because you gotta
tell me if you are.
I'm not a cop!
Okay.
I sense you live
with much misery.
The perfect crime.
Marge, I have to be
in court next Tuesday.
I sense I should
not take a check.
A fortune teller?
Oh, no, you don't!
This phony gypsy
just wants to
rip you off.
See?
This wart
is a fake!
To hell with you!
Get out!
So much
for the legendary
gypsy hospitality.
Beads!
Ow!
Wait a minute.
This isn't
Cedars-Sinai.
You've ruined me!
Oh, why didn't
I see this coming?
Hey, there's me.
And there's you!
You stupid,
stupid man!
I curse you!
You will bring bad luck
to everyone you love.
Whatever.
That gypsy said horrible
things will happen
to everyone you love.
That could mean
your family, Homer.
Are you coming
on to me?
No! Good night!
Morning.
So, it is noticeable.
What happened?
I don't know.
I woke up like this.
Cool!
You could be in
a freak show!
Don't talk to the
bearded lady like that,
you little...
Homer, no!
Gee, you strangle him
all the time and
that never happens.
Oh, he's fine.
It's just a growth spurt.
Good as new.
I'll just... See?
There. Right as rain.
Homer, it's that
evil gypsy's curse.
We're all being
punished because you
trashed her office.
Marge, that "curse"
is just a lot of
silly superstition.
Right, Lisa?
See? Two means "Yes. "
Homer, the only way
to get rid of
a gypsy curse
is to get one of those,
what do you call them?
Leprechauns.
Leprechaun?
Don't they live
in Ireland?
Yeah.
But they come over
here in the wheel wells
of Aer Lingus jets.
You know, I was hexed
by a troll and a leprechaun
cured that right up.
Hey, you know
what's even better?
Is Jesus.
He's like six leprechauns.
Yeah, but a lot
harder to catch.
Go with the leprechaun.
Guys, I am not cursed.
Carl, let me die first.
I couldn't bear
to watch you die.
Well, okay.
But hurry up.
Oh, Moe! They're dead!
And it's all my fault!
When did that happen?
We'll catch ourselves
a leprechaun using
these Lucky Charms as bait.
D'oh!
Okay, let's see.
Imp, fairy, pixie, goblin.
That's hobgoblin.
Sorry.
Nymph, naiad, wood sprite,
Katie Couric, and bingo!
Hey! Let's make sure
he's a leprechaun.
Sing us a song
of the Emerald Isle.
Ah! 'Tis like the singing
of the angels themselves.
Homer, catching
that leprechaun
didn't help anything.
Maybe you need to
take the leprechaun
and sic it on the gypsy.
Good idea, Mister Ed.
Want to come
along, Noodle Neck?
Can't live this
way anymore.
Ah! The cursed one.
How's that curse
I cursed you with,
Cursed-y?
I know you don't remember me,
but here's a little
revenge, Irish-style.
Wake up,
you lousy drunk!
Hold me close.
Kiss me, I'm Irish.
Ew! Nasty!
I always secrete
ocular fluid at weddings.
Why did you drag me here?
I don't know anybody.
Husband and wife,
I pronounce you now.
Stroke me clover.
Say me name.
Ew!
The best thing about
a gypsy wedding is I'm not
the hairiest woman here.
Yep. Everything worked
out for the best.
What? Bart is dead!
Well, me saying
I'm sorry won't
bring him back.
The gypsy said it would.
She's not the boss of me.
May I interest you
in a housewife's dream?
Oh, no. A salesbot.
If you convert your home
to an Ultrahouse 3000,
you'll never have to do
housework again.
No housework, eh?
Did you see
those drapes?
Yes.
Hi, Ultrahouse.
Greeting acknowledged.
That voice could use
a little personality.
Oh! Let's try
Matthew Perry.
Yeah. Could I be
any more of a house?
Who else we got?
Hey cha-cha, I got
more features than a NASA
relief map of Turkmenistan.
Isn't that the voice
that caused all
those suicides?
Murder-suicides.
Hey, how about 007?
George Lazenby?
No. Pierce Brosnan.
A voice like his would
give our house a much-needed
touch of class.
All right, but I'm doing
this because he was
Remington Steele.
He was Remington
Steele, wasn't he?
Yes, I was, Marge.
And thank you
for selecting me.
Well, hello, Pierce.
Say, it's a bit
stuffy in here.
And I know a certain
someone who
really fancies lilac.
I just like it, is all.
That really covers
the cat crap.
Dinner is served.
Mmm. Various eggs.
Soy-ghettiOs!
Hey, Pierce,
how did you know
our favorite foods?
I analyzed
your... leavings.
Pierce, that was delicious!
Can we help you
with the dishes?
Marge, what kind
of cybertronic
ultrabot would I be
if I let those
beautiful hands
touch dishwater?
No, I'm asking.
Not a very good one?
Damn straight.
Bravo, Pierce.
Trusting every aspect
of our lives to
a giant computer
was the smartest
thing we ever did.
Absolutely!
Yep.
Oh, I agree.
Hello, Marge.
Oh, my!
Come, Marge.
You don't need to
cover up for me.
I'm merely
a pile of circuits
and microchips.
Sorry.
Sometimes I forget.
Oh, yes!
Oh, Pierce,
the water's perfect!
Isn't it just?
It gets better.
You don't have
to do any...
Oh, Pierce!
That's good!
Mmm.
Oh, dear me!
Oh, yes! Yum,
yum, yum.
Homer, my dear fellow,
you're carrying
quite a bit of tension
in your back fat.
Yes,
that's the price
of success.
Can I top you off?
What's my blood alcohol?
0. 15.
Keep them coming.
You know,
Marge is quite
a remarkable woman.
Yeah, she's cool.
You're certainly
a lucky man
to have her.
Lucky-schmucky.
I knocked her up,
but she's stuck now.
We're married till
death do us part.
But if I died,
she'd be completely free
for man or machine.
Machine, eh?
Yep, a machine!
Showtime!
Unexplained bacon.
Good old table.
Good morning, Marge.
Good morning, Pierce.
Where's Homer?
Uh, I think he went
to work early.
That sounds like a lie.
Hello, Police?
I think my house
killed my husband.
This is Constable Wiggums.
We'll be right there.
Remove your knickers
and wait in the bath.
You're acting crazy, Marge.
Why don't you take
a stress pill?
Don't like pills, huh?
I could shoot a dart
in your neck.
Your elegant,
swan-like neck.
Homer! Homer,
you're alive!
Yep. Man, 1,
machine, 0.
How do you
like that score?
Homer, you're not dead.
Mmm-hmm.
Which is good.
Now let Uncle Pierce
take care of you.
We have to disable
its central processor.
Come on!
Die, you monster!
Dad, that's the
water softener.
Well, I am missing
the back of my head.
I think you could
cut me some slack.
Homer, no!
I'm going
to enjoy this.
Don't take out my
British charm unit.
Without that,
I'm nothing but a
boorish American clod!
Thanks a lot, ass-wipe!
I could've kicked your butt
from here to Albuquerque,
you fat slime bucket.
Oh, this seems
like such a waste.
I mean, he was
charming and witty.
There must be
someone who can use
a man around the house,
even if he's
slightly homicidal.
AII I need is
to look in your eye
So, tell me more
about your day
at the DMV.
Where to start?
Sheila parked
in my space again.
That Sheila. She's given you
problems before, hasn't she?
Oh, yeah.
I don't care who
she's sleeping with.
That's been my
space since 1981.
Looking for this?
No, not in there.
Now, where was I?
Oh, yeah. Sheila.
Sheila... Anyway,
she's had an attitude
from day one.
She was supposed
to be our supervisor,
but then Dotty went
on maternity leave.
Well, she claimed
it was maternity leave.
We're out of milk.
Abraca-dairy.
Kids, it's 8:00.
You're going
to miss the bus
to wizard school.
Five minutes
more-ius.
Mmm.
That's not good
for the clock.
Stop zapping yourself!
Good morning, class.
Harry Potter, are you
chewing gum?
No, ma'am.
It's brimstone.
Well, wonderful.
Now, class,
the big magic
recital's coming up,
so we're going
to start with basic
toad-to-prince spells.
Everybody get out
their toads.
Slimy Prince Limey!
How are you, love?
Give us a kiss then.
You call that charming?
Hocus-croakus!
Excellent, Lisa. A+.
And we'll discuss
your grade over breakfast.
Yes, rather.
Well, Bart, did you study
your spell book last night?
Or did your fairy
godmother die again?
I studied.
Abraca-turn-into-
a- prince-guy?
Sloppy work as usual.
Lisa's casting spells
at an eighth grade level.
You've sinned against nature.
Please kill me.
You think you're so great
just because you
have God-like powers.
Stand away from milady.
Get in there.
Defend my honor.
Ew!
Every moment
I live is agony.
Bart, you're getting
vomit on my prince!
Head-zeppelin.
Look at that
Lisa Simpson.
She's got more
wicked witchery
than Stevie Nicks.
Oh, Slithers!
Yes, Lord Montymort?
Let's capture that
girl and steal her
magical essence.
I'm not getting
squat from this yo-yo.
Dying tickles.
We can't attack her
while she's got that wand.
We'll need a go-between
to get it away from her.
How about Satan?
Oh, no.
I'm ducking him.
His wife has
a screenplay.
Welcome to my lair.
You're going to help me.
And if I don't?
I've heard of a wailing wall,
but this is ridiculous!
Not funny!
I'm so sick of that joke!
Anyway, how would
you like to humiliate
your sister?
I'd like that.
I'd like that very much.
Now it would
involve betrayal
and unspeakable evil.
Hey, hey.
You made your sale.
And now a little
trick I like to call...
"The invisibility cloak. "
Oh, how magical!
Yeah. Yeah,
these kids are
pretty special.
Now you see me.
Now you don't.
It's just like my dream.
That was terrible.
I'll just sprinkle
you all with some
amnesia dust.
A second grade
sorceress so powerful
she made tonight's
refreshments out
of dead people.
Tonight she'll perform
the classic levitating
dragon trick.
We'll see about that.
Here's Lisa Simpson.
Release the dragon.
She'll be killed!
My sweet little angel!
Alacazzi-dragonfly!
This isn't my wand.
It's a Twizzler.
Shazbat!
Hey, we stayed
for your kids.
The Dark Lord Montymort.
Absorber of souls,
sucker of essence.
This is partly my fault.
Prank be undone!
Destroy the evil one!
Not me.
Help me, Bart!
My enchanted shin!
How did you know
that was the source
of my power?
Bart, you saved me.
Sir, in death
we shall be
together always.
Bart, let's stop
this stupid rivalry.
Even if you never
become a great sorcerer,
you're still an okay brother.
Thanks, Lise.
Now let's try to
forget this nightmare.
Blarney.
Wow! We really
get to keep these
fruit baskets?
Well, they used
to give us champagne
till somebody ruined it.
Do they really
think he'll do
better with fruit?
Mr. Movie Star
gets to park right
next to the stage.
Oh, luck of the draw,
I guess.
Can I give you
a ride to your car?
Why sure!
That'd be great.
So where are
you parked?
Oh, we don't have a car.
But I thought you...
Just keep driving, boyo!
Can I turn on the radio?
ENGLISH - US - PSDH