(SINGING) The Simpsons
(TIRES SCREECHING)
D'oh!
(SCREAMS)
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
What?
Can't we sit on the couch
without something happening?
D'oh!
I can't believe
Mr. Burns reserved
the entire museum
just for an office party.
It doesn't seem fair
to the regular visitors.
We drove 18 hours
to come here.
On the plus side,
this rope is mighty soft.
Mmm. Touch it, kids.
KIDS: Mmm.
Party! Party! Party!
Homer, these are
people you work with.
Show some restraint.
Restraint!
Restraint! Restraint!
(LOUD WOLF HOWL)
(GRUNTING)
Mm-mm-mm.
Lighten up, Marge.
This is my chance to relax
with people from
work I never get to see.
Like this guy.
I'm your supervisor.
Really? How am I doing?
(DISGUSTED GRUNT)
Well, well, if it isn't
my favorite employee
and his spouse.
And these must be children.
Have a ginger root.
Mr. Burns acting nice?
That's odd. He must be
up to something.
Lise, Mr. Burns
is the sweetest,
kindest man I know.
How many men do you know?
Basically, him and Dad.
Nice tux, Moe.
Yeah, thanks.
I bought this
for my funeral.
It ain't got no back
so don't make
me turn around.
Hm.
Hey, I'm paying for
a silk-lined coffin,
And damn it,
I'm gonna feel it.
NARRATOR:
Since the dawn of aviation,
man has built
museums dedicated
to the history of flight
and created
audiovisual materials
to orient visitors
to those museums.
From the hand-drawn flip book
at the Wright Brothers Museum
to the IMAX movie
at Cape Canaveral,
aviation museum
audiovisual materials
have taken patrons
and docents alike
On a rocket ride
to comprehension.
This is the story
of those materials.
Hey, it's a guy in
a goofy Burns head!
Act like Burns.
(LAUGHS)
That's him to a tee!
Here we have a vintage
film of the original
Springfield Wing Walkers
Including our
own Agnes Skinner.
(MOOING)
HOMER: Wow, a wooden plane.
It's about time
trees were good
for something
instead of just
standing there like jerks!
"The Plywood Pelican
was larger than
a football field.
"It weighs more than
the state of New Hampshire.
"It was only flown
once by its creator,
Mr. C. Montgomery Burns."
I flew it at
an altitude of 6 feet
for a distance of
4 and a half feet.
Then we discovered
rain makes it catch fire.
Then the Fuhrer fired me.
What a magical
party this has been.
Mr. Burns is a great man.
I've got a bad
feeling about all this.
Come on, Marge.
This place is great.
Free admission, great grub,
and we got to use
the bathroom of the future.
Homer, that
was Apollo 12!
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Greetings, wage donkeys.
Is everyone happy and content?
Yeah!
This is great!
I would die for you!
Is your sense of
outrage dulled?
Spill it, super boss!
(CHUCKLES) Very well,
effective immediately,
the employee prescription
drug program is terminated!
What?
Why?
In these days of rising
health care costs,
blah, blah, blah,
lip service, lip service.
Get out!
(EMPLOYEES GASP)
This must be
the nasty surprise
he mentioned in
the invitation.
(UNINTELLIGIBLE ANGRY CHATTER)
No!
This sucks!
Get him!
(PANTING)
Fly. you fool!
I tried to
explain to you, sir,
this thing has
never actually worked.
Smithers, you must believe.
(GRUNTING)
MR. BURNS:
Next stop, Pirate Island!
Well, that was
a pretty good party.
Do you think
Carol from Payroll and
Mike from Shipping
are going to hook up?
(GASPING) He's married.
Change course!
Carol must be warned!
Now that Mr. Burns
has eliminated the drug plan,
we're gonna have
to cut back on our diseases.
I'll get a second job,
one that pays well.
You think those
guys on Friends
need another friend?
That show's gone off the air.
Damn it.
I would've been perfect
as Rachel's Irish cousin.
So you're all doin'
each other, are ya?
But who's gonna put
out for old Seamus?
I need a new job
that provides
full health benefits.
Uh-huh.
As long as I only
work five hours a day,
no heavy lifting,
no light clerical, none
of that Secret Santa crap,
tasteful nudity...
Uh, well,
let me see what I've got.
(BEEPING)
VIDEO GAME VOICE:
You have defeated the doombot
and sealed the portal.
Phobos is safe.
Phobos? That's a good
job for me.
Following the lead
of Springfield Nuclear Power,
other local companies
are canceling their
prescription drug plans,
even here at Channel 6.
Now, kids, I want you
to go to your parents'
medicine cabinet,
and find all the pills labeled
lithium dibromide
and send them to me now!
No one likes a bipolar clown!
(CHUCKLES)
(CRYING)
(LAUGHING)
To cope with the crisis,
many consumers are turning
to alternative
forms of treatment.
I've had to medicate Ralphie
with stuff from
the evidence locker.
(CLANCY LAUGHS)
I'm cuckoo for contraband!
Of course,
this wouldn't be necessary
if retail drug
prices were reasonable.
Dr. Julius Hibbert,
do you agree?
Well, now, Kent,
give the drug
companies a break.
They have lots
of hidden costs,
and they know how
to treat a brother.
Let me introduce you
to the fine-looking
females of Pfizer.
I like big butts
And I cannot lie
You other brothers can't deny
That when a girl walks in
With an itty-bitty waist
And a round thing in your face
You get sprung
Possible side effects
include dizziness
and shortness of marriage.
Damn!
Well, let me start out
by saying that it is
always a pleasure
to sit down with
a mother and a daughter
who have snuck past security
and burst into my office.
I just don't see
why one little
pill should cost $30.
Drugs aren't so expensive
in other countries.
In other countries,
families also lie on
the floor and eat bugs.
What countries are those?
You ever been to Norway?
No.
Well, they do
it in Norway.
And that's why I
personally thank God
we pay too much for drugs.
I mean, the right amount.
I mean, not enough.
Here. Watch this video.
PHARMACEUTICAL NARRATOR:
The mighty Amazon River.
The natives had a word for it.
Then we got rid
of the natives,
and no one
remembers that word.
But here are
some words everyone
remembers by Huey
Lewis and the News.
I want a new drug
One that won't make me sick
One that won't
make me crash my car
Or make me feel
3 feet thick
I want a new drug
One that won't hurt my head
(MAN COUGHING)
All right.
Here's your medication.
Wait a minute.
This ain't no pill.
It's a corn nut!
I got a bottle cap.
Mine flew away.
Let me explain
from behind this cage.
Now, your pills
have become very expensive,
and no one gives
a rat's ass about you.
So after a lot of thought,
we decided to let
you go cold turkey.
For those of you
who survive the night,
we'll be having
waffles tomorrow.
Ooh.
Waffles.
I didn't die
in World VVar ll
just to be pushed around
by some pill-hoarding hussy!
I'm gonna fight this thing!
Ah, he's crazy.
But what are you
gonna do? He's young.
Well, the drug
company won't do
anything to help us.
I got the answer!
Dad?
Oh. Thank God
it's the right place.
I burst into four
homes before this one.
Now listen.
All the drugs we want
are right across the border.
I have a friend
who will help us.
The border, eh?
Then I'd better sand
off my fingerprints.
Ow!
I could just wear gloves.
Nah, they're upstairs.
Ow, ow, ow!
(CRYING)
Hola, señor
We are gringos who wish
To spend mucho
dinero in your country.
Splendid. Welcome
to Canada.
D'oh!
Okay, Abe. Here are your
fake Canadian health cards.
Take them to any pharmacy,
and you'll get enough drugs
to make Regina
look like Saskatoon.
(LAUGHING)
That's a good
one, Johnny.
Thanks a million, Johnny.
In appreciation,
I'd like to give
you this DVD player.
What the heck?
Where do you pour the syrup?
I'd like some Vioxx,
Coumadin, Albuterol,
Prevacid
and an auto-inflate
blood pressure monitor
C-cuff with case.
Anything you like,
fellow Canadian.
Canadian?
Them's fightin' words!
I mean, accurate words.
One pill makes you larger
And one pill makes you small
And the ones
That mother gives you
Don't do anything at all
Go ask Alice
When she's ten feet tall
Anything to declare?
I declare that you have
the most beautiful brown eyes.
Why, I do believe
you're smuggling
a heart as big
as all outdoors.
Now get in my country,
you big lug.
(CHUCKUNG)
Did he have a passport?
Yes. To my heart.
Drugs! Various drugs!
Be sure to read instructions!
Uh-oh. Where did I put
the instructions?
Now, who's next?
I got pills to
make you sleep late,
coagulate, eliminate
and copulate, in that order.
Grampa, we would like
to thank you for all
you have done for us.
Please accept this
Operation Dumbo Drop
souvenir jacket.
Look, they used the same "D"
for "Dumbo" and "Drop."
(LAUGHS) Unbelievably, only
three were ever purchased.
Marge? Bart? Lisa?
(MUSIC PLAYING)
ALL: Aloha.
Oh. This is
just like Hawaii.
But you don't get beaten up
if you leave the hotel.
What gives?
We just wanted
to thank you.
Because of the Xanax,
I'm not overanxious
about being a Simpson anymore.
I am a little anxious
about being on Xanax,
but the Zoloft
covers that nicely.
(GULPS)
My dad, the drug mule.
(GAGGING)
Oh, man. I need something
to settle my stomach.
Wait. I was supposed
to take these with food.
Oh, look, it is Mr. Homer,
my favorite customer.
Please feel free
to paw through my Playdudes
and tell me to go back
to some country I
am not actually from.
Why the sweet talk, Apu?
Are you after
some cheap drugs?
Please let me come
on one of your
smuggling runs.
My eight babies
are driving me crazy
with their
coughing and sneezing
and general oozing.
My Janitor in a Drum
is afraid to come out!
What does that mean?
I don't even know!
That is the kind of
bad joke I am making!
I am so tired!
Help me out, Homer.
My little Roddy
needs his insulin.
Breaks my heart to watch
him jones-diddly-onesing.
Flanders? I don't know.
I mean, you haven't
done anything for me
Since you lent me
that 5,000 bucks yesterday.
I don't claim to be
the perfect neighbor.
If you let us come,
I will give you
10 minutes alone
with my Squishy machine.
Do what you will.
No cameras?
(SPLUTTERED PROTEST)
(SURRENDERING SIGH)
No cameras.
Homer, tell Mr. Ned
to stop trying
to convert me.
I was just telling him
how brave he is to
worship a false god.
I do not worship
one god. Okay?
I worship a whole super team
of deities that...
Ow! Ow! Okay,
he just pinched me!
Well, where's your
super team now?
Listen, you two.
I'll tell you
who the true god is
if you're both quiet
the rest of the trip.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
All right,
I'm coming back there!
APU: Save me, Shiva!
NED: Why don't you just
call out for Hawkman?
APU: Why don't you shut up?
Well, circle cut my bacon!
Look at all these
Yankee-doodly-dandies!
Is there another
Vietnam going on?
Hello, neighborino
to the north.
I sure like the cut
of your gibberish.
(RAPIDLY INTERLOCKING
DOODLIES, DIDDLIES)
Say, would you like to
puff on a reefer-ino?
It's legal here.
They warned me Satan
would be attractive.
Let's go!
Anyone want some coffee
for the ride back?
Not that convenience
store crap, is it?
Because I don't
feed that to my dogs.
No, no. It's home-brewed.
Careful. It's hotter
than a Fox News weather skank.
Oh, my! Hot! Hot! Hot!
La, la, la, la, la, la, la.
Here. Let me wrap
this wet towel
around your head
to cool you off.
La, la, la, la,
la, la, la. (PANTING)
Stop him! He's
expressing his faith, eh!
(GUNS COCKING)
Hold on! We're just
innocent tourists!
La, la, la, la,
la, la, la.
I took another sip.
Today Mounties busted
a major American
drug smuggling ring.
Former US
astronaut, Homer Simpson,
was taken into custody.
Oh, my butt looks so
huge during perp walks.
We've confiscated your
car and its contents.
"Nous avons confisqué
votre voiture et
ses contenus."
You may leave Canada
but never return.
"Vous êtes permis de quitter
le Canada, mais vous n 'avez
plus le droit de rentrer "
I am a big, fat,
French idiot.
"Je suis un grand
gros..."
Hey!
(CHUCKLES)
No more drugs.
We let everyone down.
Your jacket, sefior.
Thank God we did not stitch
your name over the breast.
(SIGHS)
Dad, you tried your best.
For the first time in my life,
I can say without being drunk
that I truly admire you.
Oh!
No drinking in public.
Hey, where'd it go?
Oh, well.
Ah, there's nothing
like canceling
an employee drug plan
to make one feel
so at peace
with the universe.
I agree, sir.
Shut up.
I'm so sick
of you, Smithers.
Your toadying,
your complete agreeability,
your gasping on the floor...
(GASPING)
(SHOCKED CRY)
Smithers! If this is
some sort of hijink,
stop it immediately.
Sir, my thyroid
is swelling up.
Confound it, man.
I need your throat
clear and ready for perjury.
When you canceled
the drug plan,
I couldn't afford
my Thyroxine anymore.
But before I die,
there are words
I have always longed to say.
Sir, I... (CHOKING)
Fear not, Smithers!
I'll move heaven
and Earth to save you!
It's still easier
than teaching
a new assistant
my filing system.
I just wish we could
make one last big score,
but we could never drive
past the border patrol.
There are other ways
to get into Canada.
(GROWLING)
No!
That's it! A plane!
Smuggle drugs in a plane?
That'll never work!
Sure, it will.
All we need is a pilot.
I've got everything you need.
HOMER: Katharine Hepburn?
No, you fool! 'Tis I, Burns.
Now come with me.
MR. BURNS: At last,
my plane shall be used
for its original purpose,
to subvert the laws
of the United States.
Looks like your
plane's pretty full, eh?
Don't want to overload it.
Pah! Typical
Canadian wimpiness.
That's why you have snowballs,
and we have the H-bomb!
We really appreciate
your help, Johnny.
Is there any way
we can repay you?
Well, I've always
wanted to see a man
with the IQ of a child
executed by the state.
We don't get
that up here.
Really? In America,
we do it four times a week.
You come on down,
and I'll get us
front row seats.
I'd like that.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
We're losing altitude.
Time to dump all
unnecessary weight.
What? Don't dump me out!
I can lose weight!
Just give me a chance!
One, two...
Ah, I'd rather die.
It's no use.
We've got to make
an emergency landing.
Well, at least we're
all in this together.
Now, we have three parachutes.
This one's for me.
And these two are
gifts for my nephews.
Tallyho!
(BOTH GASP)
Homer, are you sure
you can fly this thing?
We'll make it, Dad,
on a wing and a prayer.
Damn it!
(SNORING)
(GASPS)
(SIREN BLARING)
All right,
you're under arrest.
On what charge?
Making a police chief go...
(GASPS)
(GRUNTING)
Get in the car.
And don't touch those guns.
I just loaded them.
You'll have
to arrest me, too!
Abe Simpson
brought the Propecia
to keep grass
on Willie's field!
He cured my lumbago.
Thank you.
My diaper rash.
My glayvinoids
are not so hurtful.
Thanks to his
lactose intolerance pills,
I can drink this
Krusty brand milkshake.
Terrible!
Well, Simpson, you have
helped a lot of people.
So like it says in
the Springfield
Police Handbook,
"If you can't
beat 'em, join 'em."
(CHEERS)
Uh, Chief,
you know, I've been
checking the handbook.
A lot of the things
you say aren't in
there at all.
Yeah, well, look a little
closer, Lou.
(HITTING GRUNT)
(PAINFUL GRUNT)
(CHEERS CONTINUE)
(HEAVY BREATHING)
Oh, I hope I'm
not too late.
Take, potion! Hurry!
Oh, it's not working.
Only my sour, curdled breath
will quicken him.
(QUICK BREATHS)
(GASPS)
(THRILLED MOAN)
(GRUNTS)
(SIGHS)
Sir, you saved my life.
Yes.
Smithers, I was
a stingy old fool.
But from now on,
I'll provide drug benefits
to all my full-time employees.
Great news, honey.
Mr. Burns made me
a freelance consultant.
Hey, what's this lump?
(BELL TOLLING)