(Homer grunts)
Bring up the couch.
(grunting)
(sighs)
(clinking)
(theme playing)
CHOIR: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
I'm a return!
(theme music playing)
(exclaims)
(school bell ringing)
(Barney belches)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
APP: Turn left.
You're the driver.
(horns honking)
-WOMAN: Idiot!
-MAN: Watch it, ya jerk!
APP: Turn left.
Don't look at me. Look at the road.
Yes, dear.
-(tires screeching)
-(horns honking)
APP: In 50 feet ago,
U-turn without signaling.
Oh...
(tires screech)
(horns honking)
APP: Turn left, into Garbage Alley.
-(engine revving)
-(tires screeching)
(tires screech)
Mmm.
Uh, uh...
Huh? What? Huh?
What the hell do those mean?
HOMER:
Can't stop, I have to hit one of them.
Man or dog?
Oh, it's a Snoopy's Choice.
-(sighs)
-I guess your days
of eating out of the garbage
are over, Gil.
Hey... (yells)
APP: I was never here.
I saw nothing.
Now I do have to warn you, if Gil sues,
he'll end up with everything you've got.
But that's everything I got.
Okay, kids,
give me your best worried looks.
Ooh, that's good worry.
And, Maggie, when we visit Gil,
you should think about your mom
and me disappearing forever
any time we step behind a wall.
Where am I? Where am I?
(footsteps departing)
No, seriously, where did I go?
It's so dark in here.
(shrieks) Maggie!
-(pounding on wall)
-(glass shatters)
Ol' Gil, there must be something
we can do for you.
Hmm? Hmm?
Ah, there sure is,
you can let me scratch your husband.
-Sure, but why?
-Because you're the lottery ticket
I've been waiting for all my life!
Bam! Zing!
Before this goes any further,
can you just take one look
at our darling daughters?
Mr. Gunderson?
They don't let saxophones in the I.C.U.,
so I'll just tell you the song
I wrote for you.
B-flat, C, D-flat...
-If memory serves, you have a son.
-...B-flat, C...
-Where's he at?
-♪ ...Long G ♪
(imitates old woman)
I'm here to give Mr. Gunderson his shot.
Boy, the "putting him in a coma" idea
was just dinner table chatter.
-I did not sign off.
-You tapped your nose.
I was scratching it.
Well, I got to put something in a coma.
Why, you little...
(moans)
Well, I'll see you in court. Zing!
-Ah, cha-cha-cha!
-Cha-cha-cha?
-That's hopeful.
-Cha-cha-ching!
Oh.
Your Honor, my client
had just turned his life around.
His daughter recently bought
a washing machine
and promised him the box to live in.
Do you think they'll send
Dad away forever?
Oh, no, sweetie.
They just want all our money.
(gasps) Will they send us
to live with other families?
(horse neighs)
Miss Simpson,
from now on you shall live with us,
receiving musical instruction
from Mr. Adolphe Sax himself.
-(whoops)
-Adolphe.
A name that will only be associated
with beautiful music.
BART:
We'll be free to do whatever we want.
A thousand bucks a kidney?
-Take them both.
-Hmm.
BART: Ay, caramba!
(both sigh)
Mr. Simpson,
you deliberately ran your car
into my paycheck... I-I mean, my client.
No, "paycheck" is better.
What possible defense could you have?
I had no other choice.
I didn't want to hit a dog.
-ALL: Aw...
-A dog?
-He saved a dog?
-He was gonna save a dog.
-Wow.
-People love dogs.
This is our key to winning this case.
-You're on my side, right?
-I am.
(whoops)
Now, go ahead, son.
You tell us how you got your dog.
(in Cockney accent)
It was Christmas, sir.
We saved him and he saved us.
Now we love the dog,
and the dog gives us
all the love we could handle...
love.
ALL: Aw...
Could the stenographer
read that last part back
with sentimental music?
-(sentimental music playing)
-(Cockney accent) "The dog gives us
all the love we could handle...
love."
Does the defendant ask this court
to believe that in order
to avoid hitting a dog,
it is acceptable to hit a human--
my client?
It's looking good, Homie.
According to our consultant,
the toughest nut to crack
is juror number six.
Aw, good doggy.
Ladies and gentlemen,
this man is a human being,
just like you or me.
Surely his life has more value
than some creature that scoots
its buttocks along the ground.
ALL: Aw...
Or-- Or gets its head stuck
in an empty pickle jar.
ALL: Aw!
Or walks on a hot sidewalk
in a way that suggests it's dancing!
ALL: Aw!
This is ridiculous.
I'm a human being here,
not some dumb animal.
What? I never.
Who are you calling dumb?
The dogs who sniff for bombs
at the airport?
The St. Bernards who save lives
on the slopes of St. Moritz?
Or this one?
(playing "The Maple Leaf Rag")
-(all laughing)
-(Gil moans)
Now, I have a brief instruction
for the jury--
"There's more sanctity in a dog's loyalty
than there is in all your human laws."
-Ladies and gentlemen of the jury, how--
-Not guilty. (sighs)
Case dismissed.
We won! It's all because of you, boy.
-Mwah.
-CROWD: Aw...
Aw, I have never been more glad
that I didn't hit you with my car,
secretly bury you,
get another greyhound,
paint it your exact coloring,
then realize it's a girl,
stick on a fake wang,
and pretend that she's you
for however long dogs live.
CROWD: Aw...
Take us to the dog park!
(all cheering)
I know I've been through a lot,
but I always believed people
cared about a human being
more than a dog.
HOMER:
Hold it, I forgot my phone charger.
(Gil screams)
(sighs)
(screams)
HOMER: Oh, wait, this isn't mine.
(moans, groans)
It's now official--
a Springfield jury has decided
that the life of this greyhound
is more valuable
than the life of this
Greyhound station inhabitant.
Look at me, I'm a big man.
A big man!
Anybody got a quarter?
Got to be a quarter,
not two dimes and a nickel.
That ain't worth jack.
What's your take on all this,
Anger Watkins?
I'm angrier than a beehive
in a paint mixer.
This is the craziest legal decision
ever made outside of Arizona.
What's next? Cats get credit cards?
Let a snail race in the Indy 500?
(whispers) Like that stupid movie Turbo?
I tried to inhale nitrous oxide
to get fast.
I ended up naked
behind an appliance store!
Lies! Lies! Lies!
Oh, you're gonna get
ten walks a day, boy.
(quietly) You can even bite the mailman.
(whines happily)
There he is.
America's number one doggy daddy.
-Would you care to do the honors?
-Would I!
Uh, that's what I asked.
Would you?
-(shutter clicks)
-You're the greatest man
I know one thing about!
-(cheering)
-(horns honking)
Look at all those voters.
What is our current position on dogs?
We currently have a city employee
who rounds them up
and puts them to sleep.
What? I can't believe such a jerk
would even be elected dog catcher.
From this point forth,
this town will be known
as the dog-loving capital of the world.
That'll put Springfield on the map.
Yeah, why aren't we on the map?
I don't know.
I made, like, 20 calls to Rand McNally.
They don't even know what state we're in.
Thanks to these hastily-passed
untested pandering laws,
Springfield is now
the most dog-friendly city in America.
(crowd cheers)
Er, uh, arf.
♪ ♪
(gasps)
Is there anything here
the dogs haven't gotten into?
Just the dog food.
Why are you shutting me down?
You made a dog wait for a teeth cleaning
while you saved a racehorse's life?
And you call yourself a veterinarian. Ha.
And you know what we found inside?
Dogs in cages.
That's no way to treat man's best friend.
Lock him up. In a cage. Like a dog.
Don't you understand?
Dogs are born to follow and obey.
The moment the pack realizes
that humans are no longer their masters,
thousands of years
of domestication will fall away.
They'll revert to their wild wolf nature.
Well, then I guess you'll be happy
being nice and safe in jail.
Oh, yes, please! Take me there now.
You're all doomed!
Doomed.
Santa's Little Helper
didn't come home last night.
If you were a dog these days,
would you come home?
It's like doggy heaven out there,
only real.
-Doggy heaven isn't real?
-No! No, it's real!
The dogs all have harps and wings.
How do they play harps
if they don't have fingers?
Um... dogs have fingers in heaven.
How do you know so much about dog heaven?
I died for five minutes
and was sent there by mistake.
-Now leave me alone.
-(whining)
Hmm...
Ooh! Come on, girl.
Ow! Ow, ow. Just get him by the collar.
You can do it.
Come on, don't bite me.
Come on. Pull. Come on.
Dad, we don't have time for this.
Quiet. I'm doing something important.
There you go. Yes, that's it!
Well, well, well,
look what the cat dragged in.
-Worth it.
-Totally worth it.
I know.
(dogs barking)
(barking continues)
Kirk, Taquito is digging up my dahlias.
-Stop him.
-Mm.
-Sorry.
-(growling)
(gasps) Please don't hurt me.
I'm exposing my belly.
See? Exposing. Exposing! (gasping)
(growling)
(dogs snarling)
(howls)
(chuckles) See ya later, Moe!
Huh? My car's not starting.
Oh, I see the problem.
Out of gas.
Well, probably safer to walk anyway.
Yep, nothing safer than walking.
This is so healthy.
Thanks to this walk,
I'll live a lot longer.
(dramatic music plays)
(dogs growling)
Hey, here come some
of my four-footed friends.
I guess you want to meet the guy
who's responsible
for making all your lives better.
(dogs growling)
Okay, wait a minute. Let me guess.
Collie, dachshund, Tibetan Mastiff,
otterhound, Swedish Vallhund,
Finnish Spitz, Norwegian Lundehund,
Catahoula Leopard Dog, Lagotto Romagnolo,
and three wolves!
(shrieks)
Stand back! Back!
-Ow! Oh!
-(snarling)
You don't scare me.
Your bark is worse than your bite.
(barking)
Oh, those horrible barks!
(Homer whimpering)
(dogs barking)
(yipping)
Dr. Budgie warned them.
Dr. Budgie warned all of them.
But did they listen to Dr. Budgie?
All right, that's it. I'm comin' in there!
Oh, for cryin' out... (sighs)
Maybe if I turn sideways.
(grunts) Lou, get the bar butter!
This is what happens
when you buy European prison cells.
-(gasps)
-(growling)
Kids, lower the Purge armor!
-We don't have any Purge armor.
-Oh, right.
I always mean to buy it the day after
the Purge, when it's cheaper.
-What happened?
-The dogs have gone savage!
They've taken over the town!
-(howling in distance)
-(whines)
(gasps) No, boy.
Resist the call of the wild.
Like I did when they assigned
that book for summer reading.
Somebody help! Stop him!
(laughing)
(grunts) D'oh!
Oh, we've lost him to the pack.
No, he's a good dog.
He'd never turn against us.
Hmm, he's ripping the stuffing
out of your car seats.
Oh, yeah?! You think you're so smart?!
Okay! I'm eating your dog food!
This is on you!
Mmm. Oh, yeah.
(howling)
Hmm. Not one student showed up to school
just because a pack of ferocious,
masterless dogs
are roaming the playground.
-(gunfire)
-GIL: Ow! Damn it!
I thought we sent Willie
out there to deal with them.
Oh, I did. But he, uh, hasn't returned.
I've finally been accepted
for who I truly am.
(howls)
(grunting, snarling)
(dogs snarling)
How come I don't get a dog-proof suit?
Because I smell like lamb, Lou.
Very well.
You were right and we were wrong.
Yes. Um, can you remove the shackles?
Don't push your luck.
These dogs,
they walk around all high and mighty,
no regard for anyone else on the planet.
I mean, that's humans' job!
Repeal the stupid new laws!
Yes. Repeal the dog--
(quietly) and child labor-- laws!
-(crowd murmuring)
-Fine, just the dog ones.
-I say "status," you say...
-CROWD: Quo!
So passed!
Well, everything's back to normal again.
It's a pity no one told the dogs that.
-CROWD: Huh?
-Wha?!
You fools have surrendered
your position as alpha dogs.
Until you reassert human dominance,
it is you who will be calling
these savage canines master.
Who among you is brave enough
to tame this slobbering horde?
(panicked chatter)
(chatter dies away)
Well, I guess it's up to Ol' Gil.
Gil? Why are you helping these people
who think so little of you?
That's why I'm doin' it!
To show everyone
I'm not the town failure.
I thought I was the town failure!
-(chuckles) You're not even that.
-Aw!
-So who will come with me?!
-CROWD: None of us!
-One more time!
-CROWD: Nobody!
-I can't hear you!
-CROWD: Yes, you can!
Standing next to me
is the man whose life we all agreed
was worth less than a dog.
I say we stand behind him
as he redeems himself!
Even though he did nothing wrong.
CROWD: Gil, Gil, Gil, Gil,
Gil, Gil, Gil, Gil, Gil,
Gil, Gil!
We've got to get
Santa's Little Helper back.
(stammers) It's too dangerous!
-You kids ain't goin' nowhere!
-I got this.
(snoring)
Fine. But we can't go out alone.
We need someone who knows
how to fend off angry dogs.
(raving indistinctly)
Here, boy! Come on, boy!
Oh, where can he be?
(Cat Lady moans)
(creaking)
(jabbering)
Grampa, I called to make sure
the kids are okay.
They're not okay!
The boy's got sass,
and the girl thinks
she's Queen of the May.
You leave 'em with me
and I'll straighten 'em out!
I did leave them with you.
Why the hell would you do that?!
-Here, boy.
-Here, boy. Here, boy.
(squeaking)
(both whimpering)
(gasps) It's the alpha.
(growling)
I know that dog.
It's the one Milhouse got
when he didn't wet the bed for a week.
(growling)
We're about to die at the hands of a dog!
Paws. Dogs have paws.
Just remember the last thing
you did in life was correct me.
Oh, that actually makes me feel better.
(snarling)
No! This has gone on long enough!
(yipping)
-You sit!
-(growling)
-(Marge growling)
(yipping)
I'm sorry!
Mom, you've become the alpha dog!
Dogs are nice. I love dogs.
Because, in dogs,
we see the things we wish
we saw more of in people--
lifelong friendship, unwavering loyalty,
and a willingness
to eat anything you cook.
You rang?
Ol' Gil's here to save the day!
Where are those out of control pooches?
Sorry, Ol' Gil, you're too late.
But-- But I was supposed to redeem myself
and finally earn the town's respect.
Uh, good job, Gil.
You had to stop at the Automat
for an egg salad sandwich.
Well, at least
you still have the sandwich.
-(growls)
-Uh... aw...
-Baz, you belong with the Flanders'.
-Okily-dokily.
Dalmatian, fire department.
-(barks)
-(siren wails)
-Mr. Burns, the hounds.
-Excellent.
Uh, since you were gone,
all I had to release were the June bugs.
(buzzing)
Ah!
Willie, Skinner.
Aw, good boy.
(howls)
♪ Oh, you're my best friend ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Ooh, you make me live now, honey ♪
-♪ Ooh, you make me live... ♪
-(meows)
You'll have your day.
(meows sadly)
It's gonna be hard to cheer myself up
after this day.
-(whimpering)
-Hey, little fella!
You had a bad night, too, huh?
Come on out. I won't hurt ya.
(chuckles)
You just licked away a very bad day.
(barking)
Attaboy!
(ominous music playing)
-(dog howling)
-Shh!
Subtitled by B. Ives