♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
Brought to you by: I.L.G.
Selling your body's
chemicals after you die.
And by:
A subsidiary of I.L.G.
Oh, hi.
I didn't hear you come in.
Welcome to my home.
Say, did I hear some carolers?
♪ Rum-pa-pum-pum ♪
♪ Come, they told me... ♪
Hey, it's respected
private citizen
Tom Landry.
And South American
sensation
shoo... shi... sha...
shoo... sha... she...
shu... shu... boy.
ANNOUNCER:
Now, stay tuned
for a video Christmas card
from Tupac Shakur.
Hey, I thought
Krusty was Jewish.
Christmas is a time when
people of all religions
come together to
worship Jesus Christ.
-Boring!
BOTH:
HELP!
You want excitement?!
Shove this up your stocking!
Whoa!
Hmm. That looks entertaining.
(gurgling)
Oh yeah...
So tell your folks:
"Buy me: Bonestorm!
or go to hell!"
Buy me Bonestorm
or go to hell!
Bart!
Young man,
in this house
we use a little
word called "please."
It's the coolest
video game ever.
I'm sorry, honey
but those games cost
up to and including $70.
And they're violent and they
distract you from your schoolwork.
Those are all good points,
but the problem is
they don't result
in me getting the game.
I know how you feel, Bart.
When I was your age,
I wanted an electric
football game
more than anything
in the world.
And my parents
bought it for me
and it was the happiest day
of my life.
Well, good night.
Oh, I'll never get that game.
Tuck-in time.
♪ All aboard the sleepy train
to visit Mother Goose ♪
♪ Barty's stop is Snoozy Lane ♪
♪ To rest his sweet caboose ♪
Mom, I'm not
a little kid anymore.
Tuck-in time is lame.
Well, if loving my kids
is lame,
then I guess
I'm just a big lame.
Mom, it's lame to be proud
of being lame.
Well, life is like
a box of chocolates.
Mom! No, Mom!
(clanking)
.. what you're gonna get.
Ninety-nine cents!
I want to buy a copy
of Bonestorm.
Here's 99 cents.
(sighs)
Allow me to summarize
the proposed transaction.
You wish to purchase Bonestorm
for 99 cents.
Net profit to me:
negative $59.
Oh, oh, please take my $59.
I don't want it.
It's yours.
Eh, eh, eh.
Seeing as we are unfamiliar
with sarcasm
I shall close the register
at this point and state
that 99 cents
is the rental price.
Oh. Then may I please
rent it, please?
You may not.
I am all out.
Though I do have
a surprising abundance
of Lee Carvallo's
Putting Challenge.
Oh.
(lasers, explosions)
Milhouse has Bonestorm!
This is great!
And all I've done
is enter my name--
Thrillhouse.
Say, cool dude,
can I play too?
Uh, it's only
a one-player game.
Then how come it says
"second player score"?
Mom, Bart's swearing!
-No, no.
-Hey. What the hell?
-Out, right now.
-Damn it, I wasn't swearing.
Out!
Hmm.
Maybe if I stand next
to the games looking sad
someone will feel sorry for me
and buy me one.
Gavin, don't you
already have
this game?
No, Mom, you idiot.
I have Bloodstorm
and Bonesquad
and Bloodstorm II, stupid.
Oh, I'm sorry, honey.
We'll take a Bonestorm.
Get two. I'm not sharing
with Caitlin.
That must be the happiest kid
in the world.
Psst. Hey, Simpson.
Check this out.
Look what I got!
It's the kind I like.
Are you guys
shoplifting?
Four-finger discount,
dude.
Shoplifting is
a victimless crime
like punching someone
in the dark.
(both laughing)
Go ahead-a, Bart.
Take-a the Bonestorm.
The store,
she so rich.
She'll-a never notice.
Duh, it's the
company's fault
for making you
want it so much.
Don't do it, son.
How's the game going
to help your putting?
Just take it!
Take it! Take it!
Take it!
I'm outside.
I got away with it.
I'm free.
Sir, would you open
your coat, please?
Uh, I don't think this is
the kind of coat that opens.
Please step back
in the store, sir.
(swallows)
(clucking tongue)
That boy's parents
must have made
some terrible mistakes.
Shut up, Mom!
Ho-ho-ho!
Here you go, little fella.
No, no, not for him.
Oh... I see.
Hi, I'm Troy McClure.
You might remember me from
such public service videos
as "Designated Drivers--
The Life-Saving Nerds"
and "Phony Tornado Alarms
Reduce Readiness".
I'm here today to give you
the skinny on shoplifting
thereby completing
my plea bargain
with the good people at
Foot Locker of Beverly Hills.
Shoplifting began here
in ancient Phoenicia.
Thieves would literally lift
the corner of a shop
in order to snatch
the sweet, sweet olives within.
Oh, Sheheqazaramesh,
will you ever learn?
Flash forward
to ancient Babylonia...
All right, show's over.
E-excuse me?
You think you're
pretty smart, don't you?
No.
Don't smart off
to me, smart guy.
I could pay for the game.
I'll pay for it.
That kind of mush
might fly at Lamps Plus
but don't peddle it here.
If I wanted smoke
blown up my ass
I'd be at home
with a pack of cigarettes
and a short length of hose.
(nervous chuckle)
That's it, Mr. Comedian.
I'm calling your parents.
(gasps)
(telephone beeps)
Hello, Mr. and Mrs. Simpson?
This is Detective Don Brodka
from Try-N-Save security.
That's right, Don Brodka.
Your son Bart has been
caught shoplifting.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, it's a shame,
I know, but, well...
try and have
a merry Christmas.
They weren't home. Uh-huh.
But I left a message on
their answering machine.
That's right.
Um, okay.
I've really, really,
learned my lesson.
Can I please go now?
Yeah, get out
of my sight.
Hey, kid.
One more thing.
If you ever set foot
in this store again
you'll be spending Christmas
in Juvenile Hall.
Capice?
Well, do you understand?
Everything except capice.
Lousy stinking piece of crap.
Got to change
that answering machine tape.
Oh God, I got
to change that tape!
Got to change Maggie.
Dear God, we got
to change Maggie!
Hmm, we didn't have a message
when we left.
How very odd.
♪ Hello, muddah ♪
♪ Hello, faddah ♪
♪ Here I am at
Camp Granada... ♪
Marge, is Lisa
at Camp Granada?
(chuckling)
Now to put this tape
where no one
will ever listen to it.
Homer, didn't
you get any milk?
All I see is egg nog.
'Tis the season,
Marge.
We only get 30
sweet, noggy days
then the government
takes it away again.
(gasping)
I think I'm having chest pains.
(whistling)
-Bart, get your suit on.
-What for?
We're getting our
Christmas picture taken.
You lucked out,
Marge, my man
'cause I'm in
a smiling mood today.
(laughs)
Well good, so get ready
and before you know it
we'll be at the Try-N-Save.
Try-N-Save?
(loud whistle)
Oh, my teapots
are ready.
If you ever set foot
in this store again
you'll be spending
Christmas
in Juvenile Hall...
Juvenile Hall...
(cell door slams)
MAN:
Stand behind the yellow line!
You will now receive
your Christmas presents
donated by the Port Authority
lost and found office.
Pass your chit to Santa
to receive your gift!
If you do not have a chit,
you will not receive a gift.
Wow, the March 8th
newspaper.
Cool! A book of carpet samples.
Come on, new bike.
Oh, a soiled wig.
(garbled) Merry Christmas
and a Happy New Year.
(gulping)
MARGE: Bart, what's
taking so long?
If you're having that problem
with your zipper
I can send your father up.
Oh, no, I'm not.
What's the matter
with your face?
Is that a fake nose?
Are you wearing
chin putty?
I don't have to listen
to these wild allegations.
Please, Bart,
no more pranks.
It would mean
so much to me
if we could have
just one nice
family photo.
Hey!
I don't remember
saying that!
Uh-oh, almost forgot
to lock the doors.
(moaning)
I hope you're going
to the Valley Vista
Try-N-Save, kid
'cause you don't want
to come to my store.
Cat-feesh?
So we're just going to do this photo
and get out, right?
Ba-da-bing, ba-da-boom.
I want to look
at the pets
and write things
on the typewriters
and see if the new
dictionaries are in!
Okay.
I want to price some
flip-flops
and smell the new tires
and consult the pharmacist
for some free medical advice.
Sure, we're going
to have a great day.
Ba-da-bing, ba-da-boom.
Right, Bart?
Bart?
What's wrong, honey?
Uh-oh!
Somebody's
got tired little legs.
(grunts)
Mmm, wonder where
the flip-flops are...
Menswear?
Maybe it's sporting goods?
Wait, no, sleepwear.
Oh, probably, better living.
(loud sigh)
-(alarms blaring)
-(scared shudder)
Oh, Homie,
look at that watch.
I've always wanted
a watch like that.
Well, maybe someone
will give you one for Christmas.
Now she'll really be surprised
when she opens
that ironing board cover.
HOMER: Pfft, must have been
a pretty slow century.
(gasps)
The store detective!
Hey, Ansel Adams,
let's go!
Take the photo!
Wait, wait! I don't want
Maggie's face
hidden behind
that pacifier!
(whimpering)
Don't worry, mama.
I can put a smile
on baby's face.
Okay, sugarplum
it's time to meet
Mr. Funny-voice.
(high-pitched voice)
Hello, aluh...
(normal voice)
Oh, it's just air.
Well, come on.
Hurry up.
Okay, people.
One, two, three.
I thought I told you:
No returns for
busted merchandise.
What are you doing to my son?
I'm afraid your son
broke the 11th commandment.
Thou shalt not steal.
That's crazy.
Bart's not
a shoplifter.
He's just a little boy.
Oh, sure, now he's
just a little boy
stealing little toys.
But someday he'll
be a grown man
stealing stadiums
and... quarries.
My son may not
be perfect
but I know in my heart
he's not a shoplifter.
Fine! Play the tape.
Then everyone can see
you've got the wrong boy.
Wait!
Mom, I don't want
you to see this.
I did it.
LISA: Bart, I wouldn't have
expected this even from you!
My son's a thief.
Oh, Bart.
Stealing?! How could you?!
Haven't you learned
anything from that guy
who gives those sermons at church--
captain what's-his-name?
We live in a
society of laws!
Why do you
think I took you
to all those Police
Academy movies?
For fun?!
Well, I didn't hear
anybody laughing!
Did you?!
Except at that guy
who made sound effects.
(blubbering Doppler effect)
(muffled zooming)
(blows raspberry)
Honk, honk!
(imitates explosion)
(laughs)
Where was I?
Oh, yeah.
Stay out of my booze.
Mom, I'm really sorry.
I know you are.
Is there anything
I can do?
I don't know.
Why don't you
go to bed?
Okay.
(sighs despondently)
Man, I thought Mom was going
to scream me stupid.
She didn't even
raise her voice.
I admit I haven't known
Mom as long as you have
but I know when
she's really upset.
Her heart won't
just wipe clean
like this bathroom
counter top.
It absorbs everything
that touches it
like this bathroom rug.
Really? You think
this might be
one of those
forever-type things?
(muffled):
I don't know.
(squishing)
MARGE:
♪ Lisa's on the sleepy train ♪
♪ To rest her weary head ♪
♪ Her ticket is a candy cane ♪
♪ Made out of gingerbread ♪
(Lisa giggles)
LISA:
Good night, Mom.
Good night,
sweetheart.
(footsteps approaching)
Oh, great.
The tuck-in express
is right on time.
Good night.
I figured out
the boy's punishment.
First, he's grounded.
No leaving the house,
not even for school.
Second, no eggnog.
In fact, no nog period.
And third, absolutely
no stealing for three months.
I always thought
I understood
my special little guy
but somewhere
along the road
his hand slipped away
from mine.
Ah, what are you gonna do?
(groans softly)
He's not my little
baby anymore.
Maybe I mother him too much.
(yawns)
Hey, Mom, you
didn't wake me up.
Here's your
hot chocolate.
You didn't put
my marshmallow in.
I think you're old enough
to do it yourself now.
Okay. I can handle that.
Hey!
Give me a slice.
Milhouse, do you ever worry
that your Mom
might stop loving you?
What? I'm more worried
about piranhas.
Did you see that movie
where they sent a nuclear submarine
to fight the piranhas
and one of them swims
right down the periscope
and bites the guy in the eye,
and he goes:
(screams)
and that old lady
told him it would happen?!
Yeah. That was pretty good.
How come you're not
playing Bonestorm?
Ah, it got boring.
I'm really into
this cup and ball now.
Whoa! Wow! Whoa-ho-ho!
Man, you never know
which way this crazy
ball's going to go.
Yeah, right. You're just
trying to trick me
because you don't
want me playing
with your video game.
Here. Go ahead.
No. Let me try
the cup and ball.
Get your own!
Come on, don't be
a cup-and-ball hog.
Hey, give it!
That's my --
Milhouse, come on!
Give me the cup and ball.
Cup and ball hog!
Oink, oink!
Mom! Bart's smoking!
All right. Out, out.
Go, go, go, go.
Miss Milhouse, what are
you...
Okay, okay, okay.
I won't bug Milhouse
but, well...
Mrs. Van Houten
this is going to
sound kind of dumb
but can I hang out with you
while you do Mom stuff?
Who are Dan
and Sherry Adler?
Just friends of ours.
Oh. And who is Warren Burke?
Oh, he used to tune our piano
before we got rid of it.
He grew up
in Mechanicsburg.
-Oh, really?
-Mm.
Tell me I'm good.
(Marge laughing)
Oh, hey, that's Mom!
She's happy again.
You guys made a snowman family?
Check it out, boy.
It's like looking
into a living snow mirror.
Why didn't you
wait for me?
I didn't think
you'd mind.
I figured you were getting
a little too old for this.
But you can still make one.
There's some snow left
under the car.
(moans)
Stupid family.
Hey, Simpson.
Look what I swiped
from Try-N-Save.
It's a replacement tire
for a wheelbarrow.
Huh.
I knew you'd like it.
(laughs)
Everybody thinks
I'm the black sheep.
Well, I'll show them
what a black sheep can do.
Mom...
this fake snow
is making me dizzy.
We're almost finished.
There's just a
little bit of green left.
(humming)
There you are.
You can help me
spray the cookies.
Are you hiding something?
What do you have
under your jacket?
Nothing.
Oh, Bart. Not again!
Give it to me.
I told you,
I don't have anything.
You can't hide from me
in this house, Bart.
I spend 23 hours
a day here.
(laughing)
Get him, Ma.
There's no place
left to run, Bart.
Hand it over.
Oh, Bart.
I can't believe you did this.
I wanted to surprise you
for Christmas.
Oh, sweetie, this is the best
present a mother could get!
(loud smooching)
I love you so much!
My little bitty Barty!
Mom!
Since I got
my present early
I think you should get
yours early too.
Bart got a present early?!
Then I should get a present early!
I want a present!
Lisa, you have to wait.
(groans)
Okay. This is
the worst Christmas ever.
Now I know you
love video games
and I asked the clerk
which is the one every boy wants.
You got me...
(stifled groan)
Oh... yeah!
Thanks, Mom!
(halting cadence): Welcome
to Lee Carvallo's Putting Challenge.
I am Carvallo.
Now, choose a club.
(beep)
You have chosen a three wood.
May I suggest a putter?
(beep)
Three wood.
Now, enter the force
of your swing.
I suggest feather touch.
(three beeps)
You have entered "power drive."
Now, push 7-8-7 to swing.
(three beeps)
Ball is in parking lot.
Would you like to play again?
-(beep)
-You have selected "no."
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.