One month ago,
12 couples arrived
on this tropical island.
After an emergency
balloon landing,
a jellyfish explosion
and the most-viewed
cantaloupe catapult accident
of all time,
just four couples remain.
I'm Tag Tuckerbag, and this
is the greatest adventure
to take place in just one place.
- The Amazing Place!
The Place Show.
The final challenge
is the Lily Pad Leap.
They haven't done the LP Leap
since season 22...
Beauty versus Sexy.
Kayla, don't step on the stem.
You'll flip the pad.
You should know that.
You're a life coach.
- They flipped the pad!
- They flipped the pad.
What a noob.
Hector and Audrey Chang,
you have won
The Amazing Place!
- Called it.
- Mom, you always call the winner.
How do you know?
Well, your father may have
Moe's and football,
but I have being by myself
and this show.
Do you like adventure,
bandanas
and having your friends
see you melt down on TV?
We want you for season 48
of The Amazing Place.
Why don't you guys try out
for that show?
You would dominate.
Oh, no, I couldn't.
You know what they say,
you don't fail
at 100% of the shots
you don't take.
But you've watched
every episode of the show
and listened to
the director commentaries.
You even made us play
the terrible home game.
- Come on, Mom.
- Just try out.
- Come on, try out.
- Come on.
- Try out.
- Try out, Mom.
- Try out!
- Come on, just do it, Mom!
- Come on!
Just try out!
- Come on.
- Mom.
- Just try out.
- Why don't you try out?
- Come on, do it.
I'm not trying out,
so just can it.
I said can it
to my own children.
What have I become?
Baby, you've got
to tell them sometime.
Tell us what?
We know all the family secrets.
Like that Dad lost
our college funds
investing in a chain
of chewing tobacco cafes.
Dippin' Dens was a great idea.
We just weren't prepared
for all the spitting.
Well, I might as well
come clean.
The real tragedy
is now Chaw House owns
the entire
casual chewing market.
The truth is, we have tried out.
Dozens of times.
Why should you pick us
to be on The Amazing Place?
Because we're best friends
who never bicker.
We're constantly
at each other's throats.
We're motorcycle bikers.
That's our persona.
We have no idea what you want.
Just please pick us.
Why are you still doing this?
We were already on that show
where we had to crawl
into a drainage ditch.
That was just you,
and it wasn't a show.
It was a police bodycam.
That was a good show.
After 46 rejections,
I can take a hint.
They don't want us.
You know, reality shows
love a sob story,
and we've got a storage bin
full of tears.
And I've got a sister
who will edit them together
while I feed the dog
marshmallows
and see what happens.
Oh, we're not here
to make friends.
Unless I meet some awesome guy
who wants to be my friend.
Yeah, I met this really cool guy
at the boba place,
but he said he was moving
to Hong Kong and...
he didn't know his number yet.
Every reality show needs
that crazy, no-limits guy
that just shatters
society's taboos, right?
Well, break out
your pixelation machine,
because I am
your bug-eating nude fatso.
Oh, also, I'm not here
to make friends.
Oh, my God, married kids?
You're in the show.
- No...
- We're here on behalf
of some different weirdos.
Our parents have tried out
for every season
of The Amazing Place.
My dad would even record
my mom
opening your letters
in case they got picked.
So think what a magical
TV moment it would be
for our mom to find out
she made it on the show.
After losing all hope.
When she didn't even know
she applied.
The ultimate superfan
gets one last chance
to make her dreams come true.
I don't know,
it sounds a little manipulative.
You're fired.
I think we just found
our Boston Rob.
Or your Springfield Clancy.
Electric bill, past due,
Website renewal
DippinDens.com.
What's this?
Congratulations,
Marge and Homer Simpson.
You have been selected
to compete on...
The Amazing Place!
Tag Tuckerbag?
Tag Buggernut?
This is it.
After years of rejection,
you two will finally compete
for a million dollars
on The Amazing Place.
But we didn't even try out.
I edited together
your old auditions.
And I gave notes
which were ignored.
My crazy dream is coming true.
After you sign
the amazing waivers.
So many ways to die.
Falling off rocks,
rocks falling on me.
Toxoplasmosis?
That's what ate
Handsome Tom's face.
Just call me Handsome Homer.
- Bye, Mom!
- Don't get toxoplasmosis!
Welcome to The Amazing Place.
You're about to embark
on a test of mental toughness,
physical strength and interviews
where you have to pretend
that you're in the middle
of a challenge
when it's already over.
But first, let's kick things off
with a romantic beachside luau
at Lover's Lagoon.
Right after
your first challenge.
We took one item
from every person's bag
and hid it in another
contestant's luggage.
Everyone, find their
Suitcase Stowaway now.
It's the ultimate
Tarmac Unpack Attack.
Okay, Suitcase Stowaway.
They've done this
three times before.
Here's the secret,
dump and dig.
I found my stowaway.
Great. Go through my other bag.
Okay, Homie, don't panic.
The secret is to just take
your time, and...
I'm sorry, Homer and Marge,
you've been...
- Don't say it.
- Shell-iminated.
No, no. No, no, no.
We can't be
the first couple kicked off.
That's the ultimate humiliation.
I never even put on a swimsuit.
I never got to see the lagoon.
I'm crying, and no one's
even filming me.
We didn't even make it
off the tarmac.
All because of my screwup.
I guess we're going home.
No, you're going there.
A hotel? But we lost.
If we let you go home now,
fans would know
you've been kicked off
before the season airs.
So ejected contestants
must stay at this hotel
until every episode
is finished taping.
So we can't go home
for a month?
Six weeks, counting post.
I don't know what post is.
Hey, save some of those tears
for the reunion show.
You'll just put us in the back
row and won't ask any questions.
We won't even get
to hug the winner.
Yeah, but the runner-up's
always wandering around
looking for someone to hug.
That's your play.
How could I be such a noob?
I could learn
to love a noob, given time.
I already miss the kids.
Well, there's got to be
a way we can call home
without getting in trouble.
If you say anything
that reveals or implies
that you have been ejected
from The Amazing Place,
you are subject to a fine
of up to a million dollars
and, for residents of Georgia,
the death penalty.
Kids, kids, how are you?
Lisa said I can't use
the bubble bath,
but you said you bought it
for everybody.
Forget the bubble bath.
How's the show?
Are you winning?
I'm not supposed to say.
That means you're dominating.
I knew it!
No, no, we're not dominating.
I didn't reveal or imply that.
Well, you can't have gotten
kicked off yet.
You just got there.
Your mother and I are excited
to be part of the
Amazing Place family.
All further inquiries
should be submitted in writing
to Don DiBusco Productions,
Burbank, California.
What the hell
are you talking about?
This conversation
is hereby terminated.
You are each entitled
to one capful of bubble bath.
Now, that's parenting.
Come on, baby, it's not so bad.
Really?
Six weeks away from the kids,
Grampa, my sisters, your job.
With nothing to do but eat
free room service
and watch dopey movies on demand
while they keep us quiet
with an endless supply
of free booze.
It's a nightmare.
It is. It truly is.
I was up late night ballin'
Countin' up hundreds
by the thousand
I was up late night ballin'
Countin' up hundreds
by the thousand
You see, Curtis,
you never really
get an episode of SportsCenter
until you've seen it
for the third time.
Can I freshen up
that appetizer platter for you?
Nah, I better go
check in on my wife.
She's having a hard time
adjusting to hotel living.
Just let me clean.
Sweetie, I'm worried about you.
You just sit around
all day changing
the combination
on the room safe.
Do you want to put something
in the room safe?
I don't deserve valuables.
It's my fault we're stuck here.
All I deserve is to sit alone
and watch the TV channel
that's about the hotel.
Forgot your toothbrush?
No problem.
Sundries gift shop has all the
toiletries every traveler needs.
Sundries is awesome.
I got this shirt there.
Look, I know you're miserable,
but let me show you how great
this place can be.
It's just a stupid chain hotel.
Darling, take my hand, and
you'll see it's so much more.
Well, since you blew
the challenge
And we're not allowed
to tell
We're getting
all expenses paid at
Airport Hotel
The pillow's so foamy, baby
Order food on the phone-y
We'll eat Toblerone-y,
so don't cry
For breakfast
they have bagels
Cream cheese but no lox
A mini pack of cereal,
make a bowl out of the box
The pool's
so chlorine-y, baby
The towel's so teeny
No lifeguard to be seen-y,
we could die
No job, no kids, no Flanders
Choice of bar soap
or bath gel
Small ketchup's friends
With tiny mustard
Airport Hotel
Now that I've shown you, baby,
they'll leave us alone
Yeah, baby,
toilet's got a phone, yeah
Don't know why
Might the lady enjoy a movie
whose title doesn't appear
on the bill?
Maybe being trapped here
isn't so bad.
I'm not even worried
about what the kids are up to.
- Come on, dig. Dig.
- We're hot.
You can go for a nice, cool swim
after you finish
digging my pool.
I'm telling Patty and Selma
what you're doing.
What? We want a pool.
I just got my first wax
in years.
Hurt so much they had to
give me an epidural.
The fitness center only had
an old NordicTrack,
but it felt good to work out.
I sat on a yoga ball
and drank cucumber water.
It's nice to know
I can still do that.
Maybe we should peek in.
I am kind of curious to see
what's going on in the show.
Really? You sure
you can handle it?
Oh, yeah.
I'm still in a great mood after
reading that free USA Today.
Look, they're
editing our episode.
There I am, looking
for that Suitcase Stowaway.
I never found it, did I?
Great.
Go through my other bag.
Hey, that's me
looking for that thing.
Okay. Marge's vitamins,
Marge's pajamas,
Marge's giant chocolate bar.
I didn't pack
a giant chocolate bar.
What Marge doesn't know
is that her husband just ate
her Suitcase Stowaway.
This ultimate didgeri-don't
will send them packing.
I'm not the one who screwed up.
You are.
I'm so sorry.
I know you're gonna
need some space,
so I'll sleep on the couch.
What a dump.
What's that from?
- What?
- What a dump.
How would I know?
We wouldn't be in this dump
if you weren't such a flop.
I'm tired, dear. It's late.
A chocolate flop.
Yes, a chocolate flop.
That's what you keep braying
at everybody.
I don't bray!
All right, you don't bray.
I do not bray!
I said you didn't bray.
Make me a drink.
- Haven't you had enough?
- Make me a drink.
Yes, dear.
And lay out some mixed nuts.
We've got guests.
- We've got what?
- Guests. Guests!
You know, what's-their-names.
I don't know their names.
They just got eliminated
from the show.
It took them five weeks,
not five minutes.
Go answer the door.
All right, love,
whatever love wants.
Get the door. The door!
I'm getting the door.
You don't have to bray
like some subhuman monster.
Oh, go to hell!
Hi! Hi, there. Come on in.
- This is...
- Honey.
And this is Nick.
Oh, I thought his name
was what's-his-name.
Just ignore Homer,
old sourpuss.
That's me.
Hey, sourpuss, why don't you
mix them a drink?
Yes, dear.
I love your room.
We have the exact same
paintings.
You were this close to winning
The Three-Legged Chase.
You were right in there, Nick,
right at the meat of things.
There's no limit to you,
is there?
And how would you have played
the Three-Legged Chase?
Why don't I show you?
- Don't encourage her.
- Encourage me.
Inside, outside,
inside, outside,
in, out, in, out,
in, out, in, out.
You can sit around
with the minibar gin
running out of your mouth.
You can tear me apart like
the box the shower cap came in.
That's perfectly okay,
that's all right.
You can stand it.
I cannot stand it!
You married me for it.
- Our son is dead.
- No, he isn't.
- We have no son!
- Yes, we do!
Oh, yeah, Bart.
Man, last night sure was
a searing portrait
of a marriage in turmoil.
It's still in turmoil, you
chocolate-gobbling dream killer.
Attention, everyone, gather
by the bowl of mini yogurts.
For the first time ever
on The Amazing Place,
two eliminated contestants
will be brought back
to compete in the finale.
But here's the catch,
to get back in,
you have to dump your loved one
for another partner.
So, if your spouse screwed up,
this is your chance
to cut them loose.
It's the Dead Weight Drop.
I choose Nick.
That's got to sting, Homer.
I'm just glad
my friends and family
are never going to see me
humiliated like this.
This is it,
the final challenge.
Mango Tango.
First, pick and peel
enough fresh mango
to make six mango-ritas,
which you must then carry
across a log bridge.
But under the bridge is a pack
of mango-loving monkeys,
which can only be soothed
with music played
on a pennywhistle.
Also, there will be a
Kia Sportage in the background
that we couldn't figure out
how to fit into the challenge.
Your Mango Tango starts now.
And Marge draws first fruit.
I'll make the mango-ritas.
Great teamwork.
Could this be
a million-dollar puree?
I'll handle those monkeys.
It's the ultimate groovy
chill-out flute jam.
Look, the monkeys are mellowing.
This is our Kia Sportage Moment.
I did it.
We won. Without Homer.
Marge and Nick,
I want to congratulate you
on winning The Amazing Place.
I want to, but I can't.
Because you failed to salt
the rims of your mango-ritas,
rendering them mango-nothings.
I screwed up a recipe?
So get out of the way of the
actual winners, Shawn and Barry.
Hey!
Our rims are super salty.
Hey! Hey, hey, come on.
I am such a noob.
What a noob.
- Total noob.
- Classic noob.
Homie, I was such a jerk.
How can I make it up to you?
Sweetheart, you already have.
I am such a noob.
I've screwed up so many times
in our marriage,
and people always feel
so sorry for you.
But with this epic noob blunder,
I'm the one they pity.
Oh... pity.
Is this how you feel
all the time?
Kind of. I just never
let myself enjoy it.
Oh, pity feels good.
What should we watch next?
Ooh, I just heard about
a great new reality show.
PBS is showing a performance
of an Edward Albee play.
Sports talk it is.
How can you say that Phoenix
has any chance
to win the Western Conference?
What are you talking about?
We both picked the Phoenix Suns
to win it all.
Our Suns are dead.
No!