♪
Art lovers of Springfield,
good news.
The art museum
is closed forever!
[scattered applause]
Instead, our entire collection
will be digitized
and sold for a fortune
on the blockchain
as non-fungible tokens, or NFTs.
Whatever the hell those are.
[chuckles]
Now let's turn
some of our crappy art
into computer money.
Starting with
a true masterpiece, my butt.
[laughs]
[whirring]
Uh, Dad?
Ah! Technology!
[phone chimes]
I've lost Bart forever!
No!
[cash register rings]
Yes!
[whirring]
Honey? Remember how
we're always saying
we wish Bart was less fungible?
Did something happen to Bart?
Only the parts you can hug.
The rest is alive,
right here on my phone.
[yelps] My baby is an app!
Uh, no, apps actually do stuff.
He's an NFT.
- But look how much he's worth.
- [gasps]
For Bart? Hmm.
Imagine what we'd get for Lisa.
He is the first NFT
of an actual person.
I don't care.
We've got to find a way
to get him back.
[hooded figure] To do that, you,
yourself must enter the blockchain.
Who are you?
We are the enlightened
intellects
who safeguard the crypto-verse.
[Homer]
Kylie Jenner, Rob Gronkowski,
and Jimmy Fallon.
I thought you were
just celebrity shills.
Ugh, we would never
promote a technology
if we didn't understand
the distributed ledger
underpinning it.
Der!
[laughs] I can't
stop laughing, buddy.
[Homer]
Shut up.
You ruined "Cowbell."
This key is a back door
through the blockchain's
cryptographic protocol.
Once you're inside, find Bart
and use it to get
both of you out.
[grunts]
[whirring]
Huh, so this is the blockchain.
No, noob, this is
the block-train.
Speeding forever through
the loveless icy world
created by crypto-bros.
Powered by the most abundant
fuel in the universe:
FOMO, the fear of missing out.
For a digital incarnation of an
abstract mathematical concept,
it could use a good dusting.
[British accent] Well, that's because
this is the last car of the train, innit?
The dwelling place of NFTs
with no value.
Which is 99% of all NFTs
ever created.
Huh, I guess being
the second-ever human NFT
isn't worth a whole lot.
Where do they keep my son?
[French accent]
At the very front of the train
where you can never go.
Watch me!
[grunts]
[laughter]
Whoa!
[retching]
You killed Ennui Oeuf 116.
[whirring]
Congratulations,
you've moved up the train
because you are now
as valuable as us,
the Cuddle Kittens.
Because you killed another NFT.
What you call
mindless slaughter,
crypto-bros call "disruption,"
and then pour cash into it.
So, to rescue Bart,
I need to kill
a bunch of you guys.
[popping]
Ooh.
Well, I guess I got to do this.
[yowling]
Sorry! Nothing personal!
Hope... you... can't...
feel... pain. [grunts]
[whirring]
[Lisa]
Mom's price is skyrocketing!
Look at the FOMO!
Now everyone's gonna
want human NFTs.
Dad, you said you were
taking me to bumper boats.
I am. Uh, have
some more chocolate milk.
No one is putting another child
into that scanner...
before mine.
- [grunting]
- Hey!
[whirring]
[gasps]
Please kill Ralph-house.
[squishing]
[whirring]
The front of the train.
I made it.
Bart! We're getting out of here!
Whoa, Mom, what's the rush?
Grab yourself a Jaded Ape
and take a load off.
You never like my friends.
Mom's almost got Bart out.
Don't let your son become
a worthless human again.
Sell him to me
- for $100 million.
- Hmm!
No, Dad!
If you sell Bart to Mr. Burns,
he'll be trapped
on the blockchain forever.
But this is my chance
not to miss out,
after I've missed out
on everything.
The housing bubble,
the first tech bubble,
the second tech bubble,
the current tech bubble.
Just one time,
I want to be the guy
that gives all his money
to Bernie Madoff!
Mom, get out of there!
Dad's gonna crack!
He did it.
I can't believe he did it.
[whirring]
- We made it.
- Where's Homer?
I want to tell him the inside
of his phone smells.
He-he sold himself.
He was so afraid of missing out,
he tokened his own life.
Woo-hoo!
Eternity on
a super swanky train.
Ooh, twerked chicken.
[rumbling]
What happened?
Our FOMO, it's gone.
The NFT craze is over.
D'oh!
[Homer]
Ah, the romance of train travel.
♪
♪ And it's clearly
to his credit ♪
♪ That he is an Englishman ♪
♪ He remains ♪
♪ An Eng ♪
♪ Lish... ♪
Wait. Did you only
ask me to sing
to forestall your gruesome end?
Guilty as charged. [laughs]
- [Bart grunting]
- [laughing]
[screams]
Ha!
It was only by
following my hunch
that we found
the East Side Strangler
on the west side of town.
Can you explain how
you overcame childhood trauma
to become the nation's most
renowned criminal psychologist?
For that story,
you'll have to read my book.
- [school bell rings]
- [indistinct chatter]
Office Muntz.
Told you I'd smell you later.
Been a long time.
Ah, look at us.
We thought we were
gonna stay young forever.
Some of us did.
Oh, right, like Bart,
because he got murdered.
Speaking of gruesome junk,
we could use your help
on a case.
I'm flattered, but I'm the dean
of the True Crime Department.
I can't just run off and...
The killer left a message.
And we think it's for you.
♪
Maybe Rod Flanders
did grow up to become
a shockingly foul-mouthed
prop comedian,
but he didn't deserve this.
Only a super-traumatized
profiler like you
can piece together
what happened here.
Hmm.
[breathes deeply, sighs]
[Lisa]
Our killer took his time.
Had fun with it.
Enjoyed a game of Solitaire.
Red King on a Red Queen?
This psycho doesn't
play by the rules.
Damn, she's good.
Here, he had one
of those moments
where you walk into a room
and forget what you came in for.
How did my guys miss that?
One more thing.
This killer won't stop now.
There will be others.
Sarge, there's been another.
How can he also be the first?
Sarge, we got another one.
[whistles]
Boy, that's something
you don't see every...
One more, Sarge.
Got another one, Sarge.
The severed hand
opens the fridge,
which tugs on that
strip of sinew,
turning over the eyeball cup,
which rolls down the spine,
startles a cat,
which leaps onto
the butter dish seesaw,
and sends
the other eyeball flying,
turning on the coffee maker.
Even I can't get inside
a mind this deranged.
There's only one person who can.
[thunder rumbles]
Little Lisa Simpson.
You really made something
of yourself
after I made mincemeat
of your brother.
Come to thank me?
- No.
- Rude.
I don't have time
for your games, Bob.
I'm working on a...
Yes, a case so confounding
you're actually willing
to seek my help.
The Rube Goldberg Sherri
is actually quite impressive.
Hat tip, psychopath.
What about
the identical messages?
How can they all be "the first"?
Really, Professor Simpson,
am I meant to spoon-feed you
all the answers?
Speak in riddles or drop a clue
in a clever anagram
hidden in something
I've just said right now.
This is a waste of time.
Perhaps a limerick will help.
There once was a shiny machete,
that turned poor Bart's head
to spaghetti.
You're gonna die
in that cell, Bob.
And when that happens,
wherever I am,
I'll be dancing.
Can you think of anyone who
would've wanted to hurt Sherri?
No, everybody loved
my big sister.
Big sister?
You guys were twins.
Yes, but Sherri was born first.
Probably makes sense for you
to be my husband now, huh?
Sherri is the first.
Rod Flanders, Dermott Spuckler,
all firstborns,
that's the pattern.
And Bob said something
about an anagram
taking us to the killer's lair.
[gasps] That's it.
[tires screech]
[both gasp]
[clanging]
Stay here.
[creaking]
Hey, meat hooks, hook meat much?
Ha-ha...
Nelson?
Nelson, where are you?
[screams]
[panting]
[gasps]
The killer's lair looks
just like my old bedroom.
But how? Ooh.
Maybe the killer's
on the security footage.
No! It can't be!
[grunts] Freeze!
- [handcuffs click]
- Wha...?
I can't be the killer!
I turned my trauma into healing!
Oprah said so!
[thunder rumbling]
I'm sorry for the imbroglio,
but if the chef de cuisine
insists on calling it
Taco Tuesdays,
he can't very well serve flautas
and expect us not
to make a fuss.
[door locks]
Hello, Bob.
H-How did you get in here?
Well, I knew if I killed
enough people
in the most gruesome
possible ways,
they'd send me to your prison.
But to get into your cell?
I had a little help.
Lisa the killer.
I never thought
you had it in you.
The Lisa you knew didn't.
But I'm another story.
Oh, really?
Split personalities?
Trope alert!
Call the First Thought Police.
Professor Lisa had no idea
she was my accomplice.
But she's gone now.
She was my last victim.
Or, rather, second to last.
The penultimate.
[grumbles]
♪ He remains an ♪
♪ En-En-En-En-En-En-En-En ♪
♪ En... ♪
- [screaming]
- ♪ ...glishman. ♪
[munching]
Simpson.
No eating in the turbine room.
Since when?
Pfft. The nanny state
wins again.
No tanning in the reactor core,
no texting while driving
and eating ribs.
Can't even trim your hedges
with a machine gun.
When did everyone get so scared?
The world would be fine if
people just used common sense.
Like me.
Ah! Jailbreak!
Woman. Woman.
Homer, one. Nanny state, zero.
[munching]
[groaning]
[gurgling]
Stupid radioactive garbage donut
mutating my DNA while I sleep.
Hey, who stole
my Flanders's newspaper?
Sorry about that, Homer-ino,
but I-I whited out the crossword
after I did it,
so you could enjoy it, too.
[gurgling]
- [belches]
- Ah.
Better from the chimney
than the furnace, am I right?
[laughs]
[groans]
So, you see, there's nothing
in the Bible that says
a pastor and his wife
can't take separate vacations.
[grunts softly]
Daddy, are you being tickled
by the Holy Spirit?
[gurgling]
[moaning]
[gasps] I've been neighborino'd
into Home-diddly-omer.
[gasps] And why am I in church
when football is on?
[all gasping]
[belches]
[terrified chatter]
[all screaming, belching]
[all groaning, grumbling]
Kiss my ass, church-os.
I'm fat, I'm bald, and
I've never felt sexier, baby.
- Why, you little...
- [choking]
Woo-hoo!
[all belching]
[belches]
[Kent Brockman over TV] A mysterious
affliction has descended upon Springfield.
Citizens of every age,
race and catchphrase
are mysteriously transforming
into bald, pear-shaped doofi.
[sing-songy]
Donut Stu has diabetes type 2.
[belches]
News is stupid.
Somebody put on wrestling.
Do all these burping baldos
remind you of anyone?
I'd know that
butt scratch anywhere.
Everyone's turning into Dad.
[screams]
[belching]
Uh, children, your father's
less than stellar genetic code
is spreading through
burp-borne transmission.
If we're going
to cure this virus,
we need his DNA.
You three are the only ones
impervious to the virus.
You have got to find him.
Hmm. It is 11:30 in the morning.
[indistinct chatter]
- Beer, Moe.
A-beer, a-Moe.
Have you seen our dad?
No, just these hundreds
of silly versions of him,
which is the greatest thing
that has ever happened to me.
I mean,
I'm printing money over here.
[barking]
Coming right up,
Santa's Little Homer.
Real Dad wasn't at the
bowling alley, the candy store,
or mocking the hippos
at the zoo.
Wait.
Dad ate a bucket
of this chicken last night.
When that happens, where does he
always spend the next day?
[Homer]
I'll be out in a minute.
Um, is this really the most
convenient bathroom
for your father?
It's the closest one
Mom will let him use.
Dad, we need you
to save the world.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah.
Can you believe some idiot
left this perfectly good
back scratcher in there?
Look, it goes all...
the way... down.
[moans]
What?
Now, if you'll just board
the Frink-ama-copter...
- We're not calling it that.
- [grumbles]
And then we'll pop your DNA
in to the Frink-tabulizer...
We're not calling it that.
[muttering]
And everything will go back
to the way it was.
Wait. Hold on.
Why would I want that?
Finally, everyone thinks
the way I do.
Nobody's making up stupid rules
about bicycle helmets
or where you can smoke cigars.
- You want to drive without a seatbelt?
- [tires screech]
FaceTime while jaywalking?
- Enjoy a sugary soda?
- [tires screech]
Go ahead!
You're not hurting anyone!
It's a utopia.
No, a me-topia!
Yes, well, you don't really want
everyone to be like you.
Earth-shattering reveal!
[screaming]
[chuckling à la Homer]
When did insurance commercials
get so funny?
[gasps] Marge!
Cooperating with us
is the only way
to get your wife back to normal.
You've never looked
more beautiful.
[kissing]
Scooch over, gorgeous.
When we get home,
let's you and I bump muzzles.
Please. Please! If we don't have
some competent people left
to run things,
society will collapse!
Coders to run the Internet
that feeds you
the latest misinformation.
Pilots to fly the planes
you need to be restrained on.
I mean,
a world without experts...
Does Beaker ever shut up?
[chuckles] Good one, me-Marge.
Mm, well,
you leave me no choice.
I'm calling in
a nuclear air strike
to obliterate all
the Homerized Springfielders,
including, very sadly,
the touring company
of Kinky Boots.
Obliterating in three, two...
Hey, you know what you need?
A nice, relaxing scratch
on the back.
No! No! Oh, a lifetime
of study and education
down the... [groans]
[speaking gibberish]
♪ This must be just like ♪
♪ Living in paradise ♪
♪ And I don't want to go home ♪
[whoops]
♪ This must be
just like living in paradise ♪
- ♪ Just like paradise ♪
- [whoops]
♪ And I don't want to go home ♪
[whoops]
♪ And I don't want to go ♪
♪ This must be ♪
♪ Just like living in paradise ♪
[all belching]
♪ And I don't want to go home. ♪
Captioning sponsored by
20th CENTURY FOX TELEVISION
and FOX BROADCASTING COMPANY
and TOYOTA.
Captioned by Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
[belches]
[organ music plays]