♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screeching)
(glass shattering)
ANNOUNCER: The News on Parade
Corporation presents...
Bringing you the world
of current events!
New gadgets!
-(train whistle blowing)
-(all screaming)
And Hollywood!
Look! It's Amos
from radio's Amos and Andy.
Hello, everybody!
It's a proud day
as Springfield is declared...
one of America's
400 fastest growing cities!
And why not?
Business is booming!
Half the country wears
Springfield galoshes.
And say hello to the state's
first Aqua-Car factory.
Keep 'em coming, boys!
The city's even
in the celebrity business.
Everyone knows Professor "Rubber Mouth"
-hails from Springfield.
-MAN: Bravo!
Everybody's chipping in.
Even this fella has
Springfield's can-do spirit!
-(barks)
-So, watch out, Utica.
Springfield is a city
on the grow.
(crowd murmuring)
Ha! The way people
act around here,
you'd think the streets
were paved with gold.
They are.
-(tires screeching)
-(car crashing)
(siren wailing, gunshots)
Got any spare change,
man?
Yes! And you ain't gettin' it!
Everybody wants somethin'
for nothin'.
-(door slams)
-I'm old! Gimme, gimme, gimme!
(humming)
Huh? Hey!
There's something you don't see
in a toilet every day.
Anybody lose their glasses?
Last chance.
Whoo-hoo!
The sum of the square roots of any
two sides of an isosceles triangle
is equal to the square root
of the remaining side.
-That's a right triangle, ya idiot!
-D'oh!
Thank you so much for visiting
our plant, Dr. Kissinger.
It was fun.
We'll let you know
if your glasses turn up.
Uh, yes. Well, I'm sure
I left them in the car.
(thinking) No one must know
I dropped them in the toilet.
Not I, the man who drafted
the Paris Peace Accords.
-Mm-Hmm. Mmm.
-Mm. Huh.
-(scoffs, sighs)
-Mmm. Hmm.
Sir, bad news from accounting.
The economy's hit us pretty hard.
(scoffs) Tough times, huh?
I've lived through 12 recessions,
eight panics and five years
of McKinleynomics.
I'll survive this.
Even so, sir, we could stand
to lay off a few employees.
Oh! Very well. Lay off...
him, him, him, him-- Hmm.
Better keep the egghead.
He just might come in handy.
Dad, you shouldn't wear glasses
that weren't prescribed for you.
Lisa, just because you're 10 feet tall
doesn't mean you can tell me what to do.
-I'm Bart.
-Give me those.
And finally, Henry Kissinger
was hospitalized today
after walking into a wall.
Now over to Kent Brockman
with some grim economic news.
Scott, things aren't as happy
as they used to be
down here at
the unemployment office.
Joblessness is no longer
just for philosophy majors.
Useful people are starting
to feel the pinch.
I haven't been able
to find a job in six years.
Huh. And what training
do you have?
Five years of modern dance.
Six years of tap.
BROCKMAN: The economic slump
began last spring,
when the government
closed Fort Springfield,
devastating the city's liquor
and prostitution industries.
Now, at the risk
of being unpopular,
this reporter places the blame
for all this squarely on you,
the viewers.
I propose that I use what's left
of the town treasury...
to move to a more prosperous
town and run for mayor.
And once elected,
I will send for the rest of you.
Boo!
-Excuse me, Mr. Mayor?
-The chair recognizes
the little chick with the gleam
of hope in her eyes.
This piggy bank contains $15
I saved from my allowance.
It isn't much,
but I would like to help.
Aw, just what I need
to tip the skycaps.
I'll tell you what
made this town great!
Good, old-fashioned gumption!
There's nothing here
a little elbow grease won't fix!
So let's roll up our sleeves...
and--
(snoring)
People! People!
Let's be a little
more realistic.
Now, I, uh, hesitate
to bring this up,
but a number of cities
have rejuvenated their economies...
with, uh, legalized gambling.
(crowd murmuring)
There is an added bonus.
Some of the revenue...
can go to help our underfunded
public schools.
(distant cricket sound)
-Well, I like the part about the gambling.
-What do you think, Reverend?
Once something has been approved by
the government, it's no longer immoral.
-(cheering)
-By building a casino,
I could tighten my stranglehold
on this dismal town!
(cheering)
-(belches)
-(cheering)
Well, now.
Are there any objections?
MAN: Oh, probably Marge
is gonna have some.
(crowd murmuring Marge's name)
Actually, I think it might
really help our economy.
(murmuring excitedly)
Very well then.
Instead of fleeing this town,
I'll stay here and grow fat
off kickbacks and slush funds.
(cheering)
(shouting, cheering)
This could be a whole new
beginning for Springfield.
And you know
what the best part is?
We've really done
something for the children.
(man shouting)
MAYOR QUIMBY:
We're thrilled you've decided
to build your casino
on our waterfront.
Oh, I 'll never forget my carefree boyhood
days on this old boardwalk.
-(children chattering)
-(electricity buzzing)
-(chattering continues)
-♪♪ (calliope)
(screams)
Why, you-- (gasps)
Master Burns!
I mean, carry on.
-(yelping)
-(giggling)
Me leg's gone gimpy!
Who'll provide for me little ones?
(laughing)
(laughing continues)
Oh! What was I laughing at now?
(panting)
Oh, yes.
That crippled Irishman.
(laughing)
Sir, the designers are here
with some prototypes for your casino.
Gentlemen,
I give you Britannia!
Gambling with all the glitz
and glamour of the British Isles.
Best of all, the waitresses
and showgirls are all real Brits.
Fresh from the streets of Sussex they are!
(clicks tongue)
Freshen your drink,
governor?
-Get out.
-Okay. All right. Wait--
- Now-- Now, dig this, man--
- Get out!
(chuckles) Wow. Oh, let me
just get my head together.
Now!
I'll need three ships
and 50 stout men.
We'll sail round the Horn
and return with spices and silk,
the likes of which
ye have never seen.
-We're building a casino!
-Arr.
Can you give me five minutes?
(scoffs) Idiots. I'll design it myself!
I know what people like.
It's got to have sex appeal
and a catchy name.
Mom, we're having
a geography pageant at school,
and I don't know
which state to go as.
In honor of legalized gambling,
why not go as the state of Nevada?
No. Nevada makes
my butt look big.
Then how 'bout going
as Florida?
You enjoy orange juice.
Old people like you.
Dad, what do you think?
Shh! I'm trying to teach
the baby to gamble.
-Why?
-I got a job at Burns' casino.
As you know, it's been my lifelong dream
to become a blackjack dealer.
Your lifelong dream was to be
a contestant on The Gong Show.
And you did it in 1977.
Remember?
-♪♪ ("Oh! Susanna")
-(audience jeering)
(gonging continues)
We got more gongs than the break-dancing
robot that caught on fire.
Hello. I'm retired
heavyweight boxer Gerry Cooney.
Welcome to Mr. Burns' casino.
If there's anything I can do to
make your visit more enjoyable,
please, just let me know.
Yeah, great. See ya!
Uh, don't forget
to apply for...
our V.I.P. platinum club
for special discounts on--
-Hey! I said bug off!
-(whimpers)
Uh, let's see.
Eighteen, 27, 35--
Dealer bust!
Looks like you all win again.
Yee-Haw! Homer,
I want you to have
my lucky hat.
I wore it the day
Kennedy was shot,
and it always
brings me good luck.
Why, thanks, Senator. Oop!
Looks like my shift is over.
(all)
Uh-Oh!
GRAMPA:
Come on, lucky seven!
Papa needs
a new pair of spats.
I want some of that
sweet, sweet do-re-mi!
Fat City, here I come!
Please throw the dice now.
Please. Now.
Don't rush me!
I have arthritis.
Will the gentleman
please roll the dice?
All right, all right,
smart guy.
(gasps) Oh, for crying out loud,
I dropped one.
Oh! Now it's in my shoe!
Ow! Ow! Ooh!
Ow! Ooh! Ow! Ooh!
A round of applause please
for Anastasia!
She loves show business.
So much nicer than the savagery
of the jungle, ja?
-(honking)
-(low growl)
Hey, tiger! Wake up!
(growling)
(roaring)
-(roaring)
-(screaming)
(shouting in German)
Whoo-hoo! Jackpot.
Wait a minute!
Are you over 21?
-Are you?
-I'm not authorized to answer that.
(grunts)
By the way, your martinis suck!
Oh, yeah? What are you gonna do?
Start your own casino,
in your tree house and get all
your little friends to come?
I'd like to see that!
(laughing)
Hi. Yeah, welcome.
Have a lucky day! Mm-hmm.
Well, he certainly showed me.
MARGE:
Hi, Homie!
Hey, Marge, after your big tantrum
against legalized gambling,
I bet it feels pretty weird
to be in a casino.
-I was for the casino!
-Strike three, Marge!
I remember that meeting,
and I have a photographic memory.
Legalized gambling
is a bad idea.
You can build a casino
over my dead body.
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
-For you. It's the president.
-Y'ello?
And then I said to the president--
get this--
Marge? Marge?
Hmm.
Hmm, I wonder if they have
a lost and found.
Oh, what the hey!
-(coins clanking)
-♪♪ (fanfare)
Mmm!
Hmm.
-(lights buzzing)
-(distant chatter)
(chattering continues)
Hey, how's it goin'? Hey!
Good to see you. Tell your friends.
Lookin' lucky! Hey, what's happenin'?
Love the jacket.
-(meows)
-Behold the box of mystery!
The cat goes in-- (straining)
Right here--
(screeching)
(screeching continues)
Twenty-one?
Do that card-counting thing again.
Come on. Do it again.
Definitely have
to leave the table.
No! Please, please,
please, please, please.
Gotta watch Wapner. Leave the table.
Yeah, leave the table.
-No!
-(screaming)
(screaming)
Sir, you haven't slept since
the casino opened five days ago.
I've discovered
the perfect business.
People swarm in,
empty their pockets and scuttle off!
Nothing can stop me now!
Except microscopic germs.
But we won't let that happen,
will we, Smithers?
Uh-- No, sir.
-(jingling)
-(whimpering)
(whimpering)
Whoa! A baby on the table!
That's good luck!
ALL: Yay!
-Snake eyes. Sorry.
-ALL: Boo!
Garsh, it must be excitin'
to live in the casino.
-Ja.
-You know, we are having a party tonight.
-(roaring)
-(grunts)
Whoa, Marge!
You gotta watch out.
Your little boy Bart could have been
eaten by that pony!
(gasps) Oh, my God!
Barney, thank you.
I would never have
forgiven myself.
Now, you stay put,
young lady.
-(grunting)
-Oh!
Man, that's classic
compulsive behavior.
Wow! Free beer!
Buddy, those are
my quarters!
-(belches)
-Hey, this guy's paying off!
-(belching)
-(chattering)
I don't wanna hit a sore spot,
but can we talk about herpes?
♪ Herpes, herpes bo-berpes ♪
♪ Banana-fana, fo-ferpes
herpes, oh ♪
Hey, that spot
on Gorbachev's head--
Herpes! Trust me.
-Anybody here have herpes? Huh? Huh?
-(person coughing)
You people are the worst
audience I've ever seen.
Well, you're the worst
comedian we've ever seen!
Oh, great! Well, we'll just sit here
silently for the next 90 minutes.
-Fine with us.
-(groans)
They're all covered with filthy germs!
Aren't they, Smithers?
Why, what do you mean, sir?
-GERMS: Freemasons run the country!
-Ew!
(Marge grunting)
Marge, you waited for me!
(grunts)
-Okay, Marge. Let's go.
-I'll catch up to you.
-Marge, I'm taking the car.
-I'll walk.
-This late? Through the bad neighborhood?
-Yeah.
-Marge--
-Go home! You're bad luck!
Wait! I see
what's happening here.
You're just mad because everyone in
this town loves gambling except for you!
-Well, that's just sad.
-(grunting continues)
(grunting)
-Um--
-What?
Excuse me, ma'am. Don't you
think you've gambled enough?
No!
Okay. We're required by law to ask every
75 hours. Get her another free drink.
(meows)
Do you get the feeling
this family is disintegrating?
I mean, we haven't had
a meal with Mom all week.
And she hasn't even started my costume
for the geography pageant.
Pipe down, sister! I gotta book
a new act for tonight.
Turns out that Liza Minnelli impersonator
was really Liza Minnelli.
(shivers, grunts)
-There's nothing to eat for breakfast!
-You gotta improvise, Lisa.
Cloves, Tom Collins mix,
frozen pie crust-- Mmm!
Maybe Mom just doesn't realize
we miss her.
We could go down to
the casino and let her know.
Aw, come on, Lisa.
There's no reason to--
Let's go see Mom.
(grunting)
Marge, we need to talk.
You're spending
too much time at the casino,
and I think you may
have a problem.
I won $60 last night.
Whoo-hoo!
Problem solved!
Smithers,
I've designed a new plane.
I call it the Spruce Moose,
and it will carry 200 passengers...
from New York's Idlewild Airport
to the Belgian Congo in 17 minutes!
-That's quite a nice model, sir.
-Model?
-Mom!
-Huh? What? Lisa, what's up?
-I just had a bad dream.
-Oh, sure.
You just lie down
and tell me all about it.
Well, I know it's absurd,
but I dreamed the bogeyman
was after me, and he's hiding--
(screams)
Bogeyman!
You nail the windows shut.
I'll get the gun.
(grunts) Bart, I don't want
to alarm you,
but there may be a bogeyman
or bogeymen in the house.
(screams)
(tires screeching)
(trembling audibly)
-(Bart and Lisa sighing)
-Hmm.
-What happened here?
-Nothing, Marge. Just a little incident
-involving the bogeyman!
-(gunshot)
None of this would have happened
if you had been here to keep me
from acting stupid!
Oh, I'm sorry. I have been spending
too much time at the casino.
I'll be around more
from now on.
Does this mean you'll help me
with my costume?
Oh, sure, honey.
I promise.
-Thanks, Mom.
-Mmm.
Aw, just like on TV.
-(grunts)
-(canned laughter, applause)
Hi. You from the casino?
-I'm from a casino.
-Good enough. Let's go.
(lights buzzing)
I'm afraid Robert Goulet
hasn't arrived yet, sir.
Hmm. Very well.
Begin the thawing of Jim Nabors.
(panting)
Are you sure this is the casino?
I think I should
call my manager.
Your manager says
for you to shut up!
Vera said that?
Huh.
(grunting)
Dad! Mom said she'd be home
to help me with my costume.
And she's not!
And the geography pageant is tonight!
Lisa, your mom
still loves you.
It's just that she has a career now.
She's a slot jockey.
But, Dad, if I don't show up in a rubber
suit shaped like the state of Florida,
I'll be the laughingstock
of the whole school.
Oh, it's always something,
isn't it?
First I have to drive your
pregnant mother to the hospital...
so she can give birth to you,
and now this!
Ow, ow, ow, ow.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow,
ow, ow, ow!
-Dad!
-(chuckling) Oh, yeah. The costume.
Hello, "Floreda"!
(gasps)
I'm not a state!
I'm a monster!
(sobbing)
No, Lisa. The only monster here
is the gambling monster...
that has enslaved
your mother!
I call him Gamblor!
And it's time to snatch your mother
from his neon claws!
(groaning)
Marge! Where are you?
Damn this casino!
(grunts)
-(yells)
-Double stars! Everybody wins!
(cheering)
-(grunting)
-Hey!
-Seven. Lucky seven!
-(cheering)
-Yeah-- Ooh!
-He can't talk now.
(grunting)
Marge?
-Hey!
-Smithers,
I don't want that unpredictable lunatic
working in my casino.
Fine. We'll transfer him
to the nuclear plant, sir.
Oh, my beloved plant.
How I miss her.
Bah! To hell with this!
Get my razor! Draw a bath!
-And get these Kleenex boxes off my feet!
-Certainly, sir.
-And, uh, the jars of urine?
-Oh, we'll hang on to those.
Now, to the plant!
We'll take the Spruce Moose!
-Hop in!
-But, sir-- (gasps)
I said hop in.
(panting, gasps)
(grunting)
(shouting incoherently)
Homer, what is it?
Slow down.
Yer getta ferda redda oura.
Think before you say
each word.
-You broke a promise to your child.
-What?
You promised Lisa to help her
with her costume.
You made her cry.
Then I cried.
Then Maggie laughed.
She's such a little trouper.
(gasps)
Lisa's costume!
(gasps) Homer, I didn't realize.
I'm so sorry.
Marge, I want you to admit
you have a gambling problem.
You know,
you're right, Homer.
Maybe I should get
some professional help.
No, no! That's too expensive.
Just don't do it anymore.
♪♪ (jazz intro)
♪ Jingle bells
Batman smells ♪
♪ Robin laid an egg ♪
♪ Batmobile lost its wheel
and the Joker got away, hey ♪
Thank you!
Thank you very much.
-Ow!
-Oh, I'm sorry, kid.
And special awards
go to the two students...
who obviously had no help
from their parents:
Lisa Simpson and Ralph Wiggum.
-I'm Idaho!
-Yes, of course you are.
You know, Marge, for the first time
in our marriage,
I can finally
look down my nose at you.
You have a gambling problem!
That's true.
Will you forgive me?
Oh, sure!
Remember when I got caught stealing
all those watches from Sears?
-(groans)
-Well, that's nothing,
because you have a gambling problem!
And remember when I let that
escaped lunatic in the house...
'cause he was dressed
like Santa Claus?
-(groans)
-Well, you have a gambling problem!
Homer, when you forgive someone,
you can't throw it back at them like that.
Aw, what a gyp.
-Mmm.
-Remember when I--
-Homer!
-Oh, yeah. I forgot already.
♪♪
(slot machine spinning,
coins clanking)
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.