♪ The Simpsons ♪
(chalk screeches)
(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
(sucking)
(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
HOMER: Do you two have to
sit so close to the TV?
Back up or it
will hurt your eyes.
-Oh, it will not.
-Oh, yes, it will.
Our next movie is McBain.
Another 'shoot-em-up,
push them through the
plate-glass-window' splatterfest
from the Hollywood
cookie cutter.
Here's a typically
brainless scene.
Senator Mendoza is one of the most
respected citizens in this state, McBain,
and yet you ran his limo
off a cliff,
broke the necks of
three of his bodyguards,
and drove a bus
through his front door?
But, Captain, I have proof
that he's head of an
international drug cartel.
I don't want
to hear it, McBain!
You're outta here!
(screaming)
That makes two of us.
-All right, McBain!
-(laughing)
-Cool.
-"That makes two of us."
(grumbling)
You know, I can't believe
we're talking about the same movie.
-Oh, no.
-I thought McBain
was a non-stop roller coaster
of chills, thrills,
spills and kills.
And that chase at the end,
my friend? Mwah!
Are you nuts?
That movie stinks
like your creepy
one-bedroom apartment.
Your mother didn't think
it was so creepy.
My mother! Real mature.
I'm sick of your
grade-school insults.
HOMER: I love watching
the bald guy argue
with the fat tub of lard.
Ooh!
Hey!
What gives?
Dad, do something!
All right,
all right.
Time for Doctor TV
to perform
a little surgery.
-(banging)
-Umph!
Looks like you lost
a patient, doc.
Shut up, boy.
Cheap Chinese TV.
Why did I ever buy it?
-Is that better?
-BOTH: No!
Stupid-- How's this?
(screaming)
Oh, no. Okay.
Just everybody remain calm.
(grunting)
(screaming)
Hey everybody.
If you look real close,
you can kind of
make them out.
Hey, yeah.
Yeah, I think I can.
I think this is sick.
-You're staring at a dot.
-She's right! She's right!
(sobbing)
Oh, how I miss TV!
Dear God,
just give me one channel!
Homer, it's not
the end of the world.
You know, before
we got married
we hardly ever
watched television.
-You lie.
-Bart!
No, it's true,
Bart.
We used to shoot pool
and go dancing.
How romantic.
And a lot of times we'd
stay at home
and talk just like this.
I'm living it,
but I ain't loving it.
It's so hard
to picture you two then.
Hand in hand at
the crossroads of life.
There's so many
questions.
-Pick one.
-Okay. Uh...
How did Dad
propose to you?
Oh, well...
Well, uh, Miss Bouvier,
I think we've found the reason
why you've been throwing up
in the morning.
Congratulations.
-D'oh!
-Oh...
Lisa, I'd rather
tell you
a different story--
How your father
and I first met
and fell in love.
We were seniors
in high school
but we had never even met.
♪ Why do birds
suddenly appear ♪
Ugh. Gross.
Ah.
(singing along with radio)
♪ Some people call me the space cowboy ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Some call me
the gangster of love ♪
♪ Some people call me
Maurice ♪
♪ Whoo! Whoo! ♪
♪ Cause I speak
of the pompitous of love ♪
Hey, Homer,
you're late for English.
HOMER: Pfft. English.
Who needs that?
I'm never going
to England.
Come on.
Let's go smoke.
MARGE:
I'm for equal rights,
but do we really need
a whole amendment?
Come on, Marge.
Don't you think you deserve
to earn just as much as
a man who does the same job?
Well, not if I have to do
heavy lifting or math.
Oh, Marge. You really
ought to read this.
(sniffing)
Oh, the shop kids
are smoking again.
(inhaling)
(coughing)
(bell ringing)
Oh, no. We're late
for wood shop.
But we're early for lunch.
Let's go grab a burger.
Boy, you never stop eatin'
and you don't gain a pound.
It's my metabomalism.
I guess I'm just one
of the lucky ones.
Well, well, well.
If it isn't Homer Simpson
and Barney Gumble,
Springfield's answer
to Cheech and Chong.
Allow me, gentlemen.
You just bought yourselves
three days of detention--
you know where and when.
BOTH: 3:00,
Old Building, Room 106.
MARGE:
And in another article,
I found out that
to hire professionals
to do all the jobs
of a housewife,
who, incidentally,
is not married to a house,
would cost $48,000 a year.
Right on, sister!
The first step to liberation
is to free ourselves
from these
male-imposed shackles.
(cheering)
I didn't think it
would burn so fast.
I guess it's
the tissue paper inside.
Miss Bouvier,
I am surprised.
You just bought yourself
one day of detention.
You know where and when.
Well, no, I don't.
-Actually I've never--
-3:00, Old Building, Room 106.
(whistling)
Hey, Estelle?
Will you go
to the prom with me?
I wouldn't go to
the prom with you
if you were
Elliott Gould.
Oh, shot down again.
Hey, don't worry, Barney.
It's a big school.
There's got to be a girl
nobody else wants
to take to the prom.
Excuse me,
is this room 106?
Hey, who's that?
I--
I don't know.
♪ Why do birds
suddenly appear ♪
♪ Every time
you are near? ♪
♪ Just like me,
they long to be... ♪
Oh.
Hey. Would you
like to go--
She's mine.
♪ Close to you ♪
So, uh, what are
you in for?
I'm a political prisoner.
Last time I ever take a stand.
Well, I'm here
for being me.
Every day I show up,
act like me,
and they slap me in here.
Simpson, be quiet.
I haven't seen you
in school before.
-Okay, Simpson.
-What?
You just bought yourself
another day of detention.
-Maybe we should get together sometime--
-Two days.
I'm sorry. I don't even
know your name.
-I'm Homer-- J
-Three days. Four days.
-Simpson.
-Five days.
-It was worth it.
-Six days!
Okay, Simpson,
to the back of the room.
So, it was
love at first sight.
It was a
jailhouse romance, man.
I reached step one--
she knew I existed.
The only problem was
she didn't care.
-What's the matter, boy?
-HOMER: Nothing.
You haven't said 'boo'
all night,
and usually I have to
wrestle the bucket
out of your greasy mitts.
Dad, I'm in love.
Uh-oh. Why don't you
grab yourself a beer, boy.
But Dad, I don't drink--
Cut the crap.
"I just collect the cans,
Daddy."
Now grab yourself a beer
and get me one too.
Now. This girlfriend of yours,
is she a real looker?
-Uh-huh.
-A lot on the ball?
-Oh, yeah.
-Oh, son, don't overreach.
Go for the dented car,
the dead-end job,
the less
attractive girl.
Oh, well, I blame myself.
I should have had this talk
a long time ago.
Thanks, Pop.
A-b-c-d-e-f-g-h-i-
j-k-l-m-n-o-p-s.
Hi, I'm Homer Simpson.
I need some guidance,
counselor.
Okey-dokey.
(sighs)
Good Lord.
Simpson, you should have come
to see me a long time ago.
Yeah, maybe, but I just met
this girl Marge Bouvier
and I want to force
her to like me.
Well, that's not exactly
the type of guidance I give.
-Oh...
-Well, I like to think
I do something helpful
for every student
"N" through "Z."
Uh, the only advice
I can give you is...
try to share common interests
and spend, spend, spend.
Well, what interests does she
have that I could make common?
Oh, I believe she's very
active on the Forensics Team.
They meet in
the new building. Room 219.
Far out!
Homer, do you have any plans
for after graduation?
Me? I'm gonna drink a lot of
beer and stay out all night.
Oh, no, I meant career wise.
You know, that nuclear power plant
will be opening soon.
It's one of the
few outfits around
that won't require
a college education.
Me? In a nuclear power plant.
(laughs)
Kaboom!
But bringing up a son--
even a blind one--
isn't a lifetime
occupation.
Now the more
you help him,
-the more you hurt him.
-(applause)
Woe unto Shelbyville
should they underestimate
our strength
in dramatic
interpretation.
Thank you, Artie.
(clears throat)
My name's Homer Simpson.
I'd like to sign up
for something.
Well, we have an opening
on the Debate team.
-Debate? Like arguing?
-Yes.
I'll take that,
you stinkpot!
Just warming up,
Mrs. Bloomenstein.
This year's topic is
Resolved:
The national speed limit
should be lowered
to 55 miles per hour.
55? That's ridiculous.
Sure, that'll save
a few lives,
but millions will be late.
Why don't you take 'con'.
♪♪ ("Pick Up The Pieces")
No way.
ARTIE:
Our current speed limit
-is an anachronism.
-Ignoramus.
-Will you shut up.
-Wait a minute.
That word you keep
calling me--
-Ignoramus.
-Ignoramus?
It means I'm stupid,
doesn't it?
There is a difference
between ignorance and stupidity.
Not to me there isn't,
you--
-Homer.
-Ignoramus.
-You're the ignoramus.
-No, you are.
Homer, would you like
to present your rebuttal?
With pleasure.
-(zipper unzipping)
-(gasping)
-Ay, caramba!
-(groaning)
Hello.
Oh, you may not remember me.
I'm Homer Simpson.
-I mooned for rebuttal.
-Yes, I remember.
So, uh... you want
to go out with me?
Well, I, uh--
I don't think
you're my type.
Well, uh, you see--
you see the problem is
you don't know me.
I have references.
Just ask...
Coach Flanagan,
and ask Mr. Sakofsky
and Barney Gumble.
I don't know.
Look, I'm not asking you
to like me.
I'm not asking you to put
yourself in the position
where I can touch
your goodies.
I'm just asking you
to be fair.
Homer Simpson? Oh, yeah.
Junior varsity shot-putter.
Mm-hmm.
I think if he applies himself,
you know, trains real hard,
hits the weights some more,
he could go another foot.
I had him for four years.
Solid "C" student.
Made a lamp last year.
He's all things to all men
and maybe to one lucky gal.
Want to go to the prom
with me?
Good God, no!
Well put.
Well, what's the good word?
-I'm sorry.
-What?
Well, you seem like
a nice enough guy,
but I don't really
don't have the time.
Wha--
And the City Forensics
Championship is coming up.
-Yeah, so?
-Oh, and I tutor part time.
-You tutor?
-Yes.
And anyone can be tutored?
Just those who need help
with French.
-French.
-Mm-hmm.
What a coincidence.
Just the subject
I'm having trouble with.
-(chuckling)
-Why, you cagey old dog.
Great story.
Positively spellbinding.
-Work, damn you! Work!
-Bart! Pay attention.
You may be telling this
to your own son one day
if something breaks.
(humming)
Ooh, lost a few.
Oh-- (chuckles)
Well, there's plenty more
where that came from.
Uh-oh, a zit.
No problemo.
(humming)
The perfect crime.
♪ Don't be a baby, lady ♪
♪ Just be a lady, baby ♪
♪ All I ask is
one thing baby ♪
-(doorbell rings)
-Hello.
Why is there
make-out music on?
It helps me study.
Well, not me.
Shut it off
and let's get
down to business.
-(needle scratches)
-(music stops)
(beep)
-Crayon.
-Bien.
Uh...
Fen... etre.
Bien.
-Femme.
-Tres bien.
Well, I should
probably be going.
I have a big forensics
meet tomorrow.
Wait, wait, wait.
Don't go, don't go.
Wait. Wait.
Why don't we take
a little study break?
BOTH:
♪ Do the hustle ♪
MR. SIMPSON:
Keep it down!
MARGE:
Homer, you're amazing.
Before, you couldn't
say "bonjour,"
but now you can conjugate
all the regular verbs,
two irregular verbs,
and sing the first verse
of "Alouette."
♪ Alouette,
gentil alouette ♪
je te plumerai ♪
Bien.
I can't believe it.
It's sticking.
You're telling me new stuff,
and minutes later,
it's still there.
And it's all thanks to you.
Marge, when I see you forming
the vowels and continents--
-Consonants.
-Consonants
with your beautiful mouth
and your beautiful breath
pushing them past
your beautiful teeth--
Merci, I guess.
Marge...
would you go
to the prom with me?
You know, Homer,
you're like no one
I've ever met before.
You're dear,
honest and open
without a trace
of pretension.
I'll take that as a compliment.
So will you go out with me?
Please say oui.
-Oui.
-Woo-hoo!
Marge, this will be the greatest night
of your life.
I've been saving up
for a new engine for my car
but I'm gonna spend it
all on us.
I'm renting
the biggest limo.
I'm gonna buy you
the biggest corsage.
My tux is gonna have the widest lapels,
the most ruffles,
and the highest
platform shoes you ever saw.
Maybe I'll wear
my hair... up.
Wait, wait, wait, Marge.
If honest and open
is what you like,
get a load of this.
I'm not really
in any French class.
This was just a brilliant scheme
to get to know you better.
-Hmm!
-(smack)
Ow.
You knew the city Forensics
finals are tomorrow,
and you kept me here
until 1:00 a.m.
pretending to be stupid!
Homer J. Simpson,
I hate you!
Hey, Barney.
Guess who's got a date
for the prom!
Everything I know tells me
this story doesn't end
with us sitting here
and you telling it to us.
Get off the edge of your seat.
They got married, had kids
and bought a cheap TV, okay?
MARGE: Bringing up a son,
even a blind one,
isn't a lifetime occupation.
Now the more you... help him--
-Terrible.
-MARGE: The more you hurt him.
(groans)
Congratulations, Artie.
Marge, this may not be
the most appropriate forum
for what I'm about to
put forth,
but--
(clears throat)
would you go
to the prom with me?
Well--
I can think of a dozen
highly cogent arguments.
Well, the first is from
"Time Magazine,"
Dated January 8th, 1974.
"America's love affair
with the prom.
"Even wallflowers
can look forward
-to one date a year--"
-No, Artie, Artie.
The best argument
is that
I've known and
respected you for eight years,
and I would be delighted
to go to the prom with you.
If you pinch your cheeks,
they'll glow.
A little more.
Try to break
some capillaries, dear.
Couldn't we just use rouge
for this?
Ladies pinch.
Whores use rouge.
Is Marge here?
-Who...
-Or what are you?
-I'm her date.
-Mm-hm.
I suppose you want to
come in and sit down?
-Okay.
-Marge's dates
-get homelier all the time.
-Mm-hm.
That's what you get
when you don't put out.
You know, I usually insist
on approving Marge's dates,
but from what she's told me,
I'm sure you're a solid citizen.
-Thanks, Mr. B.
-(grunting)
MRS. BOUVIER:
Here she comes.
Get the camera ready.
Homer!
(camera shutter clicks)
What are you doing here?
You said you'd go
to the prom with me.
Well, I also said
I hated you,
and we haven't even
talked since then.
-I was afraid you'd cancel our date--
-(doorbell rings)
So I stayed away
from you completely,
even though it meant
skipping school for three weeks
and graduating this summer...
I hope.
I'm Artie Ziff,
Marge's date for the prom.
Well, hello.
Well, hello, hello.
-Don't we look handsome?
-Yes, indeed, we do.
Well, come in,
young man.
Wait a second.
If he's your date,
who are you?
I'm... a spare.
Excuse me.
Now that that unpleasantness
is behind us forever,
let's take a picture
of the happy couple.
Say "Cheese Whiz."
Hey, buddy,
where's your date?
-She's with him.
-DRIVER: Ouch.
So I guess you want me to
take you home, huh?
Hey! I paid for this car,
I paid for this tuxedo and
I paid for the two dinners.
-We're going to the prom.
-Prom it is.
♪ Good-bye,
yellow brick road ♪
♪ Where the dogs
of society howl ♪
Don't dance too closely now.
Have a good time.
Wait a second.
Is that a bong?
You have asthma?
All right,
move along.
Homer Simpson.
Heh.
I thought you dropped out.
You wish, Donderlinger.
That's Mr. Donderlinger.
♪♪
(camera shutter clicks)
Steak or chicken?
One of each, please.
-BARNEY: Coming through!
-Barney!
♪ Oh, yes,
they call him the streak ♪
(whistling)
That young man's bought himself
about a decade of detention.
Children, we have
tabulated your votes.
The king and queen
of Springfield High School's
class of 1974 are...
(drum roll)
Artie Ziff and Marge Bouvier.
Oh, isn't it great?
Hail Queen Marge!
Whoo!
Long live the queen!
Fellow classmates,
instead of voting
for some athletic hero
or a pretty boy,
you have elected me,
your intellectual superior,
as your king.
Good for you.
Very well said.
Now your king and queen
will share
their first royal dance.
ARTIE: (mumbling)
♪ Why do birds ♪
♪ Suddenly appear ♪
♪ Every time ♪
♪ You're near? ♪
I got to get out of here.
-(sobbing)
-(door opens, closes)
Homer?
What?
Why are you doing this?
Why can't you accept that
I'm here with someone else?
Because I'm sure we were
meant to be together.
Usually when I have
a thought,
there's a lot of
other thoughts in there.
Something says yes,
something says no,
but this time,
there's only yes.
How could the only thing I've ever
been sure about in my life be wrong?
Hmm... I don't know,
but it is.
Well, where to now, Romeo?
Inspiration Point.
Okay, but I'm only paid
to drive.
(moaning and giggling)
MARGE:
Gee, Artie... Artie, wait.
I don't know. I mean,
it was a beautiful evening.
-Let's not ruin it.
-ARTIE: Just kiss.
MARGE: Oh, Artie, please...
-ARTIE: Come on, kiss me.
-MARGE: Oh, Artie.
-Please?
-No, really, I mean it!
Now stop it!
(gasps)
(panting)
I'm sorry, Marge.
Take me home, Artie.
Well, it's 1:00.
If you want to keep me
I'm afraid it's gonna be
$45 an hour.
Nah, that's okay.
I'm broke.
I'll walk home.
Yeah, why spoil
a perfect evening?
♪♪
Marge, I would appreciate it
if you didn't tell anybody
about my busy hands.
Not so much for myself,
but I am so respected,
it would damage the town
to hear it.
-Good night.
-Yeah, right.
MR. BOUVIER: You know, when that
Simpson boy showed up,
it took years off my life.
MRS. BOUVIER: Will you stop it?
She went out with the good one.
-(horn honking)
-Shut up!
-I'm over as far as I can go.
-(horn honking)
-All right! All right!
I'll walk in the mud!
-Homer?
-Marge?
-Yeah. You want a ride?
-Sure.
You know, Homer,
when I got home,
I realized who I should have
gone to the prom with.
Who?
Oh...
Hi, prom date.
Marge, pour vous.
Mmm.
Why so glum?
(sighs)
I got a problem.
Once you stop this car,
I'm going to hug you
and kiss you,
and then I'll never be able
to let you go.
And I never have.
(gagging)
HOMER: ♪ Some people call me
the space cowboy ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Some call me
the gangster of love ♪
♪ Some people call me
Maurice ♪
♪ Whoo! Whoo! ♪
♪ Cause I speak
of the pompitous of love ♪
♪ People talk about me,
baby, yeah! ♪
♪ Sayin' I'm
doin' you wrong ♪
♪ Doin' you wrong,
♪ Doin' you wrong ♪
♪ Well don't you worry,
baby, don't worry ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm right here ♪
♪ Right here, right here,
right here, right here ♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.