CHOIR:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screeching)
D’oh!
(screams)
(tires screeching)
(beeping)
(giggles)
Nothing like reading a well-
plotted mystery on the beach.
It’s amazing
how they always solve the crime
just before they run out
of pages.
Marge.
(gasps)
James Patterson!
Come with me, Marge.
Help me think of new
nursery rhyme-themed titles
for my thrillers.
(murmurs excitedly)
Ooh, how about
"Little Bo Peep"?
That’s great.
A clue could be
her sheep.
Marge, the real mystery is
why we’re just talking
when I could be
kissing your...
(alarm clock ringing loudly)
(murmuring confusedly):
I overslept!
The family can’t start the day
without me.
Relax, baby.
While you were dreaming of me
and calling me James,
I took care of everything.
(sighing):
Oh, Homie, you woke up early?
Eh, stumbled home at dawn,
same diff.
Now, don’t worry.
I packed everyone’s
lunches and sent them off
into the world.
What kind of
lunch is this?
A drawing of a sandwich.
I’ve got Grampa’s medication.
(people screaming)
Abe, pull over!
You’re not the driver!
Shut up, pizzas!
I’ve gotta deliver you!
Oh... no lunch for me.
Unless I "scare" one up.
Hey, guys, remember
to stick together.
Today is the anniversary
of the Dark Stanley murders.
Tell us all you know.
All right,
imagine I’m holding a flashlight
-under my face.
-(screams)
Years ago, Stanley DeGroot
was a cook here at the school.
All the kids made fun of him
because he never graduated
from college.
(singsongy):
Stanley, Stanley,
no degree.
Two credits short at MIT.
(kids laughing)
One day,
Stanley picked up a cleaver
and put a new entrée
on the menu.
(theme from 12 Monkeys playing)
A delectable little dish
called kids’ head soup.
(crazed laughing)
Needs more girl.
What happened to Dark Stanley?
They hanged him for murder
and buried him in
an unmarked grave.
When they came back
the next day,
the whole cemetery was missing!
(all gasping)
(school bell rings)
Try not to
think about it.
They say Dark Stanley makes
your skull into a toilet
and wee-wees into it.
And just when you think
he’s done,
Dark Stanley takes your skin
and makes footy pajamas.
Nobody pajamanates my skin.
This is the very spot
where Dark Stanley comes
to harvest heads
for his soup of sorrow.
Why aren’t you a-scareded?
Oh, Dark Stanley
would never dare attack
a crowded, well-lit...
(kids screaming)
(shuddering):
Dark Stanley’s here.
(kids screaming)
(laughs)
(theme from 12 Monkeys playing)
(kids screaming)
Whoa!
Murther!
Well, Seymour, I certainly
appreciate you letting me
store my collection of antique
cologne bottles in your office
while they recarpet
my condo.
It’s quite a collection
and, I assume, irreplaceable.
You assume correctly.
(kids screaming)
Seymour, Gary.
(groans)
Simpson, I know
you’re behind this.
Well, you are going
to get some counseling
from our school
psychologist.
Dark Stanley’s going
to eat my brains!
Or from a qualified
professional.
But first... Willie,
get those kids back!
I’ll bring those wee ones back
dead or alive.
Not dead.
Ah, ya never let
Willie be Willie.
(theme from The
Hallelujah Trail playing)
...Zimmerman, Zorx, and...
Zzyzwiski.
Now back to class, all of you.
All right,
you heard him.
Back to class.
But we don’t go
to school.
But you do live
in the district.
That’s right.
We home-school ’em.
I teach the big ones
and the big ones teach
the little ones.
but no one ever taught me,
which makes the whole thing
just an exercise in futility.
Uh-huh.
Skinner, what is
going on here?
Sir, if we let these hill folk
into our school,
our test scores
would drop so low,
we’d lose
all federal funding.
I see...
and we’ve already lost state,
county, and local funding.
Plus our last bake sale
was a disaster.
People took bites
without buying the cookies.
Yes, we’re not very
good at anything.
Excuse me.
Lisa Simpson,
with the school paper.
Am I to understand you’re
purposely denying education
to these children?
-That’s a total mis...
-Well, I wouldn’t, uh...
-Uh, you know...
-I mean, that is
to say, uh...
You see,
the thing is...
I warn you, young lady,
we can fumfur all day.
-We, um, it’s not
that we, um...
-You see, what, uh...
-I just, we don’t, um...
-...you’re not,
uh, grasping...
-We’re not really, um...
-...the, the, the, the...
You haven’t heard the last
of this.
Well, I think
we’ve heard the last of this.
No, you haven’t.
We’re going to have
to give this some thought.
Let’s sing
while we think.
It’ll make it more
fun for everyone.
♪ How do we gag
a blabbermouth like Lisa? ♪
♪ How do we crush her
First Amendment rights? ♪
♪ How do we stop her
writing up what she saw? ♪
♪ Would she
shut her trap ♪
♪ For a gift card
from the Gap? ♪
BOTH:
♪ She might ♪
TEACHERS:
♪ Oh, how do we stop
a royal pain like Lisa? ♪
♪ How do we make
Miss Righteous ♪
♪ Less uptight? ♪
You have a lovely voice,
sir.
(groaning):
Why do you have to make
everything weird?
You asked to see me?
Lisa, would you consider
tutoring Cletus’ children?
You’ll be happy,
they’ll be happy,
and I can go home and
enjoy some delicious fondue.
Made with the fondue set
I bought you for Christmas?
No. So what do you say, Lisa?
Me? A tutor?
♪ The hillbilly tykes ♪
♪ Will become my tutees. ♪
Whoa! Ah! Oh!
CLETUS:
Hey, kids!
The plow mule done birthed
a girl-critter!
Young’uns, this here girl
is come from fairyland
to school y’all.
Now, if you need me,
I’ll be on the porch
drinkin’ Thomsen’s Water Seal.
My name’s Lisa.
What are your names?
Witney!
Jitney!
Dubya!
Incest!
Crystal Meth!
International Harvester!
Birthday!
(whining):
Are we gonna do
this much work every day?
Why do I have to go
to a stupid psychiatrist?
I told a scary story.
Big deal.
Look, boy, nobody
knows better than me
that you’re a lost cause.
But the school’s paying
for five sessions
and there’s a Chinese
restaurant next door
where I can get drunk.
Get ready, Sheila.
This guy likes the act.
(heavy Chinese accent):
Mr. Simpson! You good man!
-We happy see you!
-You not come long time!
Come sit, drinky-drinky.
Where’s Margie?
She super lady!
(laughs)
Bart, my name
is Dr. Swanson.
Stop right there, Doc.
This school has sent me
to more therapists
than you’ve had bad dates.
I’ve looked at the ink blots.
I’ve played with the puppets.
The whole racket’s
a hatful of crap.
I see.
Well... I get paid whether
you make progress or not.
Why don’t we just kill the time
playing videogames?
Yeah, right. I bet you’ve got
a bunch of "learning" games.
Why don’t you go online
and look for a boyfriend
while I take a nap?
Actually, I just got
"Death Kill City II:
Death Kill Stories."
Whoa! You’ve got "DKC2: DKS"?
That one’s rated
"Bad for Everyone."
(yelling and grunting)
VIDEOGAME NARRATOR:
You have destroyed
all human life on earth.
Level 1 complete.
(laughing):
Yes!
And that’s how a presidential
veto gets overridden.
Any questions?
How is any of this gonna
put dog meat on my plate?
Hmm. Maybe the best way
to begin your education
is to get you some exposure
to the wider world.
So, I’m gonna take you
to downtown Springfield!
We gotta get permission
from Daddy.
It’s all right with me.
DR. SWANSON:
And, lastly...
-I need a noun.
-Booger.
Read it back!
"The county fair is
always sucky to visit
on a hot summer fart."
"You can eat
delicious cotton hate,
and ride the Ferris burp
and the Merry-go- booger."
(laughing)
You can’t make
that stuff up.
What does this tell you, Bart?
That this is one terrible
county fair.
And...?
And...
My dad never takes me
on the merry-go-booger.
He’s always passed out
in the parking snot.
HOMER:
He’s lying!
You drink too many
scorpion bowl.
You go sleepy-sleepy now!
(groans)
(no accent):
Did, uh,
did you get his wallet?
Every president
has a word balloon
that says "I am gay."
(chainsaw revs)
These colorful bums is funny!
And guess what?
Ben and Ken,
the Street Magic Men,
are only the beginning!
The city is a treasure trove
of culture,
and multiculture!
♪ Mistos and lattes
and grandes and ventis ♪
♪ Browsing at bookstores ♪
♪ with fat cognoscentis ♪
♪ Books about Dali,
Degas and Miro ♪
♪ Those are the folks
that you yokels should know ♪
♪ Pretentious laughs
at Bunuel retrospectives ♪
♪ Outsider art made
by mental defectives ♪
JITNEY:
♪ Enjoying opry
that ain’t grand or ole ♪
BIRTHDAY:
♪ Comparing Jim Carrey
to Dario Fo! ♪
Your minds are opening!
Take it home!
INCEST:
♪ Eating tapas ♪
DUBYA:
♪ Freestyle rappers ♪
♪ Mrs. Skinner is Mame ♪
♪ We finally experienced
cultural things ♪
♪ And now they don’t seem... ♪
♪ ...so lame. ♪
What a number!
You kids got talent!
And I should know.
I used to have it.
Hey! You’re one of those
funny people
with a big crazy nose.
-A clown?
-No, a...
Joker! That’s right!
And I’m not a practicing joker,
so I’m not that offended.
Well it’s nice to
see you again, Krusty,
but these kids have
field trip journals to write.
Yeah, yeah, right.
Who’s your agent?
What’s an agent?
Ka-ching!
(laughs)
Finally, I get a chance
to use these gag contact lenses.
And then I had this dream
that my whole family
was just cartoon characters,
and that our success had led
to some crazy propaganda
network called "Fox News."
Bart, I think you’re making
a lot of progress,
but our time is up.
See ya next Wednesday.
Actually,
this was our last session.
Huh?
But we were doing
such good work.
Oh, Bart, I truly
enjoyed our time together,
but the school only
paid for five sessions.
I think I just got dumped.
He used to rob me
two, three times a week.
Now, I’m lucky
if I get it once a month.
He never initiates it.
I have to do all the work.
He just stands there.
Now, now, don’t talk
through him; talk to him.
Apu, sometimes
when I rob you,
it’s like
you’re not even there.
That is because
you’re robbing
my brother Sanjay.
Dude, I didn’t know.
Oh, just shut up!
KRUSTY:
That’s right.
I want to hire your entire
Appalachian dumpling gang,
and I’ll pay them
the most anyone on TV
is entitled to get: scale!
Now I don’t sign
nothin’ without
pretendin’ to read it first.
Hamburger, hamburger,
hamburger, hamburger.
Looks good!
Mr. Spuckler, wait!
Is this really good
for your kids?
Teeny, get her out of here!
Whoa!
Okay kids, let’s cut
some promos
for the affiliates.
ALL:
You’re watching Krusty the Clown
on WPPZ in Vero Beach, Florida,
home of the AccuCurl
Surf Report!
Wrong! Wrong! Wrong!
(drumroll)
Hey, hey, kids.
Have I got a treat for you.
Put your hands together for
the Sharecropper Showstoppers,
The Smashing Bumpkins,
The Spuckler Family Singers!
(cheering and applause)
(banjo music plays)
♪ I have eight teeth ♪
♪ Going on seven teeth ♪
♪ I have a curvy spine ♪
♪ We live on landfill ♪
♪ And feast on roadkill ♪
♪ While we all drink ♪
♪ Moonshine. ♪
(chugging, thudding)
You’re better than us!
(laughing):
Look at those
dumb hillbillies!
I’ll bet
they don’t even know what...
something is.
Dad, those kids
aren’t dumb.
This show just perpetuates
the stereotype
that all yokels
are hicks.
Look at those morons.
They sing
because they’re stupid.
Kids, it’s finally happening.
Your own prime-time special.
The songs will be written
by Broadway’s greatest composer:
this guy.
What’s your name
again, fuzz-face?
Stephen Sondheim.
I know you hear this
all the time,
but I think you’re great.
And I’m sure you
hear this all the time:
you cost an arm and a leg,
so let’s get to work.
Here’s the opening number.
Hmm, complex harmonies,
intricate lyrics,
pithy observations
on modern life.
What is this junk?!
Where’s the zazz?
Just do what you did in Cats!
I didn’t write Cats.
You didn’t?!
Oh, no!
All right, I’ll try
and save this.
Tell you what.
Just give me
a peppy vamp.
Okay. And I can
counterpoint it with...
No counterpoint!
Vamp! Peppy!
(peppy vamp plays)
Hey! This peppy
stuff isn’t bad.
Maybe I will right that
jingle for Buzz Cola.
(continues peppy vamp)
♪ President or ayatollah ♪
♪ Everyone loves new Buzz Cola ♪
♪ With lemon. ♪
(cheering)
Krusty, the Spuckler kids
missed their
reading class today.
Yeah? Well, take it up
with their manager.
(gulps)
Yeah.
Cletus, I think
you’re spending too much
of the kids’
earnings on yourself.
That’s a lie!
I ain’t spent
their money on naught
but necessities.
Sir, your solid gold
hound dog is here.
(reverse signal beeps)
Uh... How do we get
the real dog out?
(muffled howling bark)
Do you think I’m telling
people not to have a cow
because deep down
I want them to have a cow?
I saw you yesterday
in the dining room,
and I didn’t know
if I should say "hi" or not.
(sighing)
(concerned groan)
(door buzzer buzzing)
How can I help you?
Dr. Swanson,
I’m Bart’s mother.
I’ve been saving this money
for my husband’s
breast reduction surgery,
but I think
this is more important.
Would you please
see Bart again?
Of course. Send him in.
Bart, honey,
this is all
we can afford for now.
If it doesn’t work,
maybe when you’re an adult,
you can pay some lady
to make you happy for an hour.
You know,
I’m pretty sure I will.
And I wasn’t planned,
so when I came,
my parents had
to get married.
And they were too young,
and not ready for a kid
to screw up their lives.
Maybe I act out because...
if my parents are mad at me,
they can’t fight
with each other.
(relieved sigh)
And maybe
that’s why you do things
like scare your classmates
with Dark Stanley?
Yeah. That, and Stanley
was the brand of hammer
my dad used to hit me with.
Very good.
Bart, we have
20 minutes left.
Is there anything else
you want to talk about?
You know what?
I think I’m good.
Oh. Oh, good. Good.
Good, w-we...
Will I see you again?
Anything could happen.
One of these days I might have
a complete psychotic breakdown.
Aw... I’d like that.
I just can’t stop
thinking about him.
Do you think maybe
Bart is replacing your son
who was killed by Dark Stanley?
Oh. Oh-oh-.
I am not ready
to go there.
(markers squeaking)
You kids finish
signing those 8x10s?
I’ve told five different
dry cleaners
they’s the best.
Ain’t that lyin’,
Mr. Krusty?
Uh, yeah, maybe.
But I’ve got some great news!
Take a look at your new home!
That’s right.
You’re joining Krusty’s
No-Collar Comedy Tour!
There’s Butt-crack Barry,
Merle Values, Reverend Racist
and Andy Dick.
I’m blue collar.
I’m totally blue collar.
My dad owns a shovel.
(kids groaning)
Now kids, don’t be
a-frettin’ and a-fussin’.
I’ll be on tour
with ya...
in my brand-new monster truck!
(all groaning)
(helicopter propellers whirring)
Stop the tour!
(gun chamber clicks)
Cletus Delroy Spuckler!
What have you done
to our children?!
Brandine! You’re
supposed to be in Iraq,
stopping 9/11!
Did ya get the body
armor I sent ya?
Sold it for smokes.
Cletus, I had to stop you
exploiting the children.
So I sent her an e-mail.
My babies ain’t
going on no bus tour.
It doesn’t matter what you say.
I got a contract signed
by the father of these children.
He’s only the father
of two of ’em!
The one that can’t sing
and the one that can’t ad lib.
Nooooo!
Miss Lisa, we just want
to thank you
for introducing us to,
then saving us from,
the big wide world around us.
’Tweren’t nothin’.
(cooing)
Cletus, we’re goin’ home.
How much money
do we have left?
Uh, I owe Krusty $12,000.
We can live on that.
Baby, you’re the greatest.
(Honeymooners theme plays)
CLETUS:
How sweet it is.
Captioned by VISUAL DATA
Shh!
Enhanced by Fotokem