♪ The Simpsons ♪
(chalk screeches)
(bell rings)
(work whistle blows)
-(sucking)
-(register beeping)
(jazzy solo)
(tires screech)
(tires screeching)
(horn honks)
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-(screams)
-(tires screech)
ANNOUNCER: Products you could
only imagine before:
The Foam Dome.
The Jet Walker.
Mr. Sugar Cube.
That baby changed our lives.
I'm actor Troy McClure.
You might remember me
from such TV series as
Buck Henderson, Union Buster,
and Troy and Company's
Summertime Smile Factory,
but I'm here to tell you
about Spiffy,
the 21st century stain remover.
Let's meet the inventor--
Dr. Nick Riviera.
-Thank you, Troy. Hi, everybody.
-(applause)
ALL:
Hi, Dr. Nick.
Troy, I brought with me
the gravestone
of author and troubled soul,
Edgar Allan Poe.
MCCLURE:
One of our best writers.
RIVIERA: Yes, but unfortunately,
a century of neglect
has turned this tombstone
into a depressing eyesore.
So what? I guess we're
gonna have to throw it away.
Not so fast, Troy.
With one application of Spiffy,
you'll think
the body's still warm.
AUDIENCE:
Ooh!
Ahh!
"Quoth the raven--"
What a shine!
Ooh!
That's one clean tombstone.
Hey, Dad,
you got a power drill?
-In the garage.
-Check.
I'm offering
three bottles--
enough to clean
1,000 tombstones--
for only $39.95.
ALL:
Boo!
I'm afraid you're going to have
to do better, Doctor.
Yeah, give us a break,
Doctor.
RIVIERA: But Troy,
how can I make it lower than $39.95?
MCCLURE:
Find a way.
Hey, Homer, I can't find
the safety goggles for the power saw.
If stuff starts flying,
just turn your head.
Aw, check.
RIVIERA:
Okay. I'll throw in a fourth bottle,
the applicator glove,
and a state
of Kansas Jello mold--
-$29.95.
-(audience cheering)
D'oh! Duh...
Okay.
-Okay, calm down.
-(knocking on door)
MARGE:
Homer, can you get the door?
It's my sisters.
(quavering)
Homer. Be nice.
Okay, I will, I will.
(grumbling)
Coming over here...
Patty, Thelma,
what a pleasant surprise!
What do you know--
he's wearing pants.
I owe you a lunch.
PATTY:
Ugly.
Butch.
What's the matter?
Can't you find a
hairstyle you like?
Hold the phone.
That's the one for me.
Ed Asner?
No, next to him.
Mary Tyler Moore.
(all)
Mm.
Expiration date, June, 1989...
Uh, 2012. Yeah.
Homer, are you ordering junk
off the TV again?
-Shh! They'll hear you.
-(power saw whirring)
Oh, who's using
the power tools?
-I don't know. Some guy, I guess.
-Mmm.
Well, we're going
to the beauty parlor.
Maybe you should do something
with the kids while I'm gone.
Oh, sure, great idea.
I'd love to.
-D'oh! Did you hear that?
-Yes.
-How much?
-Everything.
What's the quickest,
cheapest, easiest way
to do something with you?
Take us to the video store?
Anything for my little girl.
Bart!
You can't weld
with such a little flame.
Stupid kid.
Ooh! McBain.
Mm-mm-mm.
Hey, McBain, you keep eating
them hot links,
you never going to make it
to a pension.
Come on,
live a little, Skowie.
No, thank you.
I got me a future, partnah.
I'm two days away from
retirement
My daughter's graduating
from college.
Little Suzie is growing up.
And as soon as we nail Mendoza,
my old lady and I
are gonna sail around the world
like we always wanted.
We just christened a boat.
Oh, yes, sir, everything
is going to be just perf...
(gunshots)
Ahhh!
Damn, damn, damn.
-McBain...
-Yes?
I'm not going to make it.
-Oh, stop talking crazy.
-No, no, no.
Just do one thing for me.
Get... Mendoza.
Mendoza!
You want to rent it, sir?
Why?
I just saw the best part.
(chuckles)
Ooh! Death By Knockout,
Blood on the Ice...
Ho, ho!
Football's Greatest Injuries.
-Lisa, we're going.
-But, Dad, I can't find
Happy Little Elves
in Tinkly Winkly Town.
Just grab something!
All these movies are great.
Look at this.
"Test your F.Q."--
Fatherhood Quotient.
Maybe you should try it
on Homer.
He'll fail it.
Uh-huh, in a second.
Well,
I don't know.
Oh, now Henry Winkler--
there's a father.
Listen to what he told
a close friend.
"I don't always keep my cool
like The Fonz,
"but my love for my kids
-has given me plenty of happy days."
-Mmm.
ANNOUNCER: They called him
"The Galloping Gazelle."
His habitat: The frozen tundra
of Soldier Field.
For six seasons
and two Pro Bowls,
he grazed on the tasty
green turf of the end zone,
until one fateful Sunday
in November,
when the Gazelle was
stopped in his tracks
by a big cat named
Wayne Suschevski.
-(door slams)
-Homey, we're back.
-(laughing)
-Don't mind that clod, Patty.
You could turn the world on
with your smile.
Homer, could you turn off
the TV?
There's a little test
I want you to take.
-(bones cracking on TV)
-Oh, great.
You made me miss Joe Theisman.
This is from the National
Fatherhood Institute.
It evaluates your knowledge
of your son and rates you as a father.
Oh, Marge.
Question one:
"Name one of
your child's friends."
Uh, let's see...
Bart's friends..
Well, there's the fat kid
with the thing.
The little wiener who's always
got his hands in his pockets.
They want a name, Homer,
not a vague description.
Okay... Hank?
Hank? Hank who?
Hank... Jones.
Homer, you made that up.
Question two:
"Who is your son's hero?"
Steve McQueen.
That's your hero.
"Name another Dad
you talk to
about parenting."
-Next.
-"What are your son's hobbies?"
Well, he's always chewing on
that phone cord.
He hasn't done that
since he was two.
-Then he has no hobbies.
-Oh, really?
Well, maybe you should go out
to the garage and see.
-Bart. Bart!
-What?
You don't have any hobbies,
do you, boy?
No, not really.
Well, that's what I...
Wait a minute,
What are you doing?
Building a Soap Box Derby racer.
(groans)
That's a hobby.
Hey, so it is.
Oh, my God.
I don't know jack about my boy.
(sobbing)
I'm a bad father.
You're also fat.
I'm also fat!
MAN (on phone): National
Fatherhood Institute. Please hold.
♪ And the cat's in the cradle
and the silver spoon ♪
♪ Little Boy Blue
and the Man on the Moon ♪
♪ When you comin' home, Dad? ♪
♪ I don't know when... ♪
National Fatherhood Institute.
Dave speaking.
I'm Homer Simpson.
I just took your test.
-I got a zero.
-Good Lord! A zero?
Lana, cancel my 1:00.
Mr. Simpson, we'll send
a wood-paneled station wagon
over for you immediately.
Hey, Bart, where did
you get the lumber?
Well, as three-time Soap Box
Derby champ Ronnie Beck says,
"Poorly guarded construction
sites are a gold mine."
A conventional design.
Oh, yeah? Are you building
a racer, Martin?
In between some other projects.
Well, gentlemen,
if you'll excuse me,
I've booked some time
at the wind tunnel.
Good-bye, son.
Hey, Bart, I think they're finally
hauling your dad away.
Maybe it's for the best.
♪ Oh, you are ♪
♪ One in a million... ♪
For starters, Mr. Simpson,
why don't you take
this complimentary copy of Fatherhood
by Bill Cosby.
If he's as smart
as he is funny, I'm sold.
Mr. Simpson,
if you want to be a good father,
you have to spend time
with your son.
That's easy for you to say,
you preachy, egg-headed
institute guy.
How much do you see your son?
Why don't you ask him
yourself.
-Homer, meet Dave, Jr.
-Huh?
How's your research coming, son?
I think we're near
a breakthrough.
-Good work.
-Thanks, Dad.
Oh, how I envy you.
Homer, that easy back
and forther you witnessed
didn't happen overnight.
It took years of effort.
I've never been afraid
of a little hard work.
That's the spirit,
Mr. Simpson.
Now, step one is to find an activity
the two of you can share.
Does the boy
have any interests?
-What boy?
-Your son.
Find something he likes to do
and share in it.
Well, he is building
a Soap Box Derby racer!
-Oh, that would be perfect.
-(klaxon blaring)
Dear God! Not again!
Bart, I'm going to help you
build that racer.
Thanks,
but I'm almost done.
Why don't you get back
on the couch and watch TV.
Okay.
No! I'm going to do it.
Sorry, Dad, but three-time Soap Box
Derby champion Ronnie Beck
never needed his dad's help.
But you can use me.
I'm good.
I built a lot of things
around the house:
-The spice rack.
-(glass shatters)
The bird feeder.
The Gymboree.
What was that?
Ah, who cares?
Son, please let me help you.
Come on, Dad.
It would be weird.
This isn't working at all.
It's hopeless.
Wait a second.
Hmm.
"Cosby's First Law
of Intergenerational Perversity.
"No matter what you tell
your child to do,
he will always do
the opposite."
Huh?
(thinking)
Don't you get it?
You gotta use
reverse psychology.
That sounds too complicated.
Okay, don't use
reverse psychology.
All right, I will.
Son, I don't think
you should let me help you.
Oh, come on, Dad,
if you really want to help,
you can clean these paint
brushes.
Thank you, Bill Cosby.
You've saved the Simpsons.
♪ There he sits
with a pen and a yellow pad ♪
♪ What a handsome lad ♪
♪ That's my boy ♪
♪ B-R-L-F-Q spells
"Mom" and "Dad" ♪
♪ Well, that ain't too bad ♪
♪ 'Cause that's my boy ♪
♪ You can have your TV
and your nightclubs... ♪
You know, Marge,
that Bart of ours is a little miracle--
his winning smile,
his button nose,
his fat, little stomach.
His face alight
with wholesome mischief.
He reminds me of me
before the weight of the world
crushed my spirit.
Hmm, yeah.
(trumpet fanfare)
I like our chances, son.
Ugh! Your father's not
supposed to help build your racer,
but you should at least
consult him about it.
-D'oh!
-You're in heat four.
-Whoa, where's your helmet, son?
-Helmets are for wusses, sir.
No, I don't think I can let you go
without a safety helmet.
This is my son, and if he
doesn't want to wear one,
you can't make him.
Okay, fine.
I want to get out
of here sometime today.
Attention, everyone.
I say to those who question
the value of the space program,
behold!
Ay, caramba!
Hey, you're not supposed
to smoke in the pit area.
Fine.
Hey, Simpson!
Where's your losermobile?
(laughing)
Losermobile. Wait a minute.
Uh, it's over there, Nelson.
Whoa, talk about
your pieces of crap.
You know, Bart,
I don't care who wins
as long as one of us
beats that guy.
Same here.
Careful boys, it took me months
to steal that bumper.
BOY:
Help! Help!
-What was that?
-You didn't hear nothing!
-Are you nervous, son?
-Don't worry, Dad.
As three-time Soap Box Derby
champion Ronnie Beck says:
"Gravity is my co-pilot."
Hey, Boss.
Just in case you need it.
Aw, thanks, guys.
Now get outta here!
Oh, I didn't realize
this hill was so high.
Could I have another--
(Martin screaming)
(screaming)
(crowd cheering)
(laughing)
Deploy, damn you!
Deploy!
(crowd gasping)
(Martin screaming)
It hurts! It hurts!
Owee! Owee! Owee! Ow!
Mm-hmm.
Young man, I'm afraid
this stress fracture
will require you
to be in a cast for six weeks.
But that means
I can't possibly race.
Son, you're lucky
to be alive.
Save your palliative clichés
for the next poor sap,
Doctor.
Is it okay to visit?
(chuckling)
Of course.
Hey, man, cool crash.
-Way to cheat death.
-Thanks, Bart.
You had the best stick
out there, man.
I wish I could
build 'em like you.
That racer transformed me
into the twisted creature
you see before you.
I'll never race again.
If you don't race,
then Nelson will win.
Even if I wanted to,
I'm in no shape to do it.
Unless...
Bart, will you drive my car?
I don't know
if I should do that.
My Dad and I built
our car together,
and if I drove someone else's,
it would kill him.
On the other hand, I'll do it.
Okay, Bart. We've got
a lot of work to do on the car.
So I'm gonna pull you out of school
for the next couple of weeks.
Dad, I don't know
how to say this, but..
I don't want to drive your car.
It's slow, it's ugly.
It handles
like a shopping cart.
Bart, the car has a few bugs
in it, I admit that,
but we're Team Simpson.
Dad, I love you,
but you taught me to win.
When did I ever
teach you that?
Well, I picked it up somewhere.
And if I drive Martin's car,
I can win.
I'm sorry, but...
No, go ahead, leave me.
-Dad...
-Go on. Go on and win.
No, go on and win
without your Dad.
I'll just sit here
in Li'l Lightnin',
which the Simpsons built,
and remember that
for one brief shining moment,
I had a son.
Ow.
Ohh!
Dad, can you take me
to Dr. Hibbert's office?
-Why? What's wrong?
-Oh, nothing.
I just scheduled a tetanus
booster.
Maybe I'm being
a little anal,
but barefoot season's coming up
and there's a world
of rusty nails out there.
Oh, sure, I'll take you,
wait with you,
worry about you,
and then you'll ride home with
someone who has a faster car.
This is how you get your kicks,
isn't it, Lisa?
Hmm.
D'oh!
Martin, your bone
is healing nicely.
Tell me something
I don't know.
(chuckles)
Dr. Hibbert, Lisa needs a...
You!
Home wrecker!
Mr. Simpson, you have every
right to be angry.
But rest assured,
your son loves you.
-(growls)
-(screams)
(Hibbert laughs)
You certainly gave that boy
the heebie-jeebies.
-Dad, aren't you coming?
-No.
-Now, don't pout.
-I'm not pouting. You are.
Dad, you gotta come.
-I just got your hat out of the fridge.
-Sorry.
Don't you at least
have something to say to Bart?
HOMER:
No. Can't think of a thing.
Homer, I've always said
you were a good father.
I've always defended you
when people put you down.
-That's for sure.
-She ain't lyin'.
But I guess I was wrong.
You are a bad father.
Leave me alone.
(fanfare playing)
TV ANNOUNCER:
Good morning, everybody,
and welcome to an event
that harkens back
to the carefree days
of the Great Depression--
The Soap Box Derby.
In just minutes,
these junior Al Unser, Jrs.
will lock horns.
Huh?
"Name your son's hobbies."
Building a soap box racer.
"Name one
of your child's friends."
Martin.
Martin!
I'll curse that name
till the day I die!
Huh?
"Who is your son's hero?"
Three-time Soap Box Derby
champion, Ronnie Beck.
Wow. I'm one question away
from being a perfect father.
"Name another dad
you talk to about parenting."
Ohh!
Hey-hey-ho, Simpson.
Shut up, Flanders.
Flanders!
Flanders, uh... uh...
When should a boy start dating?
Well, sir, there are two schools
of thought on the subject...
Great! Thanks.
I talked to Flanders
about parenting!
I'm a perfect father!
Hold on, son.
I'm a-coming.
My friend and I have a bet.
Are you Mary Tyler Moore?
(screaming)
(belches)
Ooh! Wow!
It really is you.
Bart, if she breaks up on you,
steer away from the grandstands
or else you might kill hundreds
of innocent spectators.
Bart, what did I
just tell you?
Kill spectators.
What is the matter
with you?
It's my dad--
lying there on the couch
drinking a beer,
staring at the TV.
I've never seen him
like that.
Forget about your father!
You're driving for me now.
Do it for your old man, boy.
Simpson, prepare to die.
Let's rock.
MAN (on P.A.):
Ladies and gentlemen,
to drop the green flag--
our beloved mayor
Diamond Joe Quimby.
To everyone participating today,
I salute your vigor.
Check out the rack on the blonde
in the fourth row.
(crowd cheering)
MARGE:
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Ha! Ha!
ANNOUNCER:
Like the elegant Roman in Judah Ben Hur,
these modern charioteers
battle ferociously.
No quarter given, none asked.
(camera clicking)
The world has not seen
the likes of this
since the French
carried Lucky Lindy off
on their shoulders,
from Le Bourget Field.
EMCEE:
And now, to present the trophy,
three-time Soap Box Derby
champion, Ronnie Beck.
(applause)
Congratulations, Bart.
Seeing you out there brought
back a lot of memories.
Thanks, Mr. Beck.
I was alone out there,
but someone was riding
with me in spirit.
This is for you, Dad.
No, son, you earned it.
I might remind you both,
I did design that racer.
The driver
is essentially ballast.
The better man won, Simpson.
You can really drive.
Thanks, Nelson.
Put her there.
♪ Ha-ha, ha-ha-ha ♪
Loser!
♪ Na-na, na-na-na ♪
Bart, you know there is such
a thing as being a bad winner.
Mom, I never won before.
I may never win again.
♪ Na-na, na-na-na ♪
That's my boy.
BOTH:
♪ Na-na, na-na-na ♪
♪ Did you ever know
that you're my hero? ♪
♪ 'Cause you are the wind
beneath my wings ♪
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.