(SlNGlNG) The Simpsons
(TlRES SCREECHlNG)
D'oh !
(SCREAMlNG)
(BRAKES SCREECHlNG)
Let's see. . . l'll have
1 6 Gravy Scrape 'Ems,
a bucket of Twisty Lard,
and two Super Choker
Breakfast Burritos
with macho sauce.
And mega-size it, please.
SQUEAKY-VOlCED TEEN:
l could also
deep-fry the bag.
Great. And l'll have
a Diet Coke deep-fried.
Mmm ! Mmm !
Need more lap.
(GULPlNG)
OTTO: Whoa!
l can't see! l'll have
to steer by the reflection
in my watch !
(TlRES SCREECHlNG)
Oh !
Why don't l just pull over?
MAN: Hey!
Can't stop.
Krusty collectible toy
jammed under brake pedal !
Hey-hey! Hey-hey! Hey-hey!
AUTOMATED VOlCE:
lntruder detected.
Calling local police.
(DlALlNG)
Line busy, shutting down.
Mr. Burns, the Department
of Nuclear Security
is very impressed
with your plant.
Yes. We're well protected
against every threat,
from bomb-toting Bolsheviks
to golden-armed jazzbos.
(THUDDlNG)
HOMER: Oh, no!
l hit the grief counselor!
Promise me
you'll report this.
Consider yourself fired !
l had a car!
Mom, can we go
into this bookstore?
Please, please,
please, please, please,
please, please?
Well, l could use a muffin.
(MARGE HUMMlNG)
l'm gonna go up
to the fourth floor
where the books are.
l'm gonna taunt the PhD's.
Hey, guys.
l heard an
assistant professorship
just opened up.
(ALL GASPlNG)
Oh, yeah?
At the University
of. . . Psych !
Oh.
(LAUGHlNG)
(GASPlNG)
Esme Delacroix?
She wrote
To Kiss a Scoundrel.
"And they tumbled
to the heather,
"breeches to bustle,
crinoline to burlap,
"their mansion in ashes,
their passion aflame."
End of Chapter 1 .
Yeah, when it happens
in a book, it's romantic.
But when Willie
tries to kiss ya,
you're all pepper spray
and fingernails.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Marge Simpson,
long-time reader,
first-time stander-upper.
Did you have
any special training
to become a writer?
(SCOFFS)
Just a class at the Y.
Yale University.
But anyone with
passion can write.
Anyone?
lf l write a book,
will they tell me
when it comes out?
Well, they should, yes.
Then l'll do it!
l gotta get a job
before Marge finds out
l was fired.
That's it!
l'll steal the sign
and they'll pay me
to make them a new one!
l'll show you what we do
with scammers like you.
Okay, here's how it goes.
Buyers never tell you
what they're willing
to spend.
And when they
talk privately,
we spy on them through
this one-way mirror.
We'll clean out
those stupid Americans.
(CHUCKLlNG)
You'll probably want
to talk this over so
l'll leave you two "alone."
(CHUCKLlNG EVlLLY)
Excuse me.
WeII, honey,
what do you think?
Did that salesman cut one
during the test drive?
Yeah. And for some reason
he turned on the radio
to cover up the smell.
Let's get out of here.
l'm not shaking
that guy's hand.
They'll be back.
(UPBEAT MUSlC PLAYlNG)
(MOANS)
He was my best friend.
Hmm.
Cool. An ambulance
from the '60s.
l bet a lot of hippies
were denied care
in this thing.
(LAUGHlNG)
lnjured hippies.
No, we'll never
sell this thing.
The brakes are shot,
the engine's rusted.
The only thing that
works is the siren.
(BLARlNG)
(HlGH-PlTCHED VOlCE)
Buy me! Buy me! Buy me!
Buy me!
l'll do it!
Do what?
(SlREN BLARlNG)
Guess what?
l quit my job as
a used car salesman.
You work at
the Nuclear Plant.
Get with the program, Marge.
Your husband is now
an ambulance driver.
Don't you need
training for that?
Maybe on Planet ZooZoo.
Hey, l think it's cool.
l can defibrillate Lisa!
Not if l pump your heart
full of morphine first!
Kids, kids.
Those aren't your toys.
They're to keep
Daddy asleep and awake.
l'm gonna need them
on my first shift tonight.
Tonight? But l was hoping
you could watch the kids
while l work on my novel.
Slow down, Picasso.
You were gonna
start a novel
without informing me?
Homer, you left two jobs
and bought an ambulance
without even a phone call !
l also fed some ducklings.
l know. l got your message.
Fine, fine.
l'll take the kids tonight
and you go to your
precious hair appointment.
l'm writing a novel !
Whatever. But l think
you look great already.
Thank you.
What should l write about?
That painting has always
sparked my imagination.
That's it!
A novel about whaling !
That's something
you haven't seen before.
Thank you,
Scene From Moby-Dick.
"Chapter 1 ,
starts and beginnings.
"'Swim, swim, swim,'
thought the whale,
flapping his flappers."
Brownie break!
"Mayor Quimby, Disco Stu,
"and our fighting men
and women overseas."
Well, l've finished
the thank you's.
Time to go back
to the novel.
Temperance Barrows
stared at the sea,
Iike a dog stares at a ham.
Oh, l just finished
my first paragraph.
Spell-check! Perfect.
Now let's see if
lightning strikes twice.
Where to, Mac?
For the third time,
the hospital.
You're an ambulance,
not a taxi.
Hospital, eh? Wow!
Everyone's going
there tonight.
(SlREN WAlLlNG)
Dad, you've been
driving in circles
for 20 minutes.
Why don't you just admit
you don't know where
the hospital is?
Why don't you admit
l know it's around
here somewhere?
MARGE:
"For Temperance,
the days passed on,
"as did seven
of her 1 0 children."
When will father return
from his whaling voyage?
This family
has not seen whale meat
for a one month.
Bartaby, Leezakiah,
we must be grateful
for what we have.
Family, the good Lord
has blessed my voyage.
Behold his bounty.
And for you, good wife,
Virginia's miracle
crop, tobacco.
Ohhh ! lt has colored my teeth
a healthy brown.
Was there ever
a more perfect
husband than you?
(CAR DOOR SLAMMlNG)
Marge, l'm back.
Oh, Homie, l've had
the most exciting day.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
l need some dinner stat.
And the kids
need some CPR lessons.
We're not paramedics!
l'll say.
Oh, good. You can use that
to take down my dinner order.
l'll start with the soup,
then a nice mixed grill
with a side of wild rice.
Fine! Right after
this revision.
"Temperance had to face
the unhappy truth.
"She had married a brute."
Hey, baby! l've returned
from Portsmouth.
Now let me put
my tongue down "yourmouth."
Ugh !
Now cook up my catch.
A seagull?
The whales
weren't biting, okay?
l know you did your best.
Yeah, yeah.
You know everything,
don't you?
Now, don't wait up.
l'll be at Moab's.
This story is as dark
as those new Milky Way bars.
That's a good analogy.
l'll work it in somewhere.
But now l need
some romance pronto.
Hey, Marge.
You look like
you could use a nice,
big stud detector.
(CHUCKLlNG)
They were two-for-one
at Krusty Home Depot.
So l got an extra one
for you guys.
Ned, that's so considerate.
Well, some say
being thoughtful
is old-fashioned.
lf so, then l guess
l'm just a caveman,
if they existed,
which they didn't.
Boy, when you write,
you can let your
imagination run wild.
"Temperance was
doing the laundry."
CYRUS: My, those are
pretty calluses.
And your back has
a nice New England hump.
l'm Cyrus Manley.
And l'm new to the island.
Perhaps you could
show me around.
Nantucket is an island?
What do you know? lt is.
Well, l could take you
on a tour,
as long as my husband
doesn't need me.
Hey, baby.
l know we work together.
But l think you're hot.
(BOTTLE BREAKlNG)
Let's go!
l've never met
a man like you.
You listen to what l say,
your body has known
the cleansing touch of soap.
Prithee, tell me
thou art not a Sodomite.
Nope. Not even
a Gomorrahian.
Oh, Temperance,
l've got an overpowering
urge to see you. . .
With your hat off!
Hmm. l can't.
l must remember
my wedding vows.
Did you promise
to be miserable?
To be taken for granted
by a drunken lout?
Pretty much.
We wrote our own vows.
Enough talk!
l need to see how
you look up there!
(GASPlNG)
l think my mother
had one of those.
Ahh !
l'm finished !
And it's so suggestive.
But like they say,
"Snuggling sells!"
(CHUCKLlNG)
Now, do l dare push "print"?
(MOANlNG)
(BREATHlNG HEAVlLY)
Well, what do you think?
Hmm.
l can't believe
Mom wrote a book
before we did !
And it's a little trashy.
Mom has expressed herself.
We should nurture her.
Let's kiss boys!
Binge and purge!
Rock and roll !
You're not gettin'
out till we're 1 6.
(GROWLlNG)
l'm proud of you, Mom.
But just one thing,
isn't your book
a little hard on Dad?
(NERVOUSLY)
What do you mean? My book
is set in whaling times.
"Captain Mordecai
stared at the shop
"window full of
powdered blow holes.
"Mmm !
Blow holes, he drooled."
Sounds like Dad to me.
Well, l guess that part is
loosely based on your father.
Maybe you should
let Dad read your book
before you submit it
to publishers.
l suppose l better.
Your father's
a very private person.
Marge, we're out
of bath towels.
(BELL JlNGLlNG)
Ooh ! lce-cream truck!
(SlNGlNG) Here in my car
I am hosing off bIood
Some of it's mine
but most of it's not
Here's Marge
Homie, l finished my novel.
Whoa! Typed.
lt's really
important that you read it
and tell me what you think.
No problem.
Oh, 286 pages?
lt's double-spaced.
Woo-hoo!
l'm halfway through !
All right, "Chapter 1 ."
Hmm. That makes sense.
"There once was
a girl from Nantucket."
Good, good.
"Her name was
Temperance Barrows.
"And her heart was
heavy with feeling.
"She. . ."
(SNORlNG)
No! Gotta read Marge's book!
Can't get distracted !
"Distracted,"
that's a funny word.
Does anyone
ever get "tracted"?
Let me call the suicide
hotline and ask 'em.
Well?
Well, what?
Did you read the book?
Oh. Yes.
Did you like it?
l did.
Oh ! That's wonderful.
And the characters
didn't bother you at all?
No. They were all,
in their own way,
totally awesome.
And you're fine with me
trying to get it published?
As l've always said,
"Publish or perish."
Oh, Homie!
HOMER: Now for that happy
period between the Iie and
the time it's found out.
(HOMER CHUCKLlNG)
(PHONE RlNGlNG)
Hello.
Marge. This is
the best first novel
my assistant has
ever summarized for me.
Now all we need
are some endorsements
from famous writers.
Here's your quote.
"Thomas Pynchon
loved this book
"almost as much
as he loves cameras."
Hey, over here!
Have your picture taken
with a reclusive author.
Today only, we'll
throw in a free autograph.
But wait! There's more!
Hello, this is Tom Clancy.
Would l say,
"lf you're hunting
for a good read this October,
"Marge Simpson's
book is a clear
"and present danger
to your free time"?
Hell, no, l wouldn't.
What do you mean
l just said it?
lt doesn't count!
Hello? Hello?
lf Dad ever reads that book,
he's gonna be so humiliated.
He'll never read it.
What if they make it
into a movie?
He'll never see it.
What if they
parody it on MADtv?
We're doomed !
(SlREN WAlLlNG)
So how much
bleach did you drink?
Not a talker, eh?
l love this book, Marge.
Very psychological.
Dr. Marvin Monroe?
l haven't seen you in years!
Oh, l've been very sick.
lf you ask me,
this book sounds
like Marge and Homer.
No one asked you.
Think about it.
The boorish husband,
the neglected wife,
the sensitive
hunk down the road.
(GlGGLlNG)
And on page 72,
Temperance's name
changes to Marge
for three paragraphs.
Can you believe Marge. . .
Homer doesn't know.
Marge.
(ALL TALKlNG lNDlSTlNCTLY)
Can you believe
that Homer and Marge's
marriage is just a sham?
All right, l'll order.
l'll have a medium pepperoni.
And could you
space out the meat
so that it spells,
"Happy birthday, Moe."
(SOBBlNG)
Oh, God ! l'm alone!
(SlREN WAlLlNG)
Apu, do you still
have Krazy Straws?
l've got a guy
with a broken back
and l'm trying
to cheer him up.
Oh, Mr. Homer,
anything for
a cuckolded boob.
l mean, a loyal customer.
What are you talking about?
Nothing, nothing.
lt just seems
your wife has
an active imagination.
Why do you keep
talking that way?
You'll see when you
read your wife's book.
Well, then maybe l will !
lf you do, you'll see
she lusts for Flanders.
That one l got.
This is how you talk
when you learn English
from porno movies.
l'll have to
read Marge's book.
And l swore
never to read again
after To KiII a Mockingbird
gave me
no useful advice
on killing mockingbirds!
lt did teach me
not to judge a man
based on the color
of his skin.
But what good
does that do me?
(HOMER READlNG)
ASHLEY: "The Harpooned Heart
by Marge Simpson."
Your turn, Mary-Kate.
MARY-KATE: "There once
was a girI from Nantucket.
"Her name was
Temperance Barrows.
"And her heart was
heavy with feeIing."
Take it, AshIey.
ASHLEY:
"Temperance was trapped
in a IoveIess marriage."
Bummer. l didn't know
peopIe were sad in the past.
"The Harpooned Heart Two.
Thunder Down Under. Chapter 1 .
"Temperance Barrows stared
at the shrimp on the barbie."
How can you write
such horrible things
about me?
You told me you liked it!
You didn't read it at all !
You lied to me!
l didn't lie. l was writing
fiction with my mouth.
Just tell me how
much of this is true!
Well, there is
a place called Nantucket.
l knew it! (SOBBlNG)
And what about the romance
between you and Cyrus?
lt was only my imagination.
Well, l'll make sure
you never imagine
anything again !
(DOOR SLAMMlNG)
(BANGlNG ON DOOR)
HOMER: Flanders!
Open this door, right now!
Well, l guess
it wouldn't kill me
to let you in.
(HOMER MUTTERlNG ANGRlLY)
What are you doing here?
Stealing doormats.
Dad's gonna catch Flanders,
just like the end
of Mom's book!
Oh, yeah.
How does that go again?
Ugh ! Didn't you read
Mom's book?
Fine! l'll tell you
how it ends.
"The brutish Captain Mordecai
has cornered his rival,
Cyrus. . ."
Put that
harpoon down, Captain.
You wouldn't kill the father
of your next child,
would you?
Oops!
(GROWLlNG)
Temperance,
l'll treasure your memory
as long as l. . .
No, no! Not the new guy!
(LAUGHlNG EVlLLY)
Now that your
boyfriend's dead,
l'm free
to be selfish, drunk,
emotionally distant,
sexually ungenerous,
pissy, and. . .
D'oh !
MARGE: "As Temperance
watched the two men
she had loved
"and the one whale
she admired disappear
into the ocean,
"she realized
it was the end."
(SlREN WAlLlNG)
Flanders, pull over!
l'm an ambulance!
Well, he's got me there.
(PANTlNG)
Dear Lord,
please make
Homer's blows precise
and deadly with
a minimum of pain.
Oh ! And forgive me
for those impure thoughts
l had about the girl
on the raisin box.
Flanders, l'm gonna
do something
l should've done
a long time ago!
Would you help me
be a better husband?
Huh?
ln Marge's book,
l was so mean
and you were so nice.
How can l be more like you?
Just give me some advice.
Advice?
Just call me Ann Flanders.
Uh-huh.
Oh, and another thing. . .
Please! Homie,
don't hurt him !
And a backrub can
just be a backrub.
lt doesn't have to
lead to adult situations.
Why would
l rub her back unless
l wanted to get some. . .
Oh, to make her feel good.
Oh, Homie.
You're trying to
improve yourself
and it's because of my book.
That's right.
l love you, Marge.
And l realize now l should
show you more often.
The end of your book was
the wakeup call l needed
after falling asleep
at the beginning
of your book.
That's the best review
l've gotten.
Seriously, these reviews
are terrible.
Don't worry about
those losers, Marge.
l think it's time
we went home
and collaborated
on a little project
of our own.
(CHUCKLlNG SUGGESTlVELY)
Marge, l got it all
figured out.
Lee Harvey Oswald
wanted to steal
the Jack Ruby!
Jack Ruby was a man,
not a jewel.
(GROANlNG)
All right.
We're back to square one.
Put on some coffee.
(MARGE GROANlNG)
l was so close.
English - US - PSDH