(SINGING) The Simpsons
(TIRES SCREECHING)
D'oh!
(SCREAMS)
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
(ALL SCREAM)
(DISTANT THUDDING)
(COCKING GUNS)
Something's coming,
Sarge. Something big!
Stay strong, men.
The United States is due
to win a war sometime.
Oh, good Lord!
It a Swingline!
(GASPS)
(SCREAMS)
Medic!
(GROANS)
(BOTH STRAINING)
Skinner!
(ALL SCREAM)
(STUTTERS) Yes,
Superintendent Chalmers?
Do you know
what today is?
Today? Yes,
of course I do!
(SINGING) Happy birthday
to you, happy...
It not my birthday,
Seymour.
You know
I'm a Sagittarius.
Really? I'm a Libra.
There's a lot of
compatibility there.
Skinner, be gay
on your own time.
Today is the day
we choose
who gets the school's
vending machine contract.
I anticipate
quite the dog
and pony show.
Sir, this school
has a strict
no-animal policy.
I assume
these are hypothetical
dogs and poni?
Y'arr, everyone likes
a gumball machine.
So why not
a gumbo machine? Y'arr...
(SCREAMS)
Does your school nurse
treat burns?
Nope.
It couldn't be simpler.
Kids write down
what they want,
put their money in the can,
and I take the bus
to the supermarket
and bring the snacks
the next day.
Huh? (GROANS)
Is that a yes?
Kids want a snack
that skateboards,
won't clean his room,
and hates homework.
That's why we
created Scarf-ables
by Scammer and Z-Dog!
These two spokes-rebels
were invented
by the marketing team
that came up
with Hip-Hopsicles,
the urban Popsicle.
Yes. I saw those
when my normal grocery
store was on strike.
Well, here's what
really seals the deal.
(RAPPING) Yo, yo, yo!
Slide your green
into the machine.
And don't expect
any change, dawg.
It's like a fundraising
school bake sale with slang
as the Saran Wrap.
And a subsonic
neuro-jammer disrupts
the child's judgment center.
Fair enough.
I assume these
snacks are nutritious?
That's really
none of our business.
The bottom line is,
half the profits go
to your school or camp.
You heard the lady.
Just sign the damn contract.
Yo.
(TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
Wow!
(READING)
They sound like
my kind of snacks.
(BEEPING)
on. (READING)
Oh, my God!
Look at these ingredients!
"Hydrogenated
petroleum oil,
"monosodium poisonate,
partially de-weaponized
plutonium"?
Attention, duped masses!
These new
vending machine snacks
are crammed with
processed sugar,
industrial by-products,
and trans-fatty acids!
(RAPPING) Don't flavor hate.
Participate.
Machine makes a good point.
Don't be a follower!
Be a snack-swallower!
It's fun to obey
the machine.
(WHIRRING)
Mmm. Mmm.
Mmm.
(SIGHS)
Way to go, dude.
You're 5 cents away
from an awesome
beverage or snack.
(GRUNTS)
Oh, I'm out of money!
Willie! You want to
buy my skateboard?
Hey, Why not?
For once, it'll be
all eyes on Willie!
(GRUNTS)
Look at me!
I'm an American boy!
Uh-oh! Stairway! (SCREAMS)
Hey, I'm getting the...
No, I'm not!
(GRUNTING)
Hey, okay, I'm all right.
(YELLS) No, I spoke too soon!
Ah, that's better.
(SCREAMS)
What are you looking at,
you bastards?
(HUMMING)
Bart, I spent
all afternoon
stuffing tuna fish
into that steak.
Have some.
No, thanks.
The vending machines
at school feed me now.
Oh, so I've been
replaced by a machine?
(CHUCKLES) Marge, no machine
could ever replace you.
Why, you're the...
Or could it?
Oh, Margebot,
I'm ready for some loving.
(SCREAMING)
Oh, why did I give her a gun?
But I repeat,
no one is being
replaced by a machine...
Until all the kinks
are worked out.
Well, until that day,
I'm still Bart's mother,
and I don't like him
stuffing himself with junk.
(WHINING)
Oh, fine.
(POP MUSIC PLAYING)
Yummy, yummy, yummy
I got love in my tummy
(BURPS)
And I feel like a loving you
Love, you're such
a sweet thing
Good enough to eat thing
And that's just
what I'm gonna do
Ooh, love to hold ya
Ooh, love to kiss ya
Ooh, love, I love it so
(SINGING)
(SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
(METAL SQUEALING)
(SCREAMS)
(BARKS)
Be careful!
(SCREECHING)
(SCREAMS)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANING)
My heart!
It hurts so much!
(GROANS) Like it's caught
in a vise!
(CHUCKLES)
My little boy's in love.
I think he's having
a heart attack!
(GROANS LOUDLY)
(STAMMERING) Come on, son!
You can fight this!
Do the Bartman!
(GRUNTING)
Why don't you dance?
Dance! (SOBBING)
Doctor, little kids
aren't supposed to
have heart attacks.
They're supposed
to skin their knees,
and poke their eyes out,
and be smothered by cats.
Well, Bart had a heart attack,
and it's his own damn fault!
These dark spots
in his pulmonary arteries
are malted milk balls.
His liver
looks healthy.
Mmm-hmm.
That a wad
of Laffy Taffy.
Oh!
Now when Bart goes home,
he gonna have to follow
a program of strict
diet and exercise.
Damn it, I will not
bury another patient!
Doctor, you're a pediatrician!
Yeah. But my head's
been somewhere else
this year.
(SINGING)
(HUMMING)
Oh!
Yes. Mmm-hmm.
Yup. Mmm-hmm.
Okay. We'll start with
a routine stress test.
(BEEPING)
(BEEPING ERRATICALLY)
(SCREAMS)
(EXPLOSION)
(LAUGHING)
Bart, how can you
laugh at that?
You just had
a heart attack!
Yeah, but what
does not kill me,
makes me stronger. (GASPS)
Wow!
That was a lot of words.
I need some energy.
Hey, hey, kids.
(LAUGHS)
Heart disease
can strike anyone,
including heavy-drinking,
chain-smoking clowns!
That why
I had the doctor
install a zipper!
Up, down,
up, down. Huh?
(WHISTLING)
(CHUCKLES)
(PANICKED GRUNTS)
Ah! The zipper's stuck!
(ALL GASP)
Oh, I should've gone
with the button fly.
(SOBBING)
(LAUGHING)
(AUDIENCE LAUGHING ON TV)
(GROANS)
I talked
to Dr. Hibbert today.
He gave me a list
of heart-smart foods.
“Gotta-hay cheese“?
Cottage cheese!
Yuck! From the looks of it,
this cheese has
already been eaten.
Oh, honey, please
take this seriously.
When people
used to ask me
how you were doing,
I said, "At least
he's got his health."
Now you've got nothing!
Okay, Mom.
For you, I'll try.
(CHOKING)
Okay. Now we know
you're allergic
to cauliflower.
But I made a special
platter of vegetables
that are good for you.
It graffiti you can eatie.
You get better, son.
Meanwhile, the rest of us
will be going to the library.
Where are you really going?
Milkshake festival.
Look! You can see
the booths from your window!
Hmm?
(CARNIVAL MUSIC PLAYING)
MILKSHAKE: Today only.
Free milkshakes
for 10-year-old boys!
Drink your own weight
in milkshakes,
and win a milkshake.
(GASPS)
I'd better tell Dad.
Lisa, take a picture of me
with all the milkshakes!
All right, everybody,
get in there.
Okay, we all in?
Hurry! They're melting!
Mmm. Maybe
Mom's the way to go.
(HUMMING)
(GASPS)
ALL: Intervention!
What, the family?
Uh, son, we're here
to help with your, uh...
Which addictadiddilydiction
are we going after here?
Overeating.
And if there's time,
we'll get to my drinking.
But there won't be time.
I'm telling you, Bart.
One vice
leads to another.
And then
you'll wind up like me.
So jaded
the only thing that
gets you off
is freebasing
ground-up moon rocks.
(SUCKING)
All this does
is get me to normal.
(SIGHS)
Thank you, Krusty.
Once again,
you've delivered
an important message
wrapped in entertainment.
And I'm so touched
that all of you would
take the time to...
Eat my shorts, lame-os!
(CHUCKLES)
Oh!
(STRAINING)
Help! Kidnappers!
They're not kidnappers.
They're professionally
trained child-snatchers
Who are taking you
to a maximum-security
fat camp.
I'm not fat!
(GRUNTING)
(STRAINING)
Mr. and Mrs. Simpson,
I'm facility director
Tab Spangler.
United States
Marine Corps, retired,
but not tired!
Guess how old I am?
Come on. Take a guess.
Forty-seven?
I hate when they're over.
Even on-the-nose hurts!
Wow! He's just
the kind of weirdo
Bart needs.
Mr. and Mrs. Simpson,
your boy's gonna
need one thing.
(READING)
Don't you mean
"tough love"?
Tough love.
Of course!
This has never
made sense!
The sign shop guy lied.
Stanley, you didn't
question the word "luck"?
Now look what we got!
Thanks for the correction.
That's part of the honesty.
Son, I just want
to leave you with
a piece of advice.
Become emotionally dead.
Leave your body.
Make lots of friends!
(CLAN KING)
Wake up, fatties!
Stop dreaming
about butter!
Dreamed calories
are real calories!
All right, here's how
this exercise works.
You tow me
around the track.
As we gather speed,
I whip you gently,
you state your name
and tell me how
you got so heavy.
(SWISHING WHIP)
Kent Brockman,
Channel 6 News.
I gorge on kettle corn
during the sports and weather.
We know. Your side fat's
starting to spill over
to Channel 5 and 7.
I hope you're getting
three paychecks.
Bart Simpson.
I'm just big-boned.
No such thing.
Growth spurt?
Doesn't exist.
This can't be legal!
It's legal enough!
MARGE: Jimminy Kimmel!
Look how much
they're charging
for Bart's treatment.
That freeloading fatso!
Marge, could you
cut back on
your makeup budget?
I already
use crayons
for lipstick
and fireplace
soot for eyeliner.
So that's where
my soot went!
(GROANS) This fat camp
can save Bart's life!
We have to find
a way to pay for it.
Homer, maybe you could
ask Mr. Burns for a raise.
Even better,
I'll ask him for
my job back.
I know how
we can raise money.
Youth? I hate them!
Secondly...
(IN GERMAN ACCENT)
How much is costed
for stay night of one?
How much is got,
Wolfgang Schmuck?
Let's see here.
I can offer you
$50 a week.
$50?
What about all the water
you guys will waste
with your bathing,
and showering,
and washing your clothes?
Yeah, we don't, uh...
It's not a problem.
All right, try this.
As you scoop your ice cream
into the trash,
tell it you hate it!
Talk to it! "You think
I look like what?"
What's the vanilla saying?
"No, I'm not that old!"
Come on, talk!
Let's hear you!
(GRUNTS)
Here's the scoop,
your haagen days are over.
I'm baskin' in your pain,
as I'm robbin' you of life.
(SLURPING)
TAB: Bart!
Son, I'm gonna
tell you a story
about a young man who
came here and failed.
Well, that is the story.
I shouldn't call
a sentence a story.
Anyway, it's you!
Look, I'm really,
really sorry.
Now let me get
that ice cream
off your shoe.
(SLURPING)
Young man,
there's something
I have to show you.
In one hour.
We have to drive there.
No talking on the way.
It'll hurt the drama.
Can I just...
Shh. Drama.
(GASPS)
German backpackers?
You see, son, every family
has to make extra income
when they send
a child like you
to a place like mine!
You're lucky
this is just
a youth hostel.
We had one family
who had to take
in dry-cleaning.
The chemicals
killed their dog!
Well, that's what
they told us
in the lawsuit.
I don't see a dog
living past 14 anyway,
do you?
(GROANS)
They can't see
or hear us, right?
We're not the Ghost
of Christmas Past,
Bart. They can see us.
If I were invisible,
you think I'd waste my time
with this
belt-shirt combination?
Excuse me.
We're looking for
Mr. and Mrs. Simpson.
I'm sorry to say
this is their son.
Oh! So he's
the strudel-sucking
globbenheimer
who has bankrupted them
with his expensive treatments.
"Strudel-sucking
globbenheimer."
You need to think
about that.
That's what
the human race
thinks of you.
(GASPS)
Problem number 35
with America,
no universal health care.
Number 36, no metric system.
What is this?
The time of Charlemagne?
Answer me! Answer me now!
Oh, my God.
Come on.
Lefslook
for your dad.
And if we have some time,
maybe we'll look for mine.
Guten Abend, my brave
Bavarian overlords.
The best wurst
in town.
Here is your tip, Baldylocks.
If you want it,
dance und sing.
Oh!
(SINGING IN GERMAN)
(ALL CHEERING)
More! More!
They want a second verse.
Hope he knows it.
(CONTINUES SINGING)
(ALL CHEERING AND LAUGHING)
This is all my fault.
I'll never eat junk
food again. I swear!
Good for you.
That's what
I want to hear.
It's time to take action.
I'll meet you later, son.
I'm gonna get
the car washed and try
to meet somebody.
(STRAINING)
MACHINE: Dude, you've changed.
(GRUNTING)
Yo, I'm gonna cap
a pop in your ass.
Huh!
I'm ending your vending, dawg.
Bart, what are you
doing here?
I've learned my lesson.
Mr. Spangler showed me
the true cost of
my junk food addiction.
But you're still fat.
Not for long!
I'm saying goodbye
to Scammer and Z-Dog.
I've learned that even
made-up corporate shills
can lie to you.
Did you hear that,
Foxy the Fox Network Fox?
When I raged
against the machine,
money poured out.
Oh, boy!
Marge, I know
this is ill-gotten,
but can we use it to...
To give these Germans
das Boot? Jawohl!
Uh, please to have new
face cloth, schnell.
Time to take
out the Eurotrash!
(YELLS)
(ALL SCREAM)
Oh, no! Who will put up
with our nonsense now?
To Disneyland,
where we will heap
the scorn on Goofy!
(ALL CLAMORING)
Now everything's
perfect again.
Excuse me.
I think I left
my belt here.
No, you didn't.
Don't tell me I didn't.
That's my lucky belt!
Long story. Good one.
Folks, you have
three weeks left
on a nonrefundable
weight-loss treatment.
So if anybody else
in the family wants
to use it, use it now.
But who else needs
to lose weight?
Maggie? Grampa?
My seldom seen
half-brother, Herb?
Why is everyone
looking at me?
I am not too fat.
I'm alive, aren't I?
Mr. Simpson,
you're suffering
from PSI.
Poor self-esteem.
It's not "I"!
Every sign is wrong!
Oh, that's terrible.
We got a long drive ahead.
You want to pull
off at a motel?
We'll split a room.
Where will I sleep?
We can worry about that
when we're standing naked
before the bed.
My goodness!
No wonder you eat!
TAB: What are you eating now?
HOMER: Cheeseburger.
TAB: You're a catastrophe.
Let me have half of it.
HOMER: I don't wanna.
TAB: I just want the cheese.
I don't want the meat.
I do want the meat!
HOMER: Here's a corner.
TAB: Let me just bite it.
Don't rip it!
Let me have the whole thing!
You'll get some later!
HOMER: You're a selfish jerk!
TAB: I've smelled it.
It has to be eaten.
HOMER: But it's my burger!
TAB: I'm driving.
I'll kill us.
HOMER: (MOUTH FULL)
Fine. I'd rather die!
(SHUSHING)