(SlNGlNG) The Simpsons
(TlRES SCREECHlNG)
D'oh !
(SCREAMlNG)
(BRAKES SCREECHlNG)
That's a salt-water croc,
the largest reptile
in the world !
Oh, crikey!
She's got me
by the dangle-down !
This naughty little Sheila
can snap a man's
ribcage like. . .
(CRACKlNG)
Like that!
(SCREAMS)
Hey, l'm watching that!
Not anymore.
ANNOUNCER 1 ON TV:
Malibu Stacey wants
a craft room
and Malibu Ken
needs a closet for all
his beach thongs.
They'II get heIp
from designer Jeremy on,
Dollhouse Do-Overs.
We'II aIso show you
how to turn a shoebox
into a you-box.
Oh, l missed
the feeding frenzy.
l hope you're happy.
Obviously, yes.
(BOTH GRUNTlNG)
MAN ON TV:
Bobby, I got propane
in my urethra.
ANNOUNCER 2 ON TV:
We'II be right back with
Who Will Marry
a Million Bears!
(SlNGlNG) I Iike ice cream
l like ice cream
How about you?
Look, Maggie!
A show for babies!
Topped with chocoIate syrup
Whipped cream too
Mom, that's Roofi.
His music is why
babies are idiots.
Well, Maggie likes Roofi.
And babies only
like good things.
Why don't you let us watch TV
and get her a Roofi CD?
Bart!
(lN PlG LATlN)
Ap-cray.
ROOFl: (SlNGlNG)
One, two, tie your shoe
Three, four,
pick up the fIoor
Five, six,
don't pIay tricks
Seven, eight,
cIean your pIate
Nine, ten,
start over again!
One, two, tie your shoe
Three, four,
pick up the fIoor
Five, six,
don't pIay tricks
lt's on batteries.
Clean your plate
Nine, ten,
start over again!
Backed up by solar power.
(GROANS)
Three, four,
pick up the fIoor
Five, six,
don't pIay tricks
Seven, eight,
cIean your pIate
Nine, ten,
start over again!
Look, Maggie. Funny Daddy!
(GROANlNG)
Too hard.
Nine, ten,
start over again!
One, two, tie your shoe
Three, four,
pick up the fIoor
Five, six...
(SCREAMlNG)
Three, four,
pick up the fIoor
(SHUDDERS)
(BELL RlNGlNG)
Time to go home, Bart.
You don't understand.
l can't go home.
You got to give me detention.
Look! l fed
the gerbil coffee!
Ah !
(lNDlFFERENT GRUNT)
Please, make me
write something
on the chalkboard
a thousand times!
We all got tired of that
chalkboard years ago.
Now go home.
(SlNGlNG) So he went upstairs
and knocked on the door
There's a heIpfuI bear
on the 28th floor
Twenty-eighth fIoor,
twenty-eighth fIoor
There's a heIpfuI bear
on the 28th floor
Aw! Look how happy she is.
Her eyes aren't focused.
(GROWLS)
lt makes her happy.
(MUSlC STARTS)
So does sucking on the dog.
Hello, Springfield.
Roofi is coming
to your town.
One show only.
Tickets wiII go fast,
very fast.
So your parents
shouId be getting in Iine.
If you don't come,
Roofi will be sad.
And the heIpfuI bear,
she will die!
(COUGHlNG)
(SlNGlNG) Tickets, tickets
buy them now
Roofi he wiII show you how
Visa, AMEX or MC
Or make out
that check to me!
Give Daddy
the remote, Maggie.
Give Daddy the. . . D'oh !
(LAUGHS)
Oh, wise guy, eh?
(GROANlNG)
MARGE:
l got the Roofi tickets!
l got them fair and square
and l kept my dignity,
not like Janie's mom.
("THREE STOOGES"
NOSE TWlSTlNG NOlSE)
Whatever.
(HORNS HONKlNG)
(GASPS)
This concert is oversold.
lt's as if a music promoter
acted unscrupulously.
ANNOUNCER:
And now, our opening act,
in their first live show
since Tinky Winky was
acquitted of mansIaughter.
Not guilty!
The Teletubbies!
(CHEERlNG)
Custard !
Custard ! Custard !
They make The Blue Man Group
look like Mummenschanz,
which is still pretty good.
Oh, the second one
wants custard, too?
That's a little repetitive.
(THUNDER RUMBLlNG)
Oh, no! lt's raining !
And Maggie's diapers
are extra absorbent.
(CRYlNG)
How's the crowd, Steve?
Awful fussy.
You kidding me?
Did you make funny faces?
You did? Well, did you
jiggle your keys?
l did it all, man !
ANNOUNCER:
And now, here's Roofi!
(SlNGlNG)
Sing the nonsense song
with me
Yum yum wow
Woop de we
FIibberty fIabberty
one two three
Ow! Okay, who threw that?
Who threw it?
REPORTER ON TV:
A pIay date with disaster
at Cletus' farm.
l'm at the first aid tent
where overwhelmed doctors
are trying to sort out
the owies from the boo-boos.
Now l'm told
we have the leader
of the babies on the line.
TyIer, is there
a peacefuI soIution possibIe?
(TYLER COOlNG)
(BEEPlNG)
(GASPlNG)
AII right, that's it.
Show's over!
Five, six, so Iong, hicks!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You don't want
to go in there.
Some of those babies
have their teeth.
And those super
sharp little fingernails.
Better leave it to
the professionals.
l don't feel right
clubbing women
and children, chief.
l hear ya. Some days are
tougher than others.
Just close
your eyes and club.
CLANCY: This is it, boys.
We'll have to tummy-kiss
our way out.
(BLOWlNG TUMMY KlSSES)
(BABlES LAUGHlNG)
LOU: This is a bouncer
one here, Chief.
KENT: Baby's got backIash!
Springfield citizens
are outraged
about the destruction
caused by the bad babies.
Bad babies, yes, you was.
They destroyed my home
and the equity
I'd buiIt up therein.
Asked if he intends
to take IegaI action,
the farmer repIied,
"I ain't fungified
"hidee-hoo about no
Iegrification noways,"
then scratched his rear,
hitched up his pants,
and scratched his rear again.
That riot has
far-reaching consequences.
Kabul refuses to be
our sister city anymore.
l have no sister city!
The babies' damage
exceeds $1 million.
Which will now be sucked out
of your pockets.
MAN: My loose change!
Let me now introduce a woman
who wants to make sure that
what l just did
never happens again.
Good evening.
l'm Lindsay Naegle.
And l am the founder
of SSCCATAGAPP.
Singles Seniors
Childless Couples
and Teens and Gays
against Parasitic Parents.
Catchy name.
(CLAMORlNG)
We're tired
of picking up the bills
for other people's kids.
We already pay
millions every year
in school taxes.
CROWD: Yeah !
Excuse me, everyone.
l'm a mother.
(BOOlNG)
And l'm an American.
CROWD: Yeah !
l bake apple pies.
And l love baseball.
(BOOlNG)
Save your
breath for blowing up
water wings, breeder.
l dream of
an America with nudity
and F-words on network TV!
Where the whole world
doesn't stop because
a school bus did.
Children are the future.
Today belongs to me!
CROWD: Yeah !
You can't change the rules
in the middle of the game!
We never
would've had these kids
if we thought
we had to pay for them !
Promises were made!
Tough tortellini !
l'm sick of printing
a children's menu !
Let Mickey Meatball
find his own way
out of the maze!
We're tired of
buying overpriced tickets
for your lousy school plays!
Then how would we ever
get to see CameIot?
We'll merely watch
the movie on tape!
ls that better?
To me, Ralph Wiggum
is Sir Lancelot.
(SlNGlNG)
If ever I wouId Ieave you
lt wouldn't be
in summer!
(BOOlNG)
Ladies and gentlemen,
let's kill every child. . .
. . .friendly thing in town !
(CROWD CHEERlNG)
(SQUEAKY VOlCE) lt's time
to put away childish things
(DEEP VOlCE)
and become a man !
MAN: Talkin' 'bout
my generation
I hope I die
before I get oId
CALCULATOR: Y? Y? Y?
Why don't you aII
fade away
Talkin' 'bout
my generation
And don't try to dig
what we aII say
KENT: Kids are peopIe, too.
WorthIess incompIete peopIe.
That's the battIe cry
as single Springfield-ites
are continuing
to run roughshod
over children and families.
From now on,
chiIdren acting up
in pubIic pIaces
wiII be IightIy tased.
CHILD: Mommy, pick me up.
(ELECTRlClTY CRACKLlNG)
I wasn't kidding.
And in downtown Springfield,
a statue is being erected
to America's most
misunderstood hero,
"The deadbeat dad."
That's all? Just a statue?
This country makes me sick.
Sign, sign,
everywhere a sign
BIockin' out the scenery
Breakin' my mind
Do this, don't do that
Can't you read the sign?
(CHANTlNG)
Gamble, gamble, gamble!
(SEDUCTlVE MUSlC PLAYlNG)
(LAUGHlNG)
Oh, yeah.
Miss Naegle, l'm sorry to
surprise you like this.
But l thought
if we met face to face,
we could settle
our differences.
Well, let's make it quick.
l know you have to
get back to your kids
and l'm late for
a skydiving massage.
l'll cut to the chase.
l've brought with me
the very best reason
l can think of
for what l believe in.
Her name is Lisa.
And l wouldn't trade her
for all the sleep-in Sundays
and speed dating
in the world.
Miss Naegle,
even though l disagree
with your principles,
l certainly
admire your success.
Well, Lisa,
l would be proud
if one of the eggs
l sold turned out like you.
Mom, l locked
your keys in the car.
Then wait in the shadows!
Also Maggie puked
in your purse again.
Poor me.
All my purse is full of
is disposable income.
Sorry, Marge. l don't think
l'll ever understand
your point of view.
Not even
with all my free time.
Then l guess this means war
with the most
powerful weapon
at my disposal,
a voter-sponsored initiative.
(GASPS) You wouldn't dare!
l've already
drawn up the petition.
Well, l'm not worried.
You won't get that
thing on the ballot
until the November
general election.
No. The March primary.
Mom, can we get a pretzel?
We've got pretzels at home.
Not cinnamon.
Well, we finally got things
the way we want them.
Not a highchair or
complementary crayon
in sight.
l'm gonna tell an anecdote
about lovemaking
without having
to look around.
Truly we have
entered a golden age.
(SCREAMlNG)
MARGE: Attention, everyone.
l wish to
announce the formation
of PPASSCCATAG.
Proud Parents
Against Singles, Seniors,
Childless Couples
and Teens and Gays.
PPASSCCATAG
is also a disease
of the brainstem.
That's how l'll
remember it. (LAUGHS)
To overturn these
horrible anti-family laws,
we've prepared
the Families Come
First initiative.
Now, the first thing
we're gonna need is money.
l'm so sorry, Marge.
But l guess
you get the bill?
Oh, for the love of pizza!
Luigi Risotto?
That's me.
l'm from the US
lmmigration Department.
Save our families!
Sign our petition !
The only petitions
that l sign are to bring back
canceled sitcoms.
Thank you.
America needs the wisdom of
Herman's Head
now more than ever.
Well, howdy, ma'am.
l represent the
tobacco lobby.
And frankly,
no politics gets done
in this country without
a little help from us.
(MARGE GASPS lN SURPRlSE)
Now we own you !
But l haven't
endorsed it yet!
Football injury. (LAUGHS)
Now why don't you
just sign the check?
Here, use my pen.
Forget it.
(ROARS)
l guess no one
gives a damn about
the American family anymore.
l'll sign your petition.
Mr. Burns?
You care about children?
Yes.
Particularly their
supple young organs.
Oh, unfenced backyard pools,
where would l be without you?
Hey, if Burns
is signing that petition,
maybe we should, too.
Yeah. Rich guys always want
what's best for everyone.
Coming up later,
what your dog can teII you
about your prostate.
But first, Marge Simpson's
"Families Come First"
initiative
seems to be gaining steam.
Leading her
opponents to counter
with this commercial.
As a mother,
I Iove my famiIy.
That's why I'm against
the "Families Come First"
initiative.
"Families Come First"
will hurt families.
And I Iove my famiIy
too much for that.
(lMlTATlNG MARGE)
l'm Marge Simpson,
and even I'm against
"Families Come First."
Now it's time to do some coke
off the blade of a knife.
That ad makes me
look like a criminal !
Then why did you
appear in it?
That wasn't me!
Maybe she was you
and you're not!
How many kids do we have?
Three.
Wrong, lady!
Oh, wait. The baby.
MARGE: l try my best.
They ridicule me.
They mock everything
l cherish.
Honey, this marriage
is a partnership.
When you fall,
l pick you up.
And when you can't
finish a sandwich,
l eat that sandwich.
You're my rock, Homie.
And l promise this rock
is gonna weigh you down
for the rest of your life.
Aw!
Honey, no one messes
with my missus.
l'll come down on those guys
like the garage door
on Bart's bike!
What are you going to do?
You just leave
everything to Homer.
And now l believe you owe me
half a sandwich.
l always keep one
near the bed for you.
Here comes my commercial.
ln six, five, four. . .
l probably should've
watched it first.
HOMER: You've probabIy
heard a lot of
bad things about
"Families Come First."
But newspaper writers
are a bunch of jerks.
Who reaIIy opposes
"Families Come First?"
Many chiIdIess advocates
are like Ben Affleck.
Famous, successfuI peopIe
from out of state!
They Iive in fancy houses
in other pIaces.
"Families Come First"
is supported by
life-long Springfieldians
you know and trust.
Like me, Milhouse's dad,
Bumblebee Man, Surly Duff,
and that jerk
that goes, "Yes!"
For more information,
visit our Web site,
www.aI-jazeera.com.
We're not affiliated.
We're just piggy-backing
on their message board.
l am Rudy Giuliani.
Do as I command you.
lt says, "Yes on 232."
We want no on 232!
Yes on 242!
Either way.
The important thing
is the system works.
And the bumper stickers
misspelled "on."
They all say,
"Yes No 242."
And it's the night
before the election
and you haven't
handed them out!
l need to be alone
right now.
Marge, wait!
l am Rudy Giuliani.
You must forgive Homer.
l am. . .
Bart, we're gonna lose.
We have to do something !
Lisa, kids are the problem.
Maybe kids can
be the solution !
Okay. But how?
Hey, l'm the visionary.
You come up with
the nuts and bolts.
Hmm. . .
Oh, my God !
l just had my most
brilliant idea ever!
Don't you mean "my"
most brilliant idea ever?
You don't even know
what the idea is.
l know you have
an ugly face.
Bart, why are we fighting?
Because we're kids.
Kids! Maybe that's
the answer!
(GROANS)
There's the enemy.
Give them all you got.
l love you.
l love glue!
l love you !
Aw! Such a sweet
little thing.
Time to destroy your future.
Feeling flu-ish,
fever, nausea,
child germs.
No. Must participate in
democratic process.
(GROANS)
l'm afraid
the polls have closed.
And on Prop 242,
the winner is yes!
(ALL GROANlNG)
For all their
disposable income,
for all their leisure time,
they had no immunity
against God's lowliest
creatures, children.
Looks like everything's
back the way it was
which is the only way
it should ever be.
Great. Let's dump these kids
in an R-rated movie
while we go someplace nice.
Can l bring
my laser pointer?
What do l care?
ROOFl: (SlNGlNG)
One, two, tie your shoe
Three, four,
pick up the fIoor
Five, six,
don't pIay tricks
Seven, eight,
cIean your pIate
Nine, ten,
start over again!
One, two, tie your shoe
Three, four,
pick up the fIoor
Five, six,
don't pIay tricks
Seven, eight,
cIean your pIate
Nine, ten,
start over again!
One, two, tie your shoe
Three, four,
pick up the fIoor
Five, six,
don't pIay tricks
Seven, eight,
cIean your pIate
Nine, ten,
start over again!
English - US - PSDH